<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-19T18:33:05.162Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-19T18:33:05.162Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bernardo Jurema: &ldquo;Green Brazil?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/green-brazil</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/green-brazil"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lula and the Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278967</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Latest Trump assassination news (what a world); Boeing managers and executives laid off; Diddy had better make sure the CCTV works at all times; The philosphy game ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Commentariat: Living in the Material World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278950</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/the-commentariat-living-in-the-material-world.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T14:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threads woven together by the commentariat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassination Attempt No. 2 in a Land That Worships the God of Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278960</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/assassination-attempt-no-2-in-a-land-that-worships-the-god-of-violence.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T14:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America's tendency to violence is ever more obvious with the Trump assassination attempts and enthusiasm for terrorism by exploding pagers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do You Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/why-do-you-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/why-do-you-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've never been a big fan of the pressure to "Know your why." I'm not into buzzwords and pop psychology and I definitely don't like being put on the spot. I'm still at a loss to articulate why I've done some of the most difficult and incomprehensible things in my life other than it's just what I felt like at the moment. I think that's OK. Still, I do believe in self-examination and realize that sometimes figuring out our motives is helpful, depending on what we do with that information. To that end, I'm looking at my blogging and why it's become as important as it has
to me.
The personal essays I write every day serve as a record of sorts. I've never been good at the Dear Diary kind of journaling, writing for an audience of one, future me. It's hard to find inspiration there. Instead I wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278938</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T10:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our kinetic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Barron: &ldquo;In Parenthesis&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-parenthesis</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-parenthesis"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T10:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Mendelssohn’s radicalism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Oil to Benefit From Biden’s Carbon Capture Tax Credits: Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278936</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/big-oil-to-benefit-from-bidens-carbon-capture-tax-credits-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T08:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How carbon capture tax credits funnel billions to the oil and gas industry while delivering few if any climate benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Data on Extreme Human Ageing Is Rotten from the Inside Out’ – Ig Nobel Winner Saul Justin Newman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278934</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/the-data-on-extreme-human-ageing-is-rotten-from-the-inside-out-ig-nobel-winner-saul-justin-newman.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T08:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some myths bite the dust, here related to the number who live to be over 100. Not surprisingly, the cause is crappy data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jesterswilde in "Ask HN: My son might be blind – how to best support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589348</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589348"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T07:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am blind, it was degenerative so it sounds different than what your kid has.
I have a few pieces of advice. This is more about my own upbringing, so don't take any of it as an accusation towards you.
1) Don't hide things about their condition or prospects.
I grew up in a very loving home. However, my parents found out I was going blind when I was ~8, I didn't find out until I was 13.  My mother wanted to protect me from 'being the blind kid'. But I was. Not knowing made everything so much harder and more confusing.
2) Don't rely too much on technology. Stick and dog are the best tools blind people have. Everything else, in my opinion, is a flash in the pan and won't have long term support. Not made by blind people and with minimal consulting for them. Like what a sighted person thinks a blind person needs after closing their eyes and walking around their house for a few minutes. (Screen readers are useful, I'm not talking about those.)
For a piece of tech I was excited for and is now dystopian: https://spectrum.ieee.org/bionic-eye-obsolete
3) Foster independence. The world is not made for us. It's also full of high speed metal deathtraps. The easiest thing to do is stay inside where I know where everything is. Even walking to the grocery store is a deeply uncomfortable endeavor. But I need to do it. I need to be able to live with that discomfort and not let it dissuade me from living the most human life I can.
The blind cane is very valuable. It took me too long to accept blindness as an identity, get over the shame, and start using it. I lost a lot of time to that.
Blindness sucks in every conceivable way. It affects every part of ones life. But I had a good childhood and I have a good life. All things considered, I'm extremely lucky for the circumstances of my birth because of the family I was born into. You can't take away the blindness but you can still give them a wonderful life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesterswilde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Epic Floods Are Wreaking Havoc from Africa to Asia to Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278928</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/epic-floods-are-wreaking-havoc-from-africa-to-asia-to-europe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T07:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three massive flood events across three continents have claimed over 1,500 lives and cost over $15 billion in September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploding Pagers in Lebanon, Another Israeli Terrorism Blunder?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333901</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/exploding-pagers-in-lebanon-another-israeli-terrorism-blunder/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Israeli sources, the Biden administration wanted to avoid a broader regional conflict that might involve the Resistance in Lebanon, Yemen and Iran, at least until after the U.S. elections in November. However, all indications suggest that Netanyahu is resisting the American demands, and even disregarding the opinion of his own war minister who does not believe it’s the right time to expand the war. Netanyahu’s preparations for the war could also include dismissing Yaov Gallant and replacing him with Gideon Sa'ar from the New Hope Jewish racist party. This prompted Biden to send Hochstein to warn the Israeli prime minister of dangerous consequence if he moves ahead and dismisses Gallant. More
The post Exploding Pagers in Lebanon, Another Israeli Terrorism Blunder? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the Clintons Did Haiti: Keep the Natives From Breeding]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333805</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/when-the-clintons-did-haiti-keep-the-natives-from-breeding/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been nauseating to listen to Hillary Clinton moralizing to the likes of Rachel Maddow about Trump and Vance’s racist fear-mongering about Haitians, given the vicious treatment of Haitians by Bill’s administration and the Clinton Foundation. This piece from September 1994 was one of the first  “Nature and Politics” columns Cockburn and I wrote together.  More
The post When the Clintons Did Haiti: Keep the Natives From Breeding appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair - Alexander Cockburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Extremes and Climate Grief]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333782</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/333782/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world and the places we live will experience increasing climate extremes. There is no way around this. The hope we must have is that at some point this will wake people up and force action at the scale that is required before we have plunged too much deeper into the danger zone. That is why we must continue struggling through our grief and uncertainties, and counter any sense of powerlessness with action, to do all we can to wake up the world and push its political and economic elites to action. More
The post Climate Extremes and Climate Grief appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teamsters Pave the Way for Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334014</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/teamsters-pave-the-way-for-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Teamsters announced on Wednesday that it “elected not to endorse any candidate for U.S. President.” The press release stated: “After reviewing six months of nationwide member polling and wrapping up nearly a year of rank-and-file roundtable interviews with all major candidates for the presidency, the union was left with few commitments on top Teamsters  More
The post Teamsters Pave the Way for Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Energy Transition Will Be Public]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333967</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/the-energy-transition-will-be-public/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now it has been widely reported that we just lived through the hottest summer on record. Of course, the same thing was said a year ago about the previous summer. According to the Energy Institute’s Statistical Review of World Energy, greenhouse gas emissions hit a record high in 2023, increasing by 2 percent to  More
The post The Energy Transition Will Be Public  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Grosso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Irritation: Bali’s Tourism Scourge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333969</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/beyond-irritation-balis-tourism-scourge/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like eager lice on a ripe scalp, tourists have become a much-reviled feature of various economies.  While cash and contributions come in their wake, such an industry depletes, drains and pollutes the very site it idealises.  International tourism does its bit to bloat global greenhouse gas emissions, with transportation constituting the lion’s share.  All this has engendered yet  More
The post Beyond Irritation: Bali’s Tourism Scourge appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Widening Gender Divide Among Gen Z Voters Could Decide the 2024 Race]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333971</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/widening-gender-divide-among-gen-z-voters-could-decide-the-2024-race/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may be the most under-reported story of the entire 2024 presidential race;  the ever-widening gender divide among young voters identified as Gen-Z (18-29 year olds).  The Harris campaign is touting its appeal to young voters and pointing to high levels of enthusiasm and voter registration levels among youth as evidence of its mounting edge over Donald  More
The post Widening Gender Divide Among Gen Z Voters Could Decide the 2024 Race appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Separation Perfected: Domination and Alienation in Stirner and Debord]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333777</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/333777/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have allowed the American ruling class[1] to abstract themselves almost entirely from their substantive political positions and practices. So deeply engrossed are we in their branding as products of consumption, in their spectacular representations, that we seem to have no capacity to grapple critically with the situation we find ourselves in. The moment calls  More
The post Separation Perfected: Domination and Alienation in Stirner and Debord appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David S. D’Amato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disinformation from All “Great” Powers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333939</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/disinformation-from-all-great-powers/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 14th, Reuters broke a story so shocking that it should have been headline news in the United States and around the world. Admittedly, the investigative report entered a news cycle that’s been particularly full, even for a presidential election year but, as someone who spends hours reading the news every day, it surprised me that  More
The post Disinformation from All “Great” Powers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Royden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caring for a Child Shouldn’t Cause Financial Ruin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333778</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/caring-for-a-child-shouldnt-cause-financial-ruin/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every mother in America knows this struggle well: how do you afford to raise a child? My daughter was born almost 14 years ago and my family is still financially recovering from the struggle of supporting a newborn. My family is not alone. American families are spending a greater and greater portion of their income  More
The post Caring for a Child Shouldn’t Cause Financial Ruin appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iletha Joynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“They’re Eating Pets:” Latest Example of US Politicians Smearing Haiti and Haitian Immigrants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333860</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/theyre-eating-pets-latest-example-of-us-politicians-smearing-haiti-and-haitian-immigrants/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican vice presidential candidate JD Vance continues to defend the false claim that migrants in Springfield, Ohio, have been abducting and eating area cats and dogs. That outlandish idea has been thoroughly debunked since former President Donald Trump repeatedly raised it as an anti-immigrant talking point in the Sept. 12, 2024, presidential debate. Trump never  More
The post “They’re Eating Pets:” Latest Example of US Politicians Smearing Haiti and Haitian Immigrants appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan H. Dize</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sobre o que o Musk tentou fazer hoje]]></title>
        <id>https://joselito.blog.br/sobre-o-que-o-musk-tentou-fazer-hoje/</id>
        <link href="https://joselito.blog.br/sobre-o-que-o-musk-tentou-fazer-hoje/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eu tenho a impressão que, no geral, temos a mania de achar que pessoas de mau caráter são burras. É um pouco tentador, pois elas quebram a cara com certa frequência, mas é inegável que burras elas não são.
Para conseguir explorar tanta gente e chegar onde chegaram, há um certo nível de esperteza envolvido. Quando falta inteligência própria, há riqueza suficiente para comprar a dos outros. Geralmente herança.
Desde que Alexandre ordenou o bloqueio do X no Brasil, certamente há funcionários da empresa trabalhando 24/7 para encontrar uma solução que traga o nosso país de volta à rede social. Várias matérias apontam o impacto negativo que a ausência dos brasileiros causa na plataforma.
Desde o primeiro dia, uma das formas mais disseminadas de continuar acessando o X era por meio de uma "brecha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patriotism Blinds]]></title>
        <id>https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/patriotism-is-blinding/</id>
        <link href="https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/patriotism-is-blinding/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T00:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an argument to be made about the nature of it—a form of confidence that benefits a community of like-minded individuals, a society, or in this case, a country. While I am no Nietzsche or Kafka, I live in one, like any person in today's world—a world undoubtedly centered around a prominent theme: patriotism.
What even is patriotism? The word often carries different meanings depending on who you ask. Some define it as love and loyalty to one's country, a commitment to uphold a national belief or the core values they personally hold dear. Others, however, may view it with suspicion—closely associated with nationalism, pride, and even exclusion. At its core, patriotism is often seen as an allegiance to a flag, regardless of a country’s flaws. Living within a status quo, steadfast in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Netflix’s Key-Value Data Abstraction Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1ea8a0a11b30</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-netflixs-key-value-data-abstraction-layer-1ea8a0a11b30?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vidhya Arvind, Rajasekhar Ummadisetty, Joey Lynch, Vinay Chella]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 15, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240918</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240918"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweden wants to curb screen time for children under two]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8490</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/sweden-curb-screen-time-children-under-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amelia Nierenberg, writing for The New York Times: The intention of Sweden’s policy — and others like it — is to cut down on distractions, promote healthy development and help preserve the innocence of childhood. But some experts wonder if the guidance — however well-intentioned — may be too unrealistic and too judgmental to stick. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by siva7 in "LinkedIn is now using everyone's content to train their AI tool"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585363</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585363"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T20:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somehow i feel sad for this AI model. All the others are trained on authentic content and this boy gets socialised on the most shallow content imaginable. Poor, socially awkward AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siva7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian high school allows students to study from home one day a week]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8506</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-high-school-allows-students-study-from-home-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chevalier College, an Australian high-school near the NSW town of Bowral, about a ninety-minute drive south of Sydney, will allow some senior students to study from home one day a week. The decision follows a year-long trial of the scheme. The school argues the traditional five-day face-to-face learning model fails to adequately prepare students for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The popular uprising in Ecuador on 22nd June 2022 and similarities with other rebellions in Europe and Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-popular-uprising-in-Ecuador-on-22nd-June-2022-and-similarities-with-other</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-popular-uprising-in-Ecuador-on-22nd-June-2022-and-similarities-with-other"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T19:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below is the epilogue written by Éric Toussaint at the request of the authors for the book entitled Sinchi, published in Spanish in 2024 by Leonidas Iza, Andres Tapia and Andres Madrid. The book published in Spanish was translated into English and published in London by Resistance Books in 2023: Leonidas Iza, Andrés Tapia, and Andrés Madrid, Uprising : the October Rebellion in Ecuador], consists of 16 pages, which include the ten crucial points required to change the intolerable daily (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Ecuador, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Graviton4-powered memory-optimized Amazon EC2 X8g instances]]></title>
        <id>7812a543b049dc928be3d9f6c4a97e0231eb9baa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-available-graviton4-powered-memory-optimized-amazon-ec2-x8g-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T19:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New memory-optimized X8g instances offer up to 3 TiB DDR5 memory, 192 vCPUs, and 50 Gbps network bandwidth, designed for memory-intensive workloads like databases, analytics, and caching with unparalleled price/performance and efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tedivm in "OpenAI Threatening to Ban Users for Asking Strawberry About Its Reasoning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41583996</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41583996"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd still love to understand how a non-profit organization that was founded with the idea of making AI "open" has turned into this for profit behemoth with the least "open" models in the industry. Facebook of all places is more "open" with their models than OpenAI is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tedivm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data engineering professional certificate: New hands-on specialization by DeepLearning.AI and AWS]]></title>
        <id>985360e0d64907d9a064c7b368f96ac8e90b72b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/data-engineering-professional-certificate-new-hands-on-specialization-by-deeplearning-ai-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain indispensable data engineering expertise through a hands-on specialization by DeepLearning.AI and AWS. This professional certificate covers ingestion, storage, querying, modeling, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333908</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/333908/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278901</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics;  Longshoremen to strike in two weeks (plus Boeing);  Sean “Diddy” Combs jailed in Epstein-like music industry scandal; Morning Consult: Kamala leads by 6% ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes I Made When I Started Programming and How I Overcame the Self-Doubt Phase]]></title>
        <id>https://minami.bearblog.dev/my-mistakes-as-a-noob-programmer/</id>
        <link href="https://minami.bearblog.dev/my-mistakes-as-a-noob-programmer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I reflect on my journey as a programmer, from my university days to where I am now in 2024, I realize how much I've grown and learned. This blog post is about the mistakes I made, the self-doubt I faced, and how I ultimately found my way to becoming a more confident and skilled programmer.
The University Days: A Sea of Confusion
When I started my programming journey in university, I was like a ship without a compass, drifting from one technology to another without a clear direction.
Mistake 1: YouTube Tutorial Hell
I spent countless hours watching YouTube tutorials, jumping from one video to another. While these tutorials provided quick wins, they didn't help me build a solid foundation. I was coding, but not really understanding.
Mistake 2: Language and Framework Hopping
Instead of foc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights From the NAACL 2024 Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/58d913e4cc60</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/highlights-from-the-naacl-2024-conference-58d913e4cc60?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T16:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s AI Research team recaps the NAACL 2024 conference, including data set curation and reliable LLM evaluation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Cloud Journey using Amazon Outposts and AWS Local Zones]]></title>
        <id>63c78f6fcf3b64e017f261b1da4d12cd7beb0c91</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/hybrid-cloud-journey-using-amazon-outposts-and-aws-local-zones/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T16:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Amy Flanagan, Vice President of Architecture and leader of the Virtual Architecture Team (VAT) at athenahealth, and Anusha Dharmalingam, Executive Director and Senior Architect at athenahealth. athenahealth has embarked on an ambitious journey to modernize its technology stack by leveraging AWS’s hybrid cloud solutions. This transformation aims to enhance scalability, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Chellappa Ganesan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KLG: The Commentariat – Why Naked Capitalism is Essential]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278890</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/klg-the-commentariat-why-naked-capitalism-is-essential.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:30:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLG describes one of the virtues of Naked Capitalism: how the commentariat produces Essays-In-Part.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘An Act of Terror’: Israel Behind Pager Explosions That Killed 11, Wounded Thousands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278892</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/an-act-of-terror-israel-behind-pager-explosions-that-killed-11-wounded-thousands.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on the strategic thinking behind Israel's pager bomb attacks on Hezbollah, as well as innocent pager users and bystanders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lorna Scott Fox: &ldquo;Family Ties&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/family-ties</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/family-ties"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T13:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Marie-Hélène Lafon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Modest Interpretation of Straussianism in Action]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53210</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/18/a-modest-interpretation-of-straussianism-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A class of a practical sequel (or, if you prefer, sequela) to my previous post on this topic. The great modern advocate of applied (as opposed to theoretical) Straussianism, is Tyler Cowen [update: Tyler Cowen says in email that he has a very different perspective on Straussianism – see here]. Plausibly, Straussianism provides a skeleton […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by voytec in "Why wordfreq will not be updated"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578924</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578924"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree in general but the web was already polluted by Google's unwritten SEO rules. Single-sentence paragraphs, multiple keyword repetitions and focus on "indexability" instead of readability, made the web a less than ideal source for such analysis long before LLMs.
It also made the web a less than ideal source for training. And yet LLMs were still fed articles written for Googlebot, not humans. ML/LLM is the second iteration of writing pollution. The first was humans writing for corporate bots, not other humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>voytec</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jgrahamc in "Why wordfreq will not be updated"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578834</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578834"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I created https://lowbackgroundsteel.ai/ in 2023 as a place to gather references to unpolluted datasets. I'll add wordfreq. Please submit stuff to the Tumblr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jgrahamc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows in the past. Some words on glass, the importance of repairing broken windows and GDP.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45592</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/18/windows-in-the-past-some-words-on-glass-the-importance-of-repairing-broken-windows-and-gdp/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was written because of a tweet by David Andalfatto, who wondered why medieval and early modern Europe, a society that built cathedrals, did not show any per capita growth. Per capita growth is an average, and when the rich get richer, it can increase even when the number of poor and destitute increases. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The IMF and the World Bank in the time of Coronavirus: the failed campaign for a new image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-IMF-and-the-World-Bank-in-the-time-of-Coronavirus-the-failed-campaign-for-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-IMF-and-the-World-Bank-in-the-time-of-Coronavirus-the-failed-campaign-for-a"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Health, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilie Paumard, Eric Toussaint, Milan Rivié</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Bear Hug of Netanyahu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333835</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/bidens-bear-hug-of-netanyahu/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least one thing is now obvious in the Middle East: the Biden administration has failed abjectly in its objectives there, leaving the region in dangerous disarray. Its primary stated foreign policy goal has been to rally its partners in the region to cooperate with the extremist Israeli government of Benjamin Netanyahu while upholding a  More
The post Biden’s Bear Hug of Netanyahu appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Other Lives in the Big Apple]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333861</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/other-lives-in-the-big-apple/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve lived for many years in an old apartment building in New York and, for all the years I’ve spent in this elevator building, I’ve never had a problem with mice.  Well, never until now. Over the last couple of weeks, I’ve seen a half-dozen mice run along the baseboard under a radiator and by my  More
The post Other Lives in the Big Apple appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Whys?  An Open Letter to President Biden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333749</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/some-whys-an-open-letter-to-president-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mr. President, The ongoing wars in Gaza, the West Bank and Ukraine raise serious questions about American foreign policy, questions that call for honest answers. 1. Gaza Why do you continue to enable Israel’s genocide against Palestinian civilians in Gaza? The death toll from IDF bombs and missiles has reached more than 40,000 (not counting untold  More
The post Some Whys?  An Open Letter to President Biden appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call to Action:  a Remarkable Open Letter on US Designation of Cuba as Sponsor of Terrorism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333864</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/call-to-action-a-remarkable-open-letter-on-us-designation-of-cuba-as-sponsor-of-terrorism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ignacio Ramonet, academician and former editor of Le Monde diplomatique, has written an open letter to President Joe Biden. It offers nations, organizations, and individuals a golden moment for getting rid of a key piece of the U.S. system of economic blockade of Cuba. Ramonet argues in the strongest possible terms that the U.S. President must  More
The post Call to Action:  a Remarkable Open Letter on US Designation of Cuba as Sponsor of Terrorism  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestine-Israel and A Moral Dilemma Concerning War Crimes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333858</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/palestine-israel-and-a-moral-dilemma-concerning-war-crimes/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most American Jews perceive the conflict between Jewish Israelis and Palestinians according to some variation of the Zionist narrative. That is that Israel’s creation was a legitimate response to historical antisemitism and particularly the Holocaust. The Palestinians are classified in much the same category as the American Indians. That is, the struggle is between a  More
The post Palestine-Israel and A Moral Dilemma Concerning War Crimes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eichmann in Toronto]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333894</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/eichmann-in-toronto/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week the president of the U of T allowed the Jewish Defense League, bolstered by Toronto police, to break up, brutalize and physically assault anti-genocide protesters on the campus encampment. This was even reported in Ha-aretz but not in local news. In this article I liken the president, Merick Gertler, to Hannah Arendt’spicture of  More
The post Eichmann in Toronto appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Judith Deutsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UN Summit of the Future Appears Stuck in the Past]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/the-un-summit-of-the-future-appears-stuck-in-the-past/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Nations is hosting world leaders on September 22 and 23 for a “Summit of the Future.” Unfortunately, the draft action plan for the summit, while full of lofty language and some good intentions, does not challenge the neoliberal model or corporate control of the global economy. On the contrary, it proposes, for example,  More
The post The UN Summit of the Future Appears Stuck in the Past appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manuel Perez-Rocha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now That We All Agree that 10 Percent Tariffs on Imports are Bad, How About 1000 Percent Tariffs on Prescription Drugs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333751</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/now-that-we-all-agree-that-10-percent-tariffs-on-imports-are-bad-how-about-1000-percent-tariffs-on-prescription-drugs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers are undoubtedly confused by the reference to 1000 percent tariffs on prescription drugs. We don’t call our protection for prescription drug companies “tariffs,” we call them “patent monopolies.” But government interventions in the market don’t care what we call them, they have the same effect. Like tariffs on imports, government-granted patent monopolies hugely raise  More
The post Now That We All Agree that 10 Percent Tariffs on Imports are Bad, How About 1000 Percent Tariffs on Prescription Drugs? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Researchers Measure Wildfire Smoke Exposure Doesn’t Capture Long-Term Health Effects − and Hides Racial Disparities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333761</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/how-researchers-measure-wildfire-smoke-exposure-doesnt-capture-long-term-health-effects-%e2%88%92-and-hides-racial-disparities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:25:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kids born in 2020 worldwide will experience twice the number of wildfires during their lifetimes compared with those born in 1960. In California and other western states, frequent wildfires have become as much a part of summer and fall as popsicles and Halloween candy. Wildfires produce fine particulate matter, or PM₂.₅, that chokes the air  More
The post How Researchers Measure Wildfire Smoke Exposure Doesn’t Capture Long-Term Health Effects − and Hides Racial Disparities appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joan Casey – Rachel Morello-Frosch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bring on the Climate Doomers! We Need More of Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333846</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/bring-on-the-climate-doomers-we-need-more-of-them/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:24:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently complained that public narratives about climate—those promoted on so called mainstream platforms, and featured in cryptic one-liners from Democratic Party hopefuls—boil down to evasive bullshit. We are rather stuck with a climate narrative that offers two wrong answers, and, in its bifurcated and reductionist limitations, rather mirrors our two party system that offers two, and  More
The post Bring on the Climate Doomers! We Need More of Them appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post is Concerned About the Budget Deficit, Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333950</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/18/the-washington-post-is-concerned-about-the-budget-deficit-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post gave us one of its standard deficit scold pieces yesterday. As we know, the Washington Post editorial board is absolutely the most serious of the “very serious people.” They are always worried about the debt and deficit. So, let’s have a little fun with the folks. First, we can deal with the  More
The post The Washington Post is Concerned About the Budget Deficit, Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Atwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mlyle in "Apple mobile processors are now made in America by TSMC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41575089</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41575089"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T02:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> US manufacturing is about to be reinvigorated
One thing that I think that frequently eludes people in this discussion is that US manufacturing has pretty much been constantly growing for the past century; just its share of GDP has fallen as other sectors have grown faster.  And the share of the workforce has fallen even faster, as the actual manufacturing has moved towards higher value items and greater degrees of automation.
I think the actual outcome of this policy is mixed.  I think it was a big case of corporate welfare that will result in somewhat increased chip production in the US.  I think this is a win for national security.  I don't think the government applying such levers to change how the market allocates capital probably won't be a win for economic output or quality of life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mlyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by epistasis in "Apple mobile processors are now made in America by TSMC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41575039</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41575039"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T02:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After all the wailing and rending of clothes, the industrial policy worked out great and we have top tier production here in the US, transferring knowledge from TSMC to a US workforce.
This is a significant win for the US, and just the beginning of the amazing industrial policy passed over the past few years.
US manufacturing is about to be reinvigorated, and we in the US are going to be building our own future both for chips and for energy security.
This is great news, and we should celebrate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>epistasis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Cross-Cluster Communication in EKS with VPC Lattice and Pod Identity IAM Session Tags]]></title>
        <id>7b5b1f91fdb5d401875ff465129b859d2f786a08</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/secure-cross-cluster-communication-in-eks-with-vpc-lattice-and-pod-identity-iam-session-tags/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T00:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solution overview When you create your applications and want to expose internal API endpoints, you can build your microservices using different compute options such as AWS Lambda, Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS), and Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). Then, you can deploy your applications across multiple AWS accounts and multiple Amazon Virtual Private Clouds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastien Allamand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Things Palestine, From Organizing to Liberation: Eman Abdelhadi and Khury Petersen-Smith]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333875</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/all-things-palestine-from-organizing-to-liberation-eman-abdelhadi-and-khury-petersen-smith/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T22:15:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Erik Wallenberg and Joshua Frank interview Eman Abdelhadi and Khury Petersen-Smith on all things Palestine, from organizing to liberation.
Eman Abdelhadi is an academic, activist and writer who thinks at the intersection of gender, sexuality, religion and politics. She is an assistant professor and sociologist at the University of Chicago, where she researches American Muslim communities. She is co-author of Everything for Everyone: An Oral History of the New York Commune, 2052 – 2072. She is also a columnist for In These Times where you can follow her latest. She also organzizes with Faculty and staff for Justice in Palestine and Salon Kawakib.
Khury Petersen-Smith is the Michael Ratner Middle East Fellow and Co-Director of the New Internationalism Project at the Institute for Policy Studies (IPS). He researches the U.S. empire, borders, and migration. His work has appeared widely, including in Truthout, In These Times, and Foreign Policy in Focus. He is one of the co-authors and organizers of the 2023 Black Voices for Ceasefire statement, which was signed by over 6,000 Black activists, artists, and scholars.
More
The post All Things Palestine, From Organizing to Liberation: Eman Abdelhadi and Khury Petersen-Smith appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Express One Zone now supports AWS KMS with customer managed keys]]></title>
        <id>892ccacd6d98028f49e7b3c867afd8276fe9246c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-express-one-zone-now-supports-aws-kms-with-customer-managed-keys/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T21:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your mission-critical data with S3 Express One Zone's server-side encryption using KMS keys, combining top-notch performance and robust security for regulatory compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google no longer archives cache versions of webpages]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8493</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/google-webpage-cache-ends/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Germain, writing for Gizmodo: Nostalgia for a button that a lot of people probably haven’t heard of might seem absurd, but Google’s cache function was a foundational solution to one of the web’s earliest problems. As the web transformed into a more stable infrastructure, cache was mostly abandoned by regular consumers, but it was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Teen Accounts limit Instagram use for teenagers under sixteen]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8500</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/meta-teen-accounts-limit-instagram-teenagers-under-sixteen/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instagram (IG) owner Meta is moving to make the social media platform safer for users under the age of sixteen, and introducing a host of new parental controls: Today, we’re introducing Instagram Teen Accounts, a new experience for teens, guided by parents. Teen Accounts have built-in protections which limit who can contact them and the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apollo 13: Survival, a Netflix documentary]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8484</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/apollo-13-survival-netflix-documentary/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T20:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apollo 13: Survival, a Netflix produced documentary, trailer, recounts the story of what was meant to be the third Apollo crewed landing on the Moon, in 1970. An exploding oxygen tank in the body of the command module craft, on-route to the Moon, however spelt the end of the landing attempt. Instead the flight became […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stone Yard Devotional by Charlotte Wood on 2024 Booker Prize shortlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8481</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/stone-yard-devotional-charlotte-wood-2024-booker-prize-shortlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T19:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based Australian author Charlotte Wood has gone through to the shortlist of the 2024 Booker Prize, with her novel Stone Yard Devotional, which was announced on Monday 16 September 2024. If Wood were to win the Booker Prize this year, she would become the first Australian author to do so since Richard Flanagan in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Bento: Jupyter Notebooks at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21690</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/09/17/data-infrastructure/inside-bento-jupyter-notebooks-at-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T17:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This episode of the Meta Tech Podcast is all about Bento, Meta’s internal distribution of Jupyter Notebooks, an open-source web-based computing platform. Bento allows our engineers to mix code, text, and multimedia in a single document and serves a wide range of use cases at Meta from prototyping to complex machine learning workflows. Pascal Hartig [...]
Read More...
The post Inside Bento: Jupyter Notebooks at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mmastrac in "Hezbollah pager explosions kill several people in Lebanon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569964</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569964"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T17:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That's an impressive supply-chain hack. Spend years showing how insecure modern telecom devices are and scare your enemy into going old-school, receive-only. Set up a shell company to sell pagers to your enemy's shell company. Give them devices implanted with a small explosive charge pointed inward, knowing they will be worn around the waist most of the time.
Hack the backend server, send a coordinated page to all the pagers at the same time. You've just injured and identified most of your enemies, incapacitated them, completely broken their communication network and effectively given you weeks of disarray to do whatever you want to further disrupt them.
You have to hand it to them -- it's a clever strategy with minimal casualties outside of your enemy. This is a Stuxnet-level hack that we'll probably never fully understand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mmastrac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for the Complete Removal of IMF Surcharges: Historical Precedents and a Growing Burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-the-Complete-Removal-of-IMF-Surcharges-Historical-Precedents-and-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-the-Complete-Removal-of-IMF-Surcharges-Historical-Precedents-and-a"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract This paper argues for the elimination of the surcharge policy of the International Monetary Fund (IMF). It explores the legal history of surcharges and underscores that there are precedents (i.e., in 1974, 1981, and 1992) for their complete removal. The paper also shows that surcharges are a burden on indebted countries and that the Fund's official arguments for retaining them do not hold. 
English

/ 
External debt, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Arauz, Francisco Amsler, Ivana Vasic-Lalovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tomp in "Hezbollah pager explosions kill several people in Lebanon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569506</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569506"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you think Hezbollah was buying stuff from Israel, or otherwise using Israeli supply chains?
I think it's far more likely that Mossad has infiltrated whatever foreign (non-Israeli) supply chain they were using.
So this can happen regardless of whether you're using Israeli supply chains or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tomp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by einszwei in "Hezbollah pager explosions kill several people in Lebanon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569274</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569274"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Israel's perspective, this supply chain attack was undoubtedly a clever move, but I can't help but wonder about its long-term consequences.
Although it was aimed at harming Israel's adversaries, third-party countries may now hesitate to involve Israel in their supply chains. There's also the risk that other major producers could replicate this tactic, potentially leading to further escalation in the region or beyond.
In the short term, it's a smart strategy for Israel, but they've likely opened Pandora's box in the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>einszwei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by some_random in "Hezbollah pager explosions kill several people in Lebanon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569227</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569227"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can't really do much more than speculate right now, but it seems like the most likely answer is that a shipment of pagers was intercepted and implanted with explosives. Israel has done this before to assassinate a prominent bomb maker. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yahya_Ayyash#Assassination]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>some_random</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sbeam in "Hezbollah pager explosions kill several people in Lebanon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569200</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41569200"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we try to do what we are best at here at HN, let’s focus the discussion on the technical aspects of it.
It immediately reminded me of Stuxnet, which also from a technical perspective was quite interesting.
I already wonder if this was anything that was planted in the devices perviously, or if the ones responsible had similar devices, and managed reverse engineer them and craft a payload to them, that could be sent over existing cellular protocols/networks and then, similar to Stuxnet, make the device exagerte some existing functionality to a point where it caused a malfunction? Thoughts on this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sbeam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental Training]]></title>
        <id>https://kbkartikay.com/mental-training/</id>
        <link href="https://kbkartikay.com/mental-training/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doing hard things is important. Nothing worthwhile comes easy. And lets be honest. It feels good to hit the bed at the end of the day when you know you worked hard. That self satisfaction is indescribable.
But how to do hard things? The answer is 'deliberate mental training'. When I was young I would get lazy, feel bad about myself and then get the work done. If I generated enough momentum it would last long, otherwise it would just last a few days and the cycle would repeat.
My perspective changed over the years. I don't know if it was one podcast or one book that did it or a bunch of things. But I came to look at myself more as an intellectual athlete. And just like an athlete needs physical training to get better, I needed mental training.
A lot goes into an athlete achieving peak performance. Deliberate pracise, the right mindset, diet, the right tools and lets admit it - some genetics. It is the same for an intellectual athlete. Focus on what you can control and get better. The point is to improve 'your' peak performance and not to compete with some genetic freak training since they were born.
As far as frameworks go this is both very practical and very powerful. If you are out of shape and want to run a marathon you don't expect to do it one day one. You work up to it. You don't see some pro marathon runner on social media doing insane times and feel discouraged. You know your body is malleable. You can see the fat on it. The pain in your calves when you run. You know it gets better.
The same is true for our brains. Mental training makes your brain stronger. Be able to do hard things. To get started and stay focused. To not get frustrated when you hit blocks. All these are part of mental training. Something you get better at. And you need to keep training to not get out of shape. And if you ever go out of shape or get lazy you know you just need to train yourself back up to your glory days.
Start training.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fanon and the Psychology of Oppression and Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Fanon-and-the-Psychology-of-Oppression-and-Liberation</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Fanon-and-the-Psychology-of-Oppression-and-Liberation"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T08:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can't talk about Fanon without grappling with his analysis of violence and the psychology of oppression, especially during the present era of destruction and death. What would Fanon say about the colonial genocide and ‘avalanche of murders' currently taking place in Gaza and other places? 
 For Europe, for ourselves, and for humanity... we must work out new concepts and try to set afoot a new man.' (Fanon, The Wretched of the Earth) Frantz Fanon's dynamic and revolutionary thinking, always (...)
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Algeria]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamza Hamouchene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing Our Chef Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16966</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/advancing-our-chef-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T07:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, we manage tens of thousands of EC2 instances that host a variety of services, including our Vitess databases, Kubernetes workers, and various components of the Slack application. The majority of these instances run on some version of Ubuntu, while a portion operates on Amazon Linux. With such a vast infrastructure, the critical question […]
The post Advancing Our Chef Infrastructure appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Archie Gunasekara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reagan’s Lessons: In and Out of Cold War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333675</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/reagans-lessons-in-and-out-of-cold-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the exception of Donald Trump, no president in my lifetime had a more shallow knowledge of history and foreign policy than Ronald Reagan.  Reagan entered the White House in 1981 with an extremely negative and ideological view of the Soviet Union, and it was no surprise that Soviet-American bilateral relations deteriorated to their worst level in twenty years.  In Reagan’s first press conference, he noted that Soviet leaders “reserve unto themselves the right to commit any crime, to lie, to cheat.”  More
The post Reagan’s Lessons: In and Out of Cold War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck’s Going on in Germany?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333677</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/what-the-hecks-going-on-in-germany/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[number of U.S. voters are willing to contemplate installing Donald Trump in the White House for a second term, an equally significant portion of the German electorate is willing to flirt once again with fascism. Are Germans, Americans, and others determined to repeat the history they’ve either forgotten or not bothered to learn in the first place? More
The post What the Heck’s Going on in Germany? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Should the Global South Look at the US Elections?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333651</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/how-should-the-global-south-look-at-the-us-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the U.S. elections come closer, there is growing pressure on many progressives in the Global South to make our voices heard in support of the candidacy of Kamala Harris. No act on your part is insignificant in these elections, we are told. The votes of your relatives in the United States could spell the  More
The post How Should the Global South Look at the US Elections? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Republicans’ “China Week”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333752</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/the-republicans-china-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“China Week” sounds like a time for celebrating Chinese culture and food. But for Republicans in the House of Representatives, it’s all about politics. They seem to think that targeting China will play well in the elections, so they went all out with over two dozen pieces of legislation last week. Democrats joined them on  More
The post The Republicans’ “China Week” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Will Soon Realise Putin Isn’t the Scariest Russia Can Produce: My Talk with Dayan Jayatilleka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333792</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/west-will-soon-realise-putin-isnt-the-scariest-russia-can-produce-my-talk-with-dayan-jayatilleka/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka stands at a historic crossroads as it approaches its ninth presidential election, scheduled for 21 September. This moment carries profound implications for the nation’s political and social fabric. This election arrives in the wake of a tumultuous period where public outcry led to the ousting of the sitting president and the emergence of  More
The post West Will Soon Realise Putin Isn’t the Scariest Russia Can Produce: My Talk with Dayan Jayatilleka appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilantha Ilangamuwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Getting Sick of Noise Pollution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333756</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/17/were-getting-sick-of-noise-pollution/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most pressing environmental crisis of these times, our heating of the Earth through carbon dioxide and other greenhouse gas pollution, is closely connected to our excessive energy consumption. And with many of the ways we use that energy, we’re also producing another less widely discussed pollutant: industrial noise. Like greenhouse-gas pollution, noise pollution is  More
The post We’re Getting Sick of Noise Pollution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Asia: ‘It's crucial to fight the far right in Pakistan and the region']]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/South-Asia-It-s-crucial-to-fight-the-far-right-in-Pakistan-and-the-region</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/South-Asia-It-s-crucial-to-fight-the-far-right-in-Pakistan-and-the-region"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T03:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though it is one of the most dynamic regions of world capitalism, public knows little about South Asia. But the recent student rebellion in Bangladesh has brought to the fore this region marked by instability, which includes populous countries such as Bangladesh, Pakistan and India, Sri Lanka, Nepal and Afghanistan. 
English

/ 
India, 
Pakistan, 
Asia, 
Bangladesh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farooq Tariq , Israel Dutra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Brett_Riverboat in "Indiana police are seizing FedEx packages containing cash"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41563822</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41563822"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T03:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing to see here folks, this definitely is not just another violent gang stealing from the populace with zero repercussions.
It's a state sanctioned violent gang that also happens to be completely immune from any sort of responsibility.
Totally different things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brett_Riverboat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reinventing the Amazon Q Developer agent for software development]]></title>
        <id>b149b16b17beb9a900e67c11441d698b0dca82ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/reinventing-the-amazon-q-developer-agent-for-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T00:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is the most capable AI-powered assistant for software development that reimagines the experience across the entire software development lifecycle, making it easier and faster to build, secure, manage, and optimize applications on AWS. Using your natural language input and your project context, Amazon Q Developer’s agent for software development autonomously implements multi-file […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Callot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 39896880 in "Amazon tells employees to return to office five days a week"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41562436</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41562436"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T23:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> If you or your child were sick, if you had some sort of house emergency, if you were on the road seeing customers or partners, if you needed a day or two to finish coding in a more isolated environment, people worked remotely. This was understood, and will be moving forward as well.
This is Amazon having it both ways, which is what a lot of companies are doing. You can work remotely 'sometimes,' with a secret definition of 'sometimes,' operating in the background.
I found this paragraph to be somewhat galling since, like, if you're sick you shouldn't work at all, you should be focussing on getting well. Ditto if your kid is sick. Raising one or more whole other human/s is a super important thing. One result I saw from the pandemic is fathers doing more of the childcare, and what full-RTO like this fundamentally does is shift that dynamic back to where it was before.
Shame on Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>39896880</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[n1x - Submersion]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/n1x-submersion?v=1726528854</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/n1x-submersion?v=1726528854"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T23:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: n1x
Title: Submersion
Date: 2019
Source: Retrieved on 2024-09-14 from https://www.sum.si/uploads/downloads/SUM-12_single-O.pdf

 AND THE SEA GAVE UP THE DEAD WHICH WERE IN IT; 
 AND DEATH AND HELL DELIVERED UP THE DEAD WHICH 
 WERE IN THEM: AND THEY WERE JUDGED EVERY MAN 
 ACCORDING TO THEIR WORKS. 
 REVELATION 20:13 
EPIPELAGOS
 All the wretched creatures of the earth wish to return to the sea. This I am now certain of. 
 The ocean is divided into five major zones, each characterized by their depth. Depth can be thought of best in terms of proximity to the sun and the earth’s core. The Epipelagic zone is characterized by its close proximity to light, the essential source of energy for all life on Earth. Proximity to light allows for a high degree of biodiversity. 90% of all life i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "Amazon tells employees to return to office five days a week"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41562094</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41562094"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T23:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a firmware engineer, my job demands more "in-office-y" stuff than most other engineers on HN. I have specialized equipment. Hardware. I need to interface with manufacturing. So on.
Guess what? I'm going on 1 year fully remote, and I'm doing great! Turns out, all that fancy equipment can be brought home with you. We deal with a contract manufacturer, and emailing them from home is no harder than emailing them from the office. Instead of being stuck in a concrete jungle, I can go test the product out in a more realistic environment in the park across from my home. It's made me happier, healthier AND more productive. Eliminating 2 hours a day of driving and train rides left me with more energy I can expend on my work! Who'da thunk it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Australian Prime Minister’s Literary Awards winners]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8478</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-australian-prime-ministers-literary-awards-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anam, by Melbourne based Australian author André Dao, has been named winner in the Fiction category of the 2024 Prime Minister’s Literary Awards. Anam was also shortlisted for the Miles Franklin this year, and the Mark and Evette Moran Nib Literary Award in 2023. Winners in other categories were Close to the Subject: Selected Works […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by spacemadness in "Amazon tells employees to return to office five days a week"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41560655</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41560655"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T20:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like Big Tech management is simply in revenge mode. Managers and executives felt a tiny bit less powerful for a small amount of time  due to their workers pushing for remote and having the leverage to do so. Now that interest rates have wrecked the employment market they are wasting no time going scorched earth on their current remote employees. The narratives they keep shoving down peoples throats are insulting at best. They should just tell everyone they want to stand over people and feel powerful and get it over with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>spacemadness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Soft (Re)launch of Snaps by JCProbably]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-soft-relaunch-of-snaps-by-jcprobably/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-soft-relaunch-of-snaps-by-jcprobably/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T20:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was on my previous blogging platform, I had a blog titled Snaps by JCProbably. The idea of it was to post casual photos instead of the more “curated” photos that I post on jeddacp.me.
After I left the platform, it kind of just sat there. I still wanted a place to post photos of whatever somewhere without clogging up this blog (because I wanted this to be more focused on text), or my other one (because that’s more focused on giving people context to go along with the photos). Once again, it’s a little bit more about my need for separation of spaces.
Anyways, I finally got around to transferring my photos from there to Bear blog yesterday. Feel free to follow along my posts on Snaps using this RSS feed.
My photos there will likely just be everyday shots—quick snaps (probably from my phone) that I would typically share on social media, like Instagram Stories, but I'm choosing to share them in my own corner of the internet instead.
Anyways.
For those who are new here, the breakdown of my blogs is now as follows:
JEDDACP.ME (aka unnamed): photos with an average amount of text to go along with it for context. This is the one I share with people freely. The original of the 3.
Notes by JCProbably (this): primarily text based posts.
Snaps by JCProbably (new): photos of things that catch my eye, with minimal to no accompanying text.
59/100
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've migrated my blog to Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.lauramichet.com/ive-migrated-my-blog-to-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.lauramichet.com/ive-migrated-my-blog-to-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T20:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a lot of folks I know through Cohost and gamedev, I've started using Bear for blogging. This means I've left Wordpress behind after nearly 15 years on that service.
Bear is a fantastic blogging service for people who like to touch computers... but don't want to touch computers That Much. It has a web-based post composition UI which takes markdown, which is about all I want. I want to minimize the UI fuckery needed to put words on the internet, and these days, Wordpress is all about UI fuckery.
I migrated over the vast majority of posts from my old Wordpress site and laboriously set up URL aliases, so all of them should continue to receive any incoming links they had in the past. I also took some time to heal some link rot in the older posts back between 2013-2016 or so... I was linking to a lot of twines which don't seem to be online at all anymore. Where possible, I've left a note about missing content.
Bear provides everything you need to migrate Wordpress content, but it isn't a simple task. The Bear documentation states that it takes the site owner only about 30 minutes to migrate a blog with about 60 posts, but it took me several days of intermittent work. That was mostly because I cared so much about setting up the dates and aliases correctly.
If you're seeing this in RSS, then you have proof that the RSS migration worked perfectly as well. (I don't have proof of that yet, which is part of why I'm running this post.) I selected Bear partially because it was so easy for me to confirm that I could set up an RSS alias identical to the one Wordpress had given me--and that whoever was following me from back in ancient days wouldn't lose track of what I was doing over here.
Thank you to Dante and Bruno for showing me this tool! It's 3 USD cheaper per month than my current Wordpress package, and a lot simpler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neofrommatrix in "Amazon tells employees to return to office five days a week"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41559772</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41559772"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T19:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not worth working there as a L5/L6 level engineer. The money is absolutely not worth it. Unless, your team is working on an absolutely new product. 
The only engineers,IMO, that like it there are those adept at finding new bootstrapped teams and designing and writing the product from scratch and releasing the MVP. They then hand over the crappy MVP to other engineers to support and move on to other new products. On-call is absolutely brutal because of exactly that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neofrommatrix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pknomad in "Amazon tells employees to return to office five days a week"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41559672</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41559672"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T19:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genuine question for the folks over at Amazon:
What is the value of working at Amazon (or even just AWS) these days? Every now and then I get a ring from a recruiter gauging my interest and sometimes I get the itch to just to go through the process so that I can have a FAANG in my resume.
I've heard from others that Amazon could be an amazing place to work, citing fantastic colleagues and work opportunities. But then again, Amazon doesn't claim monopoly on those and one has to assume the risk of working for a place that churns people out and has upper-level management that are hostile to IC's needs/wants.
Perhaps a better question is - if one can get an offer at other FAANGs and the equivalents... is there a reason to choose Amazon over others?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pknomad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Oracle Database@AWS, Amazon RDS, AWS PrivateLink, Amazon MSK, Amazon EventBridge, Amazon SageMaker and more]]></title>
        <id>1e2b496c082939ff24646a6cf3fb563215fbbe69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-oracle-databaseaws-amazon-rds-aws-privatelink-amazon-msk-amazon-eventbridge-amazon-sagemaker-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T17:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! It’s been an interesting week full of AWS news as usual, but also full of vibrant faces filling up the rooms in a variety of events happening this month. Let’s start by covering some of the releases that have caught my attention this week. My Top 3 AWS news announcements of the week […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It was never about the numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.aurahack.jp/numbers-bad/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.aurahack.jp/numbers-bad/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T17:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote a small thing about Cohost that I’ll probably come back to later for, like, some kinda actual “goodbye to this site”-type post but for now I just want to think (out loud) a bit on something that came up in the aforementioned post. I brought up that my digital art journey began on deviantART, touching on how critical that place was for the skills I developed and the artist I’d become.
2006 wasn’t the start of that site by any means but it was pretty early. Early enough in both its respective era and the greater “access to internet” era that its userbase skewed a lot younger and the community there was dictated by that. My friends and I there would pass around questionnaires that were fun “get to know me” kinda things and you’d build a more tight-knit group of folks around that!

(A …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gorkish in "Ask HN: Does anyone use sound effects in their dev environment?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41557551</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41557551"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T16:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From [1] The story of PING:
  ping goodhost | sed -e 's/.*/ping/' | vocoder

He wired the vocoder's output into his office stereo and turned up the volume as loud as he could stand. The computer sat there shouting "Ping, ping, ping..." once a second, and he wandered through the building wiggling Ethernet connectors until the sound stopped. And that's how he found the intermittent failure.
[1] https://ftp.arl.army.mil/~mike/ping.html>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gorkish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Start Blogging?]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/when-start-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/when-start-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you thinking about starting a blog but feel like you haven't found "your voice" yet?
That's understandable; many people feel the same way. Luckily, there's a solution to the problem:
Start blogging!
There's no better way. Or rather, it's the only way.
We might have written hundreds of texts trying to find our blogging voice, but it's only when we publish them publicly that we discover our direction and begin to understand ourselves as writers. We discover that what we considered trash is someone else’s treasure. We understand that many people identify with what we thought we were alone in feeling.
We find ourselves by connecting with others.
My first blog in Swedish started as a complete mess and then slowly but surely developed into a pure tech blog. Although technology were and still is a big interest of mine, I could never have figured out in advance that that was the direction my blogging would take. It came naturally thanks to starting to blog.
This blog is my first "serious" one in English. It's still relatively new and doesn't have a specific focus at the moment, although many of the texts are about blogging. Maybe it will continue like this, or maybe I'll start a separate blog about writing online. I don't know; time will tell...
What I do know, however, is that I will never find the answer by just sitting and writing texts privately.
Are you sitting on a bunch of texts waiting to find your voice? Get them out there! That's where they do good – both for others and for yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[using htmx on bear]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/using-htmx-on-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/using-htmx-on-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T13:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[over the weekend, i decided i wanted to add a now page to my site. the problem here is that i am bad at remembering to update things (especially more than one thing). in my ideal world, i could have it live update with things like what movies i've watched recently (from letterboxd), tv (trakt, which i don't currently use but maybe should), music (only once i fix my scrobbling setup), books (storygraph), etc etc etc.
at a glance, you'd assume that bear doesn't support this sort of thing, given its static-approach. i would say that this is a limitation of imagination; you can actually just throw whatever in here, including in the header and footer.
my first test for this is using htmx to populate a list of recently watched movies (served by a small app at blog-data.jkap.io) on page load. while it's not perfect (i don't love the "loading" flash and layout shift) it was easy to setup and works Well Enough for now.
when i say easy, i mean it. this is the extent of the code:
<div hx-get="https://blog-data.jkap.io/letterboxd" hx-trigger="load">
  <span hx-indicator>loading...</span>
</div>

you can see it in action on my now page. i'm planning to add more in here over time. just gimme a bit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doix in "How to succeed in MrBeast production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41555216</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41555216"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T12:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lot of comments here disliking MrBeast and what not, but some of the advice can definitely apply to all organizations.
> Your goal here is to make the best YOUTUBE videos possible. That’s the number one goal of this production company. It’s not to make the best produced videos. Not to make the funniest videos. Not to make the best looking videos. Not the highest quality videos.. It’s to make the best YOUTUBE videos possible.
Replace "youtube videos" with whatever the company is trying to achieve. I see it all the time in large organizations, where different teams forget what the goal of the company is and instead get hyperfocused on their teams KPI's to the detriment of the company as a whole.
Lawyers finding problems and trying to stop things from happening instead of finding solutions. Security blocking things and not suggesting alternatives. IT blocking this or that instead of trying solve problems, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by codeduck in "How to Lead Your Team When the House Is on Fire"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41553929</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41553929"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T08:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This entire blog post assumes agency that you, the EM or Team lead, rarely have in an organisation that is on a "wartime" footing.  It's cosplay.
Real wartime footing:
1. Direction and technical decisions are driven by priorities of board-level members and often arrive in email form late on Friday evening.  The entire organisation is expected to pivot immediately. A new senior leadership team member starts scheduling daily read-outs on project progress, and half the organisation spends the weekend frantically hallucinating project plans into Google Sheets.
2. Engineering staff react with dull-eyed disbelief on Monday; they knew this was coming, because the same thing happened a month ago, and six weeks before that.
3. Emails come from HR that there are are new, even-more-labyrinthine approval processes for expenses, and shrinking budgets for anything not directly related to whatever the projet du jour, which will be fed enough to make it look like it's succeeding until the next Friday evening email kills it.
4. There is wide-spread burn-out across Engineering teams, and people are reduced to reactive, sarcastic automatons.
5. A creeping understanding seizes the better engineers that things cannot improve; they sign articles of  Armistice, pretend to comply, and start interviewing elsewhere.
6. An email arrives on Friday night...
> Focus on the positive aspects of the job that can be taken for granted, like the opportunity to work on cutting-edge challenges, the company's still existing perks and benefits, the amazing team you have, the chance to work with a modern tech stack, or how your product is helping its users. Showing your team how you appreciate what's still good can help with morale.
If HN supported gifs, there'd be several in this spot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>codeduck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eating dogs’ in a world that has not lost its humanity]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53196</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/16/eating-dogs-in-a-world-that-has-not-lost-its-humanity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T06:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an article published last year, I tried to show that our moral judgement is heavily biased when it comes to migration. For instance, an action that we regard as a minimum moral obligation towards compatriots becomes, towards migrants or foreigners, non-obligatory and even forbidden. I tried to show that even ethicists well disposed towards […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Speranta Dumitru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shalmanese in "How to succeed in MrBeast production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551180</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551180"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T22:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One distressing trend I've noticed becoming ubiquitous on HN is that any writing that is confronting to a consensus worldview becomes flooded with highly upvoted comments that are, in essence, excuses for why it's not necessary in this instance to re-examine your priors.
He's making low value content/the culture of the company is horrible/he's a fraud/it's more luck than skill. The actual critiques are personalized to the content and, to one extent or another, valid, but the social purpose of the critiques is universal which is that I felt uncomfortable that reading this might mean I have to re-evaluate my worldview and I'm going to dive into the comment section and upvote all the people telling me actually, I don't have to do that.
I actually spent over an hour writing 750+ words of my takeaways reading this document and shared it privately with a few founder friends of mine and I briefly considered also posting to share with the community but I took a look at the comments and took a look at what I wrote and decided I didn't have the energy to face the endless onslaught of nitpicks and misunderstandings that are driven, at the end of the day, not by a genuine intellectual desire to reach an understanding, but by the need to prove emotionally that others are not taking this seriously so I don't have to either.
All I can do is be vague and say I think this was an enormously valuable piece of writing that is worth engaging seriously for what it is as it might change your worldview in several important ways.
But also my larger meta-point is that there's a now near ubiquitous "sour grapes" attitude that's pervaded HN that makes it an extremely unpleasant place to hold a conversation and people reading should be aware of this systematic bias when reading comments here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shalmanese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by latexr in "How to succeed in MrBeast production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551031</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551031"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T22:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Lot of people critiquing this, but you can't deny the success.
You could say that about literally any shady business. Imagine seeing a PDF proving tobacco leaders knew for decades that it caused cancer and saying what you did.
Being monetarily successful does not mean you’re good or shouldn’t be criticised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>latexr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ocean_moist in "How to succeed in MrBeast production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550368</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550368"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T21:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lot of people critiquing this, but you can't deny the success. I think a lot of the advice is applicable to startups.
1. KPIs, for Beast they are CTR, AVD, AVP, will look different if you are a startup. I am willing to bet he knows his metrics better than >95% of startup founders. Because he is literally hacking/being judged by an algorithm, his KPIs will matter more and can be closely dissected. Startups aren't that easy in that sense, but KPIs still matter.
2. Hiring only A-players. Bloated teams kill startups.
3. Building value > making money
4. Rewarding employees who make value for the business and think like founders/equity owners, not employees.
5. Understanding that some videos only his team can do, and actively exploiting and widening that gap.
The management/communication stuff is mostly about working on set/dealing with physical scale. You need a lot more hands dealing with logistics, which requires hardline communication and management. In startups, the team is usually really lean and technical, so management becomes more straightforward.
I am also getting some bad culture vibes from the PDF and really dislike the writing style. I think it's important not to micromanage to the extent he is--it's necessary, maybe, for his business. Not for startups. Interesting perspective, reminds me of a chef de cuisine in a cutthroat 90s kitchen. The dishes (videos) have to be perfect, they require a lot of prep and a lot of hands, and you have to consistently pump them out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ocean_moist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should the Australian government ban social media access to young Australians?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8471</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/should-australian-government-ban-social-media-access-young-australians/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week the Australian federal government announced its intention to restrict access to social media platforms to younger Australians. For now details remain scant. The government is yet to specify an exact age at which young Australians would be able to begin using social media. The Prime Minister, Anthony Albanese, however has indicated somewhere between […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A gentle guide to self-hosting your software]]></title>
        <id>https://knhash.in/gentle-guide-to-self-hosting/</id>
        <link href="https://knhash.in/gentle-guide-to-self-hosting/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T19:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a time when software (and games! Games are just software for fun!) were distributed on DVD. A physical disk that you would insert into your system to load up software and install. This was the 2000's, when computers prided themselves on being personal computation devices. A Chromebook was a curiosity at the time, promising to run most of your software in "someone else's computer"; all you needed was the internet and the interface. The Chromebook was a reckoning. Through the 2010's we slowly moved into the clouds of various giants; it was the easy way to compute. The giants were renting out services - subscriptions started gaining foothold as the second best way to make money online after advertisements - and we were happy to give away the control in exchange for convenience. A mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging Without Breaking a Sweat]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blogging-without-sweat/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blogging-without-sweat/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gingerbread computer  

When I inspect houses as part of my work, I always advise homeowners to check their attics a couple of times a year. I also suggest making it as easy as possible to do so, for example by installing a built-in ladder. If it feels too cumbersome to check your attic, it's easy to put it off.
For the same reason, I want as little resistance as possible when it comes to blogging. I keep my blog post ideas easily accessible, no matter where I am. When it's time to write, I do it in the default text editor if I'm at my computer, or in my phone's standard notes app.
After translating (I always write in Swedish) and editing the text, I open the browser shortcut to create a new blog post. I preview it and maybe do some formatting. Then I publish the post.
The Blogging Workflow
When I read certain blogging workflows, I'm surprised at how complicated they seem. At the same time, I think that for those particular bloggers, the technical aspect is one of the reasons they enjoy blogging. It's not a barrier; it's an example of the importance of interests.
My approach of writing in Swedish and then translating into English can certainly be perceived as complicated. But I find it fun and interesting. It took quite a while before I found a way to write in English in a way that I felt good about.
Regardless of your approach to blogging, make sure it feels easy and fun. "Easy" is of course very individual in this case. That's where the "fun" part comes in - easy can be technically complicated in a fun way.
3 Tips for Easy Blogging
It should work on any device.
It should work no matter where you are.
It should be easy to go from writing to publishing.
We live in a time of almost unlimited possibilities. Take this opportunity to play around. Find a setup that suits you, and don't be afraid to try new methods.
Keep on blogging!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DrSiemer in "Google Has Officially Killed Cache Links"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41546039</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41546039"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T08:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sucks. Cache basically guaranteed that whatever Google thought was on the page could actually be found.
These days Google will offer a result where the little blurb (which is actually a truncated mini cache) shows a part of the information I'm looking for, but the page itself does not. Removing cache means the data is just within reach, but you can't get to it anymore.
Internet Archive is a hassle and not as reliable as an actual copy of the page where the blurb was extracted from.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DrSiemer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AnarchismIsCool in "Why Scrum is stressing you out"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41544698</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41544698"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T02:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've learned to hate software process.  If you have team sizes set sanely and empower devs to do what they need to do in order to accomplish the goal, they'll be fine without the management overhead of arbitrarily imposed productivity flow.  Agile et al, along with 99% of the features in ticketing systems, exist to make managers feel like they are justifying their paycheck.
If you are a manager and this makes you angry, you're one of the bad ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnarchismIsCool</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We or They ?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53193</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/15/we-or-they/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T01:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most academics these days, I spend a lot of time filling in online forms. Mostly, this is just an annoyance but occasionally I get something out of it. A recent survey in which the higher-ups tried to get an idea of how the workforce was feeling, asked the question “Do you think of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fnordpiglet in "Terence Tao on O1"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542863"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T20:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rewind your mind to 2019 and imagine reading a post that said
“The experience seemed roughly on par with trying to advise a mediocre, but not completely incompetent, graduate student.”
With regard to interacting with the equivalent of Alexa. That’s a remarkable difference in 5 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fnordpiglet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by koala_man in "Falsehoods programmers believe about TCP"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542411</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542411"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T20:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find this "falsehoods programmers believe" format of making pointed claims that you intentionally don't clarify to be unhelpful and obnoxious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>koala_man</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lenerdenator in "How America's universities became debt factories"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541425</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541425"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T17:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1) Move most good careers that do not require a college degree out of the country for the benefit of shareholders
2) Tell everyone born between 1980 and 1995 that they'll be unable to compete in the global marketplace if they don't get at least some post-high school education, and imply that the mere presence of a degree will help instead of having a specific type of degree
3) Have next-to-zero standards for public funds used in grant and loan programs for college education, meaning people can take out loans for any sort of degree program at almost any sort of institution
4) Hold these debtors to standards that aren't applied to other types of debtors. You cannot discharge them through bankruptcy, it's very difficult to renegotiate, and SCOTUS has said that the chief executive of the note-holding institution (in this case, the President of the United States) cannot use discretion in deciding who he gets to forgive for loans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lenerdenator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wenc in "Terence Tao on O1"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541372</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541372"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T17:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once GPT is tuned more heavily on Lean (proof assistant) -- the way it is on Python -- I expect its usefulness for research level math to increase.
I work in a field related to operations research (OR), and ChatGPT 4o has ingested enough of the OR literature that it's able to spit out very useful Mixed Integer Programming (MIP) formulations for many "problem shapes". For instance, I can give it a logic problem like "i need to put i items in n buckets based on a score, but I want to fill each bucket sequentially" and it actually spits out a very usable math formulation.  I usually just need to tweak it a bit. It also warns against weak formulations where the logic might fail, which is tremendously useful for avoiding pitfalls. Compare this to the old way, which is to rack my brain over a weekend to figure out a water-tight formulation of MIP optimization problem (which is often not straightforward for non-intuitive problems). GPT has saved me so much time in this corner of my world.
Yes, you probably wouldn't be able to use ChatGPT well for this purpose unless you understood MIP optimization in the first place -- and you do need to break down the problem into smaller chunks so GPT can reason in steps --  but for someone who can and does, the $20/month I pay for ChatGPT more than pays for itself.
side: a lot of people who complain on HN that (paid/good - only Sonnet 3.5 and GPT4o are in this category) LLMs are useless to them probably (1) do not know how to use LLMs in way that maximizes their strengths; (2) have expectations that are too high based on the hype, expecting one-shot magic bullets. (3) LLMs are really not good for their domain. But many of the low-effort comments seem to mostly fall into (1) and (2) -- cynicism rather than cautious optimism.
Many of us who have discovered how to exploit LLMs in their areas of strength -- and know how to check for their mistakes --  often find them providing significant leverage in our work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh students script a victory undaunted by repression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-students-script-a-victory-undaunted-by-repression</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-students-script-a-victory-undaunted-by-repression"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T13:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sheikh Hasina Wajed, the prime minister of Bangladesh for the last 15 years had to resign and run away from the country after being driven out by student protesters. An anti-quota students' movement developed into a broader rebellion against the Awami League (AL), led by Sheikh Hasina, and her despotic government. The students achieved this victory after a fierce struggle which witnessed more than 400 people killed and thousands of others injured or reported missing. The turn of events in (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Bangladesh, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sushovan Dhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Benefits with Bottlerocket: A Purpose-Built Container OS]]></title>
        <id>7fd5d2aa425994eb182752ee6f7b22bfd45719d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/benefiting-from-bottlerocket-an-open-source-container-optimized-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T21:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post discusses Bottlerocket, a Linux-based open source operating system (OS) that is purpose-built for running containers. We walk through fleet management at scale and how users can benefit from it. We also share how the product roadmap of Bottlerocket is driven based on community and user feedback. The challenges of fleet management with General-Purpose […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Charan Teja Gopaluni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking public debt]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45589</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/13/rethinking-public-debt-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Few issues in politics and economics are nowadays more discussed — and less understood — than public debt. Many raise their voices to urge for reducing the debt, but few explain why and in what way reducing the debt would be conducive to a better economy or a fairer society. And there […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[an introduction, and some thoughts on the cohost shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/an-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/an-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! it's blogging time.
now that cohost is shutting down, i'm setting up a new home for whatever long-form (or even medium-form) writing i do. i've found over time that the microblogging formats of most social media don't really work for me, and i like having ownership / control of my writing. so here we are.
i'm spending some time migrating some of my favorite posts over from cohost to here; you can view them in the #cohost tag if you so wish.
i'm planning to write more about my overall Feelings around the cohost shutdown soon; there's a lot of things i'd do differently if we were to do it again, but i'm proud of what we accomplished regardless.
one thing that i've been contending with in the wake of the shutdown announcement is the outpouring of love for cohost that i've gotten from s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Bottle of Bourbon]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September is Suicide Prevention Month, and the IndyWeb Carnival theme is "Power Underneath Despair." We are asked to share stories about times in our lives when we managed to come back from low points. This is my contribution.
As someone who has dealt with chronic depression since the 1980s, I could share about that. But the more powerful story is how I felt almost 16 years ago during the last few weeks of active alcoholism, before I had the moment of clarity that led to my recovery.
Active alcoholism was a series of contradictions for me. I would start almost every day determined not to drink, even though it had been literally years since I'd been alcohol-free for an entire 24 hours. I was never the kind of person to keep beer in the fridge for later or to maintain a bar so that I could m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Week of Action for Climate Finance and a Fossil-Free Future!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head towards COP 29, the issues of climate finance and a fossil fuel phaseout towards a just energy transition are ever more critical for climate action. The upcoming UN General Assembly, the UN Summit of the Future and the Global Renewables Summit all taking place one after the other in September provide an important opportunity to reiterate our demands and escalate public pressure to compel governments, international institutions and corporations to listen and take action. 
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>