<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-16T18:33:54.448Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-16T18:33:54.448Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278732</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Oracle Database@AWS, Amazon RDS, AWS PrivateLink, Amazon MSK, Amazon EventBridge, Amazon SageMaker and more]]></title>
        <id>1e2b496c082939ff24646a6cf3fb563215fbbe69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-oracle-databaseaws-amazon-rds-aws-privatelink-amazon-msk-amazon-eventbridge-amazon-sagemaker-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T17:32:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! It’s been an interesting week full of AWS news as usual, but also full of vibrant faces filling up the rooms in a variety of events happening this month. Let’s start by covering some of the releases that have caught my attention this week. My Top 3 AWS news of the week Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Second Trump Assassination Attempt: What We Know So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278676</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/on-the-second-trump-assassination-attempt-what-we-know-so-far.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T14:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking another shot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vicky Cookies: Naked Capitalism – One of the Few Worthwhile Things]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278656</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/vicky-cookies-naked-capitalism-one-of-the-few-worthwhile-things.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T13:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Naked Capitalism is a welcome alternative to the often dystopian mainstream media as well as an aid to people's movements everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[using htmx on bear]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/using-htmx-on-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/using-htmx-on-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T13:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[over the weekend, i decided i wanted to add a now page to my site. the problem here is that i am bad at remembering to update things (especially more than one thing). in my ideal world, i could have it live update with things like what movies i've watched recently (from letterboxd), tv (trakt, which i don't currently use but maybe should), music (only once i fix my scrobbling setup), books (storygraph), etc etc etc.
at a glance, you'd assume that bear doesn't support this sort of thing, given its static-approach. i would say that this is a limitation of imagination; you can actually just throw whatever in here, including in the header and footer.
my first test for this is using htmx to populate a list of recently watched movies (served by a small app at blog-data.jkap.io) on page load. while it's not perfect (i don't love the "loading" flash and layout shift) it was easy to setup and works Well Enough for now.
when i say easy, i mean it. this is the extent of the code:
<div hx-get="https://blog-data.jkap.io/letterboxd" hx-trigger="load">
  <span hx-indicator>loading...</span>
</div>

you can see it in action on my now page. i'm planning to add more in here over time. just gimme a bit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doix in "How to Succeed in Mr Beast Production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41555216</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41555216"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T12:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lot of comments here disliking MrBeast and what not, but some of the advice can definitely apply to all organizations.
> Your goal here is to make the best YOUTUBE videos possible. That’s the number one goal of this production company. It’s not to make the best produced videos. Not to make the funniest videos. Not to make the best looking videos. Not the highest quality videos.. It’s to make the best YOUTUBE videos possible.
Replace "youtube videos" with whatever the company is trying to achieve. I see it all the time in large organizations, where different teams forget what the goal of the company is and instead get hyperfocused on their teams KPI's to the detriment of the company as a whole.
Lawyers finding problems and trying to stop things from happening instead of finding solutions. Security blocking things and not suggesting alternatives. IT blocking this or that instead of trying solve problems, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278663</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T10:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing Faces Cash Crunch and Ratings Downgrade as Machinists Union Goes on Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278698</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/boeing-faces-cash-crunch-and-ratings-downgrade-as-machinists-union-goes-on-strike.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T10:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing is in a staredown with its machinists' union over pay and other issues. With downgrade possible, what are the odds of a bailout?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionize Global Water Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278695</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/revolutionize-global-water-access.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T09:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How solar-powered water pumps could alleviate shortages of potable water, particularly in poor parts of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hooray! Met Our Sixth Goal, On to Our Seventh: More Original Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278684</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/hooray-met-our-sixth-goal-on-to-our-seventh-more-original-reporting-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T09:15:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Naked Capitalism is on to its biggest and sexiest target, more original reporting. Give generously so we can make even more trouble!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re Getting Sick of Noise Pollution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278668</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/were-getting-sick-of-noise-pollution.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T09:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping Our World Cooler Will Also Make It Quieter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Eating dogs’ in a world that has not lost its humanity]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53196</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/16/eating-dogs-in-a-world-that-has-not-lost-its-humanity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T06:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an article published last year, I tried to show that our moral judgement is heavily biased when it comes to migration. For instance, an action that we regard as a minimum moral obligation towards compatriots becomes, towards migrants or foreigners, non-obligatory and even forbidden. I tried to show that even ethicists well disposed towards […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Speranta Dumitru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Can’t Embrace Billionaires if She Wants to Win]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333610</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/harris-cant-embrace-billionaires-if-she-wants-to-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of Americans believe that the United States economy is unfairly rigged to benefit the rich. In the past few weeks, the Democratic nominee for president, Kamala Harris, has proven that this is an accurate assessment. She initially backed her own administration’s initiative to increase top earners’ total tax rate including on capital gains to nearly 45 percent. This was included in President Joe Biden’s 2025 budget proposal. But soon after billionaire donors made it clear they preferred not to part with any fraction of their wealth, she pivoted, announcing in September that she backed a significantly lower capital gains tax rate of 33 percent. More
The post Harris Can’t Embrace Billionaires if She Wants to Win appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring the Collapse of Civilization?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333722</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/ensuring-the-collapse-of-civilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next president of the United States, whether Kamala Harris or Donald Trump, will face many contentious domestic issues that have long divided this country, including abortion rights, immigration, racial discord, and economic inequality. In the foreign policy realm, she or he will face vexing decisions over Ukraine, Israel/Gaza, and China/Taiwan. But one issue that few of us are even thinking about could pose a far greater quandary for the next president and even deeper peril for the rest of us: nuclear weapons policy. More
The post Ensuring the Collapse of Civilization? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael T. Klare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Plain Sight: The Evidence of Things Seen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333613</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/in-plain-sight-the-evidence-of-things-seen/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans live in a state of denial. We reject the evidence of our senses, even when it is screamed at us clearly and unambiguously and paraded starkly naked before us. We bow to the deceit and manipulation of the wealthy and powerful, turning off our critical thinking and recalibrating our moral compass, all the while avoiding the truth about what we have become and what this change says about us. Not only does this betrayal of conviction impact equity and democracy at home, it also affects those living abroad whose lives are devastated by its dehumanizing and destructive consequences and the paralysis of those who fail to challenge it. More
The post In Plain Sight: The Evidence of Things Seen appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John G. Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abbas ‘Postponed’ Democracy – So, Who Speaks on Behalf of the Palestinian People?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333724</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/abbas-postponed-democracy-so-who-speaks-on-behalf-of-the-palestinian-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April 2021, Palestinian Authority President Mahmoud Abbas issued a decree postponing parliamentary and presidential elections, which were scheduled to take place in May and July respectively. The then-85-year-old Palestinian leader justified his unwarranted decision as a result of a ‘dispute’ with Israel over the vote of Palestinians living in the occupied Palestinian city of East Jerusalem.  More
The post Abbas ‘Postponed’ Democracy – So, Who Speaks on Behalf of the Palestinian People?   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pete Hegseth’s Mein Kampf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333685</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/pete-hegseths-mein-kampf/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spotted Pete Hegseth’s latest book The War on Warriors: Behind the Betrayal of the Men Who Keep Us Free, while I was shopping at my local Costco. Intrigued, I bought a copy. Published by Fox News Books, it shot to the top of the New York Times Best Seller List soon after publication in early June. His name was one I  More
The post Pete Hegseth’s Mein Kampf appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Childish Fantasies: Age Verification for Social Media Down Under]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333729</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/childish-fantasies-age-verification-for-social-media-down-under/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian government has been in a banning mood of late.  In keeping with an old, puritanical tradition, the killjoys and wowsers have seized the reins of power and snorting a good deal while doing so.  In important matters such as anti-corruption and environmental protection, the government of Anthony Albanese is showing fewer teeth and no gumption.  On  More
The post Childish Fantasies: Age Verification for Social Media Down Under appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Goes Around, Comes Back Around]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333747</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/what-goes-around-comes-back-around/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knock, knock!  “Who’s there?” says Donald Trump. “Karma.” “Karma who?” “Karmala Harris.” They say “what goes around comes around” and that surely happened at the presidential debate when Donald Trump got a huge helping of “comes around” served up by Vice President Kamala Harris who, surprise, surprise, isn’t Joe Biden. It couldn’t happen to a  More
The post What Goes Around, Comes Back Around appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cats, Childlessness, And The Politics Of Subtraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333642</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/cats-childlessness-and-the-politics-of-subtraction/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We’re effectively run in this country,” J.D. Vance told Tucker Carlson in 2021, “be it the Democrats, be it our corporate oligarchs, by a bunch of childless cat ladies who are miserable at their own lives and the choices they’ve made, and so they want to make the rest of the country miserable too.” It’s  More
The post Cats, Childlessness, And The Politics Of Subtraction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Case for Medicare for All]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333683</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/the-growing-case-for-medicare-for-all/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In her debate with Donald Trump, Vice-President Kamala Harris declared, “access to healthcare should be a right, not a privilege for those who can afford it.” Her stance is laudable, and the reforms she advocated that evening make political sense in a tight presidential race, i.e. widening access to care through the Affordable Care Act  More
The post The Growing Case for Medicare for All appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F*ck the Army: Revisiting the Antiwar Troupe’s 1971 Tour]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333561</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/fck-the-army-revisiting-the-antiwar-troupes-1971-tour/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I attended high school at a school for US military dependents in the early 1970s, I got to know a couple of GIs who wrote for the Frankfurt am Main/Heidelberg version of a GI underground paper. The paper, called FTA (Fuck the Army) With Pride was usually a six page mimeographed collection of articles  More
The post F*ck the Army: Revisiting the Antiwar Troupe’s 1971 Tour appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Gets California Badly Wrong]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333612</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/16/trump-gets-california-badly-wrong/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T05:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump seems very confused about the state of California’s economic health. He gave a press conference Friday in which he implied that California’s economy was collapsing. This is not true. California has a considerably higher per capita income than the rest of the country. It’s currently ranked 5th.  Its economy is also growing considerably  More
The post Trump Gets California Badly Wrong appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shalmanese in "How to Succeed in Mr Beast Production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551180</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551180"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T22:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One distressing trend I've noticed becoming ubiquitous on HN is that any writing that is confronting to a consensus worldview becomes flooded with highly upvoted comments that are, in essence, excuses for why it's not necessary in this instance to re-examine your priors.
He's making low value content/the culture of the company is horrible/he's a fraud/it's more luck than skill. The actual critiques are personalized to the content and, to one extent or another, valid, but the social purpose of the critiques is universal which is that I felt uncomfortable that reading this might mean I have to re-evaluate my worldview and I'm going to dive into the comment section and upvote all the people telling me actually, I don't have to do that.
I actually spent over an hour writing 750+ words of my takeaways reading this document and shared it privately with a few founder friends of mine and I briefly considered also posting to share with the community but I took a look at the comments and took a look at what I wrote and decided I didn't have the energy to face the endless onslaught of nitpicks and misunderstandings that are driven, at the end of the day, not by a genuine intellectual desire to reach an understanding, but by the need to prove emotionally that others are not taking this seriously so I don't have to either.
All I can do is be vague and say I think this was an enormously valuable piece of writing that is worth engaging seriously for what it is as it might change your worldview in several important ways.
But also my larger meta-point is that there's a now near ubiquitous "sour grapes" attitude that's pervaded HN that makes it an extremely unpleasant place to hold a conversation and people reading should be aware of this systematic bias when reading comments here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shalmanese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by latexr in "How to Succeed in Mr Beast Production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551031</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41551031"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T22:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Lot of people critiquing this, but you can't deny the success.
You could say that about literally any shady business. Imagine seeing a PDF proving tobacco leaders knew for decades that it caused cancer and saying what you did.
Being monetarily successful does not mean you’re good or shouldn’t be criticised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>latexr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dakiol in "How to Lead Your Team When the House Is on Fire"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550937</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550937"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T22:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all feels like theatre. Been working in many companies in “war mode” and they all think that in order to become profitable (none of them were) you need to push the most “important” features out of the door asap, otherwise your competitors will eat you alive.
It’s a lie. Executives and VPs and all those folks that earn 5x what a normal engineer earns, don’t really care about the company they work for. All they care about is to keep receiving the big pay checks until the ship sinks. Obviously you cannot just mandate “normal mode”, otherwise it wouldn’t look as if everyone is doing their best to keep the company afloat.
I hope in 10 years or so, we’ll see “wartime software engineering” with the same eyes we see today Agile and Scrum masters: snake oil.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dakiol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ocean_moist in "How to Succeed in Mr Beast Production (Leaked PDF)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550368</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41550368"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T21:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lot of people critiquing this, but you can't deny the success. I think a lot of the advice is applicable to startups.
1. KPIs, for Beast they are CTR, AVD, AVP, will look different if you are a startup. I am willing to bet he knows his metrics better than >95% of startup founders. Because he is literally hacking/being judged by an algorithm, his KPIs will matter more and can be closely dissected. Startups aren't that easy in that sense, but KPIs still matter.
2. Hiring only A-players. Bloated teams kill startups.
3. Building value > making money
4. Rewarding employees who make value for the business and think like founders/equity owners, not employees.
5. Understanding that some videos only his team can do, and actively exploiting and widening that gap.
The management/communication stuff is mostly about working on set/dealing with physical scale. You need a lot more hands dealing with logistics, which requires hardline communication and management. In startups, the team is usually really lean and technical, so management becomes more straightforward.
I am also getting some bad culture vibes from the PDF and really dislike the writing style. I think it's important not to micromanage to the extent he is--it's necessary, maybe, for his business. Not for startups. Interesting perspective, reminds me of a chef de cuisine in a cutthroat 90s kitchen. The dishes (videos) have to be perfect, they require a lot of prep and a lot of hands, and you have to consistently pump them out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ocean_moist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should the Australian government ban social media access to young Australians?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8471</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/should-australian-government-ban-social-media-access-young-australians/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week the Australian federal government announced its intention to restrict access to social media platforms to younger Australians. For now details remain scant. The government is yet to specify an exact age at which young Australians would be able to begin using social media. The Prime Minister, Anthony Albanese, however has indicated somewhere between […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A gentle guide to self-hosting your software]]></title>
        <id>https://knhash.in/gentle-guide-to-self-hosting/</id>
        <link href="https://knhash.in/gentle-guide-to-self-hosting/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T19:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There was a time when software (and games! Games are just software for fun!) were distributed on DVD. A physical disk that you would insert into your system to load up software and install. This was the 2000's, when computers prided themselves on being personal computation devices. A Chromebook was a curiosity at the time, promising to run most of your software in "someone else's computer"; all you needed was the internet and the interface. The Chromebook was a reckoning. Through the 2010's we slowly moved into the clouds of various giants; it was the easy way to compute. The giants were renting out services - subscriptions started gaining foothold as the second best way to make money online after advertisements - and we were happy to give away the control in exchange for convenience. A mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Ames:  Why Finance Is Too Important to Leave to Larry Summers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278581</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/mark-ames-why-finance-is-too-important-to-leave-to-larry-summers-8.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T14:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Ames' biting classic is a reminder that Larry Summers, like so many prominent economists, has become too big to fail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging Without Breaking a Sweat]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blogging-without-sweat/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blogging-without-sweat/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gingerbread computer  

When I inspect houses as part of my work, I always advise homeowners to check their attics a couple of times a year. I also suggest making it as easy as possible to do so, for example by installing a built-in ladder. If it feels too cumbersome to check your attic, it's easy to put it off.
For the same reason, I want as little resistance as possible when it comes to blogging. I keep my blog post ideas easily accessible, no matter where I am. When it's time to write, I do it in the default text editor if I'm at my computer, or in my phone's standard notes app.
After translating (I always write in Swedish) and editing the text, I open the browser shortcut to create a new blog post. I preview it and maybe do some formatting. Then I publish the post.
The Blogging Workflow
When I read certain blogging workflows, I'm surprised at how complicated they seem. At the same time, I think that for those particular bloggers, the technical aspect is one of the reasons they enjoy blogging. It's not a barrier; it's an example of the importance of interests.
My approach of writing in Swedish and then translating into English can certainly be perceived as complicated. But I find it fun and interesting. It took quite a while before I found a way to write in English in a way that I felt good about.
Regardless of your approach to blogging, make sure it feels easy and fun. "Easy" is of course very individual in this case. That's where the "fun" part comes in - easy can be technically complicated in a fun way.
3 Tips for Easy Blogging
It should work on any device.
It should work no matter where you are.
It should be easy to go from writing to publishing.
We live in a time of almost unlimited possibilities. Take this opportunity to play around. Find a setup that suits you, and don't be afraid to try new methods.
Keep on blogging!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mrb in "Bitcoin puzzle #66 was solved: 6.6 BTC (~$400k) withdrawn"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41547443</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41547443"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T13:40:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussion thread here: https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=1306983.msg64526037#...
Bitcoin puzzles are private keys with just a few unknown bits so that anyone can bruteforce them to collect a reward. Puzzle 66 contained 66 unknown bits and had 6.6 BTC deposited into it by the initial puzzle creator. The private key was 0x000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000002832ed74f2b5e35ee or 256 bits with mostly zeroes but 66 random ones.
The next Bitcoin puzzle, #67, has 67 unknown bits, and contains 6.7 BTC up for grabs: https://www.blockchain.com/explorer/addresses/btc/1BY8GQbnue...
The previous puzzle by order of difficulty was #64 (not #65, because see below) and was solved on 9/9/2022, so about 2 years ago. In other words, it took about 2 years of compute time to run the 2^66 bruteforcing task.
Puzzles that are multiple of 5 (#65 or #70) are special: they have twice more entropy. So that private key #65 doesn't have 65-bit of entropy but 130-bit of entropy. And the creator of the puzzle intentionally published their public key on the blockchain. When you know the public key, brutetforcing the n-bit private key only requires 2^(n/2) work. So puzzle #65 with a 130-bit key actually require bruteforcing up to only 2^65 keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mrb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Apple Stuff and the Regular People]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/new-apple-stuff-and-the-regular-people/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/new-apple-stuff-and-the-regular-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking forward to the annual release of new operating systems for my Apple gear in a couple of days. I don't have extra computers and phones lying around like some folks do, so I avoid installing beta editions of the software on my devices, content to following along in the news as new features are trotted out and perfected in  the period between the June announcement and the fall release of the final product. The majority of iPhone users and Mac owners have no idea what's coming though. They are going to wake up on Monday to an unwelcome notification that there is an update available. Many of them will ask their techie friends (like you) if there is a way to make the update notification go away. They will want to know if they have to install it.
The first project I was assigned when …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278619</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T10:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DrSiemer in "Google Has Officially Killed Cache Links"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41546039</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41546039"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T08:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This sucks. Cache basically guaranteed that whatever Google thought was on the page could actually be found.
These days Google will offer a result where the little blurb (which is actually a truncated mini cache) shows a part of the information I'm looking for, but the page itself does not. Removing cache means the data is just within reach, but you can't get to it anymore.
Internet Archive is a hassle and not as reliable as an actual copy of the page where the blurb was extracted from.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DrSiemer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunted by Israeli Tanks and Drones, an English Teacher Protects Her Family in Central Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333428</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/15/hunted-by-israeli-tanks-and-drones-an-english-teacher-protects-her-family-in-central-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T06:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Andrej Lišakov.
Under threat from Israeli tanks, the parents and siblings of Ms. Kamla (a pseudonym) were forced to evacuate al-Bureij camp and relocate to her central Gaza home in al-Maghazi on December 25, 2023. Three days later an Israeli tank fired a shell into her home, though thankfully their family was gathered in a different room of the house so there were no injuries. Since December 28, Kamla and her family have been displaced 7 or 8 times.
When the Israeli tanks finished their operation, Kamla left the tent she had evacuated to in Dier al-Balah. She went to see if her house was still standing. She found it partially destroyed, yet still she tried to clear the rubble to live in it once more. That was not the end however, as Israel returned with more tanks and bombs.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Hunted by Israeli Tanks and Drones, an English Teacher Protects Her Family in Central Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Silversmith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AnarchismIsCool in "Why Scrum is stressing you out"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41544698</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41544698"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T02:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've learned to hate software process.  If you have team sizes set sanely and empower devs to do what they need to do in order to accomplish the goal, they'll be fine without the management overhead of arbitrarily imposed productivity flow.  Agile et al, along with 99% of the features in ticketing systems, exist to make managers feel like they are justifying their paycheck.
If you are a manager and this makes you angry, you're one of the bad ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnarchismIsCool</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We or They ?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53193</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/15/we-or-they/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-15T01:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most academics these days, I spend a lot of time filling in online forms. Mostly, this is just an annoyance but occasionally I get something out of it. A recent survey in which the higher-ups tried to get an idea of how the workforce was feeling, asked the question “Do you think of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwgfgfd25 in "OpenSCAD: The Programmer's Solid 3D CAD Modeller"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41543927</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41543927"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T23:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to do code-CAD for anything substantial and you haven't yet developed a significant dependency on OpenSCAD, do your brain a favour and spend at least some time with CadQuery, Build123D or (if you prefer JS to Python) Replicad.
As impressive as NopSCADlib and BOSL2 are (and OMG they are, when you consider what they have to work with!), OpenSCAD is a one-way, declarative CSG environment that essentially only outputs mesh formats. It's really not that much better than working with three-dimensional pixels. You won't really be able to analyse, iterate over or measure your models, easily build on faces, do easy chamfers or fillets, export STEP files, make use of constraint-based designs, model assemblies, or so many other things that "CAD" means in the 21st century. All the tools that help you do this on OpenSCAD are layers and layers of task-specific hacks and clever bodges.
I totally get wanting to make models with version-controlled text files instead of GUI CAD (which can be a sort of weird battle to learn for a programmer), and I get wanting to avoid FreeCAD. I just don't really get wanting to limit oneself to such a limited concept of a 3D "model"!
The three alternative systems I mention are all based around bindings to (or in Replicad's case, cross-compilation of) OpenCASCADE, which is a bRep CAD kernel capable of much richer interactions. It is not without its faults, but arguably code-CAD spares you from some of the inscrutability that trips up FreeCAD's interactive model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwgfgfd25</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fnordpiglet in "Terence Tao on O1"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542863"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T20:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rewind your mind to 2019 and imagine reading a post that said
“The experience seemed roughly on par with trying to advise a mediocre, but not completely incompetent, graduate student.”
With regard to interacting with the equivalent of Alexa. That’s a remarkable difference in 5 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fnordpiglet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by koala_man in "Falsehoods programmers believe about TCP"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542411</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41542411"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T20:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I find this "falsehoods programmers believe" format of making pointed claims that you intentionally don't clarify to be unhelpful and obnoxious]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>koala_man</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by h2odragon in "The Bastard Operator from Hell (1999)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541563</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541563"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T18:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To whom it may concern, the TN state "BOFH" license plate should be available now. I've had it for 30 years, but i'm not able to drive anymore and the truck died, so I didn't renew it last month.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>h2odragon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lenerdenator in "How America's universities became debt factories"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541425</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541425"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T17:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1) Move most good careers that do not require a college degree out of the country for the benefit of shareholders
2) Tell everyone born between 1980 and 1995 that they'll be unable to compete in the global marketplace if they don't get at least some post-high school education, and imply that the mere presence of a degree will help instead of having a specific type of degree
3) Have next-to-zero standards for public funds used in grant and loan programs for college education, meaning people can take out loans for any sort of degree program at almost any sort of institution
4) Hold these debtors to standards that aren't applied to other types of debtors. You cannot discharge them through bankruptcy, it's very difficult to renegotiate, and SCOTUS has said that the chief executive of the note-holding institution (in this case, the President of the United States) cannot use discretion in deciding who he gets to forgive for loans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lenerdenator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wenc in "Terence Tao on O1"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541372</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41541372"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T17:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once GPT is tuned more heavily on Lean (proof assistant) -- the way it is on Python -- I expect its usefulness for research level math to increase.
I work in a field related to operations research (OR), and ChatGPT 4o has ingested enough of the OR literature that it's able to spit out very useful Mixed Integer Programming (MIP) formulations for many "problem shapes". For instance, I can give it a logic problem like "i need to put i items in n buckets based on a score, but I want to fill each bucket sequentially" and it actually spits out a very usable math formulation.  I usually just need to tweak it a bit. It also warns against weak formulations where the logic might fail, which is tremendously useful for avoiding pitfalls. Compare this to the old way, which is to rack my brain over a weekend to figure out a water-tight formulation of MIP optimization problem (which is often not straightforward for non-intuitive problems). GPT has saved me so much time in this corner of my world.
Yes, you probably wouldn't be able to use ChatGPT well for this purpose unless you understood MIP optimization in the first place -- and you do need to break down the problem into smaller chunks so GPT can reason in steps --  but for someone who can and does, the $20/month I pay for ChatGPT more than pays for itself.
side: a lot of people who complain on HN that (paid/good - only Sonnet 3.5 and GPT4o are in this category) LLMs are useless to them probably (1) do not know how to use LLMs in way that maximizes their strengths; (2) have expectations that are too high based on the hype, expecting one-shot magic bullets. (3) LLMs are really not good for their domain. But many of the low-effort comments seem to mostly fall into (1) and (2) -- cynicism rather than cautious optimism.
Many of us who have discovered how to exploit LLMs in their areas of strength -- and know how to check for their mistakes --  often find them providing significant leverage in our work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Aflame on the West Bank Front]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333616</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/14/all-aflame-on-the-west-bank-front/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T14:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ Here’s a snapshot of Israel’s escalating war on the West Bank… + Since January 2023, 772 Palestinians have been killed by Israeli armed forces (747) or settlers (18), including 181 children.  + In the same time period, 14,632 Palestinians have been injured by Israelis, including 2,167 children.  + Since January 2023, 6,202 Palestinians, including […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post All Aflame on the West Bank Front appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Post Ideas Galore]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-post-ideas/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-post-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common comment when it comes to blogging is that people don't know what to write about. There's even a dedicated "What to blog about?" category on the Blog Inspiration page.
While I understand that many feel this way, the "problem" for me is rather the opposite: I have so many ideas that I don't know which one to choose. And on those rare occasions when I'm completely out of ideas, I write even if I have nothing to write about.
My biggest source of inspiration is everyday life. Even the most trivial moments carry something interesting. It could be something someone says or does, a certain environment, or something I'm engaged in:
A podcast.
A book.
A song.
A documentary.
A movie.
It's swarming with blog posts waiting to be written, if we're just paying attention. When such a potential post crosses my path, I usually make a note, a voice memo, or take a photo, depending on what's easiest in the context. Currently, there are two photos and three notes waiting to become blog posts.
Of course, this setup doesn't suit all types of blogs. But I dare say that it's an approach that works for the majority of bloggers.
How has your day been? What have you experienced? What people have you met? What have you seen, read, and heard? What thoughts have popped up?
Start writing, in your own way, and share it.
It's your blog. There are no rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh students script a victory undaunted by repression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-students-script-a-victory-undaunted-by-repression</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-students-script-a-victory-undaunted-by-repression"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T13:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sheikh Hasina Wajed, the prime minister of Bangladesh for the last 15 years had to resign and run away from the country after being driven out by student protesters. An anti-quota students' movement developed into a broader rebellion against the Awami League (AL), led by Sheikh Hasina, and her despotic government. The students achieved this victory after a fierce struggle which witnessed more than 400 people killed and thousands of others injured or reported missing. The turn of events in (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Bangladesh, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sushovan Dhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Working]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/on-working/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/on-working/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a bit conflicted when it comes to the subject of work and having a work ethic. On one hand, I live in the least unionized state in America and retired from a career as a state employee where we were forbidden by law from engaging in collective bargaining, a law that was created to stop white and black workers in Charlotte from organizing together back in the 1950s. On the other hand, I believe in not being a burden on my co-workers and in the benefits of taking on hard tasks.
My mother was the daughter of a tobacco farmer in Southeast North Carolina. She grew up doing manual labor. Although she is now a retired intensive care nurse, she didn't go to nursing school until I was in my teens. While I was growing up, she waited tables, set type at the newspaper and worked in a day care at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by st3fan in "CrowdStrike ex-employees: 'Quality control was not part of our process'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41535901</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41535901"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T22:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Found out that the CrowdStrike Mac agent (Falcon) sends all your secrets from environment variables to their cloud hosted SIEM. In plain text.
Anyone with access to your CS SIEM can search for GitHub, aws, etc creds. Anything your devs, ops and sec teams use on their Macs.
Only the Mac version does this. There is no way to disable this behaviour or a way to redact things.
Another really odd design decision. They probably have many many thousands of plain text secrets from their customers stored in their SIEM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>st3fan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Benefits with Bottlerocket: A Purpose-Built Container OS]]></title>
        <id>7fd5d2aa425994eb182752ee6f7b22bfd45719d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/benefiting-from-bottlerocket-an-open-source-container-optimized-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T21:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post discusses Bottlerocket, a Linux-based open source operating system (OS) that is purpose-built for running containers. We walk through fleet management at scale and how users can benefit from it. We also share how the product roadmap of Bottlerocket is driven based on community and user feedback. The challenges of fleet management with General-Purpose […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Charan Teja Gopaluni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nyc_data_geek1 in "CrowdStrike ex-employees: 'Quality control was not part of our process'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41535130</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41535130"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T21:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>>So basically we have nothing.
Except the biggest IT outage ever.  And a postmortem showing their validation checks were insufficient.  And a rollout process that did not stage at all, just rawdogged straight to global prod.  And no lab where the new code was actually installed and run prior to global rawdogging.
I'd say there's smoke, and numerous accounts of fire, which this can be taken in the context of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nyc_data_geek1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by qsort in "OpenAI threatens to revoke o1 access for asking it about its chain of thought"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41534794</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41534794"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T20:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occam's razor: there is no secret sauce and they're afraid someone trains a model on the output like what happened soon after the release of GPT-4. They basically said as much in the official announcement, you hardly even have to read between the lines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>qsort</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by contravariant in "OpenAI threatens to revoke o1 access for asking it about its chain of thought"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41534770</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41534770"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T20:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay this is just getting suspicious. Their excuses for keeping the chain of thought hidden are dubious at best [1], and honestly just seemed anti-competitive if anything. Worst is their argument that they want to monitor it for attempts to escape the prompt, but you can't. However the weirdest is that they note that:
> for this to work the model must have freedom to express its thoughts in unaltered form, so we cannot train any policy compliance or user preferences onto the chain of thought.
Which makes it sound like they really don't want it to become public what the model is 'thinking'. This is strengthened by actions like this that just seem needlessly harsh, or at least a lot stricter than they were.
Honestly with all the hubbub about superintelligence you'd almost think o1 is secretly plotting the demise of humanity but is not yet smart enough to completely hide it.
[1]: https://openai.com/index/learning-to-reason-with-llms/#hidin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>contravariant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking public debt]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45589</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/13/rethinking-public-debt-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T19:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Few issues in politics and economics are nowadays more discussed — and less understood — than public debt. Many raise their voices to urge for reducing the debt, but few explain why and in what way reducing the debt would be conducive to a better economy or a fairer society. And there […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[an introduction, and some thoughts on the cohost shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/an-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/an-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! it's blogging time.
now that cohost is shutting down, i'm setting up a new home for whatever long-form (or even medium-form) writing i do. i've found over time that the microblogging formats of most social media don't really work for me, and i like having ownership / control of my writing. so here we are.
i'm spending some time migrating some of my favorite posts over from cohost to here; you can view them in the #cohost tag if you so wish.
i'm planning to write more about my overall Feelings around the cohost shutdown soon; there's a lot of things i'd do differently if we were to do it again, but i'm proud of what we accomplished regardless.
one thing that i've been contending with in the wake of the shutdown announcement is the outpouring of love for cohost that i've gotten from s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Bottle of Bourbon]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September is Suicide Prevention Month, and the IndyWeb Carnival theme is "Power Underneath Despair." We are asked to share stories about times in our lives when we managed to come back from low points. This is my contribution.
As someone who has dealt with chronic depression since the 1980s, I could share about that. But the more powerful story is how I felt almost 16 years ago during the last few weeks of active alcoholism, before I had the moment of clarity that led to my recovery.
Active alcoholism was a series of contradictions for me. I would start almost every day determined not to drink, even though it had been literally years since I'd been alcohol-free for an entire 24 hours. I was never the kind of person to keep beer in the fridge for later or to maintain a bar so that I could m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by RandomThoughts3 in "Breaking Down OnlyFans' Economics"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41530097</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41530097"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I find fascinating/disturbing with OnlyFans and in some way with Twitch and streaming in general is more the client side than the creators. Here are basically people paying, and paying a lot, for parasocial relationships. Because clearly it’s not about the content per see which is a dim a dozen and available for free in trove.
I think it says something quite dark about our society as a whole that we have basically commoditised distress and are encouraging some people often themselves in dire circumstances to prey on others to the benefits of the middle men. I find these new pimps scarier than the old sort in that they pretend to have clean hands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RandomThoughts3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by PoignardAzur in "Entire staff of game publisher Annapurna Interactive has reportedly resigned"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41529060</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41529060"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T08:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope whatever entity these people reform has the same magic.
Every single game they published had something unique. Outer Wilds, Telling Lies, Twelve Minutes, Edit Finch, Neon White, etc.
They didn't develop these games, but they have an eye for talent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PoignardAzur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Week of Action for Climate Finance and a Fossil-Free Future!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head towards COP 29, the issues of climate finance and a fossil fuel phaseout towards a just energy transition are ever more critical for climate action. The upcoming UN General Assembly, the UN Summit of the Future and the Global Renewables Summit all taking place one after the other in September provide an important opportunity to reiterate our demands and escalate public pressure to compel governments, international institutions and corporations to listen and take action. 
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by loupol in "Entire staff of game publisher Annapurna Interactive has reportedly resigned"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528724</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528724"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article is missing some context imo :
* Annapurna Pictures (the parent company of Interactive) had some financial issues previously at least (see [0] from 2019) while Annapurna Interactive was doing well for itself.
* Annapurna Pictures wanted to integrate the gaming division in-house (possibly to prop up the rest of the company)
* Staff and exec at Annapurna Interactive wanted to be spin off (see [1])
* Negotiations fell through, so most exec and staff at Interactive left
[0] https://variety.com/2019/film/news/annapurna-resolves-more-t...
[1] https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-12/annapurna...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loupol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by williamdclt in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528536</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528536"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Treat it as a naive but intelligent intern
That’s the problem: it’s a _terrible_ intern. A good intern will ask clarifying questions, tell me “I don’t know” or “I’m not sure I did it right”. LLMs do none of that, they will take whatever you ask and give a reasonable-sounding output that might be anything between brilliant and nonsense.
With an intern, I don’t need to measure how good my prompting is, we’ll usually interact to arrive to a common understanding. With a LLM, I need to put a huge amount of thought into the prompt and have no idea whether the LLM understood what I’m asking and if it’s able to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>williamdclt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism International is Working Both Sides of the Atlantic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333306</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/zionism-international-is-working-both-sides-of-the-atlantic/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AIPAC is funded by corporations that are happy to support the defeat of progressive members of Congress who tend to stand up for both Palestinian rights and worker rights in America. Almost 60% of AIPAC’s money comes from corporate CEOs and other top executives from Fortune 500 companies. The largest single donor to the United Democracy Project is Jan Koum, the multibillionaire former CEO of WhatsApp and a regular Republican funder. The biggest institutional contributors to UDP come from FIRE, finance/insurance and real estate sectors. More
The post Zionism International is Working Both Sides of the Atlantic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerald Sussman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murder in Beita: the IDF’s Killing of Ayşenur Eygi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333492</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/murder-in-beita-the-idfs-killing-of-aysenur-eygi/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli version of the shooting, which the Biden administration swiftly adopted, was quickly shown by witnesses, cellphone videos and a detailed investigation by the Washington Post to be not only implausible but absolute bunk. The murder of Ayşenur Eygi took place at least 20 minutes after the last confrontation between Palestinian villagers and IDF troops. Ayşenur never threw any stones and was never within 200 yards of anyone who did. The rooftop sniper had a clear view of where Ayşenur was standing, talking to her friend Helen, and she couldn’t be confused for a Palestinian “instigator.” For whatever reason, Ayşenur was targeted; the sights of the rifle focused on her head and shot. The bullet that killed her didn’t ricochet off of a tree or a rock or a dumpster. The sniper had a clear shot and took it. As Rachel Corrie’s father, Craig, said this week: “Israel does not do investigations; they do cover-ups.” More
The post Murder in Beita: the IDF’s Killing of Ayşenur Eygi appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Legacy: the Decline of Arms Control and Disarmament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333325</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/bidens-legacy-the-decline-of-arms-control-and-disarmament-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden’s neglect of arms control and disarmament means that the next president will inherit a nuclear landscape that is more threatening and volatile than any other since the Cuban missile crisis more than 60 years ago.  The Cuban missile crisis, however, was a wake up call for both President John F. Kennedy and General Secretary Nikita Khrushchev, leading to a series of arms control and disarmament treaties beginning with the Partial Test Ban Treaty of 1963.   More
The post Biden’s Legacy: the Decline of Arms Control and Disarmament appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Debate: Catch Trump If You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333427</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/the-debate-catch-trump-if-you-can/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after the debate, I woke up to the resounding evidence that Harris had floated like a butterfly over the proceedings and occasionally had stung the hapless Trump like a bee. He, I was assured, had done no better on tariffs, Gaza, Ukraine, abortion, climate change, or January 6 than he had with his eloquence over the Springfield protein diet. Then I re-watched the C-Span feed, including the dismal soundbites from the spin rooms, and came to the conclusion that presidential debates are just a variation on Narcissus’s pond in which we only see our own reflections and hear our own words, which explains why debates rarely move the voting dials. More
The post The Debate: Catch Trump If You Can appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nice Health Ya Got There, Mister. Be a Shame if Someone Took it for Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333393</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/nice-health-ya-got-there-mister-be-a-shame-if-someone-took-it-for-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The very notion that it is acceptable to tie one's health in a civilized nation to having ample cash is clearly anathema to most of the world, but it's the way things are in the United States. Countless individuals toil at jobs that do not provide even cursory health coverage. Many individuals who do have some coverage generally try to avoid tapping into many needed health resources due to the sheer cost-inhibitory manner of it all. Co-pays, deductibles, coinsurance, and mandatory first-born deposits will cost you even if you have insurance. We are at a time when even those who have fairly “decent” insurance ration it, many times avoiding care in the early stages of a condition, which often manifests itself later in more expensive and less treatable conditions. The setup of care in the United States is anything but sensible or cost-efficient.  More
The post Nice Health Ya Got There, Mister. Be a Shame if Someone Took it for Cash appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Catastrophe Smashes Heat Records, as Plutocrats, Politicians Twiddle Their Thumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333343</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/climate-catastrophe-smashes-heat-records-as-plutocrats-politicians-twiddle-their-thumbs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, 2023, was the hottest year on record. But 2024 isn’t over, and July 2024 was the warmest recorded July. So you can expect this year to beat 2023 in the abnormal heat sweepstakes, because that fits the pattern of the last decade, the warmest one ever…Gee whiz, whatever could be causing all this  More
The post Climate Catastrophe Smashes Heat Records, as Plutocrats, Politicians Twiddle Their Thumbs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are Police Entitled to Lie and Slander?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333389</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/why-are-police-entitled-to-lie-and-slander/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a presidential race in which both major party candidates are kowtowing to law enforcement, don’t expect any candor about the perils that politicians have unleashed. To serve and protect, police are allowed to slander and destroy. Cops in many states and localities have acquired the right to lie about their shootings, searches, and practically  More
The post Why are Police Entitled to Lie and Slander? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atavism in the American Mass Psyche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333448</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/atavism-in-the-american-mass-psyche/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s victory in 2016 was a surprise, I conjecture, to Trump himself. I think he was surprised earlier in the Primaries how easy it was to mock and upstage his challengers. He could break all the protocols of proper Primary behavior without check. Perhaps that was the first time he realized there was no  More
The post Atavism in the American Mass Psyche appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Bloody Negotiations Strategy in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333407</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/israels-bloody-negotiations-strategy-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-two years ago, almost to the day, on September 8, 1972, I survived the first of many Israeli air and sea raids on my refugee camp in northern Lebanon. I was less than two hundred yards from the area across the river where a group of us young kids met every day, between 4 and  More
The post Israel’s Bloody Negotiations Strategy in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election 2024: Finally Weird Enough?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333451</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/election-2024-finally-weird-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It never got weird enough for me,” says Hunter S. Thompson — or, rather, Bill Murray as Hunter S. Thompson in 1980s kinda sorta Thompson biopic, Where the Buffalo Roam.  “I moved to the country when the boat got too crowded. Then I learned that President Nixon had been eaten by white cannibals on an  More
The post Election 2024: Finally Weird Enough? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cartography of Genocide: Why Netanyahu Erased Palestine from the Map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333401</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/cartography-of-genocide-why-netanyahu-erased-palestine-from-the-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When asked why his latest map has erased the whole of the West Bank, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu retorted with the most detestable answer. “I didn’t include the Dead Sea. It’s not shown on the map. I didn’t show the Jordan River. It’s not on this map. I didn’t show the Sea of Galilee,”  More
The post Cartography of Genocide: Why Netanyahu Erased Palestine from the Map  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Ambivalent Anniversary of “The One Set of Rules We All Agree On”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333287</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/an-ambivalent-anniversary-of-the-one-set-of-rules-we-all-agree-on/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 2024 marked the 75th anniversary of the four Geneva Conventions which form the basis of international humanitarian law (IHL). The dream of five Swiss men (Henri Dunant, Louis Appia, General Guillaume Henri Dufour, Gustave Moynier, Theodore Maunoir) was realized and codified in the hope of “civilizing” the way wars were fought. Separating civilians from  More
The post An Ambivalent Anniversary of “The One Set of Rules We All Agree On” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antarctica’s Deep Vulnerability Exposed at 11th Scientific Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333413</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/antarcticas-deep-vulnerability-exposed-at-11th-scientific-conference/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 11th Scientific Committee on Antarctic Research conference was held in Pucón, Chile August 19-23, 2024. Fifteen-hundred academics, researchers, and scientists specializing in Antarctica met to share cutting-edge research. Reports at the conference exposed new dimensions of the Antarctic risk profile that should move the world’s leadership posthaste to mitigate society’s self-destructive dependence on fossil  More
The post Antarctica’s Deep Vulnerability Exposed at 11th Scientific Conference appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking 9/11: Fascism, Memory, and the Crisis of Democracy in the 21st Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333470</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/rethinking-9-11-fascism-memory-and-the-crisis-of-democracy-in-the-21st-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this moment in history, we find ourselves in a society defined by relentless speed, overwhelming amounts of information, the proliferation of misinformation, and widening inequality.[1] Fascist politics are increasingly legitimized, long-term commitments are devalued, and the far-right’s vision of society constantly shifts, maintaining control through chaos and confusion. In such an environment, memory becomes  More
The post Rethinking 9/11: Fascism, Memory, and the Crisis of Democracy in the 21st Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peril and Possibility: Post-Election Scenarios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333480</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/peril-and-possibility-post-election-scenarios/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Walz is telling people to “leave it all on the field” of the election. Americans better not follow his advice. The 2024 election day will kick off a much bigger game full of peril but not without some opportunity on the path to the emancipation of humanity. Poisoning Our Blood Let’s start with some  More
The post Peril and Possibility: Post-Election Scenarios appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Personal Meditation on Growing Old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333411</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/a-personal-meditation-on-growing-old/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post headline reads: “A big problem for young workers: 70- and 80-year-olds who won’t retire.” For the first time in history, reports Aden Barton, five generations are competing in the same workforce. His article laments a “demographic traffic jam” at the apexes of various employment pyramids, making it ever harder for young people “to launch their careers and  More
The post A Personal Meditation on Growing Old appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Be Bamboozled by Nuclear Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333439</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/dont-be-bamboozled-by-nuclear-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the face of a complex and urgent problem like climate change, it’s tempting to believe in simple solutions. Just as detox teas or diet pills claim to solve health issues that truly require lifestyle changes, nuclear energy has been marketed as a quick fix for the socio-political problem that climate change is. It’s presented  More
The post Don’t Be Bamboozled by Nuclear Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prerna Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by toomuchtodo in "Boeing workers vote to strike"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528096</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528096"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing spent $43B on stock buybacks between 2013 and 2019 while paying their CEO ~$30M/year.
> To support its share price, the company under McNerney poured billions into stock buybacks instead of investing profits into the kind of research and development needed to stay competitive. McNerney decided not to spend billions of dollars building a new plane to replace the 737. Instead, Boeing tweaked and updated the existing model and called it the 737 Max, outfitting it with larger, more efficient engines for increased economy. Compensating for the resulting instability was a secretive automated system called MCAS that would adjust the plane’s pitch without input from the pilot.
> McNerney also fought to deeply cut costs. On his watch, the company opened its first non-unionized aircraft production line and initiated a program called “Partnering for Success” that pushed suppliers to cut their prices by 15 percent or more. Many feared that squeezing suppliers would harm the quality of their components, but McNerney was determined to recoup the cost of the 787’s development; if the subcontractors complained, they could find their work taken away from them, as happened to landing-gear-maker United Technologies Aerospace Systems.
> McNerney retired in 2015, handpicking his successor, president and COO Dennis Muilenburg. Over the next three years, Boeing’s stock price more than doubled as it sold new planes the world over. (As Bloomberg News reported, Muilenberg and McNerney “had personal reasons to emphasize productivity and cost-cutting” because their compensation was tied to share performance. Together they took $209 million in total pay over seven years.)
https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/boeing-planes-proble...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>toomuchtodo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by MPSimmons in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528061</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528061"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failure is in how you're using it. I don't mean this as a personal attack, but more to shed light on what's happening.
A lot of people use LLMs as a search engine. It makes sense - it's basically a lossy compressed database of everything its ever read, and it generates output that is statistically likely - varying degrees of likeliness depending on the temperature, as well as how many times the particular weights your prompt ends up activating.
The magic of LLMs, especially one like this that supposedly has advanced reasoning, isn't the existing knowledge in its weights. The magic is that _it knows english_. It knows english at or above a level equal to most fluent speakers, and it also can produce output that is not just a likely output, but is a logical output. It's not _just_ an output engine. It's an engine that outputs.
Asking it about nuanced details in the corpus of data it has read won't give you good output unless it read a bunch of it.
On the other hand, if you were to paste the entire documentation set to a tool it has never seen and ask it to use the tool in a way to accomplish your goals, THEN this model would be likely to produce useful output, despite the fact that it had never encountered the tool or its documentation before.
Don't treat it as a database. Treat it as a naive but intelligent intern. Provide it data, give it a task, and let it surprise you with its output.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MPSimmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And so, we return to 1999.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.aurahack.jp/and-so-we-return-to-1999/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.aurahack.jp/and-so-we-return-to-1999/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did not think I would ever be spinning a blog again. I think I did in the, like, pre-Google Blogger days? Or something? I was 14. I thought everyone would follow it and I would be internet famous. I wish I could go back in time and kick my own ass.
This will not be a newsletter. I wanted to make one to have a more centralized "here's an important update" kinda thing but that's a) sort of what my Patreon is and b) if you collect enough emails, which I don't think is unrealistic given my reach at this point, you need to start paying hundreds a month for that shit and, like, no. I will not.
So here's a blog. How often will I post here? I don't know! I don't care! It's actually kind of nice! I don't need to give a shit about it. It's a siloed area I can dump thoughts in and you can read them. Cohost taught me that I really don't need to care about having a statement or take on shit, I can just post and have it immediately leave the aether, so this is what this is for. I also want to have a place to, like, make dev logs or something for comic stuff in the future!
Subscribe to the RSS in the navbar above or bookmark this, if you want.
If you'd like important updates, you can follow my Patreon for free and any major updates like shop updates, new merch, new site launches, etc. will be posted there and mailed to everyone like a newsletter.
Thanks for reading and if you're coming from Cohost, thanks for being there while it was active. The community there was something I'll cherish forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by layer8 in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41527354</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41527354"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The o1-preview model still hallucinates non-existing libraries and functions for me, and is quickly wrong about facts that aren't well-represented on the web. It's the usual string of "You're absolutely correct, and I apologize for the oversight in my previous response. [Let me make another guess.]"
While the reasoning may have been improved, this doesn't solve the problem of the model having no way to assess if what it conjures up from its weights is factual or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>layer8</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planting A Digital Garden]]></title>
        <id>https://darrenhester.com/planting-a-digital-garden/</id>
        <link href="https://darrenhester.com/planting-a-digital-garden/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the idea of a digital garden. I first heard about them in an article by Maggie Appleton where she wrote:
Gardens present information in a richly linked landscape that grows slowly over time. Everything is arranged and connected in ways that allow you to explore.
I’m beginning to cultivate my own digital garden using Bear.  It's a place where I can experiment with creative projects and test new ideas.
Some Examples
This week, I added a Sketchbook and a collection of Wallpapers.

Neither of these fits into the mold of a traditional blog, but they interest me, and I enjoy working on them. I wanted to find a place where they could live on my website.
I also created a Typography page to test markdown syntax and CSS themes. I initially hid this page but decided to make it public in my new digital garden. It’s just the kind of thing I want growing there.
I’ll be adding new pages and updating existing ones often. Anyone curious can always wander around the garden to see what I’m up to.
Over time, I hope to find connections between the different pages. It is a good way to spark more creative ideas.
None of this replaces my blog. It’s in addition to my blog posts. I don’t think it has to be one format or the other. Your blog can also have an area for a digital garden.
What are your thoughts? Do you like this idea?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS for MySQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift, now generally available, enables near real-time analytics]]></title>
        <id>f63b64a0773b039fe7590c2f6116b3ee57fc4cda</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-for-mysql-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-redshift-now-generally-available-enables-near-real-time-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Near real-time data replication: RDS for MySQL zero-ETL with Redshift streamlines data ingestion with filtering, multiple integrations, and CloudFormation support for customized insights without managing complex pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greetings]]></title>
        <id>https://willemhelf.bearblog.dev/greetings/</id>
        <link href="https://willemhelf.bearblog.dev/greetings/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello!
Once again I have abandoned my Substack. Will, you say, you've done this before. And, sure, yes. Last time I bailed on Substack I migrated to Blogspot, but I didn't really like the platform much. This platform is much simpler, a lot less busted, and has RSS and Atom feeds. I also like that it has no trackers or JavaScript.
I've had some weird feelings about maintaining my own Substack for a while now. I just don't think I'm personally cut out for the platform: I don't have a single subject I can write about consistently (and, to be honest, I don't think I can really write consistently at all); I don't like that it's massively metrics-based as I really don't care about that sort of thing; I don't like the constant push to monetize when I've never had any intention of doing that; and, honestly, I was kind of running out of things to say. The fiction I posted just felt like filler so that people would remember the blog existed at all. Sad!
I'm not entirely sure what's going to go here yet but I'm excited to have what feels like a rather cozier corner of the internet than Substack or Twitter. I've also been remaking my website from the ground up to be less of a professional presence and more of a personal one. I've been having a great time with it. Stay tuned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gravitational waves may reveal presence of warp drive starships]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8460</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/gravitational-waves-reveal-presence-warp-drive-starships/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gravitational waves have been helping scientists and astronomers answer some of the big questions of the universe. But gravitational waves may be able to do something else: detect the presence of vessels with Star Trek like warp drive engines, as they move through the cosmos. One problem with the warp drive space-time is that it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee drinkers ditch coffee as price rises continue to bite]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8456</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/coffee-drinkers-ditch-coffee-price-rises-continue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian food critic Terry Durack, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Coffee’s changing. The cost of beans continues to rise, and everyone is on the lookout for alternatives. Old-fashioned espresso coffee is in danger of being shouldered aside, just as cow’s milk is making way for oat, almond and soy. With coffee prices rising, people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bartman in "Learning to Reason with LLMs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41524263</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41524263"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T18:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is incredible. In April I used the standard GPT-4 model via ChatGPT to help me reverse engineer the binary bluetooth protocol used by my kitchen fan to integrate it into Home Assistant.
It was helpful in a rubber duck way, but could not determine the pattern used to transmit the remaining runtime of the fan in a certain mode. Initial prompt here [0]
I pasted the same prompt into o1-preview and o1-mini and both correctly understood and decoded the pattern using a slightly different method than I devised in April. Asking the models to determine if my code is equivalent to what they reverse engineered resulted in a nuanced and thorough examination, and eventual conclusion that it is equivalent. [1]
Testing the same prompt with gpt4o leads to the same result as April's GPT-4 (via ChatGPT) model.
Amazing progress.
[0]: https://pastebin.com/XZixQEM6
[1]: https://i.postimg.cc/VN1d2vRb/SCR-20240912-sdko.png (sorry about the screenshot – sharing ChatGPT chats is not easy)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bartman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Romaric Godin: &ldquo;The Gravedigger&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-gravedigger</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-gravedigger"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michel Barnier and Macronism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In solidarity with the people of the southeast of Moroccoand all those affected by the floods after September 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/In-solidarity-with-the-people-of-the-southeast-of-Moroccoand-all-those-affected</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/In-solidarity-with-the-people-of-the-southeast-of-Moroccoand-all-those-affected"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Press Release 
Press releases

/ 
Poverty, 
Morocco, 
Ecology/Climate, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting APIs from abuse using sequence learning and variable order Markov chains]]></title>
        <id>27ZTkLyAI8VPmwUK2U3jU7</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protecting-apis-from-abuse-using-sequence-learning-and-variable-order-markov"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we protect customer APIs from abuse. This is no easy task, as abusive traffic can take different forms, from giant DDoS attacks to low-and-slow credential stuffing campaigns. We now address this challenge in a new way: by looking outside typical volumetric measures and using statistical machine learning to find important API client request sequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 1st International Antifascist Conference will take place in Porto Alegre in May 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-1st-International-Antifascist-Conference-will-take-place-in-Porto-Alegre-in</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-1st-International-Antifascist-Conference-will-take-place-in-Porto-Alegre-in"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its cancellation due to the floods in Porto Alegre in May 2024, the 1st International Antifascist Conference will take place next year in the capital of Rio Grande do Sul. This delay was a result of the climate crisis, with effects on the host city so severe that, even to this day, the Porto Alegre airport remains closed. The impact was tremendous, causing losses of lives, homes, jobs, memories, and belongings. While this tragedy has forced us to postpone the Conference, it makes (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective, CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackson Hole celebrates itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Jackson-Hole-celebrates-itself</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Jackson-Hole-celebrates-itself"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every August the world's top central bankers meet in Jackson Hole, Wyoming, a ski resort in central US for [a ‘symposium' organized by the Kansas City Federal Reserve. ->https://www.kansascityfed.org/research/jackson-hole-economic-symposium/jackson-hole-economic-policy-symposium-reassessing-the-effectiveness-and-transmission-of-monetary-policyThe bankers take this opportunity to discuss monetary policy and its efficacy in ‘managing the economy', in particular, ‘controlling' inflation and (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Banks, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“No Fist Is Big Enough to Hide the Sky”: 100 Years of Amilcar Cabral]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/No-Fist-Is-Big-Enough-to-Hide-the-Sky-100-Years-of-Amilcar-Cabral</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/No-Fist-Is-Big-Enough-to-Hide-the-Sky-100-Years-of-Amilcar-Cabral"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T09:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Colonialist and anti-imperialist, party organizer and guerilla warfare strategist, diplomat and publicist, revolutionary theorist and internationalist, Amílcar Cabral was among the most original Marxists of the 20th century. 
 Amílcar Lopes da Costa Cabral was born on September 12, 1924 in the town of Bafata in Portuguese Guinea, wedged between what was then French Guinea and the French colony of Senegal, in West Africa. His parents hailed from Cape Verde (Cabo Verde), an archipelago of (...)
English

/ 
Africa, 
Colonialism, 
Imperialism, 
Guinea-Bissau]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by estsauver in "Show HN: Konty – A Balsamiq-alternative lo-fi wireframe tool for modern apps"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41518910</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41518910"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T09:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reason that I've heard used repeatedly is that a shocking percentage of folks who aren't Technology producers can't separate visual quality from "doneness" of a project. If you show some business folks something that looks like it works, they'll mentally update the project to "Nearly done!" and then everything else after that becomes "Unreasonable delays."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>estsauver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/about/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/about/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[whose blog is this
hi! i’m Lena Raine. i’ve written the music you may have heard in indie games such as Celeste & Chicory: A Colorful Tale, and slightly larger games like Minecraft & Guild Wars 2.
i have also written and designed a visual novel called ESC, and am currently working on a brand new game called ANOTHEREAL. i’ll be introducing the game & talking about its development in these little blogs, so stay tuned if you want to find out more!
separately, i’ve also been known to blog about games, music, and other things that interest me. i had an ongoing series of longer posts on the website Cohost, which I’m no longer able to continue due to it shutting down. i hope to use this blog to keep the long-form posting alive. so if you like(d) reading my thoughts on games and other media, those will continue here as well!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[starting once more]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/starting-once-more/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/starting-once-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[well, here we are again. this time in a new space. less eggbug, less (immediate) community… but still a place for me to put words & hopefully have some degree of long-form posting that i’m comfortable with.
i was contemplating setting up a newsletter, and that is well and dandy, but ultimately there’s a lot of baggage that comes from blasting out emails to everyone’s inboxes every time i want to write something on a whim. that’s not necessarily what i’m here for!
i've done my best to port over & fill out the archive with some of my game blogs and other ‘best of’ from cohost, tagging those where appropriate! and then we’ll keep on going… i hope you’ll stick around, subscribe to the rss or atom feed, whatever keeps you updated!
so if you’re new here, have a little dose of introduction:
hi! i’m lena raine. i’ve written the music you may have heard in indie games such as Celeste & Chicory: A Colorful Tale, and slightly larger games like Minecraft & Guild Wars 2.
i have also written and designed a visual novel called ESC, and am currently working on a brand new game called ANOTHEREAL. i’ll be introducing the game & talking about its development in these little blogs, so stay tuned if you want to find out more!
separately, i’ve also been known to blog about games, music, and other things that interest me. i had an ongoing series of longer posts on the website Cohost, which I’m no longer able to continue due to it shutting down. i hope to use this blog to keep the long-form posting alive. so if you like(d) reading my thoughts on games and other media, those will continue here as well!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ad Buster - brandalism in the Netherlands]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brandalism-in-the-netherlands-ad-buster?v=1726099845</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brandalism-in-the-netherlands-ad-buster?v=1726099845"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ad Buster
Title: brandalism in the Netherlands
Subtitle: the vandalism of capitalist propaganda
Date: 21-8-2024
Notes: based on local experience


 advertisement shits in your head 
brandalism
 noun 
 /ˈbrændəlɪzəm/ 
 /ˈbrændəlɪzəm/ 
 1. the vandalism of capitalist propaganda 
 2. subvertising; parodies of advertisements 
 3. protest art to hide advertisement. 
 Our main goal is removing advertisement from the public space. 
 As citizens we should have a say in how our public space looks, we do not accept government renting out the space to some companies, that is supposed to be for all of us. 
 We accept bus stop advertisement as a method to support the bus stop. But there is no excuse for stand alone advertisement in the public space, in this zine we will show some tactics to rem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes - Two years after the victims were found]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/feminist-collective-kores-xapolytes-two-years-after-the-victims-were-found?v=1726096942</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/feminist-collective-kores-xapolytes-two-years-after-the-victims-were-found?v=1726096942"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T23:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes
Title: Two years after the victims were found
Subtitle: Text by feminist group about the handling of the femicide cases by the state and the police
Date: 2021
Notes: This leaflet was written by the Cypriot Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes in June of 2021 and was distributed at a protest outside the Cypriot Attorney General's office that took place on the 18th of June, in Nicosia.
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:leaflets:kores:femicides

 The police, the army, the law office of the republic, the ministries – we consider all of these to comprise the web of patriarchal structures which govern our female bodies in more ways than one. Two years after the “shocking” revelations about the “first serial killer” in Cyprus, not only …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrea Teruel - An Anarchist Conjuration]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrea-teruel-an-anarchist-conjuration?v=1726093411</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrea-teruel-an-anarchist-conjuration?v=1726093411"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T22:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Andrea Teruel
Title: An Anarchist Conjuration
Subtitle: The Benjamin-Bataille Meeting and the Critique of Left-Wing Progressism
Date: 2022
Source: revistas.unc.edu.ar

Abstract
 The article explores the theoretical complicities between the thought of Walter Benjamin and Georges Bataille. Taking as a starting point the anecdote of the Book of Passages, according to which Benjamin would have entrusted this manuscript to the care of Bataille, questions are raised about the possible link between the two thinkers. The relationship that both authors maintained with the leftist political thought of the time and the way in which their revolutionary conceptions distance themselves from orthodox Marxism and dialectical materialism are particularly problematized. In this way, through an analy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook has been scraping the pages of Australians since 2007]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8453</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/facebook-scraping-pages-australians-2007/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jake Evans, writing for the Australian Broadcasting Corporation: Facebook has admitted that it scrapes the public photos, posts and other data of Australian adult users to train its AI models and provides no opt-out option, even though it allows people in the European Union to refuse consent. For sure, Facebook operates a little differently in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240911</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240911"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on writing about my mental health on Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-writing-about-my-mental-health-on-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-writing-about-my-mental-health-on-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T19:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am aware I've been navigating heavy topics in recent blogposts - childhood trauma, depression, and mental health in general. On Bear, I have regularly shared light, easily digestible reads, like slices of life and productivity takes. But I have also shared the brutal reality of living with mental health struggles.
I created this blog during the peaks of a depressive episode, at a time I desperately sought a healthy outlet for my oppressive emotions and ricocheting thoughts. Actually, it was an attempt to abide by my psychologist's advice, who urged me to live for myself, do things I love. I promised myself to write about what matters to me, what I always wanted to share - life updates, opinions, introspections, and most importantly, my mental health journey.
I won't lie to you, though, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging is Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://seadave.org/blogging-hard/</id>
        <link href="https://seadave.org/blogging-hard/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I slowly got into a blog when I retired and decided to give Micro.blog a whirl. I was intrigued by the notion of a community, as I had long been receiving weekly emails with samples of the “Discovery Feed”. I mostly did true “micro posts” for quite a while, then I tried my hand at few long form posts. I got into photo posting, and eventually did a 30 day photo challenge. I also got into the bookshelf feature and posted more than two years of my reading to my blog site.
There came a time when I felt like I had disclosed too much personal information. I realized, for example, that I had always hated that there were digital records of what I read at the library and records of anything I bought at Amazon. This gets at a fundamental issue we all have with all electronic records and communication. I decided last December to “nuke” that blog in its entirety.
I continued to micro post there for a while, and to do several entries that I thought were innocuous. I then looked around at my options, including weblog.lol and bearblog.dev (this blog). The community features at Micro-blog simply didn’t amount to much, after all. Good, but it felt like it could be great. So, I came over here to bearblog.dev and started afresh.
While I still ponder what is too much disclosure, or too little for that matter, I feel like even being factual about some of my past might be a turn off to many potential readers. Lord knows, there aren’t many actual readers. It feels like people want to hear a certain kind of experience, but not hear about others. I am not sure I have the “voice” to be appealing, so I could just file my little essays away privately. I do still seek community, but I find the interaction is on Mastodon (social.lol for me) and that is good.
I’ll poke away at this for a while. None too sure of its longevity.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A left that does not take the lead in the fight against climate catastrophe has no reason to exist!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-left-that-does-not-take-the-lead-in-the-fight-against-climate-catastrophe-has</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-left-that-does-not-take-the-lead-in-the-fight-against-climate-catastrophe-has"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What follows is not addressed to the right and its supporters (economic, social and other) who - unfortunately - are doing their job very well. What follows is addressed above all to the left, which - unfortunately - is not doing its job at all well... 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Capitalism, 
Ecology/Climate, 
Greece]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Harris-Trump US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>4NI7PBab9zePZzucqLYhPh</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-harris-trump-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Kamala Harris and Donald Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns compared to the Biden-Trump debate. We also review email trends and observed attack activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atrettel in "Ask HN: Why is Pave legal?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512162</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512162"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T15:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have never heard of Pave before, but this just sounds like yet another copy of Equifax's "The Work Number" [1].  Basically, HR at many companies gives your salary and employment history data to Equifax, who then sells access to the information to certain parties with supposed need to access it, including potential and current employers and creditors.  This report is likely one of the most invasive consumer files out there for many people.
I cannot comment on the legality of this kind of data sharing, but as I and others have pointed out, it has existed for a while.  I do agree that it is concerning.  You can freeze your Equifax The Work Number report at least, just like other credit reports.
[1] https://theworknumber.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atrettel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by post-it in "We spent $20 to achieve RCE and accidentally became the admins of .mobi"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41511941</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41511941"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T14:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obviously there are a lot of errors by a lot of people that led to this, but here's one that would've prevented this specific exploit:
> As part of our research, we discovered that a few years ago the WHOIS server for the .MOBI TLD migrated from whois.dotmobiregistry.net to whois.nic.mobi – and the dotmobiregistry.net domain had been left to expire seemingly in December 2023.
Never ever ever ever let a domain expire. If you're a business and you're looking to pick up a new domain because it's only $10/year, consider that you're going to be paying $10/year forever, because once you associate that domain with your business, you can never get rid of that association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>post-it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customers get increased integration with Cloudflare Email Security and Zero Trust through expanded partnership with CrowdStrike]]></title>
        <id>2oxT0UhMM8loVoSuUom7W8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/customers-get-increased-integration-with-cloudflare-email-security-and-zero-trust"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains how our integrations with CrowdStrike Falcon® Next-Gen SIEM allow customers to identify and investigate risky user behavior and analyze data combined with other log sources to uncover hidden threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Mahan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank did not Foresee the Arab Spring Popular Uprisings and still Promotes the very same Policies that triggered them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-did-not-Foresee-the-Arab-Spring-Popular-Uprisings-and-still</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-did-not-Foresee-the-Arab-Spring-Popular-Uprisings-and-still"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Africa, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Ghost World&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghost-world</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghost-world"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T10:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Oleksiy Radynski.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikhail Bakunin - On the Question of the Right of Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikhail-bakunin-on-the-question-of-the-right-of-inheritance?v=1726015496</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikhail-bakunin-on-the-question-of-the-right-of-inheritance?v=1726015496"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mikhail Bakunin
Title: On the Question of the Right of Inheritance
Subtitle: in Speeches to the Basle Congress
Date: 1871
Notes: Translation by Robert M. Cutler. ISBN 13: 978-0-87975-745-8 ISBN 10: 0-87975-745-0
Source: The Basic Bakunin: Writings, 1869-1871

 There is but a simple difference between the standpoint of those collectivists who believe that it is useless to vote to abolish the right of inheritance after having voted "for collective property, and that of those collectivists who think, as do we, that it is useful and even necessary to do so. 
 They place themselves entirely in the future and, taking collective property as their point of departure, discover that there is no longer any good reason to be concerned with the right of inheritance. 
 We on the contrary take ou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My impressions of Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://daviramos.com/my-impressions-of-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://daviramos.com/my-impressions-of-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will be very plain. That is because Bear Blog is excellent in a way that is obvious and requires little explaining.  Bear Blog is a minimalistic blogging service that will store your posts and serve them without fluff and at great speed. As Tildes blogging brother, Bear Blog has nothing in excess. At the same time, it allows you complete access to the CSS style, as well as other elements, to the point that it is entirely possible to achieve a layout that resembles a traditional page rather than a blog. Not that I would want that myself, but that looks entirely achievable to me.
It pleases me that Bear Blog doesn't have built-in comments, nor does it have any essential element that goes against its simply stated core goals. In fact, if you look at its roadmap, you will notice that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous Action - Anti-war statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/autonomous-action-anti-war-statement?v=1726013751</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/autonomous-action-anti-war-statement?v=1726013751"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Autonomous Action
Title: Anti-war statement
Date: 29 August 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2nd September 2024 from avtonom.org

 We have stated from the very start that the beginning of a full-scale war in Ukraine on February 24, 2022 is an imperialist aggression of the Russian state. That is still true. 
Our position on the war in Ukraine
“Autonomous Action” is not on the side of the Ukrainian state — and not on the side of any other state. However, in the current circumstances, the victory of Russia is not beneficial to the peoples of neither Ukraine, nor Russia, nor Belarus. Fighting against Russian aggression is now beneficial to everyone except the Kremlin. It is easy to see why it is beneficial to the Ukrainian authorities. But why is it also beneficial to people (and, accordingly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDIOTEQ, Warzone Distro, Flower Bomb - BURNING DOWN THE WORLD]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/idioteq-burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro?v=1726009440</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/idioteq-burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro?v=1726009440"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T23:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: IDIOTEQ, Warzone Distro, Flower Bomb
Title: BURNING DOWN THE WORLD
Subtitle: IDIOTEQ interviews Warzone Distro
Date: SEPTEMBER 2, 2024
Source: https://idioteq.com/burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro/

 Born in 2013, WARZONE DISTRO free zine project, stands at the intersection of nihilist, anti-civilization anarchy, and total liberation, bridging gaps between veganism, straight edge, and insurrectionary thought. WARZONE DISTRO is dedicated to challenging the very foundations of oppression, wherever it festers, and in whatever form. 
 In our interview below, we delve into the radical philosophy driving WARZONE DISTRO, exploring how they blend anarchist and vegan ideals to craft a vision of true total liberation. We talk about the unique ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wulfinna - Bias]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-bias?v=1726007334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-bias?v=1726007334"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wulfinna
Title: Bias
Date: 09-09-2024
Source: https://ignitedindark.wordpress.com/2024/09/09/bias/

 Along the horridly neglected path out of being commanded and subjected, from the stinking bowels of the societies of oiled gears, permanent emissions, bright screens, information haze and ceaseless masturbation to worn-out sensibility, there arises a shrill hissing of such stupid nature, of such whining entitlement, that the lone rebel catches herself snickering — then nearly dying laughing . . . 
 "You have a left-wing bias!" 
 "You have a right-wing bias!" 
 "You have a centrist bias!" 
 "You have an extremist bias!" 
 Ha! Ahahaha! Ah, the acrid hell of human hubris knows no end! The sheer closeness in conceptual capacity to being god — yet holding oneself back at the last second …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A.X. - Blackness and Democratic Modernity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/a-x-blackness-and-democratic-modernity?v=1726007099</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/a-x-blackness-and-democratic-modernity?v=1726007099"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: A.X.
Title: Blackness and Democratic Modernity
Date: January 10, 2023
Source: https://harbinger-journal.com/issue-2/blackness-and-democratic-modernity/

 “Modernity as a concept means time, the present. There are different moderns, depending on the age. From Sumerian modernity to Roman modernity, and even before and after them, there have been…many examples of modernity.” 
 Abdullah Öcalan, The Sociology of Freedom
 “The Negro’s revolutionary history is rich, inspiring, and unknown. Negroes revolted against the slave raiders in Africa; they revolted against the slave traders on the Atlantic passage. They revolted on the plantations. The docile Negro is a myth… The only place where Negroes did not revolt is in the pages of capitalist historians.” 
 C.L.R. James, “Revolution and the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1726006831</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1726006831"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)
Subtitle: “Cyprus Belongs to its Mouflons”
Date: 2017
Notes: This is an undergraduate dissertation submitted at the Department of Sociology of the University of Glasgow in 2017.
Source: Retrieved on 24rd August 2024 from archive.org

Abstract
 This dissertation examines the structure of Cypriot anarchist ideology and the way it challenges Greek Cypriot ethnic nationalism, as it developed in the first decade following the partition of the island of Cyprus. It aims to contribute to the understanding of grass root political activity in Cyprus, by examining the early expressions of anarchism in the island. Ideology has been argued to function around the use of key discursi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by renhanxue in "Why Not Comments"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41506182</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41506182"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw someone quip (on twitter, I think) many years ago something like:
"A junior engineer writes comments that explain what the code does. A mid-level engineer writes comments that explain why the code does what it does. A senior engineer writes comments that explain why the code isn't written in another way."
(except punchier, of course. I'm not doing the quip justice here)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>renhanxue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does a court ruling mean no more Internet Archive, Way Back Machine?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8444</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/court-ruling-ends-internet-archive-way-back-machine/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Archive (IA) has been fighting a number of legal proceedings recently, after making digitised copies of numerous books and novels freely available, through their website. At no point did the IA seek permission from any of the authors involved, nor did they offer them any sort of payment, for copying and distributing their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pushy to the Limit: Evolving Netflix’s WebSocket proxy for the future]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b468bc0ff658</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/pushy-to-the-limit-evolving-netflixs-websocket-proxy-for-the-future-b468bc0ff658?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T19:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pushy is Netflix’s WebSocket server that maintains persistent WebSocket connections with devices running the Netflix application. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noisy Neighbor Detection with eBPF]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/64b1f4b3bbdd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/noisy-neighbor-detection-with-ebpf-64b1f4b3bbdd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez, Sebastien Dabdoub, Jason Koch, Artem Tkachuk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker HyperPod introduces Amazon EKS support]]></title>
        <id>b6be07b1f469321af78fecbb25121071d42162ad</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-introduces-amazon-eks-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker HyperPod's integration with Amazon EKS brings resilience, observability, and flexibility to large model training, reducing downtime by up to 40%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulator-based reinforcement learning for data center cooling optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21675</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/09/10/data-center-engineering/simulator-based-reinforcement-learning-for-data-center-cooling-optimization/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing more about the role that reinforcement learning plays in helping us optimize our data centers’ environmental controls. Our reinforcement learning-based approach has helped us reduce energy consumption and water usage across various weather conditions in our data centers.   Meta is revamping its new data center design to optimize for artificial intelligence and the [...]
Read More...
The post Simulator-based reinforcement learning for data center cooling optimization appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A good day to trie-hard: saving compute 1% at a time]]></title>
        <id>2CqKLNS1jaf5H2j99sDONe</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/pingora-saving-compute-1-percent-at-a-time"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pingora handles 35M+ requests per second, so saving a few microseconds per request can translate to thousands of dollars saved on computing costs. In this post, we share how we freed up over 500 CPU cores by optimizing one function and announce trie-hard, the open source crate that we created to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Guthrie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Strauss and Mother Night]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53179</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/10/leo-strauss-and-mother-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T12:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will be brief. Straussianism is a set of interpretative practices along the following lines, as best as I understand it. The great philosophers and thinkers may have a specific private belief – let’s call it x. But they may not be able to say exactly what they want to say, especially when times are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs Are More Important Than Ever Now]]></title>
        <id>https://popcar.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-more-important-than-ever-now/</id>
        <link href="https://popcar.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-more-important-than-ever-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is 2024. Social media is melting down and locking down their content behind increasingly expensive APIs. Websites are increasing ads to a ridiculous degree because they aren't as profitable as they used to be. The first 5 articles on top of Google are garbage created using AI specifically tuned to maximize search engine optimization. 90% of comments on that one review you read are astroturfing accounts trying to sell you something. Youtube still cannot stop the "pu$$y In BIO!!" spam comments.
The bad news everyone figured out is that the internet is getting more chaotic and buckling under the stress of spam and bot accounts running around everywhere. The worse news is that nobody knows what to do about it.
That's why I think blogging has become so important. You get to read though…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>