<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-01-07T12:50:33.994Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-01-07T12:50:33.994Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/7/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285025</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-7-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our anti-fragile daily links: Oat milk hazards? China new virus assessment, Biden drillling ban, Trudeau quits, France looting of Africa, EU leaders + Starmer v. Musk, Finkelstein on Gaza defeat, China currency wars? Trump v. hush money sentencing, private credit worries, Tesla revenues fall]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYT Readies Terrain for Incoming Trump Administration’s Long-Telegraphed Intervention in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285080</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/nyt-lays-groundwork-for-trump-administrations-long-telegraphed-intervention-in-mexico.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media's role in selling the next military adventure should never be underestimated, even in this media-skeptic age. The more prestigious the media, the bigger the role.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental and climate debt: Who is responsible?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Environmental-and-climate-debt-Who-is-responsible</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Environmental-and-climate-debt-Who-is-responsible"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concepts of climate debt and ecological debt are central to successfully achieving the ecological bifurcation. The ecological debt owed by States – and in particular the wealthiest States and major corporations – of the North to the populations of the Global South must be recognized. That recognition must take the form of cancellation of the debt of the countries of the Global South and paying of reparations by the States of the North. The latter must compel the wealthiest interests to (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Natural Resources, 
Ecology/Climate, 
EN Dette écologique et climatique : Qui est responsable ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE: Nations Aren’t Corporations and ‘Efficiency’ Means Austerity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/doge-nations-arent-corporations-and-efficiency-means-austerity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T10:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why DOGE, if implemented on the scale intended, will be a train wreck for the great majority of Americans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health Insurers Limit Coverage of Prosthetic Limbs, Questioning Their Medical Necessity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285111</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/health-insurers-limit-coverage-of-prosthetic-limbs-questioning-their-medical-necessity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T10:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another type of example of how health insurers screw patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banana Road From South America to China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349206</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-banana-road-from-south-america-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T07:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November, Álvaro Noboa, the father of Ecuador’s president Daniel Noboa, had a heart attack. He was hastily taken to a clinic in Guayaquil, his hometown, and then after he was stabilized, flown to a hospital in New York. Álvaro Noboa unsuccessfully ran for president five times (1998, 2002, 2006, 2009, and 2013), but it  More
The post The Banana Road From South America to China appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A War Against Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349228</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/a-war-against-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our ability to make and tell stories is what makes us human. That’s also how we deal with suffering and pain and loss. But stories have an arc; there is a return from the abyss. Terrible, tragic things happen, even things which we might never heal from, but people change and adapt and weave the terrible into the story of their life. People die, but their influence lives on, their memory is celebrated and valued by those who knew and loved them. People suffer but they learn something and grow from their experiences, somehow, however awful they are. ‘Your gift will come from your wound,’ as the storytellers say.  More
The post A War Against Meaning appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Glazebrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unbearably Short Life of an Anti-War Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349387</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-unbearably-short-life-of-an-anti-war-movement/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The thing that is to be supported, and the force that is to support it should stand in geometrical proportion to each other” cardinal Richelieu, cited by Henry Kissinger “Nothing is thoroughly real, therefore everything is permitted” – Hassan I. Sabbah, Persian leader of the assassins, in Vladimir Bartol’s novel Alamut. Even if it had  More
The post The Unbearably Short Life of an Anti-War Movement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arturo Desimone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiation Smokescreen: How the U.S. and Antisemites Became Key Enablers of Israeli Genocide in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349389</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/negotiation-smokescreen-how-the-u-s-and-antisemites-became-key-enablers-of-israeli-genocide-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The devastation in Gaza continues to escalate, with ceasefire negotiations used as part of a calculated strategy and a smokescreen until Israel completes its ethnic cleansing of northern Gaza. Crucial to the success of this plan is the unwavering complicity of the Biden administration, which has embraced and amplified Israeli narratives, shielded it from accountability,  More
The post Negotiation Smokescreen: How the U.S. and Antisemites Became Key Enablers of Israeli Genocide in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Unknown or No Direction Home: The Enigma of Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349372</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/a-complete-unknown-or-no-direction-home-the-enigma-of-bob-dylan/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bob Dylan is back in the news again. A countercultural hero to people who grew up some five decades ago, yet also, perhaps not surprisingly, given his paradoxical character, someone who hated the role into which he had been cast and someone who has been incorporated in the literary establishment by virtue of his Nobel  More
The post A Complete Unknown or No Direction Home: The Enigma of Bob Dylan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John S. Auerbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Military to Prison Pipeline: Trading One Uniform for Another]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349221</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-military-to-prison-pipeline-trading-one-uniform-for-another/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like old soldiers around the country, a group of former service members gathered in Crest Hill, Illinois to remember fallen comrades on Memorial Day, 2024. Several months later, The Veteran, a newspaper published by Vietnam Veterans Against the War, ran a photo of the event they attended. It shows a multi-generational group of men–white, Black  More
The post The Military to Prison Pipeline: Trading One Uniform for Another appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Early - Suzanne Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the World Hides Liability for Climate Deaths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349368</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/how-the-world-hides-liability-for-climate-deaths/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly half the world’s children “live in countries where risks to their health and safety due to the effects of climate change are extremely high,” according to UNICEF. By 2050, almost all children globally will be “exposed to heat waves,” resulting in the rise of specific health issues, especially for smaller children, adds the agency. Rich nations’ inability  More
The post How the World Hides Liability for Climate Deaths appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Berke, Carter Dillard, Beatrix Homler and Rei Stone-Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Would Surprise America’s Rich in 2025? Not Getting Richer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349259</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/what-would-surprise-americas-rich-in-2025-not-getting-richer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new year has begun with old news: The world is continuing to become colossally more unequal — with the United States leading the way. In 2024, wealth trackers at Bloomberg have just reported in a year-end review, “the world’s 500 richest people got vastly richer.” Of the world’s 15 richest individuals, the Bloomberg data  More
The post What Would Surprise America’s Rich in 2025? Not Getting Richer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Jimmy Carter Pardoned Draft Resisters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349392</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/why-jimmy-carter-pardoned-draft-resisters/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The passing of Jimmy Carter has been duly noted in ubiquitous remembrances and commentaries on his four-year presidency, 1977-1981. Carter is lauded more for his post-presidential humanitarian projects, while his presidency is deemed a mixed bag by left and right alike. For many Vietnam War resisters – myself included, it is more personal. Jimmy Carter’s  More
The post Why Jimmy Carter Pardoned Draft Resisters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerry Condon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title Launch Observability at Netflix Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/19ea916be1ed</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/title-launch-observability-at-netflix-scale-19ea916be1ed?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T01:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: Navigating Ambiguity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Is It That xAI’s (Naïve) Grok Does Not Reveal that xAI is a Public Benefit Corporation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285055</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/how-is-it-that-xais-grok-does-not-reveal-that-xai-is-a-public-benefit-corporation.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T21:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambert annotates a Grok transcript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3: A Survey of Analytics Engineering Work at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e67f0aa82183</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/part-3-a-survey-of-analytics-engineering-work-at-netflix-e67f0aa82183?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the last in a multi-part series sharing a breadth of Analytics Engineering work at Netflix, recently presented as part of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zdc1 in "Stimulation Clicker"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614326"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finished the game without cheating. I felt like a frog being slowly boiled (and it really does feel like you're boiling at the end). It's quite the journey...
I love how everything here isn't even farfetched. It's just standard YouTube and TikTok content. The red notification bubbles were also a nice touch, I felt myself really drawn to those, and if I think back, I guess that's the earliest example I can recall of where these patterns all started: Facebook's little red notification bubble]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zdc1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 1/6/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285044</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/200pm-water-cooler-1-6-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecast 2025: roaring or tepid?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Forecast-2025-roaring-or-tepid</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Forecast-2025-roaring-or-tepid"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to make some forecasts on what will happen to the world economy and its major countries in 2025. Many people reckon that it is waste of time making such forecasts as they are never accurate and quite often the opposite happens. Of course, forecasts are wrapped in error, given the many variables involved that drive economies. Weather forecasts are still difficult to make and meteorologists are dealing with physical events and not (at least directly) with human actions. Nevertheless, (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Debt crisis, 
Recession]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup: 2025 Tech Predictions, Llama 3.3 70B, Stable Diffusion 3.5 Large, custom billing view, and more (January 6, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>4fa89b3af496404ca2ee8f7c6b9813035cee90e6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-2025-tech-predictions-llama-3-3-70b-stable-diffusion-3-5-large-custom-billing-view-and-more-january-6-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! We are witnessing technology augment human ingenuity in inspiring ways. In the coming years, using technology for positive impact will redefine the way we think about success. Amazon CTO, Dr. Werner Vogels, offers five forward-looking tech predictions for 2025, and beyond: The workforce of tomorrow is mission-driven A new era of energy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize your container workloads for sustainability]]></title>
        <id>7d5701991d02108aba8dd83e32c2ee4765f604d5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/optimize-your-container-workloads-for-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog was authored by Karthik Rajendran, Senior Solutions Architect (AWS) and Isha Dua, Senior Solutions Architect (AWS).  The software architect’s job is mostly one of trade-offs, weighing the considerations of different approaches and then choosing the one that strikes the best balance. Some architects are surprised to find that, in the AWS Cloud at least, architecting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hamandcheese in "3blue1brown YouTube Bitcoin video taken down as copyright violation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612966</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612966"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T17:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems like a huge abuse of the copyright system to me. It sounds to me like ChainPatrol doesn't actually have any IP to protect, but they are instead deputizing YouTube's copyright system to fight what they deem to be crypto scams. Absolutely wild if true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hamandcheese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wil421 in "3blue1brown YouTube Bitcoin video taken down as copyright violation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612650</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612650"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T17:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is 2030. After the AI bot wars, FaceBook and Google have been crippled. They let AI automation control their content and it was deleted after OpenAI GPT10 discovered vulnerabilities in automated copyright strikes.
Taco Bell won the franchise war and is the only restaurant remaining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wil421</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by catgary in "Justin Trudeau promises to resign as PM"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612168</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612168"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T16:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it’s worth noting that the weekend before this, local residents of Ottawa had basically “stormed” one of the trucker convoy camps to unblock a road. There were genuine concerns that the residents of Ottawa were ready to take matters into their own hands, and it would be a bloodbath. Not to mention the blockade in Alberta where they were found with guns and a pipe bomb, with their communications indicating they were planning to murder the RCMP officers on site!
Declaring the Emergency acts was overwhelmingly popular in Canada and remains one of the most popular things Trudeau ever did. The moves to restrict access to banking affected less than 20 people (and I think they were generally funnelling money from international propaganda groups or committing similar financial crimes).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>catgary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by csense in "Justin Trudeau promises to resign as PM"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42611968</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42611968"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T16:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patio11 has some good coverage of Trudeau's handling of the trucker protest against the government's handling of COVID-19 [1].
Whatever you think of the truckers' position or protest tactics, any punishment for their actions ought to go through the laws and court system.  Trudeau instead essentially told the banking system "You can't do business with those people, they're terrorists."  Patio11's words of what happened next:
"The assistant deputy finance minister...said...'The intent was not to get at the families', and when a democratic government starts a sentence that way something deeply #*&$#ed up has happened."
I'm not on the pulse of Canadian politics, so I don't really know what sins or political circumstances have led Trudeau to this point, or if he has any redeeming qualities.  Personally, I'm glad to see him gone.
[1] https://www.bitsaboutmoney.com/archive/debanking-and-debunki...
(You'll have to Ctrl+F trucker as this blog doesn't seem to have  for headings, as is customary on e.g. Wikipedia.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csense</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by armada651 in "Apple squandered the Holy Grail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42610957</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42610957"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T14:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Word processors like MacWrite absolutely transformed the ways that everyone used computers.
MacWrite was released 5 years after WordPerfect, which itself is predated by WordStar. I don't get why Apple fans have this obsession with pretending Apple invents these things.
Apple refines what others have attempted before, that's what they're good at. Part of the reason people are disappointed with Apple these days is because of this fantasy image of Apple as an inventor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>armada651</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/6/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285018</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-6-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T11:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Benefits from Russia’s War in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285040</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/who-benefits-from-russias-war-in-ukraine.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T10:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to plans, Ukraine war sanctions against Russia enriched many of Russia's top businessmen, including those sanctioned personally.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Many Rural Women, Finding Maternity Care Outweighs Concerns About Abortion Access]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285023</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/for-many-rural-women-finding-maternity-care-outweighs-concerns-about-abortion-access.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T10:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rural residents say no thanks to more abortion availability without better access to comprehensive healthcare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Cracks in the Empire – Is the American Superpower Fading?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285038</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/michael-hudson-cracks-in-the-empire-is-the-american-superpower-fading.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T09:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson provides a new, wide-ranging talk on the US hegemony-preservation efforts and what they mean for Europe, Russia, and BRICS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by padolsey in "Hitting OKRs vs. Doing Your Job"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42608823</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42608823"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T08:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now having worked in a few smaller teams since my time at FB, I realize how marvellous it is to not have to worry about OKRs, performance reviews and all that malarkey. It was so draining to run yourself as a mini PR/brand within one's team (/one's department) and market oneself (one's team) to your manager (/your company).
So much mental bandwidth was spent.
I also, from a systems-thinking POV, just fundamentally reject the value in OKRs as a meaningful proxy for the value you (/your team) are producing unless you are an entirely mechanistic function. By mechanistic I mean you have a clear discrete InputOutput expectation. Every single time an element of human activity is reduced to a metric, you lose something, and if you do it enough times, you've effectively produced a metric that is completely distinct from the thing you intended on measuring in the first place. For example: let's say you're in the suicide prevention team at FB, and your OKR is 'number of suicides averted'. Well, that sounds good, but unbeknownst to you, perverse incentives have kicked in and invisibly imbued your metric-chasing experiments a dark undertone. A new risk model might start flagging more content as potentially suicidal to boost numbers, leading to over-intervention that could traumatize users or waste resources. Or perhaps the surface we use to measure success, a UX or user activity metric, might actually be uncorrelated with crisis aversion or... and this is where it hits: the thing that's instrumental in crises is social media itself. The metric becomes a game, and it games _you_. Your team thinks you're doing X, but you're really doing Y. Because you're disattached from the real problem and comforted by incredibly lossy proxies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>padolsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Transition Travesty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/the-transition-travesty/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T07:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark the current scene.  A politically defunct, King Lear-like Joe Biden continues to make big and small policy decisions after his intended successor’s platform narrowly but clearly lost at the ballot box, even as President-elect Donald Trump conducts an incipient shadow presidency through a torrent of legal maneuvers, social media pronouncements and interviews, sounding more Caesarian by the day.  More
The post The Transition Travesty appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Medish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Will Mexico’s New President Deal With Trump, Migration and Drug Cartels?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349225</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/how-will-mexicos-new-president-deal-with-trump-migration-and-drug-cartels/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June 2024, Mexicans elected a female president, Claudia Sheinbaum to replace Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador. Arguably, Mexico is Washington’s most significant foreign policy partner, playing a central role in two issues that Donald Trump manipulated to win the 2024 presidential election: migration and drugs. More
The post How Will Mexico’s New President Deal With Trump, Migration and Drug Cartels? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Un]Happy New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349272</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/unhappy-new-year/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honestly, as 2025 begins, isn’t it finally time to reimagine American history? So, what do you think of this: George Trump, Abraham Trump, Ulysses S. Trump, Franklin D. Trump, Dwight D. Trump, John F. Trump, Lyndon B. Trump, and even Richard M. and George W. Trump. And yes, of course, on January 20th, Donald J.  More
The post [Un]Happy New Year appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letters from Gaza – ‘Alhamdulillah. We Are Not Okay’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349278</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/letters-from-gaza-alhamdulillah-we-are-not-okay/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 14 months, I have received hundreds of messages from family members throughout the Gaza Strip. The nature of the messages often conveyed a sense of urgency and panic but, at times, contentment in God’s will. Some of those who wrote these notes have been killed in Israeli strikes, like my sister, Dr.  More
The post Letters from Gaza – ‘Alhamdulillah. We Are Not Okay’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans and Violence: Chicken or Egg?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349266</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/veterans-and-violence-chicken-or-egg/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I need to cleanse my mind of the brothers I’ve lost,”  Master Sergeant Matthew Alan Livelsberger (US Army) allegedly wrote in an explanatory note on his phone before shooting himself inside a Tesla Cybertruck packed with fireworks and gas tanks set to detonate outside a Las Vegas casino, “and relieve myself of the burden of  More
The post Veterans and Violence: Chicken or Egg? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gutting the Right to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349269</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/gutting-the-right-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I usually refrain from criticizing opinions issued by the Montana Supreme Court (the Court). I cannot stand silent, however in the face of the Court’s recent evisceration of Montana’s fundamental constitutional Right to Know, Article II, section 9. This provision guarantees that “No person shall be deprived of the right to examine documents or to  More
The post Gutting the Right to Know appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James C. Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frail Egos and Sandpit Colonialism: Australia, the United States and Invading Iraq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349273</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/frail-egos-and-sandpit-colonialism-australia-the-united-states-and-invading-iraq/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Australian Prime Minister John Howard is in the news again.  The release of Australian cabinet documents from 2004 – a supposed treat for historians of Australian history each new year – has been given a typically modest, calm and boringly anodyne treatment in media outlets. One topic featured should have caused continued sharp intakes of breath  More
The post Frail Egos and Sandpit Colonialism: Australia, the United States and Invading Iraq appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Must Keep Up Our Courage:  Ending Yoon Suk Yeol’s Legacy of Betrayal and Dismantlement of Korea’s Sovereignty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349322</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/we-must-keep-up-our-courage-ending-yoon-suk-yeols-legacy-of-betrayal-and-dismantlement-of-koreas-sovereignty/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than 44 hours Koreans have braved freezing snowstorms to demand the arrest of the elusive Yoon Suk Yeol, who has barricaded himself inside his official residence in defiance of constitutional and legal authority.  Yoon, extolled by Washington as a “champion of democracy,” has vanished from public view behind hastily erected barricades manned by  More
The post We Must Keep Up Our Courage:  Ending Yoon Suk Yeol’s Legacy of Betrayal and Dismantlement of Korea’s Sovereignty appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simone Chun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Center Has Collapsed: What Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349280</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/the-center-has-collapsed-what-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who brought down the center? We the left, of course! Hey, Hurray! We the virtuous. We showed those Dems. Kicked those hypocrites where it hurts. Three Hurray’s! Well … WE didn’t do any such thing. The Arab American voters in Michigan, Palestinian American voters all over, Muslim-Americans all over, all kinds of decent people with  More
The post The Center Has Collapsed: What Now? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>REZA FIYOUZAT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stock Market and Budget Projections: Do the Numbers Add Up?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349211</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/stock-market-and-budget-projections-do-the-numbers-add-up/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a while since we’ve had Mr. Arithmetic here, but with Donald Trump coming back to the White House, we may need him around. The immediate reason for consulting his expertise is the projections for big stock market gains in 2025. It seems the median forecast is for the S&P 500 to rise by  More
The post Stock Market and Budget Projections: Do the Numbers Add Up? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental and Climate Debt:  Who is Responsible?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349208</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/environmental-and-climate-debt-who-is-responsible/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concepts of climate debt and ecological debt are central to successfully achieving the ecological bifurcation. The ecological debt owed by States – and in particular the wealthiest States and major corporations – of the North to the populations of the Global South must be recognized. That recognition must take the form of cancellation of  More
The post Environmental and Climate Debt:  Who is Responsible? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Perriot – Éric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bee_rider in "In my life, I've witnessed three elite salespeople at work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42606745</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42606745"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T01:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I know a good salesman when I see one. I was, briefly, the No. 1 telemarketer in the United States.
Oh neat, how?
> Unlike many of my less successful colleagues, I quickly learned to take yes for an answer; though we were legally required to read a long list of mandatory disclosures to all our sales, I noticed that this often broke the spell and gave people an opening to back out or “wait and ask the wife about it.” As soon as I heard a yes, I said, “Great choice!” and transferred them to confirmation. My manager occasionally came by and reminded me that it was technically illegal to skip my disclosures, but he made commission off my commission, and his tone made it clear that I could do as I pleased as long as I kept putting up numbers.
[…]
> I was one of the first to go, technically for not making my required disclosures—about cancellation fees, international rates, all that fine print nobody ever bothered to recite—on a sale.
So, he and his boss did crime together for a while and then eventually their scam stopped working and he got fired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bee_rider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by armchairhacker in "In my life, I've witnessed three elite salespeople at work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42605170</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42605170"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T21:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#1: An inmate who preaches "criminal wisdom" of questionable quality, like "want to know how to disable a burglar alarm with aluminum foil?"
#2: A telemarketing old lady with a "warm voice and metronomic cadence".
#3: An NYC beggar who "walks up to a table, falls to his knees, interlaces his hands as if in prayer, and begs, at the top of his lungs, Please please please, money, please I need a dollar!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>armchairhacker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rambles.NET, a webzine founded by Tom Knapp in 1999]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9054</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/rambles-net-webzine-founded-tom-knapp-1999/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T20:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rambles.NET is an online magazine founded by Tom Knapp in 1999, and still going strong over twenty-five later. Knapp himself continues to contribute. Rambles is another example of Indie Web in its original inception; I think a Facebook page is the only hint of social media present. I had a crack at publishing a webzine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie Web makes all of us property owners online]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9051</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-web-property-owners-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T19:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American engineer and product manager Den Delimarsky offers another way of looking at the core Indie Web tenets of owning your own website domain, and owning your own content. See yourself as a property owner, rather than a renter. If any of your online presence is on social media channels, you’re leasing the space, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inauguration insurance, another form of cookie insurance?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9049</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/inauguration-insurance-cookie-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T19:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Ellis writes about buying a plate of cookies he had no intention of eating, from an entrepreneurial twelve-year old neighbour going door to door, who was selling them. Why would anyone pay out good money for something they’re not going to consume? Ellis describes the gesture as cookie insurance: Lastly, I bought cookies I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Tech Billionaires Bought the Loudest Voices on the Left and Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348918</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/05/how-tech-billionaires-bought-the-loudest-voices-on-the-left-and-right/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T07:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube screenshot. Glenn Greenwald, Youtube […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post How Tech Billionaires Bought the Loudest Voices on the Left and Right appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Guerrilla Journalism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348927</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/05/what-is-guerrilla-journalism/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T07:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writers Against the War on Gaza (WAWOG) was launched in the waning hours of October 7, 2023, when growing numbers of journalists, artists, academicians, and poets around the world saw that Israel was escalating what had been a quieter, more contained genocide into the complete annihilation of the Palestinian people. WAWOG charges that this enhanced […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What is Guerrilla Journalism? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susie Day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Continues to Import Israeli Gas Amid Genocide in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348365</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/05/europe-continues-to-import-israeli-gas-amid-genocide-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T06:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 17, a Dutch nonprofit organization dedicated to corporate accountability, SOMO, published a study of Israel’s energy sector amid the ongoing Israeli genocide in the Gaza Strip. Since Palestinian militants attacked Israel on October 7, 2023, Israeli forces have killed more than 46,000 Palestinians, including 17,000 children, according to the Palestinian Ministry of Health, as cited by Al Jazeera. The true toll of the genocide — obscured by continued Israeli attacks, blockade and propaganda — may top 330,000 deaths by the end of the year, per estimates published in The Guardian.
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Europe Continues to Import Israeli Gas Amid Genocide in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tomalaci in "Meta is killing off its AI-powered Instagram and Facebook profiles"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42596040</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42596040"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T17:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what AI profiles I want more of? Clueless grandma/grandpa that accepts scammer calls and waste their time. Such as UK's O2 Daisy: https://news.virginmediao2.co.uk/o2-unveils-daisy-the-ai-gra...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tomalaci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Who Gives a Shit?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349096</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/04/who-gives-a-shit/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-04T15:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still from the Ask Project interviews with Israeli women about Gaza. Still from the Ask Project interviews with Israeli women about Gaza. Still from the Ask Project interviews with Israeli women about Gaza. Still from the Ask Project interviews with Israeli women about Gaza. Still from the Ask Project interviews with Israeli women about Gaza. […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post “Who Gives a Shit?” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists to explore life creation from basic chemicals + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-to-explore-life-creation-from-basic-chemicals-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-to-explore-life-creation-from-basic-chemicals-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T16:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European scientists launch MiniLife project to create lab-made life, companies in Australia start mandatory climate disclosures, and discontent shapes global elections as incumbents lose votes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Path TCP: revolutionizing connectivity, one path at a time]]></title>
        <id>6ZxrGIedGqREgTs02vpt0t</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/multi-path-tcp-revolutionizing-connectivity-one-path-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Path TCP (MPTCP) leverages multiple network interfaces, like Wi-Fi and cellular, to provide seamless mobility for more reliable connectivity. While promising, MPTCP is still in its early stages,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marek Majkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dgacmu in "Can LLMs write better code if you keep asking them to “write better code”?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42585375</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42585375"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T13:14:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm amused that neither the LLM or the author identified one of the simplest and most effective optimizations for this code: Test if the number is  max _before_ doing the digit sum. It's a free 5.5x speedup that renders some of the other optimizations, like trying to memoize digit sums, unnecessary.
On an m1 macbook pro, using numpy to generate the random numbers, using mod/div to do digit sum:
Base: 55ms
Test before digit sum: 7-10ms, which is pretty close to the numba-optimized version from the post with no numba and only one line of numpy. Using numba slows things down unless you want to do a lot of extra work of calculating all of the digit sums in advance (which is mostly wasted).
The LLM appears less good at identifying the big-o improvements than other things, which is pretty consistent with my experience using them to write code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dgacmu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BJones12 in "Why Canada Should Join the EU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583575</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583575"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Europeans could learn from Canada how to allow immigration in a fashion that the population embraces rather than tolerates
Clearly the author is ignorant. Canadians are sick of immigration. Young Canadians doubly so. Racism is becoming more acceptable by the day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BJones12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by antics in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583334</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583334"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are catching a lot of flak for this, but there is one thing you are right about. If you make tens of millions of dollars, and can't figure out what to do with those resources, you shouldn't be calling your coworkers NPCs. You're the NPC.
I truly mean this in an entirely non-judgemental way. I wish the author luck in achieving his dream of becoming high agency rather than simply high freedom. I wish it for everyone who wants it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>antics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psychiatry’s Latest Insane Magic-Bullet Treatment for Depression: Why Ketamine?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348704</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/psychiatrys-latest-insane-magic-bullet-treatment-for-depression-why-ketamine/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clinics offering ketamine infusions and injections for “treatment-resistant depression” are today claiming 24-48 hours remission, and ketamine is also being marketed for post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), obsessive-compulsive disorder, bipolar disorder, and anxiety disorder. “Between 500 and 750 ketamine clinics have cropped up across the United States,” NPR reported early in 2024 (“The Ketamine Economy: New Mental Health Clinics are a ‘Wild West’ with Few Rules”). This may be an underestimation, as Psychiatric News reported later in 2024, “More than 1,500 intravenous (IV) infusion clinics have proliferated nationwide.” Ketamine industry revenues of $3.1 billion were reported in 2022, and projected to be $6.9 billion by 2030. More
The post Psychiatry’s Latest Insane Magic-Bullet Treatment for Depression: Why Ketamine? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruce E. Levine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intolerable Opinions in the Time of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348238</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/what-would-lilburne-do-intolerable-opinions-in-the-time-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So why do I reprise the moldering life of John Lilburne now, during the time of a genocide that his country and my own have armed, funded, and run interference for, when the words that describe the horrors we’ve witnessed are being criminalized, and it’s become dangerous to speak or write about what you see happening and how you feel about it and even more perilous to act, in even small ways, to try to stop it. More
The post Intolerable Opinions in the Time of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYT’s Apologist For Israel is No Longer a “Never Trumper”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348697</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/nyts-apologist-for-israel-is-no-longer-a-never-trumper/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the reasons I’m having difficulty “enjoying the holidays” is the editorial writing of Bret Stephens.  His columns defending Israel’s brutal military campaign that targets sanctuary areas and so-called safe zones in Gaza are typically chauvinistic and bellicose.  Stephens supports any Israeli military option that “advances Israel’s national interests on all fronts.”  His lecture at Harvard last year argued that “taking out most, but not all, of Hamas is not enough,” which seems to justify the genocidal campaign that Israel conducts.  Stephens has never mentioned that this campaign targets Gaza’s hospitals and health infrastructure.  As for those who protest Israeli actions, Stephens calls them “Iran’s useful idiots” and anti-semites. More
The post NYT’s Apologist For Israel is No Longer a “Never Trumper” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dying for a Kidney:  Can Anyone Stop The Burgeoning Black Market in Human Organs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348700</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/dying-for-a-kidney-can-anyone-stop-the-burgeoning-black-market-in-human-organs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T06:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organ trafficking survives, in part, because the demand from affluent consumers in the advanced capitalist West is so high and the legal supply of organs – primarily (about 80%) kidneys, but also lungs, livers and cornea – barely keeps pace.  Many people wait at least two years to qualify to receive an organ transplant legally and thousands die every year - about 25 daily, according to the World Health Organization – because no organ becomes available in time to save them.  More
The post Dying for a Kidney:  Can Anyone Stop The Burgeoning Black Market in Human Organs? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today, as in the Past, Germany Claims the Authority to Define who is a Jew]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348536</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/today-as-in-the-past-germany-claims-the-authority-to-define-who-is-a-jew/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T06:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reawakening ghosts from a dark past, Germany once again claims to have the authority to define who is a Jew. Those who say this are Jews living in Germany who find themselves the target of processes of delegitimization from the moment they criticize Israel. Between Israel and Jews, Germany chooses the Zionist state. For the  More
The post Today, as in the Past, Germany Claims the Authority to Define who is a Jew appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Dawson on Environmentalism from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348939</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/03/ashley-dawson-on-environmentalism-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T06:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Joshua Frank and Erik Wallenberg talk to Ashley Dawson about his new book, Environmentalism from Below: How Global People’s Movements Are Leading the Fight for Our Planet (Haymarket Books). https://media.blubrry.com/counterpunch_radio/content.blubrry.com/counterpunch_radio/DawsonInterview.mp3   Ashley is a Professor of English at the Graduate Center / City University of New York and the  More
The post Ashley Dawson on Environmentalism from Below appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch Radio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pech0rin in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42581844</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42581844"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T03:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the most childish thing I’ve read. And shows a lot about he doesn’t have any people relying on him or community to support. He takes one hike and throws away 60m. Doesn’t try to find anything interesting to do at Atlassian just calls his coworkers NPCs. This is zero-empathy Peter Pan syndrome at its worse.
Sad how he just goes adventure hopping to try and find meaning. The problem is no matter where you are you are also there. Time to look inward and not outward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pech0rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by akamaka in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580494</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580494"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T00:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I should work for Elon and Vivek at DOGE and help America get off its current crash to defaulting on its own debt
I’ve got an idea: take some good economics courses so that you learn how government spending actually works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>akamaka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by madrox in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580321"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T23:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't think you have to have Fuck You Money to get to this point. Most people eventually become disillusioned with work enough that they reevaluate what matters to them. Getting a very profitable exit is just one way to trigger that experience.
In my experience, a lot of people who get into this state start self-sabotaging hard as a way of rejecting what feels, ironically, like losing control. Sudden freedom can feel foreign and lot like your world got forcibly taken away from you. I'm not surprised the author is turning down opportunities and breaking off with his girlfriend. It's a way of taking back control.
When this happened to me, I pivoted hard from getting satisfaction out of what I built to getting satisfaction out of developing people. Now I take great pride out of the careers I've nurtured...a lot more than what I've built, in most ways. I've heard others express similar ideas in different ways, like "I now enjoy making other people rich."
No matter what, I encourage the author to use this time to build connections instead of destroying them (real connections...not work or SF acquaintances). Something I did not read in this essay is how he grew closer to anyone (in fact, I read the opposite). No path out of this valley involves traveling alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madrox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cj in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580224</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580224"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T23:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t think his problem is money.
I think his problem is his identity (founder of Loom) suddenly disappeared.
Now he needs to develop a new identity.
This is especially difficult for single founders without kids (in the sense that people with spouse/kids already derive much of their identity from those 2 things).
Selling a company isn’t all that different from going through a divorce (in the sense that your identity needs to be completely rebuilt from scratch)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: A Survey of Analytics Engineering Work at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4f1f53b4ab0f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/part-2-a-survey-of-analytics-engineering-work-at-netflix-4f1f53b4ab0f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second in a multi-part series sharing a breadth of Analytics Engineering work at Netflix, recently presented as part of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scop in "Advent of Code 2024 in pure SQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577887</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577887"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T19:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reacted to this title the way I react a new menu item at Taco Bell: a strange mixture of desire, shame, and admiration for human ingenuity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Tell HN: Impassable Cloudflare challenges are ruining my browsing experience"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577504</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577504"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The "unsubscribe" button in Indeed's job notification emails leads me to an impassable Cloudflare challenge.
That's a CAN-SPAM act violation.
FTC: "Tell recipients how to opt out of receiving future marketing email from you. Your message must include a clear and conspicuous explanation of how the recipient can opt out of getting marketing email from you in the future. Craft the notice in a way that’s easy for an ordinary person to recognize, read, and understand. Creative use of type size, color, and location can improve clarity. Give a return email address or another easy Internet-based way to allow people to communicate their choice to you. You may create a menu to allow a recipient to opt out of certain types of messages, but you must include the option to stop all marketing messages from you. Make sure your spam filter doesn’t block these opt-out requests."[1]
Experian was recently fined for making it hard to opt out of their marketing emails.
The actual regulation text:
§ 316.5 Prohibition on charging a fee or imposing other requirements on recipients who wish to opt out.
Neither a sender nor any person acting on behalf of a sender may require that any recipient pay any fee, provide any information other than the recipient's electronic mail address and opt-out preferences, or take any other steps except sending a reply electronic mail message or visiting a single Internet Web page, in order to:
(a) Use a return electronic mail address or other Internet-based mechanism, required by 15 U.S.C. 7704(a)(3), to submit a request not to receive future commercial electronic mail messages from a sender; or
(b) Have such a request honored as required by 15 U.S.C. 7704(a)(3)(B) and (a)(4).
That seems to cover it. File a CAN-SPAM act complaint (spam@uce.gov). Send a copy to the legal department of the sender.
[1] https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/resources/can-spam-act...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most visited DevOps and Developer Productivity blog posts in 2024]]></title>
        <id>84ca02a5b48a54f88f390089a009976e87922bea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/the-most-visited-devops-and-developer-productivity-blog-posts-in-2024-copy/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we kick off 2025, I wanted to take a moment to highlight the top posts from 2024. Without further ado, here are the top 10 DevOps and developer productivity blog posts of 2024. Announcing CDK Migrate A single command to migrate to the AWS CDK – This blog post announces the general availability of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re:Invent 2024 DevOps and Developer Productivity Playlist]]></title>
        <id>c0274ae9899bf1d6fa6f868d7f7e54714956d4a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/reinvent-2024-devops-and-developer-productivity-playlist/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dust has settled after another re:Invent. I once again had the privilege of organizing the DevOps and Developer Productivity (DOP) track along with Jessie VanderVeen, Krishna Dalal, Megan Sattler and countless others. For 2024, the DOP track included 60 sessions. If you weren’t able to attend, I have compiled a list of the on-demand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes with Stream Live, Cloudflare’s live streaming service]]></title>
        <id>chVlt8JAjFduvvOJ5c1yl</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/behind-the-scenes-with-stream-live-cloudflares-live-streaming-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Stream Live’s design, and how it leverages the distributed nature of Cloudflare’s network, rather than centralized locations as many other live services do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Boutette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cperciva in "One of my papers got declined today"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42569873</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42569873"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T22:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2005, my paper on breaking RSA by observing a single private-key operation from a different hyperthread sharing the same L1 cache -- literally the first publication of a cryptographic attack exploiting shared caches -- was rejected from the cryptology preprint archive on the grounds that "it was about CPU architecture, not cryptography".  Rejection from journals is like rejection from VCs -- it happens all the time and often not for any good reason.
(That paper has now been cited 971 times according to Google Scholar, despite never appearing in a journal.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cperciva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia, land of the most expensive passport in the world]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9041</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-passport-worlds-most-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From yesterday, 1 January 2025, the price of a ten-year Australian passport rose to four-hundred-and-twelve Australian dollars. That’s the cost of thirty-five pints of Victoria Bitter at the local pub. Happy New Year. As a comparison, the new price converts to a little over two-hundred-and-fifty dollars American, a little under two-hundred-and-fifty Euros, and about two-hundred […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dwaltrip in "One of my papers got declined today"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42568746</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42568746"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T19:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hilarious irony:
> With hindsight, some of my past rejections have become amusing.  With a coauthor, I once almost solved a conjecture, establishing the result with an "epsilon loss" in a key parameter.  We submitted to a highly reputable journal, but it was rejected on the grounds that it did not resolve the full conjecture.  So we submitted elsewhere, and the paper was accepted.
> The following year, we managed to finally prove the full conjecture without the epsilon loss, and decided to try submitting to the highly reputable journal again.  This time, the paper was rejected for only being an epsilon improvement over the previous literature!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dwaltrip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Storing digital data for one hundred years: how is this possible?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9038</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/storing-digital-data-one-hundred-years/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T19:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maxwell Neely-Cohen, writing for Harvard Law School’s Library Innovation Lab: If you, right now, had the goal of digitally storing something for 100 years, how should you even begin to think about making that happen? How should the bits in your stewardship be stored with such a target in mind? How do our methods and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voting open for the 2024 Triple J Hottest 100 music poll]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9035</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/voting-open-2024-triple-j-hottest-100-music-poll/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T19:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The annual Hottest 100 countdown is part and parcel of the Australian music scene. Hosted by Australian indie radio station Triple J, since 1978, the poll gives listeners the chance to vote for their favourite music of the previous year. The countdown itself takes place on Saturday 25 January 2025. I don’t always listen in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gravastars and black holes, a weird cosmic double act]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9030</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/gravastars-black-holes-weird-cosmic-double-act/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T18:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of gravastars (or gravitational vacuum stars) is a fascinating alternative to the idea of black holes, although if their presence were ever proved, they would not rule out the existence of black holes. Proposed by Pawel O. Mazur and Emil Mottola some twenty years ago, these objects are consistent with Albert Einstein’s general […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by charlesabarnes in "DOOM CAPTCHA"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42566631</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42566631"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T15:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried to do it the intended way, but found it too difficult. I was able to cheese it by staying in the starting area and killing the enemies that spawned to the right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>charlesabarnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Donald in "Happy New Year 2025"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42563992</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42563992"/>
        <updated>2025-01-01T04:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[45^2 = 2025
Happy perfect square year, everyone. The previous one was 1936 and the next one will be 2116.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donald</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>