<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-18T12:37:22.465Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-18T12:37:22.465Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271701</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T10:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our far-seeing daily links: animal music, anti-sex bed, Powell's Covid, China real estate rescue, Europe youth hearts far right, Israel poor prospects, pier promo, decoding Kharkiv, China-Russia monster meeting, Garland sanction progresses. Trump wants Biden drug test, Assange, union vote wins and losses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Jill Stein & Michael Hudson: Fighting Russia & China to Last American: Destroying US From Within]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271832</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/dr-jill-stein-michael-hudson-fighting-russia-china-to-last-american-destroying-us-from-within.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T10:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The high cost and risks of the Biden Administration commitment to pursue forever wars with Russia and China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Affordable Housing Policy Works for Wall Street and Rich Developers, Not Renters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271834</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/us-affordable-housing-policy-works-for-wall-street-and-rich-developers-not-renters.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T10:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current policy doesn’t provide affordable housing very well  but does a good job of lining the pockets of real estate interests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by smt88 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396533"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T04:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look at Sam Altman's career and tweets. He's a clown at best, and at worst he's a manipulative crook who only cares about his own enrichment and uses pro-social ideas to give himself a veneer of trustworthiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smt88</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mwigdahl in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396395</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396395"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T04:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best approach to circumventing the nondisclosure agreement is for the affected employees to get together, write out everything they want to say about OpenAI, train an LLM on that text, and then release it.
Based on these companies' arguments that copyrighted material is not actually reproduced by these models, and that any seemingly-infringing use is the responsibility of the user of the model rather than those who produced it, anyone could freely generate an infinite number of high-truthiness OpenAI anecdotes, freshly laundered by the inference engine, that couldn't be used against the original authors without OpenAI invalidating their own legal stance with respect to their own models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mwigdahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwaway598 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396209</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396209"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T03:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That OpenAI are institutionally unethical. That such a young company can be become rotten so quickly can only be due to leadership instruction or leadership failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway598</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Buttons840 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395918</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395918"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So part of their compensation for working is equity, and when they leave thay have to sign an additional agreement in order to keep their previously earned compensation? How is this legal? Mine as well tell them they have to give all their money back too.
What's the consideration for this contract?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Buttons840</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by modeless in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395842"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of the brouhaha about OpenAI is silly, I think. But this is gross. Forcing employees to sign a perpetual non-disparagement agreement under threat of clawing back the large majority of their already earned compensation should not be legal. Honestly it probably isn't, but it'll take someone brave enough to sue to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>modeless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jay-barronville in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395702</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395702"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It probably would be better to switch the link from the X post to the Vox article [0].
From the article:
“““
It turns out there’s a very clear reason for [why no one who had once worked at OpenAI was talking]. I have seen the extremely restrictive off-boarding agreement that contains nondisclosure and non-disparagement provisions former OpenAI employees are subject to. It forbids them, for the rest of their lives, from criticizing their former employer. Even acknowledging that the NDA exists is a violation of it.
If a departing employee declines to sign the document, or if they violate it, they can lose all vested equity they earned during their time at the company, which is likely worth millions of dollars. One former employee, Daniel Kokotajlo, who posted that he quit OpenAI “due to losing confidence that it would behave responsibly around the time of AGI,” has confirmed publicly that he had to surrender what would have likely turned out to be a huge sum of money in order to quit without signing the document.
”””
[0]: https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2024/5/17/24158478/openai...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jay-barronville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fragmede in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395483</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395483"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T00:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to find a lawyer. I'm not one but  there's an intersection with California SB 331, also known as “The Silenced No More Act”. while it is focused more on sexual harrasment, it's not limited to that, and these contracts may run afoul of that.
https://silencednomore.org/the-silenced-no-more-act]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fragmede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by phire in "Ubershaders: A Ridiculous Solution to an Impossible Problem (2017)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394442</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394442"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T21:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has it really been 9 years since I started working on Ubershaders?
I'm a little surprised no better solution has come along. Vulkan didn't even exist back then (and DirectX 12 had only just released) but instead of making things better, it digs it's feet even deeper into the assumption that all shaders will be known ahead of time (resulting in long "shader recompilation" dialogs on startup on many games).
I've been tempted to build my own fast shader compiler into Dolphin for many common GPU architectures. Hell, it wouldn't even be a proper compiler, more of a templated emitter as all shaders fit a pattern. Register allocation and scheduling could all be pre-calculated.
But that would be even more insane than ubershaders, as it would be one backend per gpu arch. And some drivers (like Nvidia) don't provide a way to inject pre-compiled shader binaries.
On the positive side, ubershaders do solve the problem, and modern GPU drivers do a much better job at accepting ubershaders than they did 9 years ago. Though that's primarily because (as far as I'm aware) examples of Dolphin's ubershader have made their way into every single shader compiler test suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To my Sunflower]]></title>
        <id>https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/</id>
        <link href="https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:26:07.405Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little bird came to see me,
What’s you name? - I asked.
And he chirped the following words:
Leave a comment or Stay in touch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CorrectingYou in "Bend: a high-level language that runs on GPUs (via HVM2)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40393253</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40393253"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OP comes around with some of the coolest things posted in HN recently, and all he gets is extensive criticism, when it is clear that this is an early version :/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CorrectingYou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zero_k in "Computer scientists invent an efficient new way to count"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40392831</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40392831"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T18:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was involved with implementing the DNF volume counting version of this with the authors. You can see my blog post of it here:
https://www.msoos.org/2023/09/pepin-our-probabilistic-approx...
And the code here: https://github.com/meelgroup/pepin
Often, 30% of the time is spent in IO of reading the file, that's how incredibly fast this algorithm is. Crazy stuff.
BTW, Knuth contributed to the algo, Knuths' notes: https://cs.stanford.edu/~knuth/papers/cvm-note.pdf
He actually took time off (a whole month) from TAOCP to do this. Also, he is exactly as crazy good as you'd imagine. Just mind-blowing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zero_k</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271792</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics; NC pulls the anti-mask bill for revisions;Trump lawyer trips up Cohen, jeopardizing conviction; another CDC atrocity; Noonan  interviews a Wildwood, NY attendee. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[don't skip the openings]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:35:12.065Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the absolute worst thing someone can tell me about their anime viewing preferences has nothing to do with the kind of show they watch but how they watch it.
image from director nakayama ryū's chainsaw man (2022).
skipping openings just because you're on a binge can so easily rob you of what i'd argue are the best narrative and collective highs a series can offer.1
from a purely functional standpoint, they give us time to breathe and process what exactly we're watching. take, for example, the three versions of shippuden's penultimate opening— blood circulator. each variant denotes which point of the story you're at, and primes you for what's to come. (if you pay attention, you'll notice they lead into each other seamlessly! so neat.)
sometimes it's instinctual and more about building antici…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[traversing across a rainbow bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:27:15.392Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we lost our second dog today.
sherlock, my aunt’s darling boy, passed at 4:20 in the morning. at 3am, she knocked on my door saying the fateful words—i think sherlock’s dying. it was like my whole world came to a stop.
he died in her arms.
10 and a half beautiful years of his company. our kind, kind sherlock who sometimes snapped at us when we kissed him too much. our darling, darling boy who was great at finding toys we’d hide from him; who liked to eat the cheese crackers my grandma fed him when no one was looking.
he had chronic heart failure. we were counting down the months, really, but nothing could’ve ever prepared me for that 3am knock, his fading heartbeat, and his little eyes that wouldn’t close.
ten years ago today, my aunt’s dog quli—a botched attempt of naming him 去来, a dog wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DaiPlusPlus in "Non-Euclidean Doom: what happens to a game when pi is not 3.14159 (2022) [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40390195</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40390195"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T14:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens is the graphics and movement get glitchy and eventually unplayable - I wouldn’t call this “non-Euclidean Doom” - just “consequences of messing with the constants of the universe” - whereas I’d expect an actual non-Euclidean Doom to be like this: https://youtu.be/kEB11PQ9Eo8?si=0HNlpGFBii2AIK1n]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DaiPlusPlus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Privacy in the Surveillance State and Fragmenting Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271785</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/defending-privacy-in-the-surveillance-state-and-fragmenting-internet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments and private entities are eroding privacy on the internet. Is it possible to safeguard both openness and security in cyberspace?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[even the dustiest of streets has a place in memory]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:09:35.956Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is our last day at the grandparents’ house. Tomorrow we take a taxi to the city we flew into and we’ll spend the day and night there before departing in the morning.
Mom is in her parents’ bedroom with Grandma and Grandpa. She’s sharing photos of us to Grandma and showing her how to download them to her tablet. I laugh as Mom gets frustrated with Grandma’s technological ineptitude. It’s her turn to teach technology to a Boomer.
Earlier I mustered up the courage to wander a little further from home than normal. I walked all the way to the train station and park in the center of town. I’m glad I did, because I saw a lot of things I hadn’t before.
As the sun dips below the horizon vendors set up tables in front of the supermarket. They sell a wide assortment of wares. Cages with corgis,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271760</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bubbly daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EU Commission Plans to Strip Funding From Public Prosecutors Investigating Ursula von der Leyen’s Pfizergate Scandal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271670</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/eu-commission-strips-funding-from-european-public-prosecutors-investigating-commission-president-ursula-von-der-leyen-over-pfizergate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Surely just a coincidence!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Zerzan - He Means it — Do you?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Zerzan
Title: He Means it — Do you?
Date: 2002
Source: Retrieved on May 2024 from archive.org

 Today opposition is anarchist or it is non-existent. This is the barest minimum coherence in the struggle against an engulfing totality. 
 And while ten years ago the milieu generally called anti-authoritarian was largely syndicalist, those leftist residues are fading out altogether. Very few now find a vista of work and production at all liberatory. 
 As the smell of this false and rotting order rises to the heavens, registering an unprecedented toll on all living beings, faith in the whole modern world evaporates. Industrialism and its ensemble looks like it has been a very bad idea, sort of a wrong turn begun still earlier. Civilization itself, with its logic of domestication and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[abducting prosperina]]></title>
        <id>https://passerine.bearblog.dev/abducting-prosperina/</id>
        <link href="https://passerine.bearblog.dev/abducting-prosperina/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:06:38.931Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[warning: contains spoilers for gennarose nethercott's thislefoot & a lot of meandering!
each of my tour guides here have said the same thing. "in rome, a hundred years is nothing."1 and it rings true. when i ran my hands along the remaining stone walls of constantine's basilica (circa 300s) in the vatican grotto, i felt very strange. i've never dreamed of lasting.
honestly, the only thing i truly wanted to do here in rome was visit the borghese gallery. because a portion of their collection was at the corsini due to renovations. i had to choose between the two. for me, the answer was clear as day. raphael’s lady with unicorn would have to wait. bernini’s sculptures were waiting for me. i consider myself unlucky for the timing, but i could never regret my choice.
at 11-years-old i learned t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did the US Spend $320 Million on a Rube Goldberg Pier For Gaza?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271755</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/why-did-the-us-spend-320-million-on-a-rube-goldberg-pier-for-gaza.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T09:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous Gaza humanitarian aid pier is a construction and logistical nightmare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Long Goodbye? Mitch McConnell and Big Money Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271738</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/the-long-goodbye-mitch-mcconnell-and-big-money-politics.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a political system whose primary currency is not the vote but the dollar, McConnell’s role as leader has been well-earned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by earthnail in "Deutsche Bahn introduces "MetaWindow""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387373</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387373"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love this. I read so much criticism here, but noise pollution is a main issue when it comes to railroads in residential zones.
Yes, punctuality is an issue with Deutsche Bahn. No, this doesn’t fix that instantly. But as an organisation you can work on two things at the same time.
This invention is spectacular. I wish more people would work on noise pollution. It makes a huge difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>earthnail</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pixelmonkey in "Computer scientists invent an efficient new way to count"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387154</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387154"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This algorithm seems to resemble HyperLogLog (and all its variants), which is also cited in the research paper. Using the same insight of the estimation value of tracking whether we've hit a "run" of heads or tails, but flipping the idea on its head (heh), it leads to the simpler algorithm described, which is about discarding memorized values on the basis of runs of heads/tails.
This also works especially well (that is, efficiently) in the streaming case, allowing you to keep something resembling a "counter" for the distinct elements, albeit with a error rate.
The benefit of HyperLogLog is that it behaves similarly to a hash set in some respects -- you can add items, count distinct them, and, importantly, merge two HLLs together (union), all the while keeping memory fixed to mere kilobytes even for billion-item sets. In distributed data stores, this is the trick behind Elasticsearch/OpenSearch cardinality agg, as well as behind Redis/Redict with its PFADD/PFMERGE/PFCOUNT.
I am not exactly sure how this CVM algorithm compares to HLL, but they got Knuth to review it, and they claim an undergrad can implement it easily, so it must be pretty good!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pixelmonkey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re: the fear of audience expectations, by gabby]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:07:27.208Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This open letter is inspired by a post I read yesterday by Gabby of woolgathering fame.)
Dear Gabby,
It’s not just you: getting over the fear of expectations is hard. I still struggle with it, after 300 something posts. I have a feeling I’ll never get completely over it, but here’s what’s helped me so far.
Posting a lot helps. I’ve posted so much nonsense on this blog that these days there’s not much I can do that will be worse than something I’ve written before. Somehow, I still have regular readers. Realizing that there are people out there still interested in what I have to say after all the good and not so good is a great comfort. From what you write, you seem to have discovered as much.
Another perk of having a large body of work is that each new piece you create becomes a smaller and smaller part of your entire oeuvre. When you’re first starting out, it feels like each creation you put out defines you. After all, if you only have one post, it’s the only thing people can judge you on. If you have a hundred, a wayward post is a drop in the bucket.
That said, wouldn’t you still want to see the creations your friends or favorite creators aren’t proud of? Or see their art even if it doesn’t quite fit the niche they’ve carved out for themselves? Everybody half-asses things in their own unique way. There’s a beauty in doing things imperfectly, too.
All that is to say, keep up what you’re doing. Creative inertia is a very real thing. You’re doing the right thing by posting, even if you feel like you’re just posting to break the streak of inactivity. Writing in any form begets more writing.
Anyway, welcome back to Bear! It’s good to have you back.
Yours,
misu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Jews be Nazis?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322714</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/can-jews-be-nazis/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many people, the question is inflammatory. The crimes of the German Nazis were of such magnitude that comparison with any other historical violence is invidious. The genocide of the Jews was deliberate and methodical and intended to eliminate every last one. The goal was the same with the Romani and Sinti people. By comparison, the Israelis – currently accused of genocide -- are rank amateurs. They have so far killed some 35,000 Palestinians in Gaza out of a population of 2.3 million. More
The post Can Jews be Nazis? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the Missiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322850</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/follow-the-missiles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, the Biden administration has approved more than 100 Foreign Military Sales arms transfers to Israel. Two of the shipments used an emergency authority to circumvent Congressional review. The surge of weapons transfers to Israel began in early October and so much material was being shipped that the Pentagon had a difficult time finding enough cargo aircraft to deliver them. More
The post Follow the Missiles appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Clearly About the Protesters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322963</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/thinking-clearly-about-the-protesters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Do you think ‘sit-ins’ at lunch counters, ‘Freedom Buses’ and other demonstrations by Negroes will hurt or help the Negro's chances of being integrated in the South?” This question was posed by Gallup, a leading polling organization, back in 1961, during the heyday of the Civil Rights Movement. A majority of Americans at the time, 57%, believed that the sit-ins would “hurt” the movement. They were wrong. Today, we credit the Civil Rights Movement with ending racial segregation in the United States, but we cannot disconnect its success from its tactics. Martin Luther King Jr. was no advocate of passive resistance, but a firm believer in “militant nonviolence”– a consistent torrent of protests in the form of boycotts, mass marches, sit-ins, and strikes. These are similar tactics to those that students across the world are using to spread awareness of the over 30,000 Palestinians killed in Gaza and to push their universities to dissociate from the Israeli State. More
The post Thinking Clearly About the Protesters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raihan Alam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permafrost Showdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322855</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/permafrost-showdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the Arctic to Antarctica the planet is sagging, dripping, slouching, changing the face of 10,000 years of nature coexisting with humanity side-by-side until only recently as it transforms into an adversarial relationship. Permafrost ranks alongside the Arctic, Antarctica, Greenland, The Great Barrier Reef, and the world’s three largest rainforests as the most important determinates of this changing future. Within permafrost’s confines exist thousands of years of latent ingredients that have the potential to set the world on fire. Its impact could be transcendent. More
The post Permafrost Showdown appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friedman, Biden and US Weapons Sales to Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322596</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/friedman-biden-and-us-weapons-sales-to-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a long oped on Sunday titled “Biden’s Error in Pausing Military Aid,” Thomas Friedman buys into Israeli propaganda that describes Iran as an “existential threat,” and harshly denigrates President Joe Biden for announcing a pause in U.S. weapons sales to Israel. Friedman is critical of Biden for announcing the pause in the transfer of 3,500 bombs to Israel in an “off-the-cuff-exchange with CNN’s Erin Burnett during a campaign stop in Wisconsin. More
The post Friedman, Biden and US Weapons Sales to Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Humble Request]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322868</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-humble-request/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please, if you can, chip in this Spring Fund Drive, we have almost reached our goal.
The post A Humble Request appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One’s Neutral Come Eurovision Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323045</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/no-ones-neutral-come-eurovision-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Eurovision Song Contest cannot be neutral. There is just one winner. That winner is chosen by combining the popular cellphone votes of millions of viewers with the tallies of the five-member juries in each country. There is just one contestant—whether a soloist or an entire band—from each nation that makes it into the finals.  More
The post No One’s Neutral Come Eurovision Time appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brutal Punishment: The Sentencing of David McBride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322838</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-brutal-punishment-the-sentencing-of-david-mcbride/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, it’s best not to leave the issue of justice to the judges.  They do what they must: consult the statutes, test the rivers of power, and hope that their ruling will not be subject to appeal.  David McBride, the man who revealed that Australia’s special forces in Afghanistan had dimmed and muddied before exhaustion,  More
The post A Brutal Punishment: The Sentencing of David McBride appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel as a Jewish Nation-State and Antisemitism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322908</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/israel-as-a-jewish-nation-state-and-antisemitism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Judaism cannot be separated from Israel. Zionism is, simply put, the manifestation of that belief,” stated a recent message from Jewish students at Columbia University. Israel’s politics are closely intertwined with its religious beliefs. Since 2018, Israel legally considers itself a Jewish nation-state with no separation between religion and politics. That explains why Israelis consider  More
The post Israel as a Jewish Nation-State and Antisemitism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Rube! Why No Room for Others at the Biden/Trump Debate Circus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322917</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/hey-rube-why-no-room-for-others-at-the-biden-trump-debate-circus/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. participate in either of the two presidential election debates thus far announced by the Joe Biden and Donald Trump campaigns? How about independents Cornel West and Afroman, Green party candidate Jill Stein, Constitution Party candidate Randall Terry, and whoever receives the Libertarian Party’s nomination over Memorial Day weekend? The answer,  More
The post Hey, Rube! Why No Room for Others at the Biden/Trump Debate Circus? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wilderness Act at 60: A Brief Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322941</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/the-wilderness-act-at-60-a-brief-overview/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 3, 1964, humanity’s unrelenting quest to tame, civilize, industrialize, and obliterate wild nature crashed into the Wilderness Act, signed into law by President Johnson on that momentous day. This visionary legislation—written primarily by the late Howard Zahniser of the Wilderness Society—created a federal policy to secure for the American people “an enduring resource  More
The post The Wilderness Act at 60: A Brief Overview appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howie Wolke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Features of Ancient Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322902</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/seven-features-of-ancient-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple differences between antiquity’s economic practices and those of the modern world, and these should be borne in mind when considering the changing context for enterprise through the centuries. Whereas modern business largely operates on credit, in archaic and classical times handicraft workshops were located on basically self-sufficient landed estates, including those of  More
The post Seven Features of Ancient Enterprise appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1,3-Dichloropropene: The Dangerous, Sweet-Smelling Pesticide You’ve Never Heard Of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322899</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/13-dichloropropene-the-dangerous-sweet-smelling-pesticide-youve-never-heard-of/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California regulators were stunned by their air monitor results in April 1990. Concentrations of a cancer-causing pesticide at schools in Merced County were so high that regulators immediately stopped any use of that pesticide in California. It’s a chemical with an unwieldy name, 1,3-dichloropropene, that you may have never heard about. But there are many reasons why you should be  More
The post 1,3-Dichloropropene: The Dangerous, Sweet-Smelling Pesticide You’ve Never Heard Of appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck on Stupid, Biden and the Democrats Face Disaster in November]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322914</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/stuck-on-stupid-biden-and-the-democrats-face-disaster-in-november/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Let them eat cake,” Marie Antoinette once famously said, disdaining the immiseration of peasants in pre-revolutionary France.  Joe Biden didn’t use those exact words last week during his interview with CNN’s Erin Burnett, but his tone-deafness about the suffering of millions of Americans grappling with high food and gas prices and unaffordable rents was palpable. Burnett  More
The post Stuck on Stupid, Biden and the Democrats Face Disaster in November appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Lecter and Mr. Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322831</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/dr-lecter-and-mr-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Silence of the Lambs. Has anyone ever seen The Silence of the Lambs? The late, great Hannibal Lecter is a wonderful man. He oftentimes would have a friend for dinner. Remember the last scene? “Excuse me. I’m about to have a friend for dinner,” as this poor doctor walked by. “I’m about to have a  More
The post Dr. Lecter and Mr. Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Privacy in the Surveillance State and Fragmenting Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322926</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/defending-privacy-in-the-surveillance-state-and-fragmenting-internet/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the reapproval of the Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA) on April 20, 2024, Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer proudly declared that “bipartisanship has prevailed here in the Senate.” Despite the increasing rarity of bipartisanship in recent years, support for government surveillance continues to unite large majorities across party lines. Established in 1978, FISA allows government surveillance  More
The post Defending Privacy in the Surveillance State and Fragmenting Internet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Whistleblower’s Return to the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322906</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-whistleblowers-return-to-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a palpable sense of nerves approaching the day I was to travel to Perugia for the International Journalism Festival. I was invited by Kathleen McClellan and Jesselyn Radack of WHISPeR who were invited to present on the impact of leak prosecutions on the free press. I was certainly honored to be asked, but those emotions of  More
The post A Whistleblower’s Return to the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Sterling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem With Electric Vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322537</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/the-problem-with-electric-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last quarter century, those of us hoping we could slow global warming were anxious to see a quick conversion to electric vehicles (EVs). If we could get most people using electric vehicles, and have the energy coming from clean sources, we could radically reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The problem was that EVs were  More
The post The Problem With Electric Vehicles appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ideological Coup: How Disciples of Kahane Became the New Face of Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322957</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/the-ideological-coup-how-disciples-of-kahane-became-the-new-face-of-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout history, fringe religious Zionist parties have had limited success in achieving the kind of electoral victories that would allow them an actual share in the country’s political decision-making. The impressive number of 17 seats won by Israel’s extremist religious party, Shas, in the 1999 elections, was a watershed moment in the history of these  More
The post The Ideological Coup: How Disciples of Kahane Became the New Face of Israel   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Reflections on the Campus Protests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322925</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/some-reflections-on-the-campus-protests/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing pro-Palestinian protests at American universities are more than just youthful expressions of speech freedom. Rather they exemplify the informed views of students repulsed by the genocide in Gaza, which they see every day on television and in the social media.  They are motivated by a desire to end the continuing complicity of their  More
The post Some Reflections on the Campus Protests appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shooting Alone: America’s Social Priorities Shaped by Decades of War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322918</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/shooting-alone-americas-social-priorities-shaped-by-decades-of-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An acquaintance who hails from the same New Jersey town as I do spends his free weekends crawling through the woods on his stomach as part of a firearms training course, green camouflage paint on his face and a revolver in his hand. He considers this both a way to have fun in his free  More
The post Shooting Alone: America’s Social Priorities Shaped by Decades of War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Mazzarino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Rebellion Against Law and Civilization: Genocide and Its Accomplices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322541</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-rebellion-against-law-and-civilization-genocide-and-its-accomplices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Civilization is a process that progressively codifies the rules and regulations necessary for living together in peace, the process that continually engenders associations and commissions, mechanisms for monitoring and implementation of the norms. The United Nations Charter is the best rules-based order we have, a kind of world constitution that all peoples should recognize and  More
The post A Rebellion Against Law and Civilization: Genocide and Its Accomplices appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Campuses and Around the World, a Revolution of Empathy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322533</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/on-the-campuses-and-around-the-world-a-revolution-of-empathy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of so much bad news, when so many trends seem to be rolling down the wrong track, it can be hard for people who care about the future to keep our heads above water. We’re drowning in it. In the midst of all this, a light shines through, a moral awakening of  More
The post On the Campuses and Around the World, a Revolution of Empathy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of Editors: A Philosophical Argument]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323113</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/in-praise-of-editors-a-philosophical-argument/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writers need editors. We send in our manuscript and the editor corrects typos, does fact checks and urges stylistic improvements. There has been much discussion recently of the art world system. To understand contemporary art, you need to consider not only artists, but also art writers (who theorize it), curators (who display it), dealers (who  More
The post In Praise of Editors: A Philosophical Argument appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Masterpiece of Sycophancy: Kishida Goes to Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323008</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-masterpiece-of-sycophancy-kishida-goes-to-washington/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Prime Minister Kishida Fumio’s April 10 speech to the US Congress, following the American custom, began with a joke. The speaker introduced him, the audience gave him a friendly applause, and he said, “Thank you. I never get such nice applause from the Japanese Diet.” The joke was a success: it got a big  More
The post A Masterpiece of Sycophancy: Kishida Goes to Washington appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Lummis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Israel Need to Talk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322555</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/iran-and-israel-need-to-talk/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now been about four weeks since Iranian missiles filled Israeli skies, as humanity held its breath for nuclear war and possible extinction. If that strikes you as hyperbole, consider this: Had Israel suffered great damage, the war could have gone nuclear, and don’t think for a minute that Russia and China would allow their  More
The post Iran and Israel Need to Talk appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road to a Stateless Axis of Resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322865</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/the-road-to-a-stateless-axis-of-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Modernity is one of the most delicate and vital issues confronting us, the people of non-European countries and Islamic Societies. A more important issue is the relationship between an imposed modernization and genuine civilization. We must discover if modernity as is claimed is a synonym for being civilized, or if it is an altogether different  More
The post The Road to a Stateless Axis of Resistance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicky Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Oil and Civilization Don’t Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322862</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/big-oil-and-civilization-dont-mix/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue On May 10, 2024, my friend Jay Jones, emeritus professor of biology at La Verne University, invited me to see a documentary he was presenting to his students and colleagues. The documentary, The Oil Machine, was done in 2022 by BBC. It is one of the best films I have watched on the origins  More
The post Big Oil and Civilization Don’t Mix appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Immigration Policy: The More It Changes, the More It Doesn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322544</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/us-immigration-policy-the-more-it-changes-the-more-it-doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Silky Shah, the author of a new book on how many immigrants to the United States are treated by the US government, has worked with the group Detention Watch Network (DWN) for over twenty years.  During that time, the United States has seen five men occupy the White House.  Upon reading Shah’s book, titled Unbuild  More
The post US Immigration Policy: The More It Changes, the More It Doesn’t appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reply to a Zionist Troll]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322843</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/reply-to-a-zionist-troll/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is a little piece of hate mail dropped like a psychological dumb bomb into my inbox the other day… Dr. Block — When did you start becoming a self-hating Jew like Larry David, Joy Behar and decades before, Woody Allen? Your CounterPunch commentary reflects self-denial of facts, mostly one most liberal/progressives love to  More
The post Reply to a Zionist Troll appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by constantcrying in "Deutsche Bahn introduces "MetaWindow""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40386533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40386533"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T04:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is exactly nothing about defacing public infrastructure which elicits the tiniest spark of "admiration" or "interest" in me.
If you want to live out your "artistic ambitions" do it somewhere away from public property.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>constantcrying</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 20after4 in "The Downfall of DeviantArt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385401</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385401"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked at deviantArt from 2009 to 2013. It was my dream job. At the time deviantArt made money a few ways.
In no particular order, because I don't know which were profitable or which represented a larger portion of revenue:
- Subscriptions (users could pay for a few extra features and to disable ads on the site)
- DeviantArt branded merch.
- Prints and products with users' art printed on them
- Sponsored Contests. These promoted movies or other media properties, or software of interest to artists. Often the prizes included Wacom tablets and Adobe Photoshop licenses.
During my time there a significant problem we were dealing with was due to deviantArt's stance on adult content. Anything was allowed as long as it wasn't outright pornography.  In practice that meant that nudes were allowed but sexual acts were not. This had consequences for deviantArt's revenue. It meant that we could not run ads from the "reputable" ad networks and were forced to deal with seedier outfits that often (e.g. constantly) included malware in the display ads, exposing users to all sorts of nasty stuff. One of my projects was to detect and/or prevent the malware ads which proved challenging and at least given the amount of resources devoted to it, it was not very fruitful.
It really is sad for me to see what deviantArt has devolved into. Once the original founders sold out a few years ago I really didn't hold out much hope for the site's future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>20after4</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by derefr in "A forged Apple employee badge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385318</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385318"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> And that typed text is way, way cleaner than any typewriter I’ve seen.
Pedantic point: electric typewriters (which have existed since the 1960s) do type in a way that looks exactly like this.
(In fact, note that the text on the real employee ID card, shown later in the article, doesn't look any less clean! It's just set in a different, narrower font.)
The smudginess of mechanical typewriters comes from 1. them striking (and especially, releasing) at the same speed you're depressing the key, and 2. having many of the keys necessarily approach the ribbon from an angle.
The keys being swung weakly by your fingers, also has the additional implication that the ink ribbons used in mechanical typewriters have to be soft and squishy (so: made of cloth), and use thin inks. These properties ensure a transfer from even a low-velocity impact. But the trade-off is that cloth ink ribbons transfer only a rough outline of what's struck; and thin inks are high-bleed inks.
An electric typewriter, playing out a pre-buffered line with a crisp, predictable report, using linear actuators and a rotating-ball type-head to bang a tape ribbon loaded with high-viscosity ink onto the page, can create text indistinguishable from books/newspapers of the same period, or from modern laser-printer reproductions of the same font faces. They're essentially character-at-a-time letterpresses!
(Also, ignoring electric typewriters for a sec: inks bleed more on thin, cheap paper. But this is [a forgery of] an employee ID card — where, for durability, a nice heavyweight paper or cardstock would have been used. You're always going to get a better-looking result inking such paper.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>derefr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zmmmmm in "Slack AI Training with Customer Data"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40384975</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40384975"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T00:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> For any model that will be used broadly across all of our customers, we do not build or train these models in such a way that they could learn, memorise, or be able to reproduce some part of Customer Data
This feels so full of subtle qualifiers and weasel words that it generates far more distrust than trust.
It only refers to models used "broadly across all" customers - so if it's (a) not used "broadly" or (b) only used for some subset of customers, the whole statement doesn't apply. Which actually sounds really bad because the logical implication is that data CAN leak outside those circumstances.
They need to reword this. Whoever wrote it is a liability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zmmmmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lily Lynch: &ldquo;Crosshairs&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shooting of Robert Fico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Kubernetes workload isolation and security using Kata Containers]]></title>
        <id>f2c6d73c0a99a5e7cc62d68bc9a22528e5bead29</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/enhancing-kubernetes-workload-isolation-and-security-using-kata-containers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have become the dominant method for deploying and managing applications in recent years. Their widespread adoption is attributed to numerous advantages, such as isolation, efficient hardware use, scalability, and portability. In situations where resource isolation is critical for system security, many users are forced to rely on virtual machines (VMs) to mitigate the impact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mirash Gjolaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye: Revolutionizing HD map creation for autonomous vehicles with Spark on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>ef56de61f8631e9846e056ddafcc46ba422f73dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/mobileye-revolutionizing-hd-map-creation-for-autonomous-vehicles-with-spark-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye (Nasdaq: MBLY), a global leader in advanced driver-assistance systems (ADAS), is at the forefront of the autonomous driving revolution. Founded in 1999, they have pioneered groundbreaking technologies such as REM™ crowdsourced mapping, True-Redundancy™ sensing, and Responsibility-Sensitive Safety (RSS). These innovations are paving the way for a future filled with self-driving vehicles and advanced mobility […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentzi Lifshitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSS is really simple, why do so many find it complicated?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7606</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/rss-really-simple-why-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris, writing at uncountable thoughts: RSS is a pervasive, but little known, web technology that allows you aggregate all your content into one place for easy reading. There are very few websites without an RSS feed, although many don’t advertise the link (or, even realise they have it). When you put an RSS feed link […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "The Downfall of DeviantArt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40382759</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40382759"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T20:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So much of the DeviantArt story reads like Tumblr. Two platforms appealing to amateur and small artists grow to great relevance among a patchwork of subcultures. Then, they start trying to turn a profit and end up alienating the entire userbase that carried them to that point. DeviantArt is much further down that road than Tumblr is, though. It's sad to see. Both platforms were key to the WWW of my childhood.
I wish the artists well in their AI copyright legal pursuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost opportunities?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/16/lost-opportunities/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T19:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford A pile of bricks is not a house.  A group of individuals is not an economy. A lot has to happen between the one and the other.  Which is why writing theories about economies as if it were simply an accumulation of individuals and their associated capital base misses the mark.  Nor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271706</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics, Cohen's testimony in the Bragg trial plus theories of the case, Biden and Trump debate, the NC legislature bails for the weekend without passing the anti-masking bill, the Impressionists and the Paris Commune. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[158. Compounding heartbreaks and unsent love letters]]></title>
        <id>https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/</id>
        <link href="https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:23:05.119Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think one of the biggest reasons why I was utterly pissed off at the dude for ditching me was all of that  built-up anticipation, only to be disappointed at the very end. I had this really big expectation, but I think I really shouldn't count on people too much. In my mind, I hadn't had a little trip in a while, and having that cool rendezvous experience with a cute guy? I was so keen.
I can't believe that I made plans with someone, looked forward to our weekend getaway, only to find out he's changed his plans without a word and flew off somewhere instead. It completely left me feeling confused and downright pissed off. I didn't think I deserved to be left hanging like that and to not have an in-person apology. I haven't even seen him ever since we went to the museum together 1 2.

I sai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wrs in "I don't want to spend my one precious life dealing with Google's AI search"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40380743</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40380743"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is kinda crazy considering the tremendous effort Google has gone to over the decades to shave milliseconds off their response time. They invented a whole TCP replacement to reduce page latency, and now this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wrs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Stable Diffusion ComfyUI on AWS elastically and efficiently]]></title>
        <id>dcd98043e309fb462fb16c1c99293fceecad41fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/deploy-stable-diffusion-comfyui-on-aws-elastically-and-efficiently/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction ComfyUI is an open-source node-based workflow solution for Stable Diffusion. It offers the following advantages: Significant performance optimization for SDXL model inference High customizability, allowing users granular control Portable workflows that can be shared easily Developer-friendly Due to these advantages, ComfyUI is increasingly being used by artistic creators. In this post, we will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TheAmazingRace in "Sprint, T-Mobile Merger Killed Wireless Price Competition in U.S."]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40379337</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40379337"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will say, I'm not terribly fond of mergers on principle. However, based on my insight as a former customer and shareholder of the company, Sprint's goose was most definitely cooked to a crisp. If this merger had not happened, I could have seen Sprint file for bankruptcy, with Verizon and AT&T picking the carcass clean.
I think folks forget how dire Sprint's straits were at the time, and this specific merger truly was the least of all evils.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TheAmazingRace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[157. The fairy gaymothers (Malacca Day 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/the-fairy-gaymothers-malacca-day-2/</id>
        <link href="https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/the-fairy-gaymothers-malacca-day-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T12:24:53.946Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[This is a continuation of Day 1 of Malacca]
I woke up the next day around 8:30AM. Malacca wholeheartedly welcomed me, but I haven't had a chance to savor it much. I decided to have a lie-in and play on my phone for a little bit before taking on the day. Most businesses open around 10 AM and I just needed some rest.
I laid in bed, tapping away on Instagram messages and WhatsApp chats. I looked back at the photos and videos in my photo album that I haphazardly took while I was in the club and giggled. Throughout the early morning, I was updating my friends in the morning about my adventures. A bunch of them were laughing at me because it seemed like I replaced one French person with another French. However, this time- she's way more fun and she commits to the plans that we make.
Ok, I was s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Recent Inflationary Spike a Global Phenomenon?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29961</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/is-the-recent-inflationary-spike-a-global-phenomenon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, inflation rose almost simultaneously in most economies around the world. After peaking in mid-2022, inflation then went into decline—a fall that was just as universal as the initial rise. In this post, we explore the interrelation of inflation dynamics across OECD countries by constructing a measure of the persistence of global inflation. We then study the extent to which the persistence of global inflation reflects broad-based swings, as opposed to idiosyncratic country-level movements. Our main finding is that the spike and subsequent moderation in global inflation in the post-pandemic period were driven by persistent movements. When we look at measures of inflation that include food and energy prices, most of the persistence appears to be broad-based, suggesting that international oil and commodity prices played an important role in global inflation dynamics. Excluding food and energy prices in the analysis still shows a broad-based persistence, although with a substantial increase in the role of country-specific factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martín Almuzara, Babur Kocaoglu, and Argia Sbordone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;A Bronx Tale&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperativism in New York.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leashless in "VCs aren’t your friends"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40376523</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40376523"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T09:20:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember: if VCs believed in what they were doing they would not take a 2% annual management fee and 20% of the upside.
They’d take 40% of the upside and live on ramen noodles.
VCs make money by raising money from LPs.
They spend this money on investments which don’t look too bad if they fail, because nearly all of them fail. Looking good while losing all of your investors money on companies which go broke is the key VC skill.
Once in a while you get a huge hit. That’s a lottery win, there is no formula for finding that hit. Broad bets helps but that’s about it. The “VC thesis” is a fundraising tool, a pitch instrument, it makes no measurable difference to success. It’s a shtick.
Sympathy, however, for the VC: car dealership sized transactions paired with the diligence burdens of real finance. It’s a terrible job.
Once you understand that VC is one of the worst jobs in finance and they don’t believe most of their own story — it’s fundraising flimflam for their LPs - it’s a lot easier to negotiate.
1) we are a sound bet not to get you in trouble if we fail (good schools and track records)
2) we will work hard on things which your LPs and their lawyers understand, leaving evidence of a good effort on failure
3) we know how the game works and will play by the unwritten rules: keep up appearances
The kind of lunatics who actually stand to make money with a higher probability than average - the “Think Different” category - usually violate all of these rules.
1) they have no track record
2) they work on esoteric nonsense
3) they look weird in public
And they’re structurally uninvestable.
Once you get this it’s all a lot easier: the job of a VC is not to invest in winners, that’s a bonus.
The job of a VC is to look respectable while losing other people’s money at the roulette wheel, and taking a margin for doing so.
I hope that helps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leashless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[catching up]]></title>
        <id>https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/</id>
        <link href="https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:28:05.926Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[woah, hello bear! it sure has been a while since i've last written.
a little bit after my last post, i went on some back-to-back trips around asia. i spent a few days in seoul and about a week in bali. i did actually write about both of those trips with the intention of sharing them with all of you on here but for some reason i couldn't quite bring myself to publish it. i've never really written on any sort of platform before this, but i'm assuming that just like visual art, some writing is just meant to be kept to yourself.
with the only things i had written in that span of 4 weeks being private, i didn't really have much else to post. and the longer i went without posting, the harder it was to come back. this always happens to me. it was the exact same mindset i had with my art account o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by keiferski in "VCs aren’t your friends"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40375862</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40375862"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T06:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way VCs filter out potential investments seems fairly similar to the way Ivy League schools filter out potential students. (Probably because they are comprised of the same people.) It is not really about technical brilliance, or innovation, or anything that is written on their website as a core value. It's more about whether you're smart enough and can follow instructions and fit into the overarching institutional structure of school and work.
For companies that are at the point of raising venture capital, this might be what is actually needed. But it certainly seems like it filters out a lot of the more idiosyncratic, brilliant types that aren't concerned with (from their perspective, irrelevant) details, like the date on a pitch deck. It seems like a good way to get institutional operators, not rare but not-quite-conformist innovators. I can't imagine someone like Steve Jobs or Nikola Tesla passing these VC/Ivy League kinds of tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>keiferski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paranoidrobot in "Things I won't work with: the higher states of bromine (2019)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40375244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40375244"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T04:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(2019)
This is from Derek Lowe's wonderful "Things I won't work with" series from his long running blog.
Even if you're not a chemistry person, it's written in an accessible way, and usually quite humorous way.
I recommend his 2010 post on "FOOF" Dioxygen Difluoride from the same series.
[1] https://www.science.org/content/blog-post/things-i-won-t-wor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paranoidrobot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by theyeenzbeanz in "Utah Locals Are Getting Cheap 10 Gbps Fiber Thanks to Local Governments"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40374353</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40374353"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T01:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comcast lobbied so hard to get our local mileage for fiber expansion voted down. When it passed, they suddenly decided they’re going to spend 6 figures worth of money to expand their own fiber backdown (they’re not even to the house). Its amazing when corporations will spend more money fighting something than actually implementing said thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>theyeenzbeanz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Code to Quill: Embark on a Legendary Kubernetes Quest with SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've likely heard the adage, "Contributing isn't just about writing code",
whispered in forums or seen etched into the digital walls of open source communities.
But what depth of truth lies within this ancient wisdom, especially in the vast,
evolving world of Kubernetes?
Today, contributing to open source extends far beyond the realm of coding.
It's an inclusive journey that welcomes the diverse skills of all who wish
to be a part of it. Whether you're a seasoned developer or someone whose strengths
lie outside traditional programming, your contributions hold immense value.
Imagine yourself embarking on a journey that leverages your expertise and love
for free software to enhance your capabilities and strengthen the very foundation
of the Kubernetes ecosystem. This is a real opportunity …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Bossware is a big legal risk"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40373016</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40373016"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T22:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone replying with "what's the big deal?" is showing their tech privilege. You may not have to deal with intrusive monitoring, but warehouse workers are increasingly being made to wear ankle bracelets so every movement of theirs can be monitored and stack ranked. Workers in WFH "gig" jobs are made to install always-on keyloggers and other monitoring software on their personal computers and phones (which are required for the job). Companies take photos/videos of them in their homes every few minutes throughout the day. Plenty of jobs require you to hand your social media passwords to your employer. There is an entire class of companies that specialize in all of this.
Not everyone is able to say "no" to all this and still make rent next month. I'm happy the government is finally stepping in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yreg in "Apple announces new accessibility features, including eye tracking"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40372977</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40372977"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T22:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility is for everyone, including you, if you live long enough. And the alternative is worse. So your choice is death or you are going to use accessibility features. – Siracusa]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yreg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) winners]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7591</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-australian-book-industry-awards-abias-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) were held last week, on Thursday 9 May. The ABIAs are considered the Australian book publishing industry’s night of nights. A book-ish version of the Oscars, if you will. Award winners include Pip Williams, with her novel The Bookbinder of Jericho, in the General Fiction Book of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - How to find Your Local Wobbly History]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: How to find Your Local Wobbly History
Date: 2000
Notes: Published in Anarcho-Syndicalist Review #28, Spring 2000.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 One can find the forgotten Wobbly names and faces, strike stories, union halls and martyrs’ graves in any city where the IWW earned its legendary reputation. It is easy to find thorough information on the luminaries, such as Tresca, Flynn and Giovanitti, but what about those local organizers who invited these major figures to town, and then kept working after they were gone, pouring the wine of rebellion into workers’ hearts? It may take some time, but in all probability you’ll find syndicalist monuments and hallowed ground that you walk past every day, but never knew existed. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists
Date: September 2006
Notes: An earlier, much shorter version of this article, “Anarchists in Medicine and Pharmacy: Philadelphia, 1889–1930,” appeared in Clamor Magazine #6 (Dec. 2000/Jan. 2001), and had previously been posted on both the Guinea Pig Zero and Dead Anarchists websites.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 In the City of Philadelphia in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, there was a large group of professionals who practiced medicine or pharmacy as a livelihood, while committing great energies to the anarchist movement. Looking past the surface, we find a closely knit community of intellectuals who treated their comrades as patients, educated the publ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes to hours, hours to days, this is how you spend your time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7593</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/minute-hours-hours-days-how-you-spend-your-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A breakdown of how people, Americans in this case, spend their time, by each decade of their life. Things like sleeping, eating, working, caring for others, and socialising. The crunch is definitely on in our thirties, forties, and fifties, when time for sleep and socialising, for instance, is reduced. Kurzgesagt also did a presentation a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltairine de Cleyre - On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Voltairine de Cleyre
Title: On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion
Subtitle: A Private Letter to Samuel H. Gordon
Date: 1897
Notes: Edited and introduced by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

​Introduction
 Voltairine de Cleyre, by far Philadelphia’s brightest anarchist light, was 30 years old when, during the late summer or fall of 1897, she wrote the following letter in London. The letter was never finished, nor was it signed, dated, or mailed. Yet the letter, clearly in her handwriting and style, came to rest in a large group of her letters in the papers of Joseph J. Cohen (1878–1953), de Cleyre’s longtime associate in anarchism, which are stored in the Bund Collection, YIVO Archives, in New York City. It is one of the most compellin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin longlist for Australian novel writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7596</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-longlist-australian-novel-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well this is exciting, the longlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for Australian novel writing, has been published. Not sure how I missed the official announcement, but I went searching for a date the longlist would be unveiled, and instead found the longlist itself: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson - All Eyes on Rafah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson
Title: All Eyes on Rafah
Date: May 15th, 2024
Notes: The following article is a transcript of a speech given by Geelong Anarchist Communists member Tommy Lawson at an Independent and Peaceful Australia Network (IPAN) ‘Rally for Rafah’ held on Saturday 11th of May. Its content is supported unanimously by Geelong Anarchist Communists. We have decided to publish it today, on the 76th anniversary of the Nakba (‘catastrophe’) to declare that we stand with those resisting genocide and colonisation.
Source: Retrieved on May 15th, 2024 from https://geelonganarchists.org/2024/05/15/all-eyes-on-rafah/.

During al Nakba over 750,000 Palestinian people, from a total population of 1.9 million, were made refugees beyond the borders of their homeland. 53…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pmcjones in "Adobe Photoshop Source Code (2013)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40371337</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40371337"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aughts I worked at Adobe and spent time trying to archive the source code for Photoshop, Illustrator, PostScript, and other apps. Thomas Knoll's original Mac floppy disk backups were available, so I brought in my Mac Plus, with a serial cable to transfer the files to a laptop via Kermit. The first version was 0.54, dated 6 July 1988. The files on the floppies were in various ancient compressed archive formats, but most were readable. I created an archive on a special Perforce server of all the code that I found. Sadly, the earliest Illustrator backups were on a single external disk drive that had gone bad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmcjones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ein0p in "Raspberry Pi Ltd is considering an IPO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40371147</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40371147"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s like $100 per board now once you add a power supply and a case. More if you also add storage. Cheapest Intel system on Amazon is $139. The whole point of the entire thing was its affordability. That was kind of lost along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ein0p</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The aborted experiment of the Bank of the South in Latin America and the alternative policies that could have been adopted at the continental level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2007–2008, I helped to prepare the creation of the “Bank of the South” after being requested to assist in framing Ecuador's position on the issue by Argentine and Ecuadorian economists, as well as Ricardo Patiño, Minister of Economy and Finance in the administration of President Rafael Correa of Ecuador. I did so with commitment and without remuneration. In April 2007, in Quito, we drafted a proposal outlining Ecuador's position on the statutes, operating model, and objectives of the future (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Bank of the South, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Shank in "Apple announces new accessibility features, including eye tracking"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40370097</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40370097"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Vehicle Motion Cues is a new experience for iPhone and iPad that can help reduce motion sickness for passengers in moving vehicles.
This excites me so, so much! I can't really use my phone as a passenger in a car without getting motion sick after 1-2 minutes. This seems like it might be a promising thing to try.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xnx in "Apple announces new accessibility features, including eye tracking"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40369965</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40369965"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love accessibility features because they might be the last features developed solely with the benefit of the user in mind. So many other app/os features are designed to steal your attention or gradually nerf usefulness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xnx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World of Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T16:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A central feature of neo-liberal capitalism, which has ruled the global economy since the 1990s, is to deepen and widen inequalities. It makes a tiny minority indecently richer while leaving the majority in the lurch. Women and minorities such as indigenous peoples, LGBTQIA+ or racialized people are badly hit by those inequalities. In a situation in which famine and extreme poverty keep increasing, the withdrawal of the State further feeds the vicious circle of poverty and inequality. (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Capitalism, 
North, 
Inegalites 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7083</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/fixed-power-designs-its-not-if-you-peek-its-what-you-peek-at/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Sometimes we cannot estimate the required sample size needed to power an experiment before starting it. To alleviate this [...]
The post Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:10:26.460Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the longest time, I wanted to work in big tech. I got placed in one such company from campus placements. It was mostly due to my c programming skills and research work.
I am grateful for the role. I get to work on something I like. The people I work with are smart and kind. But it is just a job. Both to me and to the people I work with. One of the major perks that the HR department keeps repeating is a great work-life balance. You get time for yourself. That is very true.
Isn't that great? You get paid well. Get enough time for a good social life and side projects. You can also fund these side projects with your salary.
Yes, but what about working in a startup? A place where a lot of super passionate people are going ham at what they do. To them, it is not a job but a mission. A sort of crazy cult. Filled with kind passionate nerds. Some place where you own part of the dream. Have equity.
It sounds nice. But such places are very rare. The startup scene in India is pretty horrible. I have heard some really bad stories. So many of the startups look cool on the outside. Have great pay even. But are horrible to work for. I have had friends experience this.
I also feel like I am not good enough for those truly cracked places yet. So I am happy where I am for now and just Skill maxxing. I want to feel like a really capable engineer. I see so many of them at my org. All are really kind and happy to guide me.
Sometimes these essays help me put my life in context and clear my thinking a lot. This was one of those.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Consent and Bot Management features for Cloudflare Zaraz]]></title>
        <id>664272e7abf9e2000aee82a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-consent-and-bot-management-features-for-cloudflare-zaraz"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zaraz Consent Management now supports Google Consent Mode v2 and is compliant with the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework. Zaraz also added Bot Management support for keeping your analytics data clean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yo'av Moshe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Unexpected Inflationary Shocks Raise Workers’ Wages?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29398</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-unexpected-inflationary-shocks-raise-workers-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past year’s steady decline in nominal wage growth now appears in danger of stalling. Given ongoing uncertainty in Ukraine and the Middle East, this seems an opportune moment to revisit the conventional wisdom about the relationship between inflation and wages: if an unexpected increase in energy costs drives up the cost of living, will workers demand higher wages, reversing the recent moderation in wage growth? In new work with Justin Bloesch and Seung Joo Lee examining those concerns, our analysis shows that the pass-through of such inflationary shocks to wages is weak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I found a paper that denies one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism, so stating the obvious turns out to be useful!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52696</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/15/i-found-a-paper-that-denies-one-of-my-two-obvious-thoughts-about-originalism-so-stating-the-obvious-turns-out-to-be-useful/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a couple days to think on it, I think this post is right on. I just stumbled on a paper that stumbles, badly, over one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism. So let me point that out. Quick review. My first obvious thought is it’s weird, if you think about it, that one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidents Barber Conable and Lewis Preston (1986-1995)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with electric vehicles]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45369</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/15/the-problem-with-electric-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker For the last quarter century, those of us hoping we could slow global warming were anxious to see a quick conversion to electric vehicles (EVs). If we could get most people using electric vehicles, and have the energy coming from clean sources, we could radically reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The problem was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc. - How To Justify Workplace Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc.
Title: How To Justify Workplace Theft
Date: 14th April 2020
Source: Retrieved on 9th September 2020 from archive.org/details/workplacetheft-web

 Whether aware of it or not, your boss is stealing from you every paycheck. Employers profit off of the “excess” wealth that you, as an employee, produce. There are two ways to get paid in America: make money off the work you do, or make money off the work that other people do. Employees generate wealth, employers collect it. 
 We live in a capitalist society. We all know that. Most people are okay with it, too. After all, the competition (state communism like the USSR) doesn’t have such a good reputation. 
 But what exactly does capitalism mean? Our good friend the dictionary says capitalism is “an economic and political syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anne Archet - Sirventès of the Beast]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anne Archet
Title: Sirventès of the Beast
Date: 2014/06/27
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 I am no citizen 
 I am no consumer 
 I am no tax-payer 
 I am no employee 
 I am no convict 
 I am no beneficiary 
 I am no person of color 
 I am no lesbian 
 I am no mother 
 I am no wife 
 I am no erotic writer 
 I am no poetess 
 I am no anarchist 
 I am no woman 
 I am surely no Human 
 That vile and ethereal being 
 Which has never been spotted elsewhere 
 But in universal declarations 
 I don't want to stay seated and raise my hand 
 I don't want to wait for the teacher to tell me to speak 
 I don't want to w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, Return Fire - The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, Return Fire
Title: The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else
Subtitle: towards destroying electric mobility & decarbonizing lies
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 To read the articles referenced throughout this text in [square brackets], PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 [ed. – Taken from the German-language website SwitchOff.noblogs.org, this translation continues our interventions in the new climate movements. There are two fronts on which we would like to extend the thrust of the author/s further, in terms of its response to the text reproduced above in this chapter of Return Fire, Targets That Do Not Exist Anywhere Else. Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil - An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil
Title: An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society
Date: 02.22.2024
Source: Original translation of “Uma análise histórica anarquista das inscrições corporais na sociedade ocidental moderna”, published in Revista História em Reflexão 18(35), 2024. Retrieved on 05/07/2024 from https://doi.org/10.30612/rehr.v18i35.16476

Abstract
 In this paper, we aim to analyze the processes of stigmatization and pathologization to which certain categories of body inscriptions have been subjected throughout the history of modern Western society. Body inscriptions are defined as any and all modifications made to the body's structure. While some inscriptions are exalted and praised, others are stigmatized and discriminated aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agnes Henry - Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Agnes Henry
Title: Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism
Date: June 1896
Notes: Original text split between two consecutive monthly publications, with a misprint in the latter citing the first entry as having been published in July rather than June; transcribed from Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (June 1896) and Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (July 1896) on the Internet Archive.
Source: Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism

 The question of how for Anarchist Communism agrees exactly with State Socialism, and the exact line that divides them, has long seemed to me one that it would be well to enter into. And just now, in view of the approaching International Congress, seems a time particularly appropriate for this consideration. For surely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Scott-Brown - Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Scott-Brown
Title: Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy
Date: 2022
Notes: Routledge Studies in Radical History and Politics
Source: <doi.org/10.4324/9781003100409>

Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy is the first full account of Ward’s life and work. Drawing on unseen archival sources, as well as oral interviews, it excavates the worlds and words of his anarchist thought, illuminating his methods and charting the legacies of his enduring influence. 
 Colin Ward (1924—2010) was the most prominent British writer on anarchism in the 20th century. As a radical journalist, later author, he applied his distinctive anarchist principles to all aspects of community life including the built environment, education, and public policy. His thought was subtle, universal in a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Igor & Phil Mailer - And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Boy Igor & Phil Mailer
Title: And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)
Subtitle: The Realization and Suppression of Science and Technology
Date: 1985
Notes: A situationist critique of science and technology published in New York in 1985. This version is a new edition that was published on the 'Endangered Phoenix' website and credited to Phil Meyler. The Endangered Phoenix website is dead now, and I can’t find the updated version on the website through the wayback machine, so there are some footnotes and chapter heading levels which are unclear to me. Plus, I think chapter 3 & 4 were merged in the updated edition, so chapter numbers went out of sync, but chapter 8 was still called chapter 8 which makes it seem like chapter 7 is missing on the libcom website. It is all very confusing, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnarchyNouveau - We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: AnarchyNouveau
Title: We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy
Subtitle: An anarchist-communist’s response to Freedom News
Date: March 20, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 5/10/2024 from https://freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/23/we-dont-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-communists-response-to-freedom-news/

 In Freedom Anarchist Journal’s Winter 2023-2024 issue, Matthew Azoulay submitted an article introducing readers to Murray Bookchin’s ideas of the communalist assembly[1] which disturbed and surprised me for how much it was outdated. The means it proposes to achieve an ecologically revolutionary ends are lacking, stagnant, and fall back on modes of thinking that seem directly inherited from the anti-globalization and Occupy era[2] w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - A Proposal for the Unification of China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: A Proposal for the Unification of China
Date: 1927
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

The Political Capability of the Chinese People
 There are some who doubt that the Chinese people are capable of creating a truly democratic state. We emphatically disagree. The political environment in any country is created by its leaders. The perceptions and habits of the people can be changed to follow those of the leadership. Furthermore, Chinese society has been traditionally rich in self-governing organizations, which can be effectively used to reconstruct [China as] a democratic state. 
The Real Causes of the Turmoil over the Past Sixteen Years
1. The Problem of the Provisional Constitution
 [First,] no provision…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustav Landauer - Are These the Words of a Heretic?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gustav Landauer
Title: Are These the Words of a Heretic?
Notes: Translated from the German Daniel Wortel-London, originally entitled "Sind das Kertzergendanken?" ("Are These Heretic Thoughts?"). Originally published in Von Judentum (On Judaism) in 1911 by the Bar Kokhba League of Jewish Students.
Source: Retrieved on May 14th, 2024 from:https://x.com/dlondonwortel/status/1787470614107763006

 A characteristic of our time is that much is accomplished in spirit but little is accomplished in reality. Perhaps even the lack of actual implementation corresponds to a special activity of the mind, which constantly strives to overcome its own formations without leaving the form of fantasy and doctrine. One could imagine a human society that is structured in such a way that the ideas in it h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like describing a photo to a friend, how to write alt-text]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7584</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-describing-photo-friend-write-alt-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web designers and bloggers have been able to use alternative text, often referred to as “alt-text”, to describe images and photos, for decades. Alt-text helps people with little or no vision comprehend a website image, so long as the description is reasonably accurate. In recent years social media has caught up, and most channels, Instagram, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple text editor named Tine, by Martin Dorazil]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7582</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/simple-text-editor-tine-martin-dorazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text editor without the bells and whistles, called Tine. A nice name for a text editor. The main goal of this editor is to keep the focus on the text editing and not be distracted too much by buttons, tabs, menus, and animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New compute-optimized (C7i-flex) Amazon EC2 Flex instances]]></title>
        <id>a2b797c1aff33d1760b7816ad576286f2d84123f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-compute-optimized-c7i-flex-amazon-ec2-flex-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of applications don’t run run the CPU flat-out at 100% utilization continuously. Take a web application, for instance. It typically fluctuates between periods of high and low demand, but hardly ever uses a server’s compute at full capacity. CPU utilization for many common workloads that customers run in the AWS Cloud today. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Genders Are There?]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:45:06.631Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's 2 genders, right? We all know that.
Of course there is. You're either a bloke, who has the dangly bits between their legs, or you're a woman without said dangly bits.
But maybe there's more. Maybe you have the dangly bits, but it doesn't feel right to call yourself a man? Maybe it's the opposite? Or something in between?
Honestly, I don't give a fuck. For all I care, you could identify as a potato and I'll still respect your wishes. But getting pissed off at me if I mis-identify you is not cool.
Look, it's a fucking minefield out there when it comes to people identifying as non-binary. We've been mincing about this planet for hundreds of thousands of years, and for most that time there's been 2 genders. Male and female.
But in the last few decades there's been a number of other genders that have sprung up. So if I think you look like a man, and I refer to you as "him" don't get up on your high horse and start screaming "YOU ASSUMED MY GENDER! NAZI!"
I assumed your gender because you look like a fucking man. If you identify as something else, that's fine. Tell me politely and I'll happily respect your wishes. Live and let live, and all that. Makes no difference to me.
Irony is, if you're not a dick about the whole thing, you're far more likely to get people on-side. You're always gonna get bigoted wankers, that's par for the course. But just because someone makes a mistake, it doesn't make them a bigot, or a transphobe, or a TERF, or a Nazi.
It just makes them human.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes of Threads for web]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21199</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/14/web/threads-for-web-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Threads first launched one of the top feature requests was for a web client. In this episode of the Meta Tech Podcast, Pascal Hartig (@passy) sits down with Ally C. and Kevin C., two engineers on the Threads Web Team that delivered the basic version of Threads for web in just under three months. [...]
Read More...
The post Behind the scenes of Threads for web appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sacred black and red - Bonk]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: sacred black and red
Title: Bonk
Subtitle: University of California Office of the President Attacked
Date: May 14, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 14 May 2024 from indybay.org/newsitems/2024/05/14/18866217.php


 “The beginning of every revolution is an exit, an exit from the social order that power has enshrined in the name of law, stability, public interest, and the greater good.” 
 - Basel al-Araj 
 With the Aurora Borealis above us and the martyrs in our hearts, we attacked the UC Office of the President in solidarity with the Palestinian Resistance. Using a fire extinguisher filled with red paint we covered the facade and smashed seven windows. Then, with access to the building, we released 500 cockroaches inside and emptied a second fire exintguisher onto the interior. We finalized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Aparna Sinha, Capital One’s Head of AI Product]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5ad22603cb4f</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/introducing-aparna-sinha-capital-ones-head-of-ai-product-5ad22603cb4f?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation with AI product leader, Aparna Sinha, about her expertise in building and enabling enterprise AI/ML capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The student movement for Palestine is now spreading everywhere, inspiring resistance to the barbarism of our times…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the student movement in solidarity with the Palestinians and denunciation of their genocide by Israel intensifies in the United States and now spreads across the planet, there are growing indications that it is succeeding in influencing the central balance of forces while it is being recognized as a major factor in international developments of decisive importance! Thus, Washington's “sudden” distancing of itself from the Netanyahu government, which followed (or perhaps...preceded) Hamas' (...)
English

/ 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delinquency Is Increasingly in the Cards for Maxed‑Out Borrowers]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29844</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/delinquency-is-increasingly-in-the-cards-for-maxed-out-borrowers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, the New York Fed’s Center for Microeconomic Data released the Quarterly Report on Household Debt and Credit for the first quarter of 2024. Household debt balances grew by $184 billion over the previous quarter, slightly less than the moderate growth seen in the fourth quarter of 2023. Housing debt balances grew by $206 billion. Auto loans saw a $9 billion increase, continuing their steady growth since the second quarter of 2020, while balances on other non-housing debts fell. Credit card balances fell by $14 billion, which is typical for the first quarter. However, an increasing number of borrowers are behind on credit card payments. In this post, we explore the relationship between credit card delinquency and changes in credit card “utilization rates.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew F. Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle Scally, Wilbert van der Klaauw, and Crystal Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM done right for LLM-augmented applications]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b5abbea70c45</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/iam-done-right-for-llm-augmented-applications-b5abbea70c45?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How IAM can help you to leverage the advanced capabilities of LLMs while securing sensitive data and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i can quit any time (i won't)]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:09:15.529Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently writing this post as a break from working on the comic I have due at the end of the month. It's an eighteen-page oneshot and my very first contribution to an anthology, which is honestly very exciting. Intimidating, too, which is why I ended up putting off most of the work until the last minute.
Working on it has, as I anticipated, brought to light a number of my artistic weaknesses: I don't like inking, I half-ass shapes I don't understand rather than look for a reference, my faces are inconsistent... the list goes on. Seeing all the ways I fall short of my expectations is what I was afraid of happening, why I put it off for so long – but I don't really have the time anymore to sit and nitpick at my work, which is kind of a blessing. Stuff is getting done!
It's frustrating t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hard pills to swallow]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:56:55.178Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My throat hurts a little. I don’t know if this is because of the air quality here or because I’m actually getting sick, but I’m desperately hoping it’s not the latter. I stopped taking my immunosuppressants today and started drinking lots of juices high in vitamin C, despite research proving chugging OJ a rather ineffective method for warding off illness. (Something about all the sugar in it makes it hard for your body to absorb the Vitamin C, if I remember correctly.)
Traveling and getting sick go hand in hand for me. It’s as if arriving somewhere new triggers my immune system to self-immolate. When I visited New York in 2021 I lost my voice after a few days. I spent my first week in Latin America making chicken noodle soup and nursing myself back to health. My immune system’s never been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Radio Waves&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Ernst Schoen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English is a very religious language]]></title>
        <id>https://itapun.bearblog.dev/english-is-a-very-religious-language/</id>
        <link href="https://itapun.bearblog.dev/english-is-a-very-religious-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:18:05.300Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never really thought about it while growing up because I was raised in a religious family anyway and it's just how I was used to people talking, but at this point I've been living in Japan for several years and I often notice that very normal phrases take on a religious persona when translated to English. For example we have this word yokatta which literally translates as "it was good", but if you were to translate it normally to English as it's used than it would come out as "thank God". Or we have this other word kotoka which would be translated as "God knows" like "God only knows how bored I am" (なんて暇なことか). Also a lot of words in English are shortened versions of old phrases with religious significance like "Goodbye" coming from "God be with ye", and a lot of set phrases or common expressions in English that people use all the time come straight from the Bible like "a drop in the bucket", "go the extra mile", "by the skin of your teeth", "the root of the matter", "a labor of love", "scapegoat", "broken heart", "eye for an eye", "rise and shine", "fall by the wayside", or "a wolf in sheep's clothing"
I'm not suggesting that it's a bad thing (and I don't think it is), and Japanese has a lot of similar words or phrases which come from a religious origin too. It's just kinda weird to notice in retrospect how in English-speaking countries everything is experienced through a Judeo-Christian lens, even if you're an atheist.
Maybe that's why Western society and Japanese society are so different. Or partly why, anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s public IPFS gateways and supporting Interplanetary Shipyard]]></title>
        <id>6642fc97abf9e2000aee82eb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflares-public-ipfs-gateways-and-supporting-interplanetary-shipyard"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is transitioning traffic that comes to our public IPFS gateway to Interplanetary Shipyard’s IPFS gateway. The transition is expected to be complete by August 14th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Batraski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reclaiming CPU for free with Go's Profile Guided Optimization]]></title>
        <id>663cf36120f20e000a888047</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/reclaiming-cpu-for-free-with-pgo"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang 1.20 introduced support for Profile Guided Optimization (PGO) to the go compiler. This post covers the process we created for experimenting with PGO at Cloudflare, and measuring the CPU savings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Douch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[you want a revelation]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/you-want-a-revelation/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/you-want-a-revelation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:12:02.449Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[my supposed last term in college, i ended up failing a class and falling into academic purgatory for months. 

i try not to dredge up the past but looking back, it's not that the issue was a matter of effort. sudden losses in the family and a general fear anyone else i cared about would fall ill aggravated a condition i was largely unaware of into rearing its big, ugly head. those days i'd lived not knowing 120 bpm was my resting average. and then the waitlists. and the forced leaves. and the absurd changes to curriculum. 

hard not to fault myself for ignoring my health. i mean, i was and still am obsessed with seeming invincible. who else was supposed to notice something was wrong? but at the very least, i probably would have graduated on time had the world not been actively folding in o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aidan Rowe - The Politics of Voices: Notes on Gender, Race & Class]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aidan-rowe-the-politics-of-voices-notes-on-gender-race-class?v=1715666454</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aidan-rowe-the-politics-of-voices-notes-on-gender-race-class?v=1715666454"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aidan Rowe
Title: The Politics of Voices: Notes on Gender, Race & Class
Date: 2013-04-30
Source: <wsm.ie/c/anarchism-intersecionality-gender-race-class>

 As class-struggle anarchists dealing with the relations between gender, race and class, we must, in theory and practice, pick a path between two pitfalls. On one side is economic reductionism – the reduction of all political questions to the social relations of production – which erases the perspectives and struggles of women, queers and people of colour; submerges their voices within an overly generalised class narrative, in which the idealised Worker is implicitly white heterosexual and male; or consigns their struggles to a secondary importance compared to the “real struggle” of (economic) class against class. On the other is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[East African Internet connectivity again impacted by submarine cable cuts]]></title>
        <id>66429493abf9e2000aee82af</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/east-african-internet-connectivity-again-impacted-by-submarine-cable-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, May 12, issues with the EASSy and Seacom submarine cables again disrupted connectivity to East Africa, impacting a number of countries previously affected by a set of cable cuts that occurred nearly three months earlier]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Baby, a story of doomed loved, and changing Australian accents]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7572</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/angel-baby-story-doomed-loved-changing-australian-accents/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A scene from Angel Baby, a film by Michael Rymer, depicting stars Jacqueline McKenzie and John Lynch. Angel Baby, trailer, is the 1995 debut feature of Australian filmmaker Michael Rymer. You may have seen some of his other work: Battlestar Galactica, Hannibal, both TV series, and/or his 2012 feature, Face to Face, but likely you’ve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unwanted AI-generated content has a name: slop]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7579</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/unwanted-ai-generated-content-name-slop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seen at Simon Willison’s Weblog: Not all promotional content is spam, and not all AI-generated content is slop. But if it’s mindlessly generated and thrust upon someone who didn’t ask for it, slop is the perfect term for it. Spam and slop. Now there’s a diet guaranteed to be bad for your health and mental […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Containers on AWS Fargate: Launch time improvements]]></title>
        <id>83cc88ad2930181e507d8b8c610c04c011bc627f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/windows-containers-on-aws-fargate-launch-time-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T18:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched AWS Fargate support for Windows Server containers on Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) in October 2021 to remove the undifferentiated heavy lifting of managing the underlying host operating system (OS). This has enabled customers to run Windows containers without having to patch, scale, and harden the Windows OS, using the serverless, pay-as-you-go compute […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Purvi Goyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/talking-to-computers/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/talking-to-computers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:44:20.298Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open AI released a new update. You can now talk to your computers just like a human. Low latency. More responsive. It got me thinking about how I talk to computers.
The way I do it is more intimate. I am a low-level programmer. I write firmware code in c mostly. I think about the hardware that runs my code more than the average programmer. Yet if it was the 1980's I would be a very high-level programmer. The assembly lang bros will look at me with contempt the same way I look at the python bros. The thought alone makes me shiver.
How we talk to computers has evolved. So many great engineers built the infrastructure that I use today to turn my c code into machine code. From the libraries, the operating system, and the compiler. There is a sort of deterministic heuristic-based intelligence b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New capabilities in Amazon Bedrock, AWS Amplify Gen 2, Amazon RDS and more (May 13, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>fbfc12083190a0beba131b64489794f4257a17d2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-capabilities-in-amazon-bedrock-aws-amplify-gen-2-amazon-rds-and-more-may-13-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit is in full swing around the world, with the most recent one being AWS Summit Singapore! Here is a sneak peek of the AWS staff and ASEAN community members at the Developer Lounge booth. It featured AWS Community speakers giving lightning talks on serverless, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS), security, generative AI, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Ansible to bootstrap external container instances with Amazon ECS Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>2c010b11840f18936f90d7128e55a72e9f424e56</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/use-ansible-to-bootstrap-external-container-instances-with-amazon-ecs-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) is a fully managed container orchestration service that helps you deploy, manage, and scale containerized applications. Within Amazon ECS there is a concept known as Capacity, which is the infrastructure where your containers run. Amazon ECS provides multiple options: Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instances in the AWS Cloud, AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Santosh Vallurupalli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With a modest financial transactions tax, Jim Simons would not have been superrich]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45365</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/13/with-a-modest-financial-transactions-tax-jim-simons-would-not-have-been-superrich/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The New York Times reported that Jim Simons, the founder of Medallion hedge fund, died this week. As a result of his fund, according to the article, he accumulated more than $20 billion over his lifetime. Simons was a math genius who had made many important breakthroughs in various areas of math. Back in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disaster Recovery on AWS Outposts to AWS Local Zones with a GitOps approach for Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>1bb6bef186e39209315ed15cfd5a7524cb20d7fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/disaster-recovery-on-aws-outposts-to-aws-local-zones-with-a-gitops-approach-for-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users often need to host their Kubernetes workloads in specific locations, geographies, or on-premises to meet data locality or low-latency requirements. Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) has a broad range of deployments options from in the cloud to on-premises on customer-managed hardware with Amazon EKS Anywhere. To extend AWS infrastructure and APIs to users on-premises, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samir Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a rant? on america's youth]]></title>
        <id>https://pj.bearblog.dev/a-rant-on-americas-youth/</id>
        <link href="https://pj.bearblog.dev/a-rant-on-americas-youth/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:53:23.747Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i know, kind of random. 

these days, kids in the region where i live get chromebooks at school. 

many of my students, including the ones who are now in middle school, are not efficient typers, and in fact many of them are slamming their pointer fingers down on keys one by one, the younger ones not even remembering where any of the letters are even after countless repetitions of the same words. 

and don't even get me started on their spelling skills. 
choice, import, and scissors, although i'll cut some of the younger ones slack on scissors. 

something else i find pretty funny is that occasionally they'll try to touch the screen on the desktop to navigate. 

and this is all coming from an area where many of the school districts are top in the nation. 

did you also know that kids nowadays are more susceptible to online scams and malware? 

and overall, kids throughout the nation are reading at a significantly lower level than they should be, even with schooling. 

that's it from me, thanks for reading my rant:)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Borrowing and Lending in the Eurodollar and Selected Deposit Markets?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29775</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/who-is-borrowing-and-lending-in-the-eurodollar-and-selected-deposit-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Liberty Street Economics post discussed who is borrowing and lending in the federal funds (fed funds) market. This post explores activity in two other markets for short-term bank liabilities that are often perceived as close substitutes for fed funds—the markets for Eurodollars and “selected deposits.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Gonzalo Cisternas, and Will Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Australian study on IndieWeb, decentralised social media]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7568</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-study-indieweb-decentralised-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Pang is studying Design in Visual Communications at the University of Technology, Sydney, in Australia. As part of the degree course, she’s doing an assignment looking at IndieWeb, and decentralised social media, such as Mastodon. She’s interested in hearing the views of people on the subject, and if you’re interested in offering your thoughts, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M. Gouldhawke - Intro to Anarchists & Fellow Travellers on Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/m-gouldhawke-intro-to-anarchists-fellow-travellers-on-palestine?v=1715571820</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/m-gouldhawke-intro-to-anarchists-fellow-travellers-on-palestine?v=1715571820"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: M. Gouldhawke
Title: Intro to Anarchists & Fellow Travellers on Palestine
Date: 2024
Notes: Intro to a collection of links to texts by various writers.
Source: Retrieved on May 12, 2024 from mgouldhawke.wordpress.com

 Anarchists over the course of history have never had a unified stance on Palestine and Zionism. 
 Some Jewish anarchists active in the late 1800s and early 1900s, such as Bernard Lazare and Hillel Solotaroff, drifted toward Zionism over time (as noted by Mina Grauer in an article from 1994). 
 In 1906, Jewish anarchist Emma Goldman published an pseudonymously-authored article by a fellow Jewish anarchist which criticized Zionism, as well as nationalism more generally, and claimed that "Prejudices are never overcome by one who shows himself equally narrow and bigoted.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vernon Richards - Terrorism In Palestine: “Democracy” at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/vernon-richards-terrorism-in-palestine-democracy-at-work?v=1715571806</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/vernon-richards-terrorism-in-palestine-democracy-at-work?v=1715571806"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Vernon Richards
Title: Terrorism In Palestine: “Democracy” at Work
Date: 1937
Notes: From ‘Spain and the World’, Vol. 1. No. 22., 27th October, 1937,London, UK
Source: Retrieved on April 27, 2024 from mgouldhawke.wordpress.com

 The tragic events in Palestine have provided yet another happy hunting ground for Mussolini. 
 The Press announces that Arab notabilities in Lybia have sent a message to Mussolini reaffirming their solidarity with the Arabs in Palestine. This message naturally comes as a result of Mussolini’s fine words when he called himself the “defender of Islam.” On the other hand Alfred Roke, a member of the Arab Higher Committee declared to Arthur Koestler, News Chronicle special correspondent that he was expressing the opinion of the Committee, including the Mufti, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share links on your personal website like it was a socials channel]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7564</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/share-links-personal-website-like-socials-channel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthias Ott, writing at Own Your Web: Today, social media sites have made it seductively convenient to quickly post links that will immediately be rewarded with views, likes, and reposts. As a result, many of us seem to instinctively drop most of the interesting links we find right into the timelines of the many — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wu Zhihui and Chen Jiongming - Wu Zhihui’s Letter and Chen Jiongming’s Reply]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wu-zhihui-and-chen-jiongming-wu-zhihui-s-letter-and-chen-jiongming-s-reply?v=1715513506</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wu-zhihui-and-chen-jiongming-wu-zhihui-s-letter-and-chen-jiongming-s-reply?v=1715513506"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T11:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wu Zhihui and Chen Jiongming
Title: Wu Zhihui’s Letter and Chen Jiongming’s Reply
Date: May 1924
Notes: Introduced, translated, edited and annotated by Leslie H. Chen. Original Chinese versions published in Kang Baishi (1978). Chen Jiongming zhuan (A biography of Chen Jiongming). Hong Kong: Culture Book House, pp. 120–148.
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

Wu Zhihui’s Letter
 On April 29, 1924, Wu Zhihui wrote Chen Jiongming a long letter from Shanghai, in which he argued the necessity of a Chen-Sun reconciliation to save the country from disintegration. It reveals the views held by prominent members of the Nationalist Party on national affairs, politics, and political personages in China at that crucial point in modern Chin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - Foreword to Minxing bao]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-foreword-to-minxing-bao?v=1715511073</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-foreword-to-minxing-bao?v=1715511073"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T10:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: Foreword to Minxing bao
Date: 1919
Notes: Originally published in Minxing bao, in Zhangzhou, Fujian. Edited and translated by Leslie H. Chen. Excerpted from the full, original Chinese article, as printed in Wusi shiqi qikan jieshao (1959), pp. 525–529.
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

 The happiness of full equality is not the kind of false hope that Heaven will automatically bless every single soul on earth. Rather, it gives the human spirit the opportunity for regeneration. If we want to realize this happiness of equality and the opportunity for spiritual regeneration, there is no need for us to do any more searching. What we need is a great awakening of every mind so that all may be free of the prev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Originalism For Realists: Two Obvious Thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52684</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/originalism-for-realists-two-obvious-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T07:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like I haven’t posted for a couple years. Probably time to fix that! This one kicks off from a tweet I fired off, off-handedly, that led somewhere useful. “If you were wanting a paradigm case-in-point to illustrate the plausibility of legal realism, the history of legal originalism would be hard to improve on.” A […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Abandoned restaurant complex near Mèze, France]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52680</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/sunday-photoblogging-abandoned-restaurant-complex-near-meze-france/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T06:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>