<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-01T12:45:15.667Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-01T12:45:15.667Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274241</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T11:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the TIPS‑Treasury Valuation Puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30548</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/exploring-the-tips-treasury-valuation-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the late 1990s, the U.S. Treasury has issued debt in two main forms: nominal bonds, which provide fixed-cash scheduled payments, and Treasury Inflation Protected Securities—or TIPS—which provide the holder with inflation-protected payments that rise with U.S. inflation. At the heart of their relative valuation lie market participants’ expectations of future inflation, an object of interest for academics, policymakers, and investors alike. After briefly reviewing the theoretical and empirical links between TIPS and Treasury yields, this post, based on a recent research paper, explores whether market perceptions of U.S. sovereign credit risk can help explain the relative valuation of these financial instruments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Roussellet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU ‘Doom Loop’: Bloc Set to Embrace More Austerity Despite Evidence It Will Cause Further Rightward Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274217</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/the-eu-doom-loop-embracing-more-austerity-will-cause-further-rightward-shift.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T10:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Rally wins first round in France. Why do the self-described centrists keep making it so easy for the far right?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Camping Bans − Like the One the Supreme Court Just Upheld − Can Fit into ‘Hostile Design’: Strategies to Push Out Homeless People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274249</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/how-camping-bans-%e2%88%92-like-the-one-the-supreme-court-just-upheld-%e2%88%92-can-fit-into-hostile-design-strategies-to-push-out-homeless-people.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T09:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Supreme Court decides it is not cruel to make it illegal for homeless people to sleep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Green Goals and Financial Realities: Labour’s Net Zero Dilemma]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274248</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/balancing-green-goals-and-financial-realities-labours-net-zero-dilemma.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:48:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another example of inadequate green targets meeting the notion that even that much action is somehow too costly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities need more trees]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up just outside of Johannesburg, which is touted to be "the greenest city in the world". During the summer, when seen from above, it's a verdant, green landscape, with the tops of buildings popping through the canopy.

Yes, there's a full city beneath those trees.
However, this is not what the land originally looked like.
To cut a long story short, Johannesburg was established following the discovery of gold in 1886. It's known colloquially as eGoli, or "The City of Gold". Gold extraction here is vastly different to other parts of the world. We don't have gold veins running through the rock like in old Western movies. Instead it's mineralised into the rock itself which requires significant processing to extract.
This form of extraction leads to the crushing of millions of tons of ro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Catastrophe of Our Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326974</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/the-true-catastrophe-of-our-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been writing about climate change for so many years now but, in truth, it was always something I read about and took in globally. It was happening out there, often in horrific ways, but not what I felt I was living through myself. (It’s true that, in past winters, Manhattan’s Central Park went 653 days without producing an inch of snow, almost double any previous record, but if you’re not a kid with a sled in the closet, that’s the sort of thing you don’t really feel.) More
The post The True Catastrophe of Our Times appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Debate: a Victory for Pathological Liars Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326830</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/trumps-debate-a-victory-for-pathological-liars-everywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump is a pathological liar and a political predator, and once he realized on the debate stage that neither President Joe Biden nor the feckless CNN moderators would  offer any challenges to his lies or falsities, he went for the kill.  Biden’s tired voice and overall pathetic performance undoubtedly earned him no support from fence sitters or independents, but it is unlikely that Trump’s braggadocio won him any new adherents. More
The post Trump’s Debate: a Victory for Pathological Liars Everywhere appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunted Biden: The First Presidential Debate Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326982</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/hunted-biden-the-first-presidential-debate-disaster/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was cruel.  Sinister cruel.  While Donald Trump was always going to relish the chance to be not only economical with the truth but simply inventive about it, Joe Biden, current Commander in Chief of the United States, leader of the self-described Free World, seemed a vanishing shadow, longing for soft slippers and the fireplace with cocoa, a case of comfort rather than the battling rage of politics. More
The post Hunted Biden: The First Presidential Debate Disaster appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Down With Dirty Dirt and ‘Waste in Place’ in Butte]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326987</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/down-with-dirty-dirt-and-waste-in-place-in-butte/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to tip one to a rare victory in the never-ending battle to achieve an actual clean up, not a cover up, of Butte’s toxic mining wastes since it was listed as a Superfund site more than 40 years ago.   Thanks to the ferocious efforts of a very determined band of citizens who want their inalienable  More
The post Down With Dirty Dirt and ‘Waste in Place’ in Butte appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the Roots of Religion in Human Prehistory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326979</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/finding-the-roots-of-religion-in-human-prehistory/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A glance at recorded history shows us that humans have “always” felt a need to explain phenomena perceived to exist beyond our comprehension. Today, we turn to science to seek answers to our questions about the universe. But in the past, preliterate people developed spirituality to deal with their deepest metaphysical queries. But when exactly  More
The post Finding the Roots of Religion in Human Prehistory appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Barsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YIMBY Want to Raise Your Rent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326834</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/yimby-want-to-raise-your-rent/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past decade, a new political formation has arisen in the US, the YIMBY which stands for “Yes In My Backyard.” YIMBY posit themselves as the antithesis of the NIMBY, “Not In My Backyard,” a constructed political bogey person, who YIMBY claim are responsible for the high cost of housing in the US. Starting  More
The post YIMBY Want to Raise Your Rent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Salomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preparing for a Middle East War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326873</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/preparing-for-a-middle-east-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:50:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can Israel Be Restrained? Reports from the Middle East these days have two things in common: All the parties wish to avoid a war, yet all the movement is toward one, centered in Lebanon. Israel’s army is preparing to expand the war into Lebanon, where it would face a heavily armed foe very different from  More
The post Preparing for a Middle East War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Browning of Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326833</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/the-browning-of-europe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How should we interpret the results of the EU parliamentary elections? In Croatia the voter turnout was only 21.35% The first observation: in the EU elections held in all 27 member countries between 6 and 9 June 2024, voter turnout was once again very low. The average for the entire European Union was 51%. But  More
The post The Browning of Europe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Trump “Debate” – Fiascos for Both Candidates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326819</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/biden-trump-debate-fiascos-for-both-candidates/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was, of course, not a presidential debate. Not a surprise. Trump came in ready to repeat what he tells audiences at his rallies – raging, lying by the microminute, promising perfection and spewing hate at Biden. Biden – flustered, bumbling at times, stumbling over facts, at least tried to answer specific questions from the  More
The post Biden Trump “Debate” – Fiascos for Both Candidates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Court Halts Massive Illegal Old Growth Logging Project in Montana’s Little Belt Mountains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326841</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/court-halts-massive-illegal-old-growth-logging-project-in-montanas-little-belt-mountains/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 27, 2024, a federal court halted an illegal logging project on federal public lands in the Little Belt Mountains of Montana. The Alliance for the Wild Rockies and Native Ecosystems Council filed their lawsuit to stop the Horsefly project in the Helena-Lewis and Clark National Forest in April 2021. The project called for cutting and  More
The post Court Halts Massive Illegal Old Growth Logging Project in Montana’s Little Belt Mountains appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Garrity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SCOTUS and the Sackler Bankruptcy Settlement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326964</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/scotus-and-the-sackler-bankruptcy-settlement/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gainesville, Florida (Special to Informed Comment; Feature) – Allen Frances, M.D., distinguished former chair of psychiatry at Duke University school of medicine wrote in a Oct., 2017 New Yorker magazine expose, “Their name (Sackler/Purdue Pharma) has been pushed forward as the epitome of good works and of the fruits of the capitalist system. But, when it comes  More
The post SCOTUS and the Sackler Bankruptcy Settlement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>F. Douglas Stephenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinky Friedman, the Abbie Hoffman of Country Music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326927</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/kinky-friedman-the-abbie-hoffman-of-country-music/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T04:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I read Kinky Friedman’s obituary the other day I felt like crying and laughing. Laughing because I laughed at the lyrics to many of his songs, including “They Ain’t Makin’ Jews Like Jesus Anymore,” which pokes fun at Jews and non-Jews alike. Also, because I found his many murder mysteries immensely entertaining and even  More
The post Kinky Friedman, the Abbie Hoffman of Country Music appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez - Up Against the Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T04:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez
Title: Up Against the Firewall
Date: June 2024
Source: XRDS: Crossroads, The ACM Magazine for Students, Volume 30, Issue 4 Pages 26–30, DOI: 10.1145/3665595

In a revolt against techno-optimism and the real-world violence it upholds, members of radical research collective Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL) call for an empiricism rooted in technopolitical critique. Drawing from their own years of labor in the struggles against racial and surveillance capitalism, current work in HCI, and radical theorists like Alfredo M. Bonanano and Modibo Kadalie, LPL invites us to incorporate an ethics of rebellion and progress our tech practices into principled, anti-authoritarian praxis.
 Our organization, Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL), is a collective of researchers, journ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignatius - No Such Thing as Neutral]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-no-such-thing-as-neutral?v=1719787300</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-no-such-thing-as-neutral?v=1719787300"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T22:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignatius
Title: No Such Thing as Neutral
Subtitle: On the Tools We Use
Date: June 2023
Source: Retrieved on 30 June 2024 from ia800301.us.archive.org/4/items/zines-anarchism/Fist_Full_of_Concrete-screen.pdf

While I had already conceptualized and begun writing this piece prior to the publication of “An Anarchist Anti-Gun Manifesto,” the final form of “No Such Thing as Neutral” has been largely influenced by the response to the former. In particular, I was inspired by the common response of guns being “a tool” and “therefore neutral,” of the assumption that my critique of guns, and their world of relations, was of a moral character, and as such the concept of “neutrality” would hold some rhetorical weight. This piece is an attempt to break out of the confinement of moral frameworks …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Honeyeater, the new novel by Australian author Jessie Tu]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7927</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-honeyeater-new-novel-australian-author-jessie-tu/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Honeyeater is the second novel by Sydney based Australian writer Jessie Tu, and will be in bookshops on Tuesday 2 July 2024. That’s tomorrow. I read Tu’s 2020 debut A Lonely Girl is a Dangerous Thing almost four years ago. It was the story of a once child prodigy musician, who wasn’t always successfully […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whazor in "Butterflies flew 2,600 miles across the Atlantic without stopping"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839364</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839364"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T19:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I certainly hope the butterfly has more energy after eating through one apple, two pears, three plums, four strawberries, five oranges, a chocolate cake, an ice-cream, a pickle, a cheese, a salami, a lollipop, a cherry pie, a sausage, a cupcake, a watermelon, and finally a green leaf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whazor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital in the 21st Century: Ownership of the Firms Producing Raw Materials]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274225</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/capital-in-the-21st-century-ownership-of-the-firms-producing-raw-materials.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors from outside the EU control a significant share of the capital of global listed companies involved in the mining of cobalt, copper, lithium, nickel, and rare earths, underscoring the need to enhance the EU’s strategic autonomy and devise a metal-specific strategy going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indymedia - Interview with Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/indymedia-interview-with-pedro-bautista-rojas-of-cipo-rfm?v=1719773220</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/indymedia-interview-with-pedro-bautista-rojas-of-cipo-rfm?v=1719773220"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Indymedia
Title: Interview with Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM
Subtitle: Cipo-RFM activist Pedro Bautista-Rojas explains the history of the indigenous struggle in Oaxaca and also the implications of the forest dispute for both the people of San Isidro Aloapam and their children.
Date: December 4th, 2008
Notes: Translated by Bea Lopez.
Source: Retrieved on June 30 2024 from https://www.indymedia.org.uk/en/2008/04/396318.html


Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM.

He explains the consequences of deforestation for the village of San Isidro.

For its people...

...and their children.
 Q.- What’s your name and position? 
 A.- My name’s Pedro Bautista Rojas, member of the organising committee of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca. 
 Q.- First, what’s thehistory of this struggle and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - A Letter of Resistance from the Magónista Women’s Commission of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-letter-of-resistance-from-the-magonista-women-s-commission-of-the-popular-indigenou?v=1719772685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-letter-of-resistance-from-the-magonista-women-s-commission-of-the-popular-indigenou?v=1719772685"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: A Letter of Resistance from the Magónista Women’s Commission of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca
Subtitle: A report from Magónistas on the impact of COVID-19 in Mexico.
Date: May 13 2020
Source: Retrieved on June 30th 2024 from https://itsgoingdown.org/a-letter-of-resistance-ricardo-flores-magon-cipo-rfm/

 We must bear in mind that no government, honest as it is, can decree the abolition of misery. It is the people themselves, the hungry, the disinherited, who have to abolish misery. – Ricardo Flores Magón (Regeneration, Nov. 19, 1910) 
 Once again, the indigenous peoples are forgotten in the oblivion; There is not a single security measure by governments to protect us, and the indigenous women are triple violated. 
 Both before COVID-19 and now, our battl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Becker - CIPO: Oaxaca and Chiapas]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-becker-cipo-oaxaca-and-chiapas?v=1719771759</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-becker-cipo-oaxaca-and-chiapas?v=1719771759"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mark Becker
Title: CIPO: Oaxaca and Chiapas
Date: July 9, 2007
Source: Retrieved on June 30 2024 from https://www.yachana.org/reports/mex07/2007/07/cipo-rfm.html

 This afternoon we met with Dolores Villalobo from the Consejo Indígena Popular de Oaxaca “Ricardo Flores Magón” (CIPO-RFM). She began the discussion with an explanation of who was Ricardo Flores Magón–an Indigenous person from Oaxaca who rose up against Porfirio Diáz in the Mexican Revolution. He was persecuted so fled into exile into the United States, but was imprisoned at Levenworth where he was executed. Franciso Madero offered him the vice presidency, but Flores Magón said he preferred jail to his government that was not of the people and who did not represent the change for which they had fought. Dolores said that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janice1999 in "Canada 'sleepwalking' into cashless society, consumer advocates warn"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40838754</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40838754"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T17:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments really need to break the Visa and Mastercard Duopoly.
Not mentioned in this article, but certainly related, was the Canadian governments unprecedented step to freeze hundreds of bank accounts of protestors during COVID protests using their Emergencies Act. While I couldn't be more politically removed from the protestors, using a legislative power envisioned for war like conditions to personally ruin protestors financially is more than worrying.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emergencies_Act]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janice1999</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am asking y'all for help: write me emails.]]></title>
        <id>https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/i-am-asking-yall-for-help-write-me-emails/</id>
        <link href="https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/i-am-asking-yall-for-help-write-me-emails/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T15:51:35.784Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, here goes.
Being in a long distance relationship is hard. It is especially hard when I live alone, well, sort of. I don’t talk much with my mom. Maybe I should, but I don’t intend to talk to her for the moment. That means, despite living with her under the same roof, I feel very lonely. And my mental health starts to deteriorate when I am alone and bored.
Thoughts could drive someone crazy when that is all they have being the single person in the room.
I am turning to y’all for support, so please write me emails at corneliuswastaken@proton.me. I would love anything. Book /music/video games recommendations, memes, photos of your pet, tell me about yourself. Heck, send me a string of random letters and numbers if you want. It is just nice to know that there is someone out there listening to my rambling, and that I am not alone. Expect the reply to happen in a while though. Replying to messages becomes a chore when self-care is in dire need.
Thank you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elias Manzanera - The Iron Column]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-manzanera-the-iron-column?v=1719756506</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-manzanera-the-iron-column?v=1719756506"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T14:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Elias Manzanera
Title: The Iron Column
Subtitle: Testament of A Revolutionary
Date: 2006
Source: Booklet from the Kate Sharpley Library - https://www.katesharpleylibrary.net/w6mb2w

What is Anarchism?
 Anarchism is a political theory which opposes the State and capitalism. It says that people with economic power (capitalists) and those with political power (politicians of all stripes left, right or centre) use that power for their own benefit, and not (like they claim) for the benefit of society. Anarchism says that neither exploitation nor government is natural or necessary, and that a society based on freedom, mutual aid and equal shares of the good things in life would work better than this one. 
 Anarchism is also a political movement. Anarchists take part in day-to-day struggl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Swain - The FBI Can Go Fuck Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-fbi-can-go-fuck-itself?v=1719751091</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-fbi-can-go-fuck-itself?v=1719751091"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T12:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sean Swain
Title: The FBI Can Go Fuck Itself
Subtitle: A History of the State Terror Organization and An Analysis of Its Political Repression of Me, Based on Its Own Declassified Documents
Date: 11/09/2022
Notes: Prepared For: The Labadie Collection, University of Michigan To Accompany the 223 Disclosed Pages of My FBI File For Posting, Dissemination, and Publication
Source: Retrieved on 5/30/2024 from: <seanswain.noblogs.org/2022/11/the-fbi-can-go-fk-itself>

INTRODUCTION.
 I have been through a lot. For more than a decade now, the Federal Bureau of Investigation has waged a state terror program designed to drive down me to suicide in order to permanently silence me and, in the process, amassed over four thousand pages of files on me, less than three hundred pages of which they ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Bloom and Russell Maroon Shoatz - Dragon and Hydra Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steve-bloom-and-russell-maroon-shoatz-dragon-and-hydra-revisited?v=1719750440</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steve-bloom-and-russell-maroon-shoatz-dragon-and-hydra-revisited?v=1719750440"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T12:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Steve Bloom and Russell Maroon Shoatz
Title: Dragon and Hydra Revisited
Subtitle: A Dialogue
Date: 2016
Source: <www.oldandnewproject.net/Essays/Maroon_D%20and%20H%20Revisited.html>

Special introductory note by the editors
 In the “Policies of this Website” we explain that we are seeking to promote discussions “where participants are engaged in active listening and a search for commonalities or convergences—giving at least as much emphasis to this as we do to ‘clarifying differences.’ The overall goal of our project is not just to recapitulate well-established views but to transcend them if/when we can in order to create a stronger collective synthesis of revolutionary thought.” 
 We believe that the exchange below is an excellent case study in this process and how it can work eff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274194</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T10:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our cool, calm, and collected daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Status of US Dollar as Global Reserve Currency: Central Banks Diversify from USD-Assets to Other Currencies and to Gold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274202</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/status-of-us-dollar-as-global-reserve-currency-central-banks-diversify-from-usd-assets-to-other-currencies-and-to-gold.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T10:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long, slow erosion of the US dollar’s dominance. China’s renminbi keeps losing ground, many other currencies gain, as does gold]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrewism - How Anarchy Works]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrewism-how-anarchy-works?v=1719739207</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrewism-how-anarchy-works?v=1719739207"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Andrewism
Title: How Anarchy Works
Subtitle: A Guide To Organising Anarchy
Date: 1 May 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2 May 2024 from https://youtu.be/lrTzjaXskUU

Introduction
 What if we didn’t need bosses, politicians, borders, landlords, police, or prisons? 
 There was a time when each of these things did not exist, and whatever you may believe now about their absolute necessity, have you considered that there can be a time again when we can do much better without them? 
 Anarchists dare to desire a world without rule. 
 Neither the rule of the minority nor the rule of the majority. Neither the rule of the capitalists nor the rule of the bureaucrats. Neither the rule of men nor the rule of royalty nor the rule of the elderly nor the rule of warlords. An-archy. Without rule. 
 The wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pikante - Opposing the massacre in Gaza!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pikante-opposing-the-massacre-in-gaza-an-anarchist-perspective?v=1719738560</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pikante-opposing-the-massacre-in-gaza-an-anarchist-perspective?v=1719738560"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pikante
Title: Opposing the massacre in Gaza!
Subtitle: An anarchist perspective
Date: April 2024
Notes: This is a translation of a text that had been published in the paper “Pikante”, in Toulouse (fRance), in the beginning of April 2024. Contact : pikante(a)riseup.net
Source: Original in French: <mars-infos.org/s-opposer-au-massacre-a-gaza-un-7502>

 To write from here an article about this situation is something that will inevitably be limited, but the silence appears worst to us. We feel the need to write about what is going on, in order to take the emotions out. Also, to try to take ourself out of the media and state propaganda. Even if words won’t ever be enough against this incredibly unfair violence that is falling on an entire population. More than 2 millions of people, gui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henri Sulku - The Budapest Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascis?v=1719738079</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascis?v=1719738079"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Henri Sulku
Title: The Budapest Trial
Subtitle: How Hungary Exploits a Dubious EU Mechanism to Chase Anti-Fascists Across the Continent
Date: 22.05.2024
Source: Retrieved on 28.5.2024 from https://turningpointmag.org/2024/05/22/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascists-across-the-continent/

 On March 28, 2024, the streets surrounding Milan’s main courthouse, the Palace of Justice, are swarmed with different branches of Italian law enforcement. The municipal police have brought one patrol car, casually parked next to a newspaper kiosk. State police and military police (the Carabinieri) can be seen on the side streets, sporting riot gear in their trademark armored vans, light and dark blue respectively. The scenery does not yet make a stri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metrius - The Simian Redemption]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/metrius-the-simian-redemption?v=1719737957</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/metrius-the-simian-redemption?v=1719737957"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Metrius
Title: The Simian Redemption
Subtitle: Bridging the divide between humanity and nature
Date: April 2, 2014

The simian redemption
 “You don’t know nothing, but you don’t need to know. The wisdom’s in the trees, not the glass windows”. – Jack Johnson[1]
 A lot of theories have surfaced in the relatively new millennium concerning the human species’ relationship to the planet it calls home. Historically, the mechanized view on nature advocated in the 17th century Scientific Revolution is criticized by ecological movements as alienating humanity from its origins. With the advent of the clock for example, man started measuring time according to its own inventions, exempting the sun of this function. Likewise, the clock became a metaphor for the machinery of nature, and “God” bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur and Barbara Gelb - O’Neill]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-and-barbara-gelb-o-neill?v=1719737733</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-and-barbara-gelb-o-neill?v=1719737733"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arthur and Barbara Gelb
Title: O’Neill
Date: 1960
Notes: The photo gallery broke up paragraphs in 3 places in the source book, so it has been moved to the back matter here.
Source: <archive.org/details/oneill0000gelb_u1k6>

Acknowledgments
 A great many persons, libraries, institutions, organizations and publications have given their help and cooperation in the preparation of this book. We will never be able to thank all of them adequately, and can only try to outline the extent of their assistance and indicate the measure of our gratitude. 
 We acknowledge, first, our debt to Carlotta Monterey O’Neill. With the understanding that we were to have the freedom of complete objectivity, she graciously allowed herself to be interviewed on many occasions, put documents and photographs at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen - From Revolution to Destitution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikkel-bolt-rasmussen-from-revolution-to-destitution?v=1719737327</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikkel-bolt-rasmussen-from-revolution-to-destitution?v=1719737327"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen
Title: From Revolution to Destitution
Date: May 29th, 2024
Source: https://illwill.com/from-revolution-to-destitution

 What happened to the notion of revolution? In his companion piece to “The Movement of Refusal,” Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen retraces the rise and fall of revolutionary theory from its earliest systematic expression during the First International to the first proletarian offensive of 1917–1921, and onwards to the crisis at the hands of a bourgeois “anti-fascism” that instrumentalized the specter of fascism as a means to save capitalism, before ditching it, after 1945, in order to integrate the laboring class into the nation state. Although the post-war welfare state was the great achievement of the workers’ movement, the price paid for it was the ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brynn Emond - Scenes from the pro-Palestine encampment at OttawaU]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brynn-emond-scenes-from-the-pro-palestine-encampment-at-ottawau?v=1719737130</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brynn-emond-scenes-from-the-pro-palestine-encampment-at-ottawau?v=1719737130"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Brynn Emond
Title: Scenes from the pro-Palestine encampment at OttawaU
Source: https://mutualrage.wordpress.com/2024/05/03/what-the-student-pro-palestine-encampments-are-actually-like/

 The other day my friend and I decided we wanted to visit the student-led pro-Palestine encampment that has recently sprung up on the lawn of OttawaU. On one of the organizing group’s social media pages, they had recently sent out a message informing people they were accepting donations, specifically of certain types of things (like hot water, garbage bags, blue tarps, yoga mats, etc.). I felt driven by the urge to donate whatever I could – so, during my shift, I furtively searched the back storeroom, digging through years’ worth of defunct paper cups, lids, and out-of-season teas. There was enough …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowers & Lawler - Anarchism as a Methodological Foundation in Mathematics Education]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bowers-lawler-anarchism-as-a-methodological-foundation-in-mathematics-education?v=1719737002</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bowers-lawler-anarchism-as-a-methodological-foundation-in-mathematics-education?v=1719737002"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Bowers & Lawler
Title: Anarchism as a Methodological Foundation in Mathematics Education
Subtitle: A Portrait of Resistance
Date: 2021/2022
Source: https://www.exeter.ac.uk/research/groups/education/pmej/pome39/index.html

 
 
A large swath of research in mathematics education claims to serve an equity agenda. However, too often this research is conducted atheoretically, failing to disrupt the worldviews that produce injustice and oppression, for both the researcher and the reader. Responding to this commonplace divergence of intent and impact, we propose a methodological approach that anchors research and praxis in a sociopolitical foundation of anarchism. We seek cohesion of theory and practice by consciously demanding that values common to the equity agenda—cooperation, mutual a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angie Barbosa - Marginal Ontologies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies-1?v=1719736373</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies-1?v=1719736373"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Angie Barbosa
Title: Marginal Ontologies
Subtitle: Challenges of a Transfeminist Anarchism
Date: 08.03.2023
Notes: Translation: Cello L. Pfeil
Source: Original translation of “Ontologias Marginais: Desafios de um Anarquismo Transfeminista”. Retrieved on 04.28.2024 from https://revistatapuia.com.br/ojs/index.php/revista/article/view/29/19

Abstract[1] [2]
 In this text, written as a speech for the 1st Anarchist Fair in Rio de Janeiro, contradictions of the historically predatory relationship of brazilian democracy with brazilian travestis and transsexuals are presented, paying attention to the ontological marginality of the travesti body under the capitalist patriarchy of white supremacy. Based on this reflection, transfeminist challenges to radical and anarchist politics are presen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Creaghe - “No Rent” in Sheffield]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-no-rent-in-sheffield?v=1719736177</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-no-rent-in-sheffield?v=1719736177"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Creaghe
Title: “No Rent” in Sheffield
Date: July 1891
Source: Retrieved on 6 June 2024 from https://www.marxists.org/history/international/social-democracy/commonweal/1891/index.htm

We refer elsewhere to Comrade Creaghe’s plucky assault upon the landlord robbers. As some of our readers may like to know what he has to say for himself, we quote the following from the first issue of our bright little contemporary, the Sheffield Anarchist, to which we wish all success.
 Comrades, 
 As I find we are now boycotted by the Sheffield Telegraph, which, no doubt, while it silences us, will continue, with its usual sense of fair play, to attack us in its columns, I write to you for the satisfaction of the only public we respect, namely, the workers. 
 I have been held up to the reprobati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Azoulay - We need a plethora of tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/matthew-azoulay-we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics?v=1719735889</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/matthew-azoulay-we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics?v=1719735889"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Azoulay
Title: We need a plethora of tactics
Subtitle: Considering “metacrisis” and the ever greater need to re-embrace Bookchin’s social ecology.
Date: Mar 10th
Notes: This article first appeared in the Winter 2023-4 issue of Freedom Anarchist Journal
Source: Retrieved on 2024-06-30 from <freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/10/we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics>

 ‘Metacrisis’ is my chosen umbrella term for the escalation of multiple global crises of climate, ecology, and political economy, which have reached such a point now that all radical organising is a form of crisis response. And I know for folk on the sacrificial frontlines of capitalism, the terms ‘radical organising’ and ‘crisis response’ belie that they have to fight just to survive. The metacrisis is hidden from many of us a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: good morning!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52804</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/30/sunday-photoblogging-good-morning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to go looking for photos, but this is what greeted me when I got up to make the coffee the other morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Misogyny and the Attacks on Bodily Autonomy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326709</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/30/misogyny-and-attacks-on-bodily-autonomy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who works against weapons and militarism, and war, it’s hard not to see everything through that lens—including the relentless and increasing attacks on women, pregnant people, queer folks, and sexual assault survivors. And it’s hard not to see these attacks as connected—to each other and the broader spectrum of violence, including war and genocide. Perhaps understanding these connections can help us stand together in solidarity for all our freedom.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Misogyny and the Attacks on Bodily Autonomy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Acheson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prabowo Subianto, Cuddly Mass Murderer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326314</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/30/prabowo-subianto-cuddly-mass-murderer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prabowo Subianto opens the 2011 Pencak Silat SEA Games tournament held in Taman Mini, Jakarta. Photo: Wikipedia, CC BY-SA 3.0.
In East Timor (now Timor Leste), Prabowo and the Suharto family made their killing by exterminating as much as a fifth of the population during the 24-year occupation. In 1999 the Suharto family controlled 564,867 hectares of land, mostly used for timber and sugarcane plantations. Titiek owned marble quarries, had a monopoly on coffee production and export, was co-owner of a pearling company and, helped by pro-integration Timorese officials, of a drinking water and a textile company. Prabowo’s local protégé, governor Abilio Osorio Soares, was deputy head of the board that determined who could invest in East Timor.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Prabowo Subianto, Cuddly Mass Murderer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: Macron's gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-Macron-s-gamble</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-Macron-s-gamble"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France votes over two rounds on June 30 and July 7 in a snap [parliamentary election->https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/frances-snap-election-how-does-it-work-whats-next-2024-06-18 called by President Macron after his party suffered a heavy defeat in the June EU Assembly elections. France has two rounds of voting: if a candidate gets 50% of more in the first round, he or she is elected. If not, then in the second round, the top two candidates fight it out. A survey released by pollster (...)
English

/ 
France, 
Crisis, 
Recession]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To All the Cameras I've Loved Before]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-all-the-cameras-ive-loved-before/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-all-the-cameras-ive-loved-before/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T02:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is apparently National Camera Day. I have no idea who comes up with these seemingly random National holidays, but I’m here for it.
And so today got me thinking of some of the digital cameras I’ve owned in the past. I’ve owned quite a few that I regrettably no longer own, or have forgotten so we’ll start the with the ones I do remember.
A handful of Canon Coolpix: loved these things, and I feel like they’re making a comeback. I think I owned 2-3 of these in the early days. At one point, my university gave me one to document my “life as a student” as a part of their marketing campaign.
Nikon D40: my very first DSLR. I remember working endless amounts of hours at Staples over the summer to save up enough money to buy this on my own. This was around when it first came out, and was roughl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[George Barrett - The Last War]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/george-barrett-the-last-war?v=1719711090</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/george-barrett-the-last-war?v=1719711090"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T01:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: George Barrett
Title: The Last War
Date: 1915
Source: Our Masters Are Helpless (ISBN 978-1-904491-32-3) pp. 31-50

 The great European war has come. The truth has almost staggered our imagination, we do not know what to do and the one only definite thought is that we must win. To this end all our efforts are bent. We fight, with the men and women of France, of Russia, of Belgium. It is exactly the same, alas! with the men and women of Germany and Austria. We are all prompted by the same strong feelings of patriotism. We and they rejoice to give our lives that our country may be victorious, and more than all do we each rejoice if we may take the life of another. 
 Such is war. It is strange, is it not? Almost to a man we, in the countries concerned, have thrown aside what belief we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 999900000999 in "A bunch of programming advice I'd give to myself 15 years ago"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40832107</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40832107"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T17:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'll add one point. You are not your job. Don't take things personally at work. And never be afraid to leave if you're not fitting in with your company .
I've left jobs over a few reasons, primarily bad managers, increased compensation, and bad code .
If people are writing bad code at your company, to the point where you know it's going to come back to haunt you later, it's okay to just walk away .
Don't embarrass anybody, don't escalate to a manager and explain how horrible the code is. I was in a situation where someone our team was effectively writing code that pretended to do things it really didn't. I got into a really nasty argument with half my team about this. I ended up putting in my two weeks, and then my manager was like oh you were right the entire time .
Life is too short to deal with incompetent people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>999900000999</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patterns for TargetGroupBinding with AWS Load Balancer Controller]]></title>
        <id>d710f7ae96ae535d56b495119bc31892821121ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/patterns-for-targetgroupbinding-with-aws-load-balancer-controller/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T16:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although provisioning load balancers directly from clusters has been the Kubernetes native method for exposing services, in some cases this creates a provisioning process that doesn’t align with the architecture of the applications. Therefore, there’s a need to have another mechanism for it. For those use-cases, which we describe in this post, provides the functionality […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tsahi Duek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Willing Executioners]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326794</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/29/israels-willing-executioners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2023, Israeli troops laid siege to the Anan apartment building in Gaza City. For more than a week, the building was routinely shelled by Israeli tanks and quadcopters and strafed by sniper fire. The entrances and exits were blocked by bulldozers. The water was cut off. Then on the morning of December 19, […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Israel’s Willing Executioners appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Azoulay of Epic Tomorrows - A plethora of tactics does not preclude a strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strategic-literacy-metacrisis-matthew-azoulay-of-epic-tomorrows-a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not?v=1719663129</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strategic-literacy-metacrisis-matthew-azoulay-of-epic-tomorrows-a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not?v=1719663129"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Azoulay of Epic Tomorrows
Title: A plethora of tactics does not preclude a strategy
Subtitle: A call for strategic literacy in the Metacrisis
Date: May 10th 2024
Source: Retrieved on 21/06/24 from https://epictomorrows.com/2024/05/10/a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not-preclude-a-strategy-a-call-for-strategic-literacy-in-the-metacrisis/

Introduction
 For the winter 23–24 issue of the paper version of the Freedom journal (UK) I wrote a piece titled 'Social Ecology vs The Metacrisis.' On the 10th of March 2024 it was republished online by Freedom as 'We Need A Plethora of Tactics' with the subtitle: 'Considering “metacrisis” and the ever greater need to re-embrace Bookchin’s social ecology.' AnarchyNouveau then wrote a response piece titled 'We don`t need a plethora of tactics: w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaku Shin Gi - Buddhist Anarchism in the Dharma-Ending Age]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age?v=1719662749</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age?v=1719662749"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Shaku Shin Gi
Title: Buddhist Anarchism in the Dharma-Ending Age
Subtitle: Commentary on the Cakkavatti-Sihanada Sutta
Date: 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2024 from https://contra.net.br/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age/

1. Introduction
 Mahayana Buddhism divides human history into three ages: the Age of the Right Dharma (shōbō), which occurred in the first 500 years after the birth of Buddha Shakyamuni, where enlightenment was fully possible and the Buddha’s teachings were maintained; the Era of Semblance Dharma (zōhō), the 500 years following the shōbō era, where the Buddhist teachings and practice still existed but were deteriorated and lacked confirmed enlightenment; and finally, the Dharma-Ending Age (mappō), in which gradually all teachings bequeathed by the Buddha wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Consensus]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-consensus?v=1719662606</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-consensus?v=1719662606"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Consensus
Subtitle: A New Handbook for Grassroots Social, Political and Environmental Groups
Date: 2006

Introduction
 Making the shift to the consensus decision-making process might be the most important thing that we can do to build a democratic society. Consensus can give us the power we need to focus our society’s attention on improving education, making peace, providing universal healthcare and creating the world we desire. 
 Consensus creates true democracy—not the democracy in name only that sickens any aware person. Consensus empowers all who participate in it. In-name-only democracy disempowers all who participate in it (who dutifully trudge to the polls every few years to select new masters). True democracy might be a large part of the solution to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tiro - Relationship Anarchy and its Discontents]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/relationship-anarchy-and-its-discontents?v=1719662543</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/relationship-anarchy-and-its-discontents?v=1719662543"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: tiro
Title: Relationship Anarchy and its Discontents
Date: 2/10/2020
Notes: originally written by tiro on his personal blog (now deactivated). republished on queertopia's webpage and also as a print copy from 2022.
Source: Retrieved via the Wayback Machine on 6/23/24 from https://web.archive.org/web/20200218151651/https://kalasutra.wordpress.com/

 Once considered the cool, edgy version of polyamory, a sort of polyam++, relationship anarchy is increasingly coming under scrutiny because it is being used to justify a specific kind of harmful behavior in relationships. 
 This behavior is probably best described in blunt terms: (mostly) cis guys are fucking around with (mostly) femmes, and disconnecting from them the moment there’s any mention of romantic feelings, hopes for a more ent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federico Ferretti - For an Anarchist Decolonial Agenda]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/federico-ferretti-for-an-anarchist-decolonial-agenda?v=1719661124</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/federico-ferretti-for-an-anarchist-decolonial-agenda?v=1719661124"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T11:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Federico Ferretti
Title: For an Anarchist Decolonial Agenda
Subtitle: New Perspectives on Anarchism, Marronage, and Indigeneity from Brazil/Pindorama
Date: 18 June 2024
Source: DOI: 10.1111/anti.13068

Abstract
 This paper proposes new perspectives on anarchism, indigeneity, and Afro-descendent struggles, by discussing the case of Brazilian anarchists’ commitment to luta afroindígena. They mean by this term the intersection of indigenous and Afro-descendant resistances for the recognition of land, against the violence of states, agribusiness, and extractivism. I argue that this case offers key insights to radical geographies, and to the broader field of decolonial scholarship, to challenge cultural and racial essentialisms by connecting different militant traditions. I also argue t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274148</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T10:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our electric daily links: prenatal CBD effects, Canada predicts summer Covid wave, EV owners want to go back to gas cars? US naval threat display, new yen low, French far right wants EU rebate, failure of Israel far right? Russia to target NATO Black Sea drones, Obama making Biden intervention? Dimon disses US education]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[june notes]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/june-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/june-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am writing this sprawled on bed, laptop on my lap, listening to Stray Kids's Ex. Next to me is Murakami's Wind-up Bird Chronicles, which I recently started. On the table next to my bed, I have my journal open, where I was reflecting on my June. I am drinking a hot cup of Americano and having dark chocolate - my favorite. I spontaneously thought of sharing some notes from June with you.
I think of June as the month where I decided to take my life more seriously. Not to say I was ever a careless, unserious person. I always worked hard, but it was more like if you aim to stay alive for the long run, you need to get it together.
Thinking about it though, June was the first month I felt proud of myself since a long time. During the start of the month, I set a long list of goals for myself: ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kstenerud in "I'm terrified of old people"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40828705</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40828705"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T08:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every 10 years or so I'll look back on my life and cringe at all the stupid stuff I said and believed over the past 10 years and how I naively thought that I knew everything. And then I'd breathe a sigh of relief now that I finally do know everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kstenerud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey Trolls, Opt-In Polls, and the New Era of Survey Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274188</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/survey-trolls-opt-in-polls-and-the-new-era-of-survey-science.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T07:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As polling methods evolve, it can be hard to distinguish solid survey findings from those that dissolve under scrutiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: 18th Century Writers Understand Effects of War Debt Better Than IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274186</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/michael-hudson-18th-century-writers-understand-effects-of-war-debt-better-than-imf.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T07:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson explains how the IMF's view of war debt is dangerously misguided and older economic thinkers had much better take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tw04 in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40827429</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40827429"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T02:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>Fundamentally there’s nothing wrong with the position of supreme court to push the responsibility of lawmaking back on congress.
It would literally be impossible for congress to make a law covering every single nuance agencies are tasked with. This Supreme Court knows it. This is nothing more than deregulation on a scale not seen in modern American history.  When you can’t find clean drinking water in 30 years, this will be why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tw04</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[all the good and golden things]]></title>
        <id>https://reverie.bearblog.dev/all-the-good-and-golden-things/</id>
        <link href="https://reverie.bearblog.dev/all-the-good-and-golden-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T01:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Friday again. The weeks have been absolutely flying by! I find myself more than a little disoriented by the internal flash of light and color as June hurtles into July. And now I have to meet with the fact that we're halfway through the year & I only have so much to show for it.
Here is where I might usually lay into all of the ways I've fucked up my goals and plans for this year...but I don't feel like doing that right now!
I'm in a really good mood. So I wanna talk about what I feel like I've actually done a good job of this year!!!
Okay! Number one: I've been so social! This is probably the most social-butterfly version of myself I've managed to muster up in years. Maybe not so much throughout this month in particular, but I've been recharging from all of the events, reconnections, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Notes 011]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-011/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-011/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🗓️ // 062224 - 062824
When you’re not paying attention, time seems to zoom by without even giving you a chance to take a breath. I drowned in meetings throughout the week that I thought would never end, and then before I could even inhale and exhale, it’s Friday.
It’s good, and bad depending on how you look at it. Time keeps getting away from me, but at the same time, I feel like I’m not accomplishing enough.
Our Internet was down for 26 hours at home, which forced us to work in a nearby cafe. I was in that cafe for 9.5 hours straight in a little corner, 6+ of which I was in some sort of Zoom video meeting. Not the most ideal, and would definitely not want to repeat again.
They redid the asphalt on our side street / alley way. I’m itching to take my longboard down it because it looks like it’d be a really smooth and fun ride.
I started a new Thursday series on my photoblog to highlight some of my photos from the archive.
Did some changes here and there on the blog this week, including introducing dark mode. Created a Changelog page to keep track of everything.
📸 Photos
Cali Alley in Berkeley, CA
A Stop sign spotted in Berkeley
Throwback Thursday 001 - State Fair
📚 Reading
Finished book 19 of 2024 - Sorry for the Inconvenience by Farah Naz Rishi (4/5⭐)
Started: A Court of Silver Flames by Sarah J Maas - last book of the series
📺 Watching
Watched Ender’s Game (2013) on Netflix. It was LSC’s first time. (4.5/5⭐)
Watched the Presidential debate. That’s it. No other comment.
The Incredibly True Adventure of Two Girls in Love (1995) on Netflix. This movie was absolutely terrible but it had Tina from the L Word (1.5/5⭐️)
🎧 Listening
Recently played tracks on Spotify
Chelsea by The Summer Set
The Perfect Mistake by Cartel
Hells Over Head by BOYS LIKE GIRLS
Say You Love Me by Jessie Ware
Buzzcut Season by Lorde
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vundercind in "It's getting harder to die"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825584</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825584"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T21:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently watched someone close die over a couple days, after a long decline.
The last 24 hours were monstrous to inflict on anyone. Torture. Evil.
Hours and hours of faltering breathing, often restarting with what was plainly a panicked adrenaline-pumping response. It looked like they felt like they were about to drown every few minutes, hour, after hour, no relief. No IV fluids (terminal anyway, so no trying to keep them alive with techniques like that) and unable to drink, so certainly terribly thirsty the whole time. Unable to communicate or really engage with surroundings, and quite high on pain meds anyway (the closest thing to a mercy in all this). It’s fucked up that that’s a fairly normal way for dying people to make their exit. I’m sure there are all kinds of problems with trying to provide a way out when someone can’t make the choice for themselves, without opening it up to abuse, but damn, I hope this isn’t the best we can do because it’s terrible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vundercind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VincentEvans in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825091</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825091"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T20:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress can actually legislate the right of agencies to interpret the gaps in the laws back into effect - by passing a law that explicitly gives agencies this power.
Just like congress can legislate abortion laws rather than leaving it to judicial precedence.
Fundamentally there’s nothing wrong with the position of supreme court to push the responsibility of lawmaking back on congress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VincentEvans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mosh pit rules applied to social media]]></title>
        <id>https://pcalv.es/mosh-pit-rules-applied-to-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://pcalv.es/mosh-pit-rules-applied-to-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t jump straight in. Observe and see how people are moving before you get involved.
Look out for each other. If someone falls over, help them get up. You are there to have fun together.
Start at the sides and work your way in for a more intense experience. Stay on the outside until you get your bearings. Then, when you’re ready, venture further into the center to get really wild.
Never try and intentionally hurt someone. If you get hit by accident or intentionally do not retaliate.
Treat everyone with respect and stay safe!
⁂
✍️ Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lanstin in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40824075</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40824075"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T19:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AOL's server code was excellent. It was written by some people that had done similar things for BITNET and had a deep understanding of Unix programming and how to use event loops for scalability.
It was in C, but the process was expected to run for months without crashing or running out of memory; if it had an abnormal exit, you'd (the owner as set in some code thing) get an email with the core backtrace. If it had a memory leak, ops would be on you quickly. Ops was considered a primary driver of requirements to dev, and absolutely everything could be reloaded into a running server without restarting it. There was a TCP control port where a TCL interpreter inside the service was exposed and generally you wrote the (very simple, CS 101 style) TCL commands to manage the server.  It was a "No…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lanstin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823777</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823777"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T18:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One that was written from scratch, by me. All others are terrible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pradn in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823142</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823142"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T17:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's monorepo, and it's not even close - primarily for the tooling:
* Creating a mutable snapshot of the entire codebase takes a second or two.
* Builds are perfectly reproducible, and happen on build clusters. Entire C++ servers with hundreds of thousands of lines of code can be built from scratch in a minute or two tops.
* The build config language is really simple and concise.
* Code search across the entire codebase is instant.
* File history loads in an instant.
* Line-by-line blame loads in a few seconds.
* Nearly all files in supported languages have instant symbol lookup.
* There's a consistent style enforced by a shared culture, auto-linters, and presubmits.
* Shortcuts for deep-linking to a file/version/line make sharing code easy-peasy.
* A ton of presubmit checks ensure uniform code/test quality.
* Code reviews are required, and so is pairing tests with code changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pradn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Milind Naphade, Capital One’s SVP of AI Foundations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/86df019ebf76</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/meet-milind-naphade-capital-ones-svp-of-ai-foundations-86df019ebf76?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T17:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Milind Naphade, Ph.D., about his tech background, vision for AI in finance and approaches shaping our AI future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by brettcvz in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821274</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821274"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems like the judicial branch just voted to give itself substantially more power.
Are there any checks against this? Or can justices just keep granting themselves more powers and invalidating any restraints?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>brettcvz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the first 2024 US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic and security trends]]></title>
        <id>667eb7fea4598c000bd70735</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-first-2024-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic-and-security-trends"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Biden and Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns, email trends, and heightened cybersecurity concerns across digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by consumer451 in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821187</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821187"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Justice Kagan's dissent on page 82:
> This Court has long understood Chevron deference to reflect what Congress would want, and so to be rooted in a presumption of legislative intent. Congress knows that it does not—in fact cannot—write perfectly complete regulatory statutes...
> It knows that those statutes will inevitably contain ambiguities that some other actor will have to resolve, and gaps that some other actor will have to fill. And it would usually prefer that actor to be the responsible agency, not a court...
> Put all that together and deference to the agency is the almost obvious choice, based on an implicit congressional delegation of interpretive authority. We defer, the Court has explained, “because of a presumption that Congress” would have “desired the agency (rather than the courts)” to exercise “whatever degree of discretion” the statute allows. Smiley v. Citibank (South Dakota), N. A., 517
U. S. 735, 740–741 (1996).
> Today, the Court flips the script: It is now “the courts (rather than the agency)” that will wield power when Congress has left an area of interpretive discretion. A rule of judicial humility gives way to a rule of judicial hubris. In recent years, this Court has too often taken for itself decision-making authority Congress assigned to agencies. The Court has substituted its own judgment on workplace health for that of the Occupational Safety and Health Administration; its own judgment on climate change for that of the Environmental Protection Agency; and its own judgment on student loans for that of the Department of Education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>consumer451</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Postgres Named Prepared Statements in Hyperdrive]]></title>
        <id>667c105ba4598c000bd70518</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/postgres-named-prepared-statements-supported-hyperdrive"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperdrive (Cloudflare’s globally distributed SQL connection pooler and cache) recently added support for Postgres protocol-level named prepared statements across pooled connections. We dive deep on what it took to add this feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Repp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 23, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racial and Ethnic Inequalities in Household Wealth Persist]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30411</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/racial-and-ethnic-inequalities-in-household-wealth-persist/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disparities in wealth are pronounced across racial and ethnic groups in the United States. As part of an ongoing series on inequality and equitable growth, we have been documenting the evolution of these gaps between Black, Hispanic, and white households, in this case from the first quarter of 2019 to the fourth quarter of 2023 for a variety of assets and liabilities for a pandemic-era picture. We find that real wealth grew and that the pace of growth for Black, Hispanic, and white households was very similar across this timeframe—yet gaps across groups persist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Natalia Emanuel, and Ben Lahey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by prinny_ in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819222</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819222"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The one in my previous job, which was an admin board for a market intelligence application. Ultimately, the reason it was good was because the engineers had zero ego on top of having excellent skills. The team that set the codebase were basically 4 seniors and 3 principals (the client actually did pay for top talent in this case) so not only everything was based on industry standards, written elegantly and organized perfectly, but every time some new requirement came up, these senior / principal engineers would discuss it in the most civilized matter I have ever seen.
E.g, "we need to come up with a way to implement X". Person A gives their idea, person B gives another idea and so on until everybody shared their thoughts. Then someone would say "I think what person C said makes the most sense" and everybody would agree and that was it. 30 minutes to hear everybody out, 3 minutes to discuss who will do it and when and the meeting was over.
I think the biggest testament to this code base was that when junior members joined the team, they were able to follow the existing code for adding new features. It was that easy to navigate and understand the big picture of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>prinny_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tlarkworthy in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819157</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819157"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google3 codebase. It's just so vast and it works. It's a miracle. I feel lucky to have seen it. Everytime you change it, it reruns the dependencies. Everyone has different view concurrently. Commits are efficient immutable snapshots. It's just incredible multiplayer. So massively beyond what can be done with GitHub. Really I feel it's peak codebase. I've not seen what the other big techs do but it blew my mind]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tlarkworthy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16717</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/proactive-measures-against-password-breaches-and-cookie-hijacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, we’re committed to security that goes beyond the ordinary. We continuously strive to earn and maintain user trust by safeguarding critical components integral to every user’s experience. From passwords to session cookies, and tokens to webhooks, we prioritize protecting everything essential to how users log into the platform and remain authenticated. Through proactive […]
The post Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Lehotsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper: On the curious diet of the Speckled Mousebird]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52787</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/28/occasional-paper-on-the-curious-diet-of-the-speckled-mousebird/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So my wife took this picture in our garden yesterday, here in Kigali, Rwanda: Take a close look.  This little bird — about the size of an American cardinal, or a European robin — is facing us.  It’s also facing the sun, though you can’t see that.  It is holding two twigs with its little […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is turning black and brown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How should we interpret the results of the EU parliamentary elections? 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of the Innocence: Railroading Marcellus Williams to Death Row]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326677</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-end-of-the-innocence-railroading-marcellus-williams-to-death-row/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T06:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was, as prosecutors often say, an evidence-rich crime scene. Felicia Gayle’s murderer left behind footprints in her blood, fingerprints, hair, and, most crucially, DNA on the knife used to kill her. The problem was: none of the evidence implicated the person the DA charged, tried, convicted, and sentenced to death for the crime. More
The post The End of the Innocence: Railroading Marcellus Williams to Death Row appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Combats Climate Change. The U.S., Not So Much]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326599</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/china-combats-climate-change-the-u-s-not-so-much/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two leading U.S. presidential candidates offer a dismal future for the earth ecosystem. That’s because it’s time for a real climate president, not a phony one, like Joe “More Oil Leases” Biden or a climate wrecker like Donald “Let the World Burn” Trump. The earth is warming, and we all know how to apply the brakes: stop burning oil, gas and coal. But both Biden and Trump refuse such a so-called radical step, thus condemning our species to a hotter, less human-friendly planet, at best. More
The post China Combats Climate Change. The U.S., Not So Much appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antarctic Ice Melt – New Sobering Studies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/antarctic-ice-melt-new-sobering-studies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was only two years ago that studies of the infamous Thwaites Glacier, aka: the Doomsday Glacier located in West Antarctica, found rapid melting. At the time, scientists said it was “hanging on by its fingernails.” (Source: ‘Doomsday Glacier’ Which Could Raise Sea Level by Several Feet, is ‘Hanging by its Fingernails,’ Scientists Say, CNN,  More
The post Antarctic Ice Melt – New Sobering Studies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Altalena Affair: Is Israel Heading Towards a Civil War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326762</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-altalena-affair-is-israel-heading-towards-a-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“There will be no civil war” in Israel, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on June 18. But he might be wrong. Netanyahu’s statement was made in the context of the growing popular protests in Israel, especially following the long-anticipated resignations of several Israeli War Cabinet Ministers, including Benny Gantz and Gadi Eisenkot – both  More
The post The Altalena Affair: Is Israel Heading Towards a Civil War? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assange is Finally Free as America, Britain, Sweden and Australia are Shamed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/assange-is-finally-free-as-america-britain-sweden-and-australia-are-shamed/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Assange, the founder of the whistleblower organization Wikileaks, after being hounded by the US with the help of its sycophantic allies in the governments of the UK, Sweden, Ecuador and, most shamefully, his native Australia, for 14 years since his Wikileaks organization obtained and released  documents proving systemic war crimes by the US in Iraq and Afghanistan, has been freed. He spent the last 14 years fighting efforts by the US to lock him up oar execute 9or even to assassinate him ,spending 12 of those years in the hell of confinement in a British maximum security prison and earlier seven years as an asylum seeker trapped in the Ecuadoran Embassy in London. More
The post Assange is Finally Free as America, Britain, Sweden and Australia are Shamed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Debates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326744</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-not-so-great-debates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based upon their published programs and utterances last night, Trump and Biden largely agree. They aim to send asylum seekers and economic migrants alike to concentration camps in the Southwest, or holding areas in southern Mexico. In the U.K., Sunak wants to ship an annual 50,000 U.K. migrants to Rwanda in contravention of both U.K, and international law. Starmer wants to unleash MI5 on them, and smash “the cartels” that supposedly enable small boats with migrants to cross the channel. I half expected him to announce, a la Churchill, “we shall fight them on the beaches…” More
The post The Not-So-Great Debates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assange’s Release: Exposing the Craven Media Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326771</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/assanges-release-exposing-the-craven-media-stable/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WikiLeaks project was always going to put various noses out of joint in the journalistic profession. Soaked and blighted by sloth, easily bought, perennially envious, a good number of the Fourth Estate have always preferred to remain uncritical of power and sympathetic to its brutal exercise. For those reasons, the views of Thomas Carlyle,  More
The post Assange’s Release: Exposing the Craven Media Stable appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bribery Case Touches SCOTUS In A Tender Spot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326758</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/bribery-case-touches-scotus-in-a-tender-spot/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a former mayor of Portage, Indiana, James Snyder will forever remain known for three things: First, steering $1.1 million in city business to Great Lakes Peterbilt for the purchase of five garbage trucks in 2013. Second, receiving a $13,000 “consulting fee” from Great Lakes Peterbilt in 2014. Third, getting the Supreme Court to pretend  More
The post Bribery Case Touches SCOTUS In A Tender Spot appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman Was Defeated by a Toxic Blend of Zionism and Militarism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326559</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/bowman-was-defeated-by-a-toxic-blend-of-zionism-and-militarism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Congressman Jamaal Bowman lost a primary election Tuesday because of unprecedented spending against him by powerful forces that insist Israel does no wrong. By last week, AIPAC had already devoted more than $14 million to defeating Bowman, in retaliation for his outspoken support of human rights for all — including Palestinian — people. Since last fall, most Democratic voters  More
The post Bowman Was Defeated by a Toxic Blend of Zionism and Militarism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liberal Zionism: Gatekeeping Criticism of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326707</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/liberal-zionism-gatekeeping-criticism-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s ongoing genocide is part of a downward spiral for the Zionist project. In the words of acclaimed historian Professor Ilan Pappe: “We are witnessing a historical process – or, more accurately, the beginnings of one – that is likely to culminate in the downfall of Zionism.” Yet Zionism’s long-standing settler goals have not only thrived through genocidal  More
The post Liberal Zionism: Gatekeeping Criticism of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Years After Dobbs, Women are Still Fighting to Reclaim Their Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326740</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/two-years-after-dobbs-women-are-still-fighting-to-reclaim-their-rights/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its Dobbs ruling two years ago this June, the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade. Since then, abortion restrictions have had devastating effects not only on pregnant people but on our society more generally. Abortion restrictions force poor women to travel out of state to seek care. This requires not only the funds to pay for the procedure, which  More
The post Two Years After Dobbs, Women are Still Fighting to Reclaim Their Rights appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgia Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old Mole Comes Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326729</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/old-mole-comes-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reds— the title of Warren Beatty’s Bohemian/Bolshevik love story that features John Reed and Louise Bryant— is also the title of Maurice Isserman’s new book subtitled, “The Tragedy of American Communism.” Issermam is the author of three other books about communism with a big letter C and a small letter c: If I had a Hammer:  More
The post Old Mole Comes Back appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Earth Farms Is Proof That Intentional Communities Can Succeed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326745</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/red-earth-farms-is-proof-that-intentional-communities-can-succeed/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperative living might look idyllic on paper, but intentional communities aren’t easy to sustain. It takes a hardy soul to weather all the monetary struggles, power imbalances, compromises with neighbors, and other complications that come with choosing this lifestyle. According to Diana Leafe Christian’s book, Creating a Life Together: Practical Tools to Grow Ecovillages and Intentional Communities, 90 percent of all ecovillages  More
The post Red Earth Farms Is Proof That Intentional Communities Can Succeed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Election in Danger?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326679</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/an-election-in-danger/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials and election experts are now struggling in a big-time way. How, they wonder, can they effectively address mounting threats — of violence, election denialism, foreign influence, and voter discrimination? Do they run the risk of alarming the public to the point of reducing voter turnout? Are there reasons to assuage fears about either election disinformation  More
The post An Election in Danger? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JULIAN ZELIZER - KAREN J. GREENBERG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Venezuela Is Overcoming the US Blockade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326717</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/how-venezuela-is-overcoming-the-us-blockade-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Venezuela’s Bolivarian Revolution, a target of US imperial power since its inception in 1998, may be decided on July 28, the date of their presidential election. Incumbent President Nicolás Maduro and seven other presidential candidates pledged to abide by the choice of the electorate. Edmundo González, promoted by the US, and another  More
The post How Venezuela Is Overcoming the US Blockade appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lpolovets in "FDA warns top U.S. bakery not to claim foods contain allergens when they don't"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T23:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My understanding is this allergen over-labeling was inspired by the FDA in the first place. https://www.fastcompany.com/90830854/sesame-seed-allergen-fd...
From the linked article (from Jan 2023):
  But sesame does differ in one distinct way from eggs, peanuts, shellfish, milk, and soy: The seeds are teeny tiny and hard to keep track of. This means they’re prone to “cross-contamination,” in food-allergy terms. If you operate a bakery that makes sesame bagels, the odds are decent that rogue seeds will end up in your other products, too. Bad news for people with severe sesame allergies. But it’s also expensive and frustrating for food manufacturers to ensure the seeds are kept away from other foods, if they’re on the FDA’s major allergens list.
  
  Advocates have therefore been warning since December that the FASTER Act is poised to have a counter effect. Rather than minimize cross-contamination, as they argue the law requires, many big food brands have opted to add sesame to their bread products, then simply declare it as an ingredient. They are intentionally adding sesame flour to “avoid complying with the spirit and intent of the FASTER Act,” FARE tells Fast Company. That is cheaper than certifying that their facilities are 100% sesame-free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lpolovets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Pools: Cost-effective, non-persistent virtual desktops]]></title>
        <id>984d71ca0c0d724236063c172b55b47f247b8d96</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-pools-cost-effective-non-persistent-virtual-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T22:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline virtual desktop management: provision non-persistent desktops, configure apps and resources, and automatically scale capacity based on demand, all from a centralized platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janalsncm in "Supreme Court blocks controversial Purdue Pharma opioid settlement"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pound for pound, the Sacklers probably did more damage to America than any other drug dealers in history. More damage than any serial killer or mass shooter. In my mind they should be considered public enemies 1 through N. I sincerely hope they face civil and criminal liabilities for what they’ve done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janalsncm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tetris font, fun and games with typography]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7921</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tetris-font-fun-games-with-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a version of Tetris that requires the player to try and spell words with the Tetris pieces, as they fall from the sky? If there is, I’ve not heard of it. But, that’s not saying much, as I don’t know a whole lot about gaming. Anyway, Tetris Font, developed by Erik Demaine and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing end-to-end data lineage (preview) visualization in Amazon DataZone]]></title>
        <id>879d02790e78c3e2de51ba7702fc1da289789fe1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-end-to-end-data-lineage-preview-visualization-in-amazon-datazone/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trace data from origin to insights with an intuitive visual graph, empowering engineers, analysts, and admins to validate provenance, troubleshoot pipelines, and ensure governance with ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>95dac704f4314c4f6db2eca43810d24e08e0c1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of an enhanced AWS Well-Architected Framework. In this update, you’ll find expanded guidance across all six pillars of the Framework: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability. In this release, we updated the implementation guidance for the new and existing best practices to be more prescriptive. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doublet00th in "Supreme Court blocks controversial Purdue Pharma opioid settlement"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40814431</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40814431"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T19:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think there's a misunderstanding in what the settlement is about. As part of Purdue's bankruptcy, the Sackler family is voluntarily providing 6 billion dollars to help settle claims opioid victims have brought against Purdue Pharma.
As a condition to provide the 6 billion dollars, the Sackler family has asked the bankruptcy judge to not even allow any new suits against the Sacklers related to the Opioid epidemic. This is something bankruptcy courts do regular for the company Purdue Pharma, but it is irregular when it comes to the Sackler family (this is not the entity going bankrupt!)
This is the issue that went up to the Supreme Court, and the Supreme Court ruled that the protection given to the Sackler family is not something that can be given  by a bankruptcy judge during the bankruptcy of Purdue Pharma.
Matt Levine has a much better explanation here: https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2024-06-27/purdue...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doublet00th</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by freedomben in "Remembering Larry Finger, who made Linux wireless work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40813002</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40813002"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, this is sad news indeed for the world at large, but also me personally.  I'm suddenly in deep regret for having procrastinated reaching out the thank him.  He doesn't know this, but he was somewhat of a mentor for me.
In the early 00s I bought a laptop that had an RTL 8188 CE card in it that ran awful under Linux.  I forked his driver and made a number of changes to it and eventually got my wifi working really well (by doing things that could never be upstreamed due to legal/regulatory restrictions).  Over the years I rebased often and reviewed the changes, and learned a lot from watching his code.  It took a bit of getting used to, but a certain amount of beauty and appreciation emerged.  One thing was very clear:  This man was doing a lot of the work to keep the ship together.  Even just keeping the driver compilable with each kernel release often took some non-trivial refactoring, which he did reliably and well.
Larry, you will be missed my friend.  RIP.
If you are waiting to reach out to somebody, don't wait too long or it may suddenly be too late.  The years can slip by in a flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freedomben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst now supports GitLab and Bitbucket repositories, with blueprints and Amazon Q feature development]]></title>
        <id>66767bb7893b7246f1f08f78664b23f8a53f9820</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codecatalyst-now-supports-gitlab-and-bitbucket-repositories-with-blueprints-and-amazon-q-feature-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your code across popular git repositories with Amazon CodeCatalyst's new integration with GitLab.com and Bitbucket Cloud. Use blueprints and Amazon Q feature development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded function calling in Workers AI: easier, smarter, faster]]></title>
        <id>667d8733a4598c000bd705cd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/embedded-function-calling"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new way to do function calling in Workers AI by running function code alongside your inference. Plus, a new @cloudflare/ai-utils package to make getting started as simple as possible]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harley Turan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michaelothomas in "Google Sheets ported its calculation worker from JavaScript to WasmGC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40811857</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40811857"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T15:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WasmGC version is twice as fast as the JS version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaelothomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - Anarchist solidarity with the people of Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-anarchist-solidarity-with-the-people-of-ukraine?v=1719492063</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-anarchist-solidarity-with-the-people-of-ukraine?v=1719492063"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: Anarchist solidarity with the people of Ukraine
Date: 25 February 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 On February 24, hundreds of anarchists in several cities across Europe took to the streets in solidarity with the people of Ukraine on the second anniversary of the start of full-scale Russian invasion. The Anarchist Bloc was at actions in Warsaw, Vilnius, Berlin, Tbilisi, Vienna and Zurich. It was important for us to express words of support to people from Ukraine, whose country has been tormented by the Kremlin’s aggression for two years, to applaud the steadfastness of all those who oppose this aggression with weapons in their hands, especially our comrades. 
 At the actions we included audio messages from anarchists, who right now are holding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - 6 activists of the anarchist group “Black Nightingales” were arrested in Belarus]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/prame-6-activists-of-the-anarchist-group-black-nightingales-were-arrested-in-belarus?v=1719490222</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/prame-6-activists-of-the-anarchist-group-black-nightingales-were-arrested-in-belarus?v=1719490222"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: 6 activists of the anarchist group “Black Nightingales” were arrested in Belarus
Date: 30 April 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 As it became known from a propaganda video on youtube published by the state media, anarchists from the group “Black Nightingales” were detained in Belarus several months ago. According to the regime’s version, they were planning to attack the state infrastructure and sabotage the support of the Russian military in Belarus. The list of the group members includes Maria Misyuk, Trofim Barysau, Sergey Zhigalyou, Dmitry Zahoroshko, Anastasia Klimenka, and Aleksandra Pulinovich. Based on the attitude of the Belarusian regime towards anarchists, we believe that any recorded testimony was obtained under torture until the co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - Putin’s reelection victory in the Russian Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-putin-s-reelection-victory-in-the-russian-federation?v=1719490126</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-putin-s-reelection-victory-in-the-russian-federation?v=1719490126"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: Putin’s reelection victory in the Russian Federation
Date: 20 March 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 No one doubted the ability of Vladimir Putin and his cohort to draw a 50%+ figure to maintain their own power. It would be naive to believe that any action in the controlled environment of the polling stations could affect the percentages displayed on the screens of the Russian empire and the entire planet. Whether you spoil a ballot, write a message on it, or nuke a polling station, Putin will still consistently win. 
 Smart voting, apps on phones and even prayers will not be able to influence the results of the vote. 
 But that’s not the victory we want to talk about today. Rather, we want to talk about the political victory around mobilizati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "6 months ago, I left the bullshit industrial complex"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40807299</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40807299"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T04:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While this author is of a younger generation, this really resonated with me as a Gen Xer. I feel there is so much disillusionment among folks that came of age during the 90s because there was so much techno optimism then, and it didn't quite turn out like we envisioned. Two things made me think about this recently:
1. I saw a Reddit post that was titled something like "The 90s were peak humanity. Enough tech to make life comfortable, but not so much that it had totally taken over the focus." It was a video of a packed mall around the holidays filled with generally happy people socializing in public.
2. That viral quote that was making the rounds, "I want AI to do my laundry and dishes so that I can do art and writing, not for AI to do my art and writing so that I can do my laundry and dishes."
I just feel there has been a growing chasm over the past 25 years where tech is no longer solving pressing human problems (generally, obviously not true in all areas e.g. decarbonization tech) but is more concerned with just rent-seeking value extraction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by changexd in "Show HN: I built an indie, browser-based MMORPG"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40806835</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40806835"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T03:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logged in, saw a guy spitting out racist words, attacked the shit out of him with two other strangers, we've beat racism, 10/10 game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>changexd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[this love is strong, why do i feel weak?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/whitney/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/whitney/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been in a writing slump lately. I've been going out (a little bit) and doing things and even posting some pictures to keep the Publish button warm. But the voice in my head has been awfully quiet, so today I'm going to sit here and coax him out.
Last week my dad flew to New Jersey for a business trip and did me a favor by bringing a bag of my clothes with him, so I took the train over to Newark (EWR) to meet him and pick up my stuff. While waiting for him I killed some time riding in the airport Airtrain that whisks you from one terminal to another. The Airtrain is so strange. The train cars are absurdly small — I'm used to them being subway sized — and fit probably no more than 10 people each. I spent a few minutes alone in my tiny metal capsule and did not pass up the opportunity to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yongjik in "South Korean telecom company attacks torrent users with malware"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805755</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805755"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea at least used to have blazingly fast internet infrastructure.  Of course that didn't make up for shitty banking websites that you could only use by running Internet Explorer and allowing it to install "security plugins" that hook into Windows kernel, but at least the internet was fast, and it did give Korea an edge for its IT industry.
That was, I think, about twenty years ago.
I've been living in the US for 10+ years so I'm not very well informed, but basically the ISP industry ended up in an oligopoly where everybody's friends with the government, and they kept raising prices while neglecting infra upgrade.  Until nobody can call Korea's internet "fast" any more.
Now all we've got is shitty websites.  (To be fair, they are somewhat less shitty now... you can now access your banking websites on Mac!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yongjik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Migrating to the cloud with AWS]]></title>
        <id>59dc679b0c05157308218c9126cc3375da8e04e1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-migrating-to-the-cloud-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, businesses are increasingly turning to the cloud for its scalability, agility, and cost-effectiveness. Migrating your data center to the cloud can be a daunting task, but with the right approach and tools, it can be a successful journey. This Let’s Architect! blog post will guide you through the process of migrating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Federica Ciuffo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aerroon in "South Korean telecom company attacks torrent users with malware"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805471</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805471"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T22:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, terrible Korean internet strikes again. ISPs try to charge companies insane fees because customers want to connect to their servers. Company decides to use peer-ro-peer instead so the ISP starts installing spyware on customer computers.
Makes me wonder where this myth of "good Korean internet" even came from if everything ends up so bandwidth constrained. Is it because all the customers and services are in the same city so it appears low latency?
I hope everyone involved in this catches criminal charges, all the way up the chain. Completely unacceptable behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aerroon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/about/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/about/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi 👋  I’m JC (Probably)
But you can call me Jedda.
🚧 This page is a work in progress, but I too, am always a work in progress, so I think it all works out.
Based in the Bay Area (CA), but originally from the East Coast. I’m a Product Manager by profession, photography hobbyist, avid reader, and a creative by nature. I have a 12-year old dachshund named Cocoa (Chanel), who pretty much runs my life.
I’m not great at writing (or talking) about myself. If you stick around, little bits and pieces of my life do surface itself in the things I create and write.
This blog doesn’t have a specific theme. It’s mostly anything and everything that pops into my head. It was initially started as a place for quick notes, that turned into long form thoughts, but now is just an overall place for my primarily text-based everything.
I’d love to hear from you, even if it’s just to say hello. I’m typically available on socials such as 🐘Mastodon but can easily be reached via email through my Letterbird (or the email embedded in my posts). If you’d like to subscribe via RSS, you can do so 📡 here.
Welcome to my Notes. I am so glad you're here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BobAliceInATree in "Living Computers Museum to permanently close, auction vintage items"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40804651</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40804651"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sad reality is that you can spend a lifetime collecting something, the but likelihood that any of your potential heirs is also interested in it, is pretty close to zero. That's true of multi-million dollar vintage computers, or your childhood stamp collection that's mostly worthless. Paul's mistake was not properly establishing a foundation & endowment to maintain this musuem, which almost certainly leaks lots of money.
I personally have a decent art collection that I've amassed over the past couple decades. I have a few pieces earmarked in my will to specific friends & family that have really liked certain pieces (they don't know), but the reality is that my estate executor is going to sell the vast majority of it, and at 50¢ on the dollar of what I paid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BobAliceInATree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the universe exist before the Big Bang? Maybe…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7915</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/did-the-universe-exist-before-the-big-bang-maybe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened, or was there, before the Big Bang that is said to have brought the universe into being? Was there nothing, to which something came? It is the question of the ages. In his recent documentary series, Universe, British physicist Brian Cox posits that the universe existed before the Big Bang. How long this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically replacing polyfill.io links with Cloudflare’s mirror for a safer Internet]]></title>
        <id>667c60c6a4598c000bd7056a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/automatically-replacing-polyfill-io-links-with-cloudflares-mirror-for-a-safer-internet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T20:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[polyfill.io, a popular JavaScript library service, can no longer be trusted and should be removed from websites]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ai safety]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/ai-safety/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/ai-safety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:15:59.737Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the author thought of the next word
him and autocomplete concurred
the artist put up a blank canvas
the generative ai left it spotless
the woman applied for a loan
two bytes, “no”
the people yelled in defiance
the drone left only silence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nomel in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802490</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802490"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think there's a severe problem with this implementation. By using wrapping, I can't write "boobs" and have everyone else read my graffiti without them having having the same zoom wrapping point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ssalka in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802377</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802377"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tried doing:
```
$$('input[type=checkbox]').forEach(elt => elt.click());
```
and got an alert that said "CHILL LOL". fun site]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ssalka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting My BearBlog]]></title>
        <id>https://wand3r.net/crafting-my-bearblog/</id>
        <link href="https://wand3r.net/crafting-my-bearblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of days ago someone in Discord messaged and said "I don't believe your site is bearblog - it looks nothing like it!" Today, someone on Mastodon asked if they could see under the curtain so to speak to maybe get some ideas of their own. So - I thought a blog post detailing my theme might be helpful. Please note though:
This might be technical.
It will be pretty specific to BearBlog.
It's highly opinionated because I've crafted it for me.
If you aren't familiar with BearBlog - it's worth checking out. It's one of those tools that might not look like much from screenshots or a quick "dip" into it but it is actually quite flexible and powerful if you take the time to play a little. I'm loving that aspect of it.
Anyways, to go over everything, I'll break it down into 3 sections: header…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eieio in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801815</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801815"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(developer here)
this is....more popular than i expected. the server's gonna be having some problems for a while]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eieio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by adityaathalye in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801514</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801514"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "One million checkboxes that anyone can check"
> Why
> I don’t really know. The idea came up in a conversation last Friday and I felt compelled to make it.
The best kind of reason :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adityaathalye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methodological fetishism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45459</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/26/methodological-fetishism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Beyond the significant financial expenses required to conduct RCTs … critics have raised concerns about considerable opportunity costs associated with their privileged status in programme and policy assessment. These costs result from how an over-emphasis on experimental evaluations in evidence generation systematically undermines alternative research methods potentially better equipped to answer questions about causal mechanisms (or the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) for speed and scale]]></title>
        <id>d4565ed778c5a0e98b15e9b099d374724e2830bf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/optimizing-amazon-simple-queue-service-sqs-for-speed-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SQS boosts performance, scaling capabilities, and energy efficiency without impacting existing behavior - a behind-the-scenes look at AWS's continuous improvement journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare incident on June 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>667b4709a4598c000bd7048c</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-june-20-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new DDoS rule resulted in an increase in error responses and latency for Cloudflare customers. Here’s how it went wrong, and what we’ve learned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lloyd Wallis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate and environmental crisis: Sorcerer's apprentices at the World Bank and the IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Ecology/Climate, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libertarian Communist Group - Towards a Programme]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Libertarian Communist Group
Title: Towards a Programme
Date: 1977
Notes: Another, earlier TOWARDS A PROGRAMME text can be found on <www.thesparrowsnest.org.uk/collections/public_archive/15788.pdf>

Preface (2004)
 This document was originally drafted by members of the Anarchist Workers’ Association, (A.W.A.) following a resolution passed at the 1976 [?] A.W.A. conference, which called for the A.W.A. to agree a clearer definition of its theory and strategy. At that time the A.W.A. had groups and members in England and Scotland, and a sympathiser or two in Ireland, and published the monthly newspaper ‘Anarchist Worker’. The text below was adopted as a ‘provisional’ rather than as a definitive text by the tendency whose members went on to publish ‘Libertarian Communist’, and renamed t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you! I’m trying to read your blog post so don’t stop.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecombine.bearblog.dev/thank-you-im-trying-to-read-your-blog-post-so-dont-stop/</id>
        <link href="https://thecombine.bearblog.dev/thank-you-im-trying-to-read-your-blog-post-so-dont-stop/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T02:35:34.071Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found this blog site a few weeks back. I have a very hectic schedule at the moment and don’t have too much time for writing.
But I do seem to have time for browsing what others write while I wait on the mundane waits in life, which normally translates to waiting in a line, waiting in a waiting room (probably the most obviously named room in the english language)  or waiting for the dog to stop sniffing around and pee.
In these little moments, the phone comes out and I look at the recent posts. I’m fascinated by what you write. The honesty, the freeform, the choice of blog styles, the navigation tabs (I’m really happy with the “nope” and will be adding one soon), all of it.
I’m just really glad to be here. And I want to thank you all for your contributions. You make my world brighter.
And for those of you that think “no one will see this”. You are wrong. Someone will.
So keep writing please!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Street]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T01:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is intended to be the most basic of rundowns in getting a top job offer for Carnegie Mellon SCS freshman.
While the following may sound annoyingly prestige-oriented, and compensation-driven, it is bluntly intended to reflect the realities of an increasingly competitive professional landscape. There is a lot of yapping, beware. Get some Tsaocaa boba and settle in.
About me, for context, I grew up low-income in a suburban town with immigrant parents that never attended high school. I took up to Calc AB in high school, and I only knew basic web development coming into CMU. I graduated from Carnegie Mellon University this semester. My highest offer this year included a total compensation of $550k. I had offers from trading firms, two FAANGs, tiktok.
CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Stre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murray Bookchin - Theses on Libertarian Municipalism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/murray-bookchin-theses-on-libertarian-municipalism?v=1719362952</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/murray-bookchin-theses-on-libertarian-municipalism?v=1719362952"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T00:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Murray Bookchin
Title: Theses on Libertarian Municipalism
Date: 1984
Source: Anarchy: A Journal of Desire Armed, No. 13 (Fall/Winter 1986): https://archive.org/details/ajoda-13

 Historically, radical social theory and practice have focused on two arenas of human societal activity: the workplace and the community. Beginning with the rise of the Nation-State and with the Industrial Revolution, the economy has acquired a predominant position over the community – not only in capitalist ideology but in the various socialisms, libertarian and authoritarian, that emerged early in the last century. The shift from an ethical emphasis on socialism to an economic one is a problem of far-reaching proportions that has been widely discussed. What is relevant to the immediate issue at hand is th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by farhadhf in "Microsoft breached antitrust rules by bundling Teams and Office, EU says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794676</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794676"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T23:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This essentially killed my (EU-based) startup in the project management and collaborate space. Before MSFT bundled Teams with O365 we were rapidly growing and closing enterprise customers in the automotive, energy and education industries with high retention rates. Right around the time the Teams bundling started our retention dropped, churn went through the roof, growth slowed down, we failed to raise our next round because of it and had to drastically downsize the company, causing even more churn (about 80% net churn in 2 years). This move by the EU is good, but too little too late - 99% of the companies that were hurt by this have already shut down, and the ones still running will take years to recover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>farhadhf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Netflix Reliability with Service-Level Prioritized Load Shedding]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e735e6ce8f7d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/enhancing-netflix-reliability-with-service-level-prioritized-load-shedding-e735e6ce8f7d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Quality of Service techniques at the application level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by itsoktocry in "Waymo One is now open to everyone in San Francisco"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794263</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794263"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love how we've gone from "Taxis are gross and dirty, that's why I love Uber!" to"Ubers are gross and dirty, that's why I love Waymo!" in the span of 5 years.
What do you think comes next? These cars are literally unsupervised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>itsoktocry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ye Old Blogroll, a trove of links to blogs, personal websites]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7911</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ye-old-blogroll-trove-links-blogs-personal-websites/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My thanks to Ray for recently adding disassociated to Ye Old Blogroll, a directory of small and independent websites and blogs. Directory websites like Ray’s are invaluable when it comes to promoting the work of Indie and Small Web writers and bloggers, which is often overshadowed by all sorts of things, including some of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[about me]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm boon.
appreciate you for being here.
i've always wanted to be an astronaut but i found myself making bits fly instead. i love that which is aesthetic and i take great pride in designing beautiful distributed systems. i enjoy dota, strawberries, and software (in that order).
i like to think reasonably, objectively, creatively, simply, and always with the future in mind. i'm very strongly opinionated, but i love nothing more than being corrected correctly. i love learning experiences.
the majority of my posts will probably be irrelevant to you, especially since i enjoy yapping, but peruse at your leisure.
always happy to chat on twitter.
see you sometime,
boon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse, an IndieWeb arts community by Chris Shaw]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7899</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-artocalypse-indieweb-arts-community-chris-shaw/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse is a subscription based community for artists on IndieWeb, created by Chris Shaw at uncountable thoughts. This a great cross-promotional idea, showcasing the work of artists, while also spreading the word about IndieWeb. I dare say some of the participating artists will already have followings elsewhere, and their membership of Artocalypse will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 forces data backup to OneDrive, possible workaround]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7893</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/windows-11-forces-data-backup-onedrive-possible-workaround/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe it’s time to start a Windows 11 is going just great website, similar to Molly White’s Web3 is Going Just Great. I say this after reading about another instance of heavy-handedness on Microsoft’s part, at Neowin: Quietly and without any announcement, the company changed Windows 11’s initial setup so that it could turn on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lera Khotina - Dogma]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lera-khotina-dogma?v=1719343444</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lera-khotina-dogma?v=1719343444"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T19:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Lera Khotina
Title: Dogma
Subtitle: Anarchists on the War in Ukraine
Date: 5 April 2024
Notes: Order “Dogma” in english at Sabotage Distro – www.sabotage.ninja
Source: Retrieved on 25th June 2024 from pramen.io

 A year and a half after the original dogma podcast series, we have converted the audio to text format. This is a collection of interviews with anarchist activists from Ukraine, Belarus, Russia, Poland, Germany, France, Greece and Finland. Inside you will find different views of anarchists on the war in Ukraine and how anarchist movements in different parts of Europe reacted to it. Original conversations happened in January-February 2023, but since then many points remained the same. 
 We would like to thank everyone who helped us in the work on this material – members of o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21409</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/25/developer-tools/the-key-to-a-happy-rust-c-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of Rust at Meta goes all the way back to 2016, when we first started using it for source control. Today, it has been widely embraced at Meta and is one of our primary supported server-side languages (along with C++, Python, and Hack). But that doesn’t mean there weren’t any growing pains. Aida [...]
Read More...
The post The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices working with self-hosted GitHub Action runners at scale on AWS]]></title>
        <id>c54a5e17bad2934e3e0477995d7d86a4bf854ecd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-working-with-self-hosted-github-action-runners-at-scale-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview GitHub Actions is a continuous integration and continuous deployment platform that enables the automation of build, test and deployment activities for your workload. GitHub Self-Hosted Runners provide a flexible and customizable option to run your GitHub Action pipelines. These runners allow you to run your builds on your own infrastructure, giving you control over the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shilpa Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Errico Malatesta - Military Service]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/errico-malatesta-military-service?v=1719322935</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/errico-malatesta-military-service?v=1719322935"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Errico Malatesta
Title: Military Service
Date: 1902
Notes: An excerpt from “Fatti ed Opinioni,”, La Rivoluzione Sociale (London), no. 3 (November 1, 1902), translated by Andrea Asali, published in ‘The Complete Works of Malatesta, Vol. V, The Armed Strike: The Long London Exile of 1900–13′, edited by Davide Turcato
Source: Retrieved on June 25, 2024 from The Complete Works of Malatesta, Vol. V, The Armed Strike: The Long London Exile of 1900–13

 There is currently much discussion among French comrades about whether an anarchist should meet the draft obligation, evade the draft, or desert. 
 Some say that the anarchist, who naturally abhors militarism and continuously makes propaganda against it, must at any cost refuse to wear the abhorrent uniform and take up fratricidal arms, in homage to our principles and to set a good example. 
 Others say that refusing service forces one to go abroad, where, for economic reasons and because of differences in language and customs, he is incapable of making propaganda, whereas it is useful and necessary to bring the spirit of rebellion and the yeast of anarchist ideas within the very ranks of the army. 
 We believe that the matter does not have a single solution, applicable to all individuals, under all circumstances. 
 Aside from considerations of personal advantage, which we shall not get into, it is certain that, depending on each person’s particular talents and the dose and type of courage he possesses, some can be more useful by entering the army, making propaganda among soldiers and setting an example, when the case arises, of refusing obedience and open rebellion, while others better succeed by deserting and facing the vagabond life of a man in an illegal position. 
 The essential thing is that, within or outside of the army, one always keeps aflame his hatred against the institution, always keeps alive the spirit of propaganda and sacrifice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>