<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-20T02:00:42.098Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-20T02:00:42.098Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O Globo, Hostis - There is a Third Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/o-globo-hostis-there-is-a-third-thing?v=1729373618</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/o-globo-hostis-there-is-a-third-thing?v=1729373618"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T21:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: O Globo, Hostis
Title: There is a Third Thing
Subtitle: Brazilian capo speaks like a prophet; everything he said is both actual and unsettling.
Date: 2017
Notes: Taken from O Globo, Translated by Pepe Rojo
Source: Retrieved on 9/24/2024 from https://incivility.org/2017/07/22/there-is-a-third-thing/.

 Marcos Camacho, better known by his nickname Marcola, is the leader of a criminal organization in São Paulo, Brazil, called Primer Comando de la Capital (PCC, Capital’s First Commando). 
 Marcola’s answers allow us to get a glimpse at what could be the future of common delinquency in Latin America. 
O Globo: Are you part of PRIMER COMANDO DE LA CAPITAL (PCC)? 
Marcola: Even more than that, I am a sign of these times. I was poor and invisible. You neves glanced at me during decades, wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Y_Y in "Love being interrupted when my monitor asks me to accept user agreements"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41889498</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41889498"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T18:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this the future you wanted?

    (Agree) (Later)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Y_Y</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinwar’s Dead; the Genocide Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338700</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/19/sinwars-dead-the-genocide-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T16:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100,000 dead Palestinians later, Israel finally killed Yahya Sinwar. He wasn’t wearing a dress. He wasn’t hiding in a tunnel with Israeli hostages. He wasn’t shielded behind women and children. Bodyguards didn’t surround him. AI didn’t track him down. Another Palestinian didn’t rat him out.  He hadn’t strapped explosives to his body.
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Sinwar’s Dead; the Genocide Continues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Towards Another Uprising]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-towards-another-uprising?v=1729345150</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-towards-another-uprising?v=1729345150"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T13:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Towards Another Uprising
Date: Early October, 2024
Source: Retrieved on October 19, 2024 from https://anarchistnews.org/content/towards-another-uprising

 At the end of 2010 an individual act of despair in the town of Sidi Bouzid ignited a daring, enraged, and joyful upheaval that travelled through North Africa into the Middle East and beyond. People defied the oppressive systems they had been immersed in for generations and came together in the streets to topple the political elites at their helm. The authorities, at first stunned by this courageous spirit that they couldn’t understand, then unleashed a cynical and brutal response. 
 This defeat is still being inflicted on the people in the region, and is also felt all over the world by those who stood in solidari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Face to Face with the Enemy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-face-to-face-with-the-enemy?v=1729336093</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-face-to-face-with-the-enemy?v=1729336093"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Face to Face with the Enemy
Subtitle: An Introduction to the WCCGT pipeline, PRGT pipeline and Ksi Lisims LNG
Date: October 2022
Notes: This is from the zine "Between Storms: Anarchist Reflections of Solidarity with Wet'suwet'en Resistance" (2022). Some information regarding ownership over PRGT may no longer be accurate.
Source: Retrieved on Sep 23 2024 from https://ia903104.us.archive.org/24/items/ZineArchive/BetweenStorms-read.pdf

 Many have stood by as our Wet’suwet’en friends and neighbours have for decades resisted development in their territories, in the process participating in and witnessing inspiring moments of resistance against multiple pipelines and now most recently the Coastal Gaslink line. With heavy hearts we have fought back against the land being…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethel Mannin - Bread and Roses]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ethel-mannin-bread-and-roses?v=1729335939</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ethel-mannin-bread-and-roses?v=1729335939"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T11:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ethel Mannin
Title: Bread and Roses
Subtitle: An Utopian Survey and Blueprint
Date: December 1944
Notes: London, December, 1943 — May, 1944.
Source: https://archive.org/details/in.ernet.dli.2015.213271/page/n7

I. UTOPIA — THE EVERLASTING DREAM
 Throughout the ages, from the earliest times, men of all nations have dreamed of that ‘ideal commonwealth whose inhabitants exist under perfect conditions’. What constitutes ‘perfect conditions’ is obviously a matter of personal preferences and prejudices, but there is a common basis to the visionary dream in all its forms — the increase of human happiness, or, perhaps, more accurately, well-being — the greatest good for the greatest number, whether it is the Golden Age of ancient Greek and Roman mythology, or the confused contemporary drea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280586</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 1]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-1?v=1729334634</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-1?v=1729334634"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 1
Source: Retrieved on february 29, 2019 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/index/

Children’s Oppression, Rights, and Liberation, by Samantha Godwin
Excerpt: academia.edu/2046034/Childrens_Oppression_Rights_and_Liberation (Citations Omitted)
 The legal, political, scientific and media discourse prevalent in previous generations promoted the idea that race and gender are biologically determinate categories with biologically determined attributes, characteristics, and social roles. Historically, many anthropologists and psychologists believed they had found physical evidence that non-white people had an inferior capacity for reason and rationality. These supposed differences fit into an imperialist ideology of a ‘white ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising dangers of imperial+sub-imperial partnering:]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Rising-dangers-of-imperial-sub-imperial-partnering</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Rising-dangers-of-imperial-sub-imperial-partnering"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the Johannesburg BRICS summit in August 2023, the new ‘BRICS+' – whose leadership will be hosted by Vladimir Putin in Kazan from October 22-24 – now consist of not only Brazil, Russia, India, China and South Africa, but also Egypt, Ethiopia, Iran and the United Arab Emirates – with Saudi Arabia potentially joining before 2024 ends, in the event Donald Trump is not elected U.S. President on November 5. 
English

/ 
G7 / G20, 
Capitalism, 
BRICS, 
Imperialism, 
Sub-imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, CrimethInc. - Ya Ghazze Habibti—Gaza, My Love]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-ya-ghazze-habibti-gaza-my-love?v=1729334208</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-ya-ghazze-habibti-gaza-my-love?v=1729334208"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, CrimethInc.
Title: Ya Ghazze Habibti—Gaza, My Love
Subtitle: Understanding the Genocide in Palestine
Date: 2024-10-03
Source: Retrieved on October 19, 2024 from https://crimethinc.com/2024/10/03/ya-ghazze-habibti-gaza-my-love-understanding-the-genocide-in-palestine

 After slaughtering more than 42,000 Palestinians, including 16,500 children, the Israeli military is now invading Lebanon and threatening to go to war with Iran. In the following in-depth account, an anarchist from occupied Palestine reviews the history of Zionist colonialism and Palestinian resistance, makes the case for an anti-colonial understanding of the situation, and explores what it means to act in solidarity with Palestinians. 
Ya Ghazze Habibti
 Ya Ghazze habibti, oh Gaza my love. Gaza, which Napol…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 3]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-3?v=1729332633</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-3?v=1729332633"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 3
Source: Retrieved on february 29, 2019 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/index/

Young and Oppressed, by Brian Dominick and Sara Zia Ebrahimi
 While most common oppressions, such as sexism, racism, classism, heterosexism, even speciesism, have been identified, widely acknowledged, thoroughly discussed and deeply analyzed, one oppression remains largely untouched. This fact is astonishing given that the group oppressed by this ignored injustice is one to which every adult human has once belonged. It is the one oppression with which all humans can identify, having suffered from it directly. It is not an oppression of a tiny minority to which few will ever belong. It is not the oppression of people who can be blamed them…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 4]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adam-fletcher-benjamin-fife-john-taylor-gatto-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-4?v=1729332433</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adam-fletcher-benjamin-fife-john-taylor-gatto-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-4?v=1729332433"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 4
Source: Retrieved on february 29, 2019 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/index/

Why We Can’t Wait, by Adam Fletcher
 “Freedom is never voluntarily given by the oppressor;
 it must be demanded by the oppressed.”
 I look at the people around me
 and see the prisons and traps
 we are all stuck.
 From an early age we are taught and trained:
 sit still, hold on, walk (don’t run),
 and be quiet.
 Whatever you do, be quiet. 
 So we do. We go to polite schools or content jobs.
 We type and read and feel nice.
 Our hair is nice and our hearts are nice.
 We live nice lives. 
 But what if…
 what if we were shown the whole picture
 from the first day?
 What if they said
 “Hey, when you’re poor, you’re screwed.
 If you’re black, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why America Is Buying up the Premier League – And What It Means for the Future of ‘Soccer’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280622</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/why-america-is-buying-up-the-premier-league-and-what-it-means-for-the-future-of-soccer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T10:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Texas-based Friedkin Group’s recent deal to buy Everton goes through, 11 of the 20 Premier League clubs will be controlled or part-owned by American investors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 7]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-7?v=1729331982</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-7?v=1729331982"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 7
Date: Dec 1, 2017
Source: Retrieved on 12 June 2021 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/index/

Documents and Depression, by Kris Anne Bonifacio
 Joaquin Luna’s dream was simple. He wanted to become a civil engineer. But the Texas student’s undocumented status limited his options for the future. Left without hope, the 18-year-old shot himself the day after Thanksgiving last year. In his goodbye letters, Luna expressed despair. In one letter addressed to Jesus Christ, he wrote that he had “no point of existence in this cruel world... I’ve realized that I have no chance in becoming a civil engineer the way I’ve always dreamed of here… so I’m planning on going to you and helping you construct a new temple in heaven.” 
 Lun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 13]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-13?v=1729331619</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-13?v=1729331619"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 13
Date: 12/01/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/01/12/no-issue-13/

Against Parental Rights 
 (Excerpt: academia.edu/19663920/Against_Parental_Rights) 
Samantha Godwin
 There is a significant disjunction between child protectionist theory and rhetoric and the extent of parental powers. The extensive deference to parental preference and discretion seems to have little to do with preserving children’s interests and more to do with parental autonomy. We must conclude that only respect for parental autonomy and freedom, rather than child protection, would lead to the belief that parents ought to be granted rights beyond those narrowly derivable from a child’s interests. This is tr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 14]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-14?v=1729331579</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-14?v=1729331579"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 14
Date: 06/02/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/02/06/no-issue-14/

The Pedagogy of Religion
Peter Gelderloos
 It was my grandfather’s memorial service, and the Dutch Reform pastor took a break from talking about God and Heaven to the members of the congregation, in which I, as a dutiful grandson, was unfortunately included for the moment, in order to address the children in the audience, the grand-kids and great grand-kids of the deceased, nearly all of them baptized into the Dutch Reform church or a like-minded denomination, as the apple does not fall far from the tree. 
 “Now, you all might be wondering,” began the pastor in a condescending tone, only slightly more exact in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 15]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-15?v=1729331539</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-15?v=1729331539"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 15
Date: 21/02/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/02/21/no-issue-15/

Mistrust and Things
Layla AbdelRahim
 Since the 1950s of Soviet Russia, Lena Alexeevna Nikitina and Boris Pavlovich Nikitin, have been sounding alarm that children’s most vicious enemy is, in fact, adults’ mistrust that begins with holding the child when she walks, helping her up when she falls, forbidding her to climb “dangerous” stairs even on the primitive children’s playgrounds marked “for use between 0–3 years old”, picking up the child and sticking her on the slide, constantly telling her what to do or not, what to wear, eat, feel, know, think, and so on, in other words, exercising total control. Mistrus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 16]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-16?v=1729331497</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-16?v=1729331497"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 16
Date: 07/03/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/03/07/no-issue-16/

I Am
 DAVID: A younger version of myself waits for the bus after school. My friend starts to tell me some of the jokes about “illegals” he knows. I look visibly uncomfortable and he acknowledges it: “You shouldn’t take it personally” he says with a smirk, “I mean, unless you’re ‘illegal.’ “ I freeze and then fumble to change the subject. His reasoning is perfectly sound. Why would I be offended unless I was “illegal”? I take the bus home thinking what a close call that was, and I start to plan how I’ll make it so that this never happens again. I become super-conscious of the potential trajectory of conversatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 17]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-17?v=1729331457</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-17?v=1729331457"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 17
Date: 22/03/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/03/22/no-issue-17/

There Is a Better Way
Vicki Larson
 The pressures and pace of modern life has made parents and children stressed and miserable. With the rise of dual-earning families, mothers, and increasingly, fathers are struggling with work-life issues, forcing many to lean in or opt out. But is it truly modern life that’s at fault or is it our expectation that two people – whether hetero or same-sex – can do it alone and do it well? Is the nuclear family all it’s cracked up to be? 
 Despite the belief that monogamous male-female bonding is how mothers and children were supported and thrived, the anthropologist Sarah Blaff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 18]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-18?v=1729331416</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-18?v=1729331416"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 18
Date: 23/04/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/04/23/no-issue-18/

Adult Education (TED Transcript) 
Adora Svitak
 Now, I want to start with a question: When was the last time you were called “childish”? For kids like me, being called childish can be a frequent occurrence. Every time we make irrational demands, exhibit irresponsible behavior, or display any other signs of being normal American citizens, we are called childish. Which really bothers me. After all, take a look at these events: Imperialism and colonization, world wars, George W. Bush. Ask yourself, who’s responsible? Adults. 
 Now, what have kids done? Well, Anne Frank touched millions with her powerful account o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Franks - Between Anarchism and Marxism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/benjamin-franks-between-anarchism-and-marxism?v=1729331266</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/benjamin-franks-between-anarchism-and-marxism?v=1729331266"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Benjamin Franks
Title: Between Anarchism and Marxism
Subtitle: the beginnings and ends of the schism …
Date: 2012
Source: Journal of Political Ideologies, Volume 17, 2012 — Issue 2. DOI: 10.1080/13569317.2012.676867

Abstract
 This paper analyses the development of the schism between Marxism and anarchism and explores two distinct methodological approaches to investigating these apparently discrete ideologies: one is derived from analytic political philosophy; the other is an adaptation of Michael Freeden’s conceptual approach. The former views the division between Marxism and anarchism as the result of a clear distinction in universal principles, an account that is found to be flawed. Using the alternative conceptual approach, this paper argues that the schism that marked the rela…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ausonia Calabrese (T.F.G) - The return of the repressed]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-return-of-the-repressed?v=1729331147</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-return-of-the-repressed?v=1729331147"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ausonia Calabrese (T.F.G)
Title: The return of the repressed
Subtitle: (Anti)religious anarchism and Protestant presuppositions
Source: https://pleroma.noblogs.org/the-return-of-the-repressed-antireligious-anarchism-and-protestant-presuppositions/

 This article, foremost, is a response to a critique published on my work Against Individualism by a certain Aleph. In short, Aleph is not convinced of my account of the Creative Nothing and is concerned with a “Christian” basis for my mystical methods — among other minutiae. This, he feels, undermines my reading of the apophatic, unsayable Self beyond self, and problematizes my relationship to pagan authors like the divine Plotinus and Porphyry. I will explore all of these in-depth, as I am always one for meaningless chatter. However, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Katja Einsfeld - Anarcho-Communist Planning]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarcho-communist-planning?v=1729330873</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarcho-communist-planning?v=1729330873"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Katja Einsfeld
Title: Anarcho-Communist Planning
Date: 06/2024
Source: Retrieved on 2024-10-06 from https://transform-social.org/en/texts/anarcho_communist_planning/

Abstract
 In recent years, the discussion about economic concepts different from both capitalism and central planning has gotten more interest, new ideas emerged, and old ideas were rediscovered. This paper presents a modern version of the economic concept of anarcho-communist planning, originating from the late 19th century. The proposed idea is based on the needs of the people while respecting the planetary boundaries. It rejects ideas like markets, work remuneration, and money or other universal units of account. This paper first discusses the shortcomings of markets, central planning, and previous post-capitalist …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louve Rose - For a revolutionary queer movement.]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/louve-rose-for-a-revolutionary-queer-movement?v=1729330470</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/louve-rose-for-a-revolutionary-queer-movement?v=1729330470"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Louve Rose
Title: For a revolutionary queer movement.
Date: August 2023
Notes: Originally written for the second edition of Première Ligne magazine.
Source: https://pink-bloc.info/en/2023/10/30/pour-un-mouvement-queer-revolutionnaire/

Current context
 The current condition of queer communities is paradoxically one of the best and one of the worst we've seen in modern capitalist Western societies. Sixty years of continuous mobilization by the queer movement (and protoqueer before it, if we consider all the developments of the gay and lesbian movements) have led to the legalization and almost total emancipation of our communities within the bourgeois state legal system. We can now, as never before, exist openly within society, putting on our true faces. Yet material violence against…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Swann - Towards an anarchist cybernetics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/thomas-swann-towards-an-anarchist-cybernetics?v=1729329170</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/thomas-swann-towards-an-anarchist-cybernetics?v=1729329170"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Thomas Swann
Title: Towards an anarchist cybernetics
Subtitle: Stafford Beer, self-organisation and radical social movements
Date: 2018
Source: Retrieved on 2024-10-15 from [https://ephemerajournal.org/contribution/towards-anarchist-cybernetics-stafford-beer-self-organisation-and-radical-social]

abstract
 In the early 1960s, a number of anarchist writers showed an interest in cybernetics, in which they saw the tools for better articulating radical forms of self-organisation. Discussions on the connections between anarchism and cybernetics did not advance very far, however, and by the 1970s the topic seems to have fallen off the anarchist radar. With an increase in interest in cybernetics over the last few years, this paper picks up where these debates left off and highlights some …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Shaman-Poets’ Vision for a Better Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280619</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/americas-shaman-poets-vision-for-a-better-future.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author and Jungian analyst Steven Herrmann discusses the concept of “spiritual democracy” as explored in the writings of American poets like Walt Whitman, Herman Melville, and Emily Dickinson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Institute For The Study of Insurgent Warfare - On Deep Green Failures or The Problem of Inert Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/institute-for-the-study-of-insurgent-warfare-on-deep-green-failures-or-the-problem-of-inert-str?v=1729327419</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/institute-for-the-study-of-insurgent-warfare-on-deep-green-failures-or-the-problem-of-inert-str?v=1729327419"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T08:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Institute For The Study of Insurgent Warfare
Title: On Deep Green Failures or The Problem of Inert Strategy
Date: 2014
Notes: Published in Insurgencies: A Journal of Insurgent Strategy Vol. 1.
Source: Retrieved on 25th May 2021 from libgen.is

 “We tend to destroy our leaders with criticism, often personal and vicious.” 
 — Lierre Keith, Deep Green Resistence 
Looting the Corpses That Come Before You
 I’m not here to praise or condemn Caesar, but to make sure he stays buried. Often when a movement falls (and Deep Green Resistance is very much falling) there is a “nostalgic” tendency to attempt to exhume the corpse and at least loot it for a few precious baubles. Part of this necrophilia is the belief that to have persisted or to have attained some notability entails a certain degre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathways to sustainability (1)]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45658</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/19/pathways-to-sustainability-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Maria Alejandra and WEA Pedagogy Blog Setting the scene Economists and policymakers continue to dominate headlines with the conceptualization of “sustainability,” “sustainable investing,” and “sustainable finance,” along with their various worldwide geographical manifestations. The prevailing scenario, which is characterized by conflict, economic instability, and political disputes, is not favorable to incorporating sustainability into investment […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alejandra Madi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop Optimizing Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/stop-optimizing-everything/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/stop-optimizing-everything/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was listening to a podcast episode of the Tim Ferriss Show where he interviewed Derek Sivers. Sivers told this story about cycling along a beach route. Every time he did this route, he would go as fast as possible, pushing himself. He would always finish his ride in about forty-three minutes, red-faced and sweating, totally exhausted.
Then one day, he decided to take it easy. Instead of going all out, he relaxed and enjoyed the view along the way. When he got to the end of the ride, he checked his time, and it was forty-five minutes. Only two minutes slower than when he’d been pushing himself to the max. He couldn’t believe it. Two minutes slower, and he enjoyed the whole ride. He wasn’t tired or drenched in sweat.
For me this story is a perfect example of how we’re always trying to opti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is basically discontinuing Windows. What will happen, then?]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/microsoft-is-basically-discontinuing-windows-what-will-happen-then/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/microsoft-is-basically-discontinuing-windows-what-will-happen-then/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T03:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So the end of life for Windows 10 looms ahead of us, which is a problem because Windows 11 has two fundamental problems, as it currently stands:
First, it just won't run on the majority of hardware that currently runs Windows 10. This isn't just, like, ancient hardware; I have a desktop gaming PC that is perfectly fine to play current-gen AAA games on; it's what I played Cyberpunk 2077 on and that was totally okay. But somehow it doesn't meet Win11 requirements because of the CPU; it has a Ryzen 5 1600X in it, a CPU from 2017 that is apparently still actively being manufactured.
Moore's law has been dead for a while, so the long plateauing of, particularly, CPU power has meant that some of this hardware has a looong shelf life. I still haven't run into a game I want to play on PC that is c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wongarsu in "Jury awards American Airline $9.4M from website behind 'skiplagging' hack"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41884864</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41884864"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T01:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Skiplagging is not illegal, but airlines view it as a policy violation that is grounds for termination of a traveler’s entire itinerary since the airline can't sell the empty seat in the onward flight.
The poor airline, unable to sell an empty seat because ... checks notes ... the seat is already sold to someone, and that person decided not to show up. Truly the horror. Just think of all the revenue the airline lost because they couldn't charge more for a shorter flight and now have to fly the last leg with less weight
But it seems like the entire court case was mostly centered around the legality of the branding of the website. I guess overall the guy behind skiplagged will be happy to have gotten away with what amounts to 10% of revenue in exchange for a lot of publicity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wongarsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[wake up calls]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/wake-up-calls/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/wake-up-calls/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T23:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's 7 on Friday night. P's in town this weekend with her boyfriend. They invited me to dinner tonight, which I originally accepted and then canceled when I found out they were going at 9:30. Who meets for dinner at 9:30? Under normal circumstances I likely would have swallowed my objections and gone, but I've been burning the candle at both ends this week and I have to get up early tomorrow to catch a flight out of EWR.
Work was surprisingly busy today. My director (my manager's supervisor) flew in from London and asked to meet me in person, so I went into the office and took a call with him. It went okay. I felt a little nervous because my manager told me to lead the meeting minutes before it started, and afterwards she gave me some constructive criticism about how I could have better fa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Life So Far in Writing Tools (Partly, at Least)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280590</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/my-life-so-far-in-writing-tools-partly-at-least.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T21:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reference works I have known]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have a Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/you-have-a-choice/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/you-have-a-choice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T20:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I began reading Meditations for Mortals by Oliver Burkeman. I've been trying to distance myself from self-help/psychology/philosophy books, but I saw someone on reddit make an interesting post regarding some content in the book, so I decided to give it a read.

The book is designed so that you read one micro chapter a day for four weeks. Mr. Burkeman discusses a topic and gives you time to reflect on it. I think this is wise, since in so many situations with books offering advice/guidance, you are so overwhelmed with information that by the end of it you're lucky to walk away with one or two nuggets of wisdom.
I reached chapter three recently, and it stuck with me enough to want to write a bit about it. But before I do that, let's go back in time, sometime around 1995 in Orlando,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rsc in "Show HN: Go Plan9 Memo"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41882801</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41882801"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T19:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No. It's just Go assembly.
(It happens to be a Plan 9-derived syntax, but we call it Go assembly.)
See https://go.dev/doc/asm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280564</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T18:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Friday Charts: RCP chart; shows Big Mo shifting toward Trump; Covid charts show nothing but good news; Walz fabricator vanishes; Trump cancellations; Boeing waits on SEC approval for stock and bond offering; FAA opens new safety review ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US forms coalition over North Korea’s actions + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/us-forms-coalition-over-north-korea-s-actions-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/us-forms-coalition-over-north-korea-s-actions-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T16:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada's deficit tops $46.8 billion in new report; US warns about North Korea's military support for Russia; report urges Australia to rethink AUKUS submarine deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mountain Town Confronts an Unexpected Public Health Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280560</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/mountain-town-confronts-an-unexpected-public-health-catastrophe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T15:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Communities are still shaking off the shock of a storm they never thought could touch these mountains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're overcomplicating production]]></title>
        <id>https://paravoce.bearblog.dev/youre-overcomplicating-production/</id>
        <link href="https://paravoce.bearblog.dev/youre-overcomplicating-production/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You're going to have outages in production. They're inevitable. The question is how to best minimize outages, both their frequency and duration.
Common wisdom advocates for using managed k8s and databases, containerized services, horizontal scaling for redundancy, building images in CI/CD, and defining your infrastructure as code. This is Best Practice™, and no one was ever fired for doing that. In fact it's quite good for your resumé.
I will argue that such common wisdom is wrong. These tools are complex, and complex infrastructure is a wildly net-negative distraction to your business and inherently risky.
Over the past 10 years I've run services in production with millions of customers, exceeding 4-9's uptime. During that time I experimented with a wide variety of architectures, starting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jgrahamc in "Code that helped end Apartheid"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41879323</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41879323"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So when he DM’d me to say that he had “a hell of a story”—promising “one-time pads! 8-bit computers! Flight attendants smuggling floppies full of random numbers into South Africa!”—I responded.
Ha ha ha. Yes, that was literally my very short pitch to Steven about Tim Jenkin's story!
The actual DM: "I think this has the makings of a hell of a story: https://blog.jgc.org/2024/09/cracking-old-zip-file-to-help-o... If you want I can connect you with Tim Jenkin. One time pads! 8-bit computers! Flights attendants smuggling floppies full of random numbers into South Africa!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jgrahamc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deal with inflation?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45688</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/18/how-to-deal-with-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Europe (the Euro area, to be precise), both unemployment and inflation are down, according to Eurostat,. Which, again, shows that the Phillips curve, a crucial concept behind neoclassical macroeconomic thinking that assumes a more or less stable negative relation between unemployment and inflation (high unemployment will bring inflation down), is not the place to go […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280544</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T10:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As UK’s NHS Drowns in PFI Debt, Private Healthcare Providers Offer to Lend a Helping Hand (sarc)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280527</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/as-uks-nhs-drowns-in-pfi-debt-private-healthcare-providers-offer-to-lend-a-helping-hand-sarc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T10:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The scale of the expansion being considered would surpass moves made by the Blair government, which first introduced use of the private sector by the NHS."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Organized Labor Shames Its Traitors: The Story of the “Scab”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280553</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/how-organized-labor-shames-its-traitors-the-story-of-the-scab.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T10:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any labor action today will inevitably lead to someone getting called a scab, an insult used to smear people who cross picket lines, break up strikes or refuse to join a union.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by noirscape in "Why does everyone run ancient Postgres versions?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41877487</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41877487"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T08:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because the actual process of upgrading Postgres is terrible.
I say this as someone who absolutely loves using it, but the actual process of upgrading Postgres is something that takes significant downtime, is error-prone and you're often better off just dumping all the databases and reimporting them in a new folder. (A good idea in general since it'll vacuum and compact indexes as well if you do it, combining a few maintenance routines in your upgrade path.)
It requires having the previous version of Postgres installed, something which can mess with a number of distro policies (not to mention docker, which is the most popular way to deploy software that will typically rely on Postgres), and unlike most software with that issue, Postgres is software you want to be managed by your distro.
Therefore, most people only upgrade by necessity - when their distro forces the upgrade or the version they're using reaches EOL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noirscape</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pissing Everyone Off for 30 Damn Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338287</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/pissing-everyone-off-for-30-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:37:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that a little, rag-tag radical publication like CounterPunch could survive thirty long years. Yet, here we are, three decades in, and still at it.
We all have a story about how we landed on the CounterPunch homepage. Mine dates back to 1999, shortly after the WTO protests in Seattle. I was going to college in Oregon and hopped on a bus to join others in waging our disgust against the impacts of unfettered globalization. After five days, I returned to Portland, feeling invigorated. I could still taste the pepper spray and feel the vibrations of those rowdy streets. How do I make sense of what the hell I had just experienced? More
The post Pissing Everyone Off for 30 Damn Years appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Text Me You Haven’t Died’ – My Sister was the 166th Doctor to Be Murdered in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338283</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/text-me-you-havent-died-my-sister-was-the-166th-doctor-to-be-murdered-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Your lives will continue. With new events and new faces. They are the faces of your children, who will fill your homes with noise and laughter." 
These were the last words written by my sister in a text message to one of her daughters. 
Dr. Soma Baroud was murdered on October 9 when Israeli warplanes bombed a taxi that carried her and other tired Gazans somewhere near the Bani Suhaila roundabout near Khan Yunis, in the southern Gaza Strip.  More
The post ‘Text Me You Haven’t Died’ – My Sister was the 166th Doctor to Be Murdered in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Unbound: October in Gaza, One Year Later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338346</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/october-in-gaza-one-year-later/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A retaliatory military operation that many wizened pundits predicted would last no more than a month or so has now thundered on in ever-escalating episodes of violence and mass destruction for a year with no sign of relenting. What began as a war of vengeance has become a war of annihilation, not just of Hamas, but of Palestinian life and culture in Gaza and beyond. More
The post Israel Unbound: October in Gaza, One Year Later appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris: Speed Dating Howard Stern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338400</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/harris-speed-dating-howard-stern/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When did shock jock and satellite-radio wit Howard Stern turn into a cream puff and shill for Kamala Harris and her floundering campaign for the presidency? Is she really that far behind that she needed to play vaudeville, first The View and then The Howard Stern Show, presumably on the basis that a defanged Howard would lay off Californication questions about cocaine or encounters of a hot-tub kind. More
The post Harris: Speed Dating Howard Stern appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli General’s Plan in Gaza: Genocide by Starvation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338280</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/the-israeli-generals-plan-in-gaza-genocide-by-starvation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[George Orwell’s dystopian foresight could easily find new expressions in the ongoing Israeli wars of genocide in Gaza and Lebanon. Much like “war is peace,” the Biden administration and the European Union have contributed to creating phrases such as “aggression is self-defense,” “murder is collateral damage,” “safe areas are death traps,” and “humanitarian aid is  More
The post The Israeli General’s Plan in Gaza: Genocide by Starvation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the United States Election That Important?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338103</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/is-the-united-states-election-that-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is the United States election that important? “What kind of question is that?” most people would ask. The obvious answer is a resounding “Yes.” As an example: “So much hinges on this election,” American political commentator Joe Klein wrote in The New York Times in explaining why he is voting for Kamala Harris. His choice  More
The post Is the United States Election That Important? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Slippery Slope to Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337944</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/israels-slippery-slope-to-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Omar Bartov is a historian specializing in the history of genocides, particularly the Holocaust. He published a lengthy and complex article in the British newspaper The Guardian (with a circulation of 300,000 copies) on August 13, 2024, in which he acknowledged that Israeli military interventions in the Gaza Strip have all the appearances of a  More
The post Israel’s Slippery Slope to Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Howlett-Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dockworkers Could Be Striking, Come Inauguration Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338126</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/dockworkers-could-be-striking-come-inauguration-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So the dockworkers’ strike is off for now, with a promise that it could resume in January. Did union bureaucrats accept a 62 percent pay hike in return for ending their three-day, early October walkout as part of a deal to help the Harris presidential campaign? If so, you can hardly be surprised. They endorsed her, and most of labor, with the notable exception of Teamsters president Sean O’Brien, regards a possible Trump presidency with the alarm reserved for earthquakes or tornados. More
The post Dockworkers Could Be Striking, Come Inauguration Day appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Principles for the Coming Resistance to MAGA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338260</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/ten-draft-principles-for-the-coming-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The entire US system must be dismantled if burning children in a hospital is the lesser evil. – Hadi Nasrallah, October 15, 2024 Note to readers: The author is aware that the coming election’s outcome is uncertain and that Kamala Harris could squeak out a highly contested victory in a process that seems likely to  More
The post Ten Principles for the Coming Resistance to MAGA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cuba Under Intensified US Sanctions Confronts Its Greatest Challenge: the Continuity of Obama-Trump-Biden Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338342</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/cuba-under-intensified-us-sanctions-confronts-its-greatest-challenge-the-continuity-of-obama-trump-biden-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The majority of Cubans support Castro…every possible means should be undertaken promptly to weaken the economic life of Cuba…to decrease monetary and real wages, to bring about hunger, desperation and overthrow of government.” – Lester D. Mallory, US Deputy Assistant Secretary of State, 1960. Despite draconian coercive measures by the US – overwhelmingly condemned every  More
The post Cuba Under Intensified US Sanctions Confronts Its Greatest Challenge: the Continuity of Obama-Trump-Biden Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Corporate Vehicles Changing International Commerce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338428</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/the-corporate-vehicles-changing-international-commerce/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 17, 2024, thousands of pagers belonging to Hezbollah members simultaneously exploded across Lebanon, killing dozens and wounding thousands, including civilians. The pagers were licensed by Taiwanese company Gold Apollo from the manufacturer BAC Consulting, a Hungary-based company registered in 2022. BAC Consulting is suspected of being an Israeli front company, working alongside Israeli shell  More
The post The Corporate Vehicles Changing International Commerce appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaires Are Not Going to Save Us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338276</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/billionaires-are-not-going-to-save-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was William Shakespeare who, in Troilus and Cressida, wrote, “One touch of nature makes the whole world kin.” And yet, in the polarized news cycle since Hurricane Helene ravaged the southeastern United States and the hurricanes have kept coming, we’ve heard a tale not of shared humanity, but of ruin, discord, and political polarization. Hundreds are dead  More
The post Billionaires Are Not Going to Save Us appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Theoharis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s War on the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338265</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/israels-war-on-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each new week brings new calamities for people in the countries neighboring Israel, as its leaders try to bomb their way to the promised land of an ever-expanding Greater Israel. In Gaza, Israel appears to be launching its “Generals’ Plan” to drive the most devastated and traumatized 2.2 million people in the world into the  More
The post Israel’s War on the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Benjamin - Nicolas J. S. Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of Reunification?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338341</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/the-end-of-reunification/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dream of Korean reunification is now over 80 years old. This year, the notion that the two halves of the Korean peninsula could be stitched back together has become so feeble that it entered hospice. The children of this dream of reunification are responsible for putting it into the intensive care ward. The northern  More
The post The End of Reunification? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tipped Wage System Is Failing Us. Removing Taxes on Tips Won’t Save It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338128</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/the-tipped-wage-system-is-failing-us-removing-taxes-on-tips-wont-save-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both major presidential candidates have called for eliminating taxes on tips. But that won’t help most restaurant workers. What will? Replacing the subminimum wages that tipped workers make with one fair wage nationwide. The federal minimum wage for most workers is just $7.25. But for workers who get tips, employers are allowed to pay them  More
The post The Tipped Wage System Is Failing Us. Removing Taxes on Tips Won’t Save It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Schomburg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Fever: War Mongering on Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338429</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/nuclear-fever-war-mongering-on-iran/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent string of exaggerated military successes – or at least as they are understood to be – places Israel in a situation it has been previously used to: prowess in war.  Such prowess promises much: redrawing boundaries; overthrowing governments; destroying the capabilities of adversaries and enemies.  Nothing, in this equation, contemplates peace, let alone diplomatic resolution.  More
The post Nuclear Fever: War Mongering on Iran appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scapegoating Immigrants Hurts Everyone…But the Elites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338432</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/scapegoating-immigrants-hurts-everyone-but-the-elites/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans are counting on fears of immigrants to draw white conservatives to the polls. This calculation is dangerous — and it lets the real villains in our politics off the hook. There’s a direct line between Donald Trump’s 2015 declaration about Mexican “rapists” and his 2024 lie about Haitians eating pets. Trump’s running mate, Senator JD Vance (R-OH), has echoed the  More
The post Scapegoating Immigrants Hurts Everyone…But the Elites appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zelensky’s 5/8ths Victory Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338510</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/zelenskys-5-8ths-victory-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month de facto president of Ukraine, Volodymyr Zelensky, visited the White House to present his new Victory Plan to US president Joe Biden. Days before the meeting, Zelensky announced to the world he had a new comprehensive plan for Ukraine’s victory in its war with Russia but provided no details. Biden was the  More
The post Zelensky’s 5/8ths Victory Plan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Rasmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warped Government Priorities Make Climate Disasters Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338539</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/warped-government-priorities-make-climate-disasters-worse/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s hurricane season has been devastating. Hurricane Helene left a trail of wreckage across the Southeast and Appalachia, where over 230 people have died so far. Barely two weeks later, Milton slammed into Florida, killing dozens more, destroying homes, and leaving over a million people without power. Insurers are predicting that losses from Milton could reach $60  More
The post Warped Government Priorities Make Climate Disasters Worse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Basav Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sun King Playlists]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338503</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/sun-king-playlists/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:52:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“To faint was a fault past hope of pardon,” wrote the Duke of Saint-Simon in his Memoirs of Louis XIV, an insider’s account of battlefield debacles, antechamber intrigues and bedroom assignations during the reign of the Sun King. Yet the Duke recounts several fainting spells at court, including that of Madame de Montespan, the sovereign’s  More
The post Sun King Playlists appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swastikas at Trump’s Madison Square Garden Rally Stir Controversy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338115</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/swastikas-at-trumps-madison-square-garden-rally-stir-controversy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(NEW YORK, October 28, 2024) Controversy continues to swirl after the onstage display at Madison Square Garden last night, of a pair of 20-foot-high banners displaying black swastikas on a red field. They flanked Donald Trump’s podium and were brightly illuminated throughout the former president’s 80-minute address. Swastikas also appeared on a pair of cuffs  More
The post Swastikas at Trump’s Madison Square Garden Rally Stir Controversy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aid Restrictions Hold Americans Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338455</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/aid-restrictions-hold-americans-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I loved my childhood. My dad worked hard and had two jobs while my mom stayed home with my sister and me. We had a nice house and a middle-class lifestyle. I never even thought about poverty and struggle. But when my parents divorced, I suddenly had a very intimate relationship with poverty. My mom  More
The post Aid Restrictions Hold Americans Back appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brazil Jefferson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UNESCO’S Peace Vocation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/unescos-peace-vocation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War may sometimes be a necessary evil. But no matter how necessary, it is always an evil, never a good. We will not learn to live together in peace by killing each other’s children.” ― JIMMY CARTER The Nobel Peace Prize Lecture The UNESCO Constitution[1], adopted in London on 16 November 1945, places great importance on  More
The post UNESCO’S Peace Vocation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Search of an Honest Climate Campaigner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338356</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/in-search-of-an-honest-climate-campaigner/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As some of you are well aware, the Man was never really a paid professional activist. I did manage to hold down a few gigs with some large organizations for a short period of time. Mostly, it was because they were paying me to do something I was already doing, and when it more or  More
The post In Search of an Honest Climate Campaigner appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIKE ROSELLE</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[San Francisco Bay Blues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337959</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/san-francisco-bay-blues/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It wasn’t the sonorous saxophone melding into a lively piano solo that opens Miguel Zenón’s Golden City that began my most recent trip to San Francisco.  Instead, it was the mechanical female voice of a recording on the BART train telling riders what the train’s next stop was.  Although soothing, the voice on the train  More
The post San Francisco Bay Blues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinwar is Dead; We Must End Our Complicity in This Cruel and Illegal War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338522</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/sinwar-is-dead-we-must-end-our-complicity-in-this-cruel-and-illegal-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar, a war criminal who masterminded the brutal October 7th terrorist attack that killed 1,200 innocent people and took 250 hostages, is now dead. There is now no justification for Prime Minister Netanyahu and his extremist government to continue their all-out war against the Palestinian people, which has killed 42,000 Palestinians and  More
The post Sinwar is Dead; We Must End Our Complicity in This Cruel and Illegal War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernie Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Have All Good Socialists Gone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338271</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/where-have-all-good-socialists-gone/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What Small Numbers Can Accomplish In a system of winner-take-all (except in Maine and Nebraska) to decide the delegates for the electoral college, 270 of which is necessary to win the presidency, and in a tight race as it is, a small number of votes, this way or that way, can make a huge difference  More
The post Where Have All Good Socialists Gone? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>REZA FIYOUZAT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War’s Victims Speak the Deepest Truth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338274</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/wars-victims-speak-the-deepest-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The past carries unforgettable trauma and pain across the land and among generations of refugees; yet we choose to transform victimhood into agency. We want to be the authors of our future.” Let these words resonate. In a sense, they’re all we have — if we oppose war and envision a future that transcends it.  More
The post War’s Victims Speak the Deepest Truth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture of Cities: The Melding Dreams of Film]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338358</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/18/architecture-of-cities-the-melding-dreams-of-film/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Queen of the Night bloomed. It was akin to the queen bee mating naked amid a sanctuary of hives: So many dreams remain, if you wish: Godzilla comes to mind often: The dinosaur scoured the Tokyo metropolis: Horrified, the child’s eyes remained riveted to the screen: Laughter might seem insolent, but the story is true:  More
The post Architecture of Cities: The Melding Dreams of Film appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Schulman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lynn Stuart Parramore - ‘A Kaleidoscopic Sense of Possibility’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lynn-stuart-parramore-a-kaleidoscopic-sense-of-possibility?v=1729200367</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lynn-stuart-parramore-a-kaleidoscopic-sense-of-possibility?v=1729200367"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Lynn Stuart Parramore
Title: ‘A Kaleidoscopic Sense of Possibility’
Subtitle: Interview with David Graeber on Democracy in America
Date: April 24, 2013
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.alternet.org

Editor’s note: We think we know what democracy is. But do we? Anthropologist David Graeber burst into national consciousness in 2011 with the Occupy movement he helped to spark. The author of Debt: The First 5,000 Years has written a daring book about democracy in America: its origins, its opponents, and its chances of happening today given the stranglehold of the wealthy on our economic and political systems. Part reflection on Occupy Wall Street, the first major stirring of democratic spirit in the living memory of many, and part journey through the questions and tensio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachael Kiddey - An Interview with David Graeber]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rachael-kiddey-an-interview-with-david-graeber?v=1729200189</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rachael-kiddey-an-interview-with-david-graeber?v=1729200189"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rachael Kiddey
Title: An Interview with David Graeber
Date: 2016
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.isrf.org

This interview between Rachael Kiddey and David Graeber was conducted in 2016 and was originally published in issue X of the ISRF Bulletin. We republish it here in David’s memory.
RACHAEL KIDDEY: Each year, the ISRF team up with a different university to co-produce a workshop. This year we’re working with Professor Charles Stewart from UCL. The theme of the workshop is ‘Discovery & Recognition’. That is, that as social scientists our work constantly surprises us. May I ask for your thoughts on the theme?
 DAVID GRAEBER: Yes. Probably my favourite line in my book Fragments of an Anarchist Anthropology—the book that has got me into so much trouble with anthropolo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Graeber, Aro Velmet - Anarchism, work and bureaucracy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-aro-velmet-anarchism-work-and-bureaucracy?v=1729200015</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-aro-velmet-anarchism-work-and-bureaucracy?v=1729200015"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Graeber, Aro Velmet
Title: Anarchism, work and bureaucracy
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: 9 May 2017
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.eurozine.com

 ‘On a deep, cultural level, people actually believe that if you don’t do something that at least mildly frustrates you, then your work is not valuable.’ Anthropologist, activist and bestselling anarchist David Graeber on the police state, bullshit jobs and why people need no telling that capitalism is bad. 
Aro Velmet: When you visited Estonia in 2003 and spoke about the Movement for Global Justice, it was a pretty bleak time for progressives. Only a couple of years had passed since 9/11, the Iraq War was gearing up, and the protests seemed to be failing. But one of the interesting things you noted…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Whelan - Anthropologist David Graeber Explains Why Dead-End Jobs Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-whelan-anthropologist-david-graeber-explains-why-dead-end-jobs-exist?v=1729199825</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-whelan-anthropologist-david-graeber-explains-why-dead-end-jobs-exist?v=1729199825"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Whelan
Title: Anthropologist David Graeber Explains Why Dead-End Jobs Exist
Date: February 10, 2015
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.vice.com

 If you’ve ever spent 15 minutes listening to the same U2 song while on hold to your mobile-phone provider because the 27 people you’ve spoken to so far have no idea who the hell you are, you’ll know all about the throb in the ass that is bureaucracy. Our lives fundamentally suck because of it. 
 David Graeber—the anthropologist who wrote the international best seller Debt: The First 5,000 years (a book Russell Brand says will “make you cleverer”)—argues in his new book, The Utopia of Rules, that we’re trapped in jobs created by the ruling classes to feed into their debt-extraction schemes. In other words, we’re working …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austin D Munday - Basic Income & Meaningless Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/austin-d-munday-basic-income-meaningless-jobs-1?v=1729199627</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/austin-d-munday-basic-income-meaningless-jobs-1?v=1729199627"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Austin D Munday
Title: Basic Income & Meaningless Jobs
Subtitle: David Graeber interview & Stenography
Date: February 1, 2016
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from medium.com

 Recently, Switzerland’s government has agreed to vote on implementing a Basic Income. If it passes, then Switzerland will be one of the first countries to introduce a Basic Income. 
 The Basic Income theory or system has been floating around in many different intellectual circles. Less than a week ago Sam Altman of Y-Combinator wrote an essay on it. And there is a whole subreddit devoted to it. 
 I’m not surprised by its popularity. Most people could really use some extra cash each month, ipso facto a lot of people want the Basic Income. 
 Anyways, I stenographed a conversation David Graeber had a whil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Jones - Bookforum talks with David Graeber]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rachel-jones-bookforum-talks-with-david-graeber?v=1729199328</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rachel-jones-bookforum-talks-with-david-graeber?v=1729199328"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rachel Jones
Title: Bookforum talks with David Graeber
Date: March 19, 2012
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.bookforum.com

David Graeber is an anthropologist, anarchist, the author of Debt: the First 5,000 Years, a professor at Goldsmith’s, University of London, and one of the organizers of Occupy Wall Street, which is the subject of his forthcoming book. Bookforum spoke with the writer in Los Angeles about the future of anthropology, ecstatic moments in activism, and the problem of political imagination.
Bookforum: You’re an anthropologist who has written a book that combines history, economics, and philosophy. What drew you to anthropology as a discipline? 
David Graeber: I got involved in anthropology largely because I like to think of it as the intellectual equi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Future - Bullshit jobs and the yoke of managerial feudalism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/open-future-bullshit-jobs-and-the-yoke-of-managerial-feudalism?v=1729199100</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/open-future-bullshit-jobs-and-the-yoke-of-managerial-feudalism?v=1729199100"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Open Future
Title: Bullshit jobs and the yoke of managerial feudalism
Date: June 29, 2018
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.economist.com

Not since Dilbert has truth been spoken to power in soulless work settings. But the cartoon character’s successor may be David Graeber. In 2013 he achieved viral fame with cubicle zombies everywhere after he published a short essay on the prevalence of work that had no social or economic reason to exist, which he called “bullshit jobs”. The wide attention seemed to confirm his thesis.
Mr Graeber, an anthropologist at the London School of Economics, has expanded on the ideas in a recent book. He responded to five questions from The Economist’s Open Future initiative. He rails against “feudal retinues of basically useless flunkies.” …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book buyers go indie as they skip social media, algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8694</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/book-buyers-indie-skip-social-media-algorithms/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T21:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sarah Manavis, writing for The Guardian: A survey commissioned by the Booksellers Association ahead of Bookshop Day tomorrow has found that gen Z and millennials are more likely to buy a book based on a bookseller’s recommendation — in person, in a bookshop — than older age groups: 49% and 56% respectively, compared with 37% […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - Anarchism in the Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-anarchism-in-the-mainstream?v=1729191191</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-anarchism-in-the-mainstream?v=1729191191"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: Anarchism in the Mainstream
Date: 17 October 2024
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from organisemagazine.org.uk

 In March 2020, when the virus raged across the globe but before we in the UK realised how serious and tragically lethal it would become or how much of a long-term problem it would be, Freedom Press published its first Covid-related update on its news site. Titled Covid Mutual Aid Groups: A List, the text came out ten days before the first UK lockdown and stated: 
 “As the global Covid-19 pandemic is upon us, a number of mutual aid groups have started forming across the country. (...) It is estimated that 2–3 people out of a hundred [infected by Covid] will die. We must do everything we can to prevent this from happening. (...) The Tory government…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[meaning-making]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/meaning-making/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/meaning-making/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm sitting on the couch with my laptop on my thighs.
Typing, thinking.
Gilmore Girls is playing in the background.
Thinking a lot about Meaning-Making. "Doing your hearts work".
Scrolling on YT I see a plethora of vids with titles such as: I quit my job and became a full-time artist. Really? REALLY? I want to gouge my eyes out. I don't want to read/see this kind of entrepreneurship-fetish anymore. Strike this from my algorithm.
Did i really spring into existence just to make money?
SKETCHBOOK PEEK:

the self: a study

starry night friends
READING:
A few years ago i started reading Saga, the comic written by  Brian K. Vaughan and illustrated by the talented Fiona Staples. Not quite sure why I stopped reading it but decided to pick it up again. I bought the box set Vol 1-9! And it arrived today so i'm v excited to jump back into this world.

Saga Vol. 1
WATCHING:
Only Murders in the Building. I adore this show and so glad it's back on. Can I please live in a fancy building like this and befriend a couple of peculiar yet distinguished fellows, but instead of solving murders, we just make zines and talk books?
WEB HEARTS 🧹 WEB FINDS:
On work and capitalism: how to escape the tyranny of work under capitalism.
MUCH MUSIC Stamps!
Eden Clifton's pottery is adorable.
I need this Snoopy sweatshirt in my life. Idk, but lately, I've been nostalgic for cutesy childhood things for comfort.
Been enjoying reading  Morning Music these days. I like their concept of sharing what they're listening to over morning coffee.
These tiny handmade dolls by myrtlemakes are so precious! I'm inspired to make little things like this. New hobby, perhaps?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Kenyan Uprising]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Kenyan-Uprising</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Kenyan-Uprising"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than two months after its government's controversial Finance Bill 2024 sparked widespread unrest, the flame of resistance remains bright across Kenya. The youth-led struggle—largely forged on social media platforms like X (formerly Twitter), TikTok, and WhatsApp by Generation-Z Kenyans—has ignited years of smoldering frustration into fresh demands for accountable governance, dignity, and justice. Following the government's cancellation of the bill, the rallying call shifted from (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Africa, 
Kenya, 
Colonialism, 
Neo-liberalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zachary J. Patterson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuart Jeffries - David Graeber interview: ‘So many people spend their working lives doing jobs they think are unnecessary’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/stuart-jeffries-david-graeber-interview-so-many-people-spend-their-working-lives-doing-jobs-the?v=1729189350</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/stuart-jeffries-david-graeber-interview-so-many-people-spend-their-working-lives-doing-jobs-the?v=1729189350"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:22:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Stuart Jeffries
Title: David Graeber interview: ‘So many people spend their working lives doing jobs they think are unnecessary’
Subtitle: The anarchist author, coiner of the phrase ‘We are the 99%’, talks to Stuart Jeffries about ‘bullshit jobs’, our rule-bound lives and the importance of play
Date: 21 March 2015
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.theguardian.com

A few years ago David Graeber’s mother had a series of strokes. Social workers advised him that, in order to pay for the home care she needed, he should apply for Medicaid, the US government health insurance programme for people on low incomes. So he did, only to be sucked into a vortex of form filling and humiliation familiar to anyone who’s ever been embroiled in bureaucratic procedures. 
 At one point, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Frank - David Graeber is Gone: Revisiting His Wrongful Termination from Yale]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/joshua-frank-david-graeber-is-gone-revisiting-his-wrongful-termination-from-yale?v=1729189200</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/joshua-frank-david-graeber-is-gone-revisiting-his-wrongful-termination-from-yale?v=1729189200"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Joshua Frank
Title: David Graeber is Gone: Revisiting His Wrongful Termination from Yale
Date: September 4, 2020
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from www.counterpunch.org

I am so very sad to hear that David Graeber died yesterday in Italy at the age of 59. David was not only brilliant, but he was genuine, accessible, and passionate. What a huge, immeasurable loss, could 2020 be any worse? Here is an interview I did with David in 2005 when he was wrongfully fired from his post at Yale. RIP friend. The world, and our movement, was so much better off with you in it. Your fighting spirit will live on. – JF
 David Graeber, PhD, is an Assistant Professor of Anthropology at Yale University, and the author of Toward an Anthropological Theory of Value: The False Coin of Our Own Drea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Lydon - David Graeber On Jeremy Corbyn, ‘The Most Unlikely Leader Ever’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christopher-lydon-david-graeber-on-jeremy-corbyn-the-most-unlikely-leader-ever?v=1729188952</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christopher-lydon-david-graeber-on-jeremy-corbyn-the-most-unlikely-leader-ever?v=1729188952"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christopher Lydon
Title: David Graeber On Jeremy Corbyn, ‘The Most Unlikely Leader Ever’
Subtitle: In Conversation with the London-Based Writer and Anthropologist
Date: June 20, 2017
Source: Retrieved on 17th October 2024 from lithub.com

London-based anthropologist David Graeber talks to Christopher Lydon about the recent UK elections and potential change to come. This interview originally appeared at Radio Open Source.
 David Graeber emerged as something of a cult writer behind the Occupy movement of six years ago. He’s a Yale-trained cultural anthropologist, meaning in his case, he’s a tracker of the invisible stitching around matters of debt and wealth from ancient times. He has prophesied at different times a standard 15-hour work week and the dissolution of the US empire. In …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280517</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T18:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Democrat angst; Musk PA events for Trump could break the law; Boeing strike: Wall Street, WSJ, maybe DOD, rush to Boeing management's assistance; Reader query: AI poisoner sought for photographs ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by conesus in "Using Cloudflare on your website could be blocking RSS users"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41871474</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41871474"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T17:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I run NewsBlur[0] and I’ve been battling this issue of NewsBlur fetching 403s across the web for months now. My users are revolting and asking for refunds. I’ve tried emailing dozens of site owners and publishers and only two of them have done the work of whitelisting their RSS feed. It’s maddening and is having a real negative effect on NewsBlur.
NewsBlur is an open-source RSS news reader (full source available at [1]), something we should all agree is necessary to support the open web! But Cloudflare blocking all of my feed fetchers is bizarre behavior. And we’re on the verified bots list for years, but it hasn’t made a difference.
Let me know what I can do. NewsBlur publishes a list of IPs that it uses for feed fetching that I've shared with Cloudflare but it hasn't made a difference.
I'm hoping Cloudflare uses the IP address list that I publish and adds them to their allowlist so NewsBlur can keep fetching (and archiving) millions of feeds.
[0]: https://newsblur.com
[1]: https://github.com/samuelclay/NewsBlur]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>conesus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending October 13, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241017</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241017"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryandrake in "Adobe's new image rotation tool is one of the most impressive AI tools seen"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41870217</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41870217"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm making some big assumptions about Adobe's product ideation process, but: This seems like the "right" way to approach developing AI products: Find a user need that can't easily be solved with traditional methods and algorithms, decide that AI is appropriate for that thing, and then build an AI system to solve it.
Rather than what many BigTech companies are currently doing: "Wall Street says we need to 'Use AI Somehow'. Let's invest in AI and Find Things To Do with AI. Later, we'll worry about somehow matching these things with user needs."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryandrake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by achow in "Adobe's new image rotation tool is one of the most impressive AI tools seen"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41870168</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41870168"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The source (Adobe MAX) 'demoes' full range of incredible scenarios..
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gfct0aH2COw]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memories outlast pictures.]]></title>
        <id>https://whoknows.bearblog.dev/memories-outlast-pictures/</id>
        <link href="https://whoknows.bearblog.dev/memories-outlast-pictures/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:02:31.770Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pictures sit in folders on my device for years. But whenever I see something similar, the memories come rushing back. I deleted those pictures, but the memories still stick with me forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking Reserve Ampleness in Real Time Using Reserve Demand Elasticity]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32246</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/tracking-reserve-ampleness-in-real-time-using-reserve-demand-elasticity/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As central banks shrink their balance sheets to restore price stability and phase out expansionary programs, gauging the ampleness of reserves has become a central topic to policymakers and academics alike. The reason is that the ampleness of reserves informs when to slow and then stop quantitative tightening (QT). The Federal Reserve, for example, implements monetary policy in a regime of ample reserves, whereby the quantity of reserves in the banking system needs to be large enough such that everyday changes in reserves do not cause large variations in short-term rates. The goal is therefore to implement QT while ensuring that reserves remain sufficiently ample. In this post, we review how to gauge the ampleness of reserves using the new Reserve Demand Elasticity (RDE) measure, which will be published monthly on the public website of the Federal Reserve Bank of New York as a standalone product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Domenico Giannone, Gabriele La Spada, and John C. Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The story of web framework Hono, from the creator of Hono]]></title>
        <id>2P9zNPNEmMlhOCUA8XM37a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-story-of-web-framework-hono-from-the-creator-of-hono"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hono is a web framework that is fast, lightweight, and built using the Web Standards API. Hear the story of Hono by the creator of Hono.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yusuke Wada</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doing the Best We Can]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/doing-the-best-we-can/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/doing-the-best-we-can/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One piece of pop psychology that actually seems to be true is the premise that at any given time we are all doing the best we can. Football coaches and motivational speakers may beg to differ, but they have a vested interest in making people think that they can always just try harder to achieve success by whatever definition is popular that day. I don't buy it. I believe that people want to succeed. They want to be good parents, good employees, good spouses. Hell, they just want to be good. In the real world though we are faced with all kinds of mundane challenges, from differing energy levels, differing states of mental clarity and motivational levels that rise and fall on a sea of different inputs.
I'm not advocating using this sentiment as a cop out for slacking. I'm advocating it as an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Disruptive Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-disruptive-elements?v=1729159011</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-disruptive-elements?v=1729159011"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Disruptive Elements
Subtitle: The Extremes of French Anarchism
Date: 2014
Notes: A dense compendium of old and brand-new translations of a dizzying array of names from the individualist anarchist tendency, mostly from early 20th Century France. New translations from Wolfi Landstreicher, Shawn Wilbur, and Vincent Stone. Anyone who is interested in this tendency, fans of My Own, Enemies of Society, Stirner’s works, etc., will find much to enjoy and fodder for future research in this book.
Source: <opendistro.net/pdf-library/disruptive-elements>

If Pierre Chardon overflowed with ardor, enthusiasm, activity, he was intransigent. Verbosity inspired pity in him; the verbosity of rhetoricians as well as that of revolutionaries. He wanted to “practice” in the field …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by amatecha in "Using Cloudflare on your website could be blocking RSS users"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41867018</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41867018"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I get blocked from websites with some regularity, running Firefox with strict privacy settings, "resist fingerprinting" etc. on OpenBSD.  They just give a 403 Forbidden with no explanation, but it's only ever on sites fronted by CloudFlare.  Good times.  Seems legit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>amatecha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 economic sciences laureates]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45678</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/17/the-2024-economic-sciences-laureates/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The Sveriges Riksbank Prize in Economic Sciences in Memory of Alfred Nobel 2024 is awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson “for studies of how institutions are formed and affect prosperity.”  Daron Acemoglu and James Robinson’s work, particularly in Why Nations Fail (2012), is widely recognized within new institutional economics for its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[man! i feel like a woman!]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/man-i-feel-like-a-woman/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/man-i-feel-like-a-woman/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T02:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just got home from class. I didn't have a particularly good start to the day—it was kinda straight out of a sitcom, now that I think about it. I woke up about 40 minutes before I was supposed to be in class because I either slept through my alarm or it didn't ring at all. I got there 20 minutes late, but miraculously, it turned out my professor had sent a message saying we'd be starting 30 minutes late and I just didn't see it while I was rushing to get ready.
I couldn't decide what to wear in such a short amount of time, so I ended up putting on some rarely-worn jeans and one of my mom's old sweaters. The color is a bit too cool-toned for my skin, but I wore it anyway. No makeup or hair styling, either. I felt so...not me, but time was ticking and I didn't know we were starting late, so I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pfooti in "Amazon reveals first color Kindle, new Kindle Scribe, and more"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41864842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41864842"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T23:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a pretty old paperwhite. When it started deleting books i had side-loaded via calibre, I decided to get a kobo. I have a libra color, and I have to say: price notwithstanding, it's a great device. I don't have a lot of experience with more recent devices, but compared to my 2nd gen paperwhite, it is _amazing_.
Color is good enough to read comic books on it, the google drive integration means it's not too hard to get my CBR/CBZ files on directly. The annotation / notetaking featureas are nice (I haven't leaned into them yet, but they work well even on the small screen size), plus all the regular stuff with normal book reading. Also, since it's kobo/rakuten, the libby integration is better (search and select library books right from the device).
The actual reading app is maybe 90% as good as reading on the kindle (or a more specialized reader like perfectviewer on android). There's some annoyingly fiddly features- font size is kind of weirdly variable, when going through CBR files there's no "read next in the folder" gesture nor is there a "this is read/unread" state in the google drive ui, so you always have to remember which book you are finishing when opening the next in the series.
I tried out one of those boox readers with the android apps, which would be even better software-wise, but the boox hardware seems like garbage (for an N=1 at least). My display came with several rows of stuck pixels, and apparently it's a good thing that I ordered from amazon instead of the boox store, because the reviews indicate getting an RMA from boox directly is a pain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pfooti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reduce bad screen time, while needing good screen time?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8691</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/how-reduce-bad-screen-time-while-needing-good-screen-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Grace Descourouez, writing for Stanford Lifestyle Medicine: Additional studies found that adults who engage in excessive screen time or have a diagnosed smartphone addiction had lower gray matter volume. Gray matter is brain tissue essential for daily human functioning and is responsible for everything from movement to memory to emotions. Gray matter volume naturally […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexandrB in "AI PCs Aren't Good at AI: The CPU Beats the NPU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863552</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863552"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Also, people often mistake the reason for an NPU is "speed". That's not correct. The whole point of the NPU is rather to focus on low power consumption.
I have a sneaking suspicion that the real real reason for an NPU is marketing. "Oh look, NVDA is worth $3.3T - let's make sure we stick some AI stuff in our products too."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexandrB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives and progressives have different brain structures]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8687</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/conservatives-progressives-different-brain-structures/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to political leanings, I’m probably centre/left. But I have a number of family and acquaintances who definitely lean more to the right. Of course, everyone is different, but certain of the mannerisms of the more conservative people I know are particularly distinct. To me, these seemed to go beyond regular personal preference. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by isusmelj in "AI PCs Aren't Good at AI: The CPU Beats the NPU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863460</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863460"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think the results show that just in general the compute is not used well. That the CPU took 8.4ms and GPU took 3.2ms shows a very small gap. I'd expect more like 10x - 20x difference here.
I'd assume that the onnxruntime might be the issue. I think some hardware vendors just release the compute units without shipping proper support yet. Let's see how fast that will change.
Also, people often mistake the reason for an NPU is "speed". That's not correct. The whole point of the NPU is rather to focus on low power consumption. To focus on speed you'd need to get rid of the memory bottleneck. Then you end up designing your own ASIC with it's own memory. The NPUs we see in most devices are part of the SoC around the CPU to offload AI computations.
It would be interesting to run this benchmark in a infinite loop for the three devices (CPU, NPU, GPU) and measure power consumption.
I'd expect the NPU to be lowest and also best in terms of "ops/watt"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>isusmelj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating multi-AZ high availability for WebLogic administration server with DNS: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>4b7294a6fcaa6819d859ea467faf2491ebb12ac2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/automating-multi-az-high-availability-for-weblogic-administration-server-with-dns-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, we used a floating virtual IP (VIP) to achieve hands-off high availability (HA) of WebLogic Admin Server. In Part 2, we’ll achieve an arguably superior solution using Domain Name System (DNS) resolution. Using a DNS to resolve the address for WebLogic admin server Let’s look at the reference WebLogic […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Geddes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS optimized Amazon Linux 2023 accelerated AMIs now available]]></title>
        <id>593079c1e25d7535b97de1bcd70da92cb64657a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-optimized-amazon-linux-2023-accelerated-amis-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Earlier this year we announced support for Amazon EKS optimized AL2023 AMIs that provided many enhancements in terms of security and performance. Amazon Linux 2023 (AL2023) is the next generation of Amazon Linux from Amazon Web Services (AWS) and is designed to provide a secure, stable, and high-performance environment to develop and run your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Manuel_D in "Reflections on Palantir"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861649</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861649"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I interned at Palantir (summer 2014) their business was mostly in data ingestion, visualization, and correlation.
A typical workflow for a Palantir customer was that Palantir would come in and dump a ton of data out of old crufty databases and into Palantir's datastore. Then, they'd establish connections between that data. This is all sounds kind of hand-wavy, but the gist of it is that a lot of government agencies have data that lives in separate databases and they can't easily correlate data between those two databases. Once the data was in Palantir's system, they could do queries against all their data, and make connections and correlations that they wouldn't otherwise be able to find when the data was previously siloed.
One of the sample use cases was identifying people filling prescriptions for schedule II drugs multiple times on the same day, and correlating that with pharmacies run by people connected to known drug traffickers. Previously, this was hard to do because the database of prescription purchases was disconnected from the database of drug convictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manuel_D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling a Large Language Model with NVIDIA NIM on Amazon EKS with Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>959b0cd8030d1d8de276b6f0cd400ca1059430a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/scaling-a-large-language-model-with-nvidia-nim-on-amazon-eks-with-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations are building artificial intelligence (AI) applications using Large Language Models (LLMs) to deliver new experiences to their customers, from content creation to customer service and data analysis. However, the substantial size and intensive computational requirements of these models may have challenges in configuring, deploying, and scaling them effectively on graphic processing units (GPUs). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shawn Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Calavar in "Winamp deletes entire GitHub source code repo after a rocky few weeks"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861254</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861254"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've lost a lot with the deletion of this repo. Not the code - that's already out in the ether - but the absurdist comedy of the issues, pull requests, and commit history of trying to piecemeal delete third party non-FOSS software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Calavar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance release control with AWS CodePipeline stage-level conditions]]></title>
        <id>65f440ccd69151ae494d678b6627abe59b90c9e0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/enhance-release-control-with-aws-codepipeline-stage-level-conditions/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an established practice for development teams to build deployment pipelines, with services such as AWS CodePipeline, to increase the quality of application and infrastructure releases through reliable, repeatable and consistent automation. Automating the deployment process helps build quality into our products by introducing continuous integration to build and test code, however enterprises may sometimes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Bachman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by justinpombrio in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861129</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861129"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsubscribe links are a fantastic regulation, but there is a workaround. I must have received at least a dozen emails from Brown after graduating despite unsubscribing to every email they sent.
The trouble is they're endlessly creative about the lists they put you on. I'd get one email from "Alumni Connections" and then another from "Faculty Spotlight" and then another from "Global Outreach" and then another from "Event Invitations, 2023 series". I'm making those names up because I forget exactly what they were called, but you get the idea. I hope this was in violation of the regulation: surely you can't invent a new mailing list that didn't used to exist, add me to it, and require me to unsubscribe from it individually.
They finally stopped after I sent them an angry email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinpombrio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Uehreka in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41860626</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41860626"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people try and say that regulating stuff like this is impossible, I often think about how unreasonably great the regulations around “Unsubscribe” links in emails are.
There really seems to be no loophole or workaround despite there being huge incentive for there to be one. Every time I click an “Unsubscribe” link in an email (it seems like they’re forced to say “Unsubscribe” and not use weasel words to hide the link) I’m either immediately unsubscribed from the person who sent me the email, or I’m taken to a page which seemingly MUST have a “remove me from all emails” option.
The level of compliance (and they can’t even do malicious compliance!) with this is absurd. If these new rules work anything like that, they’ll be awesome. Clearly regulating behavior like this is indeed possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uehreka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ajkjk in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41859541</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41859541"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are so many things like this that have needed fixing for such a long time. The fact that something is happening, even slowly, is so heartening.
If your reaction is wondering if this is legal then you should be interested in the passing of new laws that make it unequivocally legal. Society should be able to govern itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ajkjk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Bradshaw - An Interview With David Graeber: Debt’s History, Implications, and Critical Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alex-bradshaw-an-interview-with-david-graeber-debt-s-history-implications-and-critical-perspect?v=1729080706</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alex-bradshaw-an-interview-with-david-graeber-debt-s-history-implications-and-critical-perspect?v=1729080706"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:11:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alex Bradshaw
Title: An Interview With David Graeber: Debt’s History, Implications, and Critical Perspective
Date: August 4, 2011
Source: Retrieved on 16th October 2024 from imaginenoborders.org

 David Graeber has spent the last decade challenging the line drawn between scholar and activist. While many academics fancy themselves “radicals,” the anthropologist professor has been an active participant in anarchist and anti-authoritarian groups and organizing. Graeber has used his skill-set as an anthropologist to compile ethnographic data—far away from the classroom and campus, to be sure—regarding the contemporary anarchist movement in North America; the results were published in 2009 as Direct Action: An Ethnography. David Graeber is the author of several books, including Fragment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Graeber - Fancy Forms of Paperwork and the Logic of Financial Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-fancy-forms-of-paperwork-and-the-logic-of-financial-violence?v=1729080467</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-fancy-forms-of-paperwork-and-the-logic-of-financial-violence?v=1729080467"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Graeber
Title: Fancy Forms of Paperwork and the Logic of Financial Violence
Date: September 21, 2016
Notes: Published in ROAR issue #3.
Source: Retrieved on 16th October 2024 from roarmag.org

 David Graeber is one of the world’s leading anthropologists and a well-known activist who played an important role in the early days of Occupy Wall Street in New York. In this wide-ranging interview for ROAR’s third issue, he speaks about the unexpected history of inequality, the role of debt in contemporary capitalism, the nature of money as a social relation, the violent and self-destructive logic of financialization, the class power of the 1 percent, and the challenges of building a radical-democratic movement against the rule of finance. 
ROAR: It’s been five years since thousands …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hannah Chadeayne Appel - Finance Is Just Another Word for Other People’s Debts]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hannah-chadeayne-appel-finance-is-just-another-word-for-other-people-s-debts?v=1729080084</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hannah-chadeayne-appel-finance-is-just-another-word-for-other-people-s-debts?v=1729080084"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hannah Chadeayne Appel
Title: Finance Is Just Another Word for Other People’s Debts
Subtitle: An Interview with David Graeber
Date: 2014
Notes: Published in Radical History Review Issue 118; doi:10.1215/01636545-2350939.
Source: Retrieved on 16th October 2024 from davidgraeber.org

 Odd things happened in fall 2011 as Occupy Wall Street began to inhabit down- town Manhattan. People rode the subway carrying signs that touted the merits of the Glass-Steagall Act; they started sidewalk conversations about corporate person-hood and about the social purpose of derivatives. Legislation, legal precedent, and financial products that had once been obscure emerged in public in new ways. 
 In the months after city officials forcibly evicted occupiers from Liberty Square (née Zuccotti Park), t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Well-Architected CDK Resources with Solutions Constructs Factories]]></title>
        <id>7008c6ada575bca57e3ce795352aa4475347ca7d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/instant-well-architected-cdk-resources-with-solutions-constructs-factories/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For several years, AWS Solutions Constructs have helped thousands of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) users accelerate their creation of well-architected workloads by providing small, composable patterns linking two or more AWS services, such as an Amazon S3 bucket triggering an AWS Lambda function. Over this time, customers with use cases that don’t match an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Biff Gaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways to optimize code with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>b9326e05e2ea846501a662f4c405f59150fe3959</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-ways-to-optimize-code-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical improvement and optimization of software quality requires expert-level knowledge across various subjects. As such, in this blog we shall look at how Amazon Q Developer can help improve your development team productivity and application stability by enabling automation around code optimization by improving your code’s quality, performance, application infrastructure specifications. The blog will also look […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karthik Chemudupati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code security scanning with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>6d44f9c81cc19acd510afee10e3ea6effb8cc074</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/code-security-scanning-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A primary objective of software developers is to develop products that uphold the highest standards of data privacy and security, fostering trust and confidence among their users and customers. Developers seek to secure their software by identifying and mitigating security vulnerabilities in their codebase, thereby enhancing its resilience against cyber threats. Amazon Q Developer, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surabhi Tandon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs Are Not Commodities]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/blogs-are-not-commodities/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/blogs-are-not-commodities/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somehow, when I first investigated starting a blog, I managed to avoid the many websites devoted to creating a money-making machine USING THESE 10 SIMPLE TRICKS!!! The blogs I was familiar with weren't covered in ads, and I didn't have to pay to read them. There was an occasional invitation to buy the writer a coffee, but nothing high-pressure or gross.
A couple of weeks ago, Keenan, the creator of A Very Good Blog, wrote a long, heartfelt post about his lifelong relationship with his much-loved cousin and how the American political divide affected their relationship. It's the kind of work that deserves to be included in an anthology and everyone's Best of 2024 collections. It wasn't surrounded by banner advertisements or cut off in the middle with a place for paying customers to log in. N…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milenko Srećković - Imagination – the Solution for Society’s Problems]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/milenko-sreckovic-imagination-the-solution-for-society-s-problems?v=1729075005</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/milenko-sreckovic-imagination-the-solution-for-society-s-problems?v=1729075005"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Milenko Srećković
Title: Imagination – the Solution for Society’s Problems
Subtitle: Interview: David Graeber, anthropologist and anarchist
Notes: Interview was originally published in Serbian language in the Serbian Daily ”Politika”.
Source: Retrieved on 16th October 2024 from milenkosreckovic.com

According to the testimony of his older colleagues, David Graeber is ”one of the best anthropologists of his generation”. By political conviction, he is an anarchist that advocates real, direct democracy, and is widely regarded for his contribution to the Occupy Wall Street movement especially in the early days of its creation when the organizational structure was decided; Graeber worked in the favor of more horizontal movement that would break with the tradition of hierarchical way of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ellen Evans & Jon Moses - Interview with David Graeber]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ellen-evans-jon-moses-interview-with-david-graeber?v=1729074754</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ellen-evans-jon-moses-interview-with-david-graeber?v=1729074754"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ellen Evans & Jon Moses
Title: Interview with David Graeber
Date: December 2011
Source: Retrieved on 16th October 2024 from www.thewhitereview.org

 Six months ago, while preparing to interview David Graeber, I decided to conduct some brief internet research on the renowned anthropologist and activist. Although critically acclaimed in academic circles (he has been described as ‘the best anthropological theorist of his generation’), I was surprised to find relatively little on the man and his work – save a few articles and interviews regarding his involvement in various alter-globalisation movements over the past decade, a few more concerning his controversial departure from Yale, (he now teaches at Goldsmiths University of London), and of course, the odd intellectual dispute with S…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Pinterest’s Custom Spark Job logging and monitoring on Amazon EKS: Using AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and ADOT]]></title>
        <id>bdee5c2591496eec52dbc266a230659e41d9f831</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/inside-pinterests-custom-spark-job-logging-and-monitoring-on-amazon-eks-using-aws-for-fluent-bit-amazon-s3-and-adot-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1, we explored Moka’s high-level design and logging infrastructure, showcasing how AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and a robust logging framework make sure of operational visibility and facilitate issue resolution. For more details, read part 1 here. Introduction As we transition to the second part of our series, our focus shifts to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vara Bonthu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Pinterest’s Custom Spark Job logging and monitoring on Amazon EKS: Using AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and ADOT]]></title>
        <id>2906849e01c03228ff10bcb7b325af81d37d5136</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/inside-pinterests-custom-spark-job-logging-and-monitoring-on-amazon-eks-using-aws-for-fluent-bit-amazon-s3-and-adot/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Part 1 of the blog post. Introduction Pinterest is a visual search and curation platform focused on inspiring users to create a life they love. Critical to the service are data insights, recommendations and machine learning (ML) models that are produced by synthesizing insights provided by the over 500 million monthly active users […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vara Bonthu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On enjoying my work]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/on-enjoying-my-work/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/on-enjoying-my-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So over on Aura's blog, an anonymous asker asks:
Hello! A Youtube video essayist I follow on Bluesky (Big Joel if you know of him) posted this:
“How do you become a person who just really likes doing work? I thought having a very interesting job would do it but this has not paid off as you might expect”
The first two people I thought of who give me the impression they enjoy their jobs are you and Bruno Dias, so I was wondering if you had an answer for this (because I sure don’t!)
I was slightly taken aback by this, as one often is when one sees one's name in print unexpectedly, and I had to pick apart a little this idea that I give the impression that I enjoy my job.
I certainly have talked very positively about my work in public; I believe most readers should be familiar with the old (but…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jdright in "Show HN: Pumpkin – A Modern Minecraft server written in Rust"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854995</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854995"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://dayssincelastrustmcserver.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jdright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 19]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-19?v=1729044044</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-19?v=1729044044"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 19
Date: 31/05/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/05/31/no-issue-19/

Bullying Health
Elena Hagopyan
 As soon as you got any “bigger” health problem, you’re basically in trouble, not only by the things you’re facing by your condition, but actually the opinion is far harder. Today it is better to be some picture perfect child, young person or adult, as otherwise, you will be looked down upon by others. The silly of it is the fact no one is picture perfect, everyone who seems this way, it is just an act. 
 Myself, I have epilepsy, it always has been a problem, basically because I have to hide it every single day. If you have epilepsy, you better have the version of seizures most k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 20]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-20?v=1729043075</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-20?v=1729043075"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T01:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 20
Date: 21/06/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/06/21/no-issue-20/

Condemned and Hated
Isis Nelson
 Adults have consistently ignored young opinions and voices forever. It’s taught to us that we should respect our elders, because they’re old, and not speak unless spoken to by an adults. They constantly fail to protect and help us. The history of our world is filled with young people and children being failed by adults and losing their rights. From birth, we’re told that we are inherently inferior. Year after year, young people’s ideas are shot down by older relatives, older siblings, teachers, professors, leaders, bosses, etc. Our ambitious, often progressive, ideals and value…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexErrant in "Why don't we use awnings anymore (2022)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854344</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854344"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T00:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "Technology Connections" youtube channel recently discussed awnings too. (And it had more or less the same message as this blog.)
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uhbDfi7Ee7k]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexErrant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a website is easy: a guide to the first steps]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8674</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/building-website-easy-guide-first-steps/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for people, by American software developer Blake Watson, is a helpful resource for people wishing to build their first website, with a simple text editor. HTML for people guides first time web designers through the process of creating webpages, to uploading them, to produce a live website. You, my friend, are about to go […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://absoluteblank.bearblog.dev/why-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://absoluteblank.bearblog.dev/why-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:38:08.781Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is my belief that we all have something interesting to say. Whether you are an average Joe or a high status individual, your thoughts and opinions matter. If they didn't then why do they have the urge to socialize with friends or family? Okay so we chat with the people we love, so what? Why would I need to blog? For those that tell me that their journal is their blog I do not disagree that it isn't important. The only difference is that your written word now has an audience. Gasp! Being perceived?! This can be scary to some but let's look at the positive aspects of blogging.
First, there are no rules to blogging. Blogs serve different purposes depending on the person. For example, this blog you are reading is a personal blog that doesn't have a specific focus or target audience. I just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean author Han Kang wins 2024 literature Nobel Prize]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8679</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/south-korean-author-han-kang-wins-2024-literature-nobel-prize/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Seoul based author is the first South Korean to be named a Nobel Prize literature laurate. Han Kang has written over a dozen novels since 1995, so if you’re a book reader, chances are you’ve seen at least one. The Vegetarian, published in 2016, won the International Booker Prize in the same year. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Amazon DynamoDB zero-ETL integrations with Amazon Redshift now generally available]]></title>
        <id>5718e2ab1acb3131b5cb8e4c41f4e24e864f2f93</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-amazon-dynamodb-zero-etl-integrations-with-amazon-redshift-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T19:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock insights instantly with Amazon Redshift's new zero-ETL integrations for Aurora PostgreSQL and DynamoDB, eliminating complex ETL pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCP Summit 2024: The open future of networking hardware for AI]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21834</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/15/data-infrastructure/open-future-networking-hardware-ai-ocp-2024-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Open Compute Project Summit (OCP) 2024, we’re sharing details about our next-generation network fabric for our AI training clusters. We’ve expanded our network hardware portfolio and are contributing two new disaggregated network fabrics and a new NIC to OCP. We look forward to continued collaboration with OCP to open designs for racks, servers, storage [...]
Read More...
The post OCP Summit 2024: The open future of networking hardware for AI appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s open AI hardware vision]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21832</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/15/data-infrastructure/metas-open-ai-hardware-vision/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Open Compute Project (OCP) Global Summit 2024, we’re showcasing our latest open AI hardware designs with the OCP community. These innovations include a new AI platform, cutting-edge open rack designs, and advanced network fabrics and components.  By sharing our designs, we hope to inspire collaboration and foster innovation. If you’re passionate about building [...]
Read More...
The post Meta’s open AI hardware vision appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO-to-worker compensation ratio, 1965-2023]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45655</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/15/ceo-to-worker-compensation-ratio-1965-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All In Its Own Time]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/all-in-its-own-time/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/all-in-its-own-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to be obsessed with timelines.
When I was young and naive, I had a list of things I wanted to accomplish by specific points in my life. Some of those goals included:
Five years after earning my degree, I should be making a certain amount of money.
By 25, I should be engaged, and shortly after, should be married.
By a certain age, I should have a specific number of children.
Before that, I should own a particular kind of house in a specific location.
And so on, and so on.
Life is a fickle thing. I was young and didn’t fully grasp that wanting to achieve something by a certain time didn’t guarantee I would actually do it then.
Having a goal was good for me. During those 5 years, I worked really hard to reach a specific point in my career to hit that number. What was not helpful was be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of the EPYC 145% performance gain in Cloudflare Gen 12 servers]]></title>
        <id>1Sj8x3oCQRSZqU8oNgMmkE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/analysis-of-the-epyc-145-performance-gain-in-cloudflare-gen-12-servers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s Gen 12 server is the most powerful and power efficient server that we have deployed to date. Through sensitivity analysis, we found that Cloudflare workloads continue to scale with higher core count and higher CPU frequency, as well as achieving a significant boost in performance with larger L3 cache per core.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JQ Lau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP O’ Malley - Interview: David Graeber, leading figure of Occupy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-interview-david-graeber-leading-figure-of-occupy?v=1728997340</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-interview-david-graeber-leading-figure-of-occupy?v=1728997340"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: JP O’ Malley
Title: Interview: David Graeber, leading figure of Occupy
Date: 3 May 2013
Notes: davidgraeber.org & davidgraeber.institute
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.spectator.co.uk

 The anarchist movement in the United States has had the support of leading libertarian intellectuals, such as Noam Chomsky; but it has lacked a figure who could transform its guiding principles into something resembling a political movement. In the autumn of 2011, David Graeber seemed to be the man who could drag anarchism into mainstream politics. 
 Graeber, along with other leading figures in the Occupy movement, coined the term ‘we are the 99 percent’. The catchphrase caught on, and within weeks — with the assistance of social media — Occupy transformed a small group of idealists…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta]]></title>
        <id>7LZCXzvQgHwLVGoT4O4Pj6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protect-against-identity-based-attacks-by-sharing-cloudflare-user-risk-with-okta"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uphold Zero Trust principles and protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta. Learn how this new integration allows your organization to mitigate risk in real time, make informed access decisions, and free up security resources with automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Kagan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qalandar Bux Memon and Zaki Abbas - Prefiguration of a Common Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/qalandar-bux-memon-and-zaki-abbas-prefiguration-of-a-common-dream?v=1728996194</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/qalandar-bux-memon-and-zaki-abbas-prefiguration-of-a-common-dream?v=1728996194"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Qalandar Bux Memon and Zaki Abbas
Title: Prefiguration of a Common Dream
Subtitle: An Interview with David Graeber
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from nakedpunch.com

Qalandar Bux Memon: Can you explain why you support horizontal organisation, collective assemblies and a dialogical method for organising for social change as opposed to the vertical left party?
 David Gaeber: I like to make the distinction between forms of organization that could exist outside structures of coercion – that is, in the absence of any ability to call up men armed with weapons to threaten anyone who refuses to go along with a decision – and those which could not. It seems to me it’s the responsibility of those who are trying to create a free society to do so through forms of organization that cou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur De Grave - The era of predatory bureaucratization]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-de-grave-the-era-of-predatory-bureaucratization?v=1728995026</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-de-grave-the-era-of-predatory-bureaucratization?v=1728995026"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arthur De Grave
Title: The era of predatory bureaucratization
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: 27 January 2016
Notes: This interview was originally published in Socialter n°14.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from legacy.ouishare.net

 David Graeber is an anthropologist and a well-known anarchist figure. He was one of the initiators of the Occupy movement in 2011. He is the author of a major essay, Debt, the First 5,000 Years. I met him in Paris for the release of his latest book, The Utopia of Rules: On Technology, Stupidity, and the Secret Joys of Bureaucracy.
Back in 2011, you were among the initiators of the Occupy movement. Several similar social movements have happened ever since, but it seems none of them managed to stay alive long enough to reach their…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Durel - Teach Me if You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steven-durel-teach-me-if-you-can?v=1728994563</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steven-durel-teach-me-if-you-can?v=1728994563"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Steven Durel
Title: Teach Me if You Can
Subtitle: An Interview with David Graeber
Date: November 21, 2005
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from towardfreedom.org

 David Graeber: It’s not really Yale’s leadership so much as the Department of Anthropology and senior faculty who decided to cut me off. For a long time I really tried to avoid getting involved in campus politics. I thought that I had come up with a nice formula, that I would be an activist in New York and simply a scholar here in New Haven. 
 Generally speaking, the academy really doesn’t care what you say and think or what you write, so long as you don’t do anything. If you’re willing to be a hypocrite, they’re fine with you, whatever you espouse. On the other hand, if there’s any sign that you might actually liv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Wolfe - The movement as an end-in-itself?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ross-wolfe-the-movement-as-an-end-in-itself?v=1728994191</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ross-wolfe-the-movement-as-an-end-in-itself?v=1728994191"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ross Wolfe
Title: The movement as an end-in-itself?
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: February 2012
Notes: Published in Platypus Review 43.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from platypus1917.org

On December 16, 2011, Ross Wolfe interviewed David Graeber, Reader at Goldsmiths College in London, author of Fragments of an Anarchist Anthropology (2004), and central figure in the early stages of the #Occupy Wall Street Movement. What follows is an edited transcript of the interview.
Ross Wolfe: There are striking similarities between the #Occupy movement and the 1999 anti-WTO protests in Seattle. Both began in the last year of a Democratic presidency, were spearheaded by anarchists, motivated by discontents with neo-liberalism, and received the support of organized …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suzi Weissman - The Rise of Bullshit Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/suzi-weissman-the-rise-of-bullshit-jobs?v=1728988945</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/suzi-weissman-the-rise-of-bullshit-jobs?v=1728988945"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Suzi Weissman
Title: The Rise of Bullshit Jobs
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: June 30, 2018
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from jacobin.com

 In his latest book, David Graeber, the best-selling author of Debt: The First 5000 Years, argues that many jobs today are essentially pointless — or, as the book’s title calls them, Bullshit Jobs. 
 Jacobin Radio’s Suzi Weissman sat down with Graeber to find out what bullshit jobs are and why they’ve proliferated in recent years. 
A Taxonomy
Suzi Weissman: Let’s just get right down to it. What is the definition of a bullshit job? 
David Graeber: A bullshit job is a job which is so pointless, or even pernicious, that even the person doing the job secretly believes that it shouldn’t exist. Of course, you have to pretend…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP O’ Malley - The Utopia of Rules, David Graeber Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-the-utopia-of-rules-david-graeber-interview?v=1728988786</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-the-utopia-of-rules-david-graeber-interview?v=1728988786"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: JP O’ Malley
Title: The Utopia of Rules, David Graeber Interview
Date: 1st April 2015
Notes: JP O’ Malley interviews anthropologist, activist, anarchist and author, David Graeber, who was one of the early organisers of Occupy Wall Street.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from bellacaledonia.org.uk

 In a compelling new book of essays entitled The Utopia of Rules: On Technology, Stupidity, and the Secret Joys of Bureaucracy, the American anarchist, and anthropologist, David Graeber argues that in all western countries today bureaucracy—whether it comes from multinational corporations or government offices— informs almost every single aspect of both public and private life. 
 Graeber is a radical thinker who is not afraid to dream big and envision a society that is profoundly d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sen$e - Why America’s favorite anarchist thinks most American workers are slaves]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/making-sen-e-why-america-s-favorite-anarchist-thinks-most-american-workers-are-slaves?v=1728988512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/making-sen-e-why-america-s-favorite-anarchist-thinks-most-american-workers-are-slaves?v=1728988512"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Making Sen$e
Title: Why America’s favorite anarchist thinks most American workers are slaves
Date: April 17, 2014
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.pbs.org

Editor’s Note: Conservative proponents of the guaranteed income want a lump sum payment (Charles Murray suggests about $11,000 to all adults) to replace existing social welfare programs and downsize American bureaucracy. But some leftists oppose those government welfare agencies, too, London School of Economics professor David Graeber says. The leftist critique of private and public bureaucracies, Graeber explains, is that they “employ thousands of people to make us feel bad about ourselves.” 
 Bureaucrats pushing paper decide what we and our work are worth. But somewhat ironically, Graeber suggests, it’s those bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elias Isquith - “I found myself turning into an idiot!”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-isquith-i-found-myself-turning-into-an-idiot?v=1728988254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-isquith-i-found-myself-turning-into-an-idiot?v=1728988254"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Elias Isquith
Title: “I found myself turning into an idiot!”
Subtitle: David Graeber explains the life-sapping reality of bureaucratic life
Date: March 5, 2015
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.salon.com

 David Graeber, a professor of anthropology at the London School of Economics, is a man who wears many hats. He’s an academic, of course — and a respected one at that. But he’s also an author, an activist and political anarchist. But his most unique attribute may be this: He’s an honest-to-God public intellectual in an era when such figures are few and far between. 
 Graeber proved as much with “Debt: The First 5000 Years,” his ambitious tour de force overview of the role debt has played throughout the history of civilization and into the present day. And while it ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Agnes Callard, on the Art of Governing Teaching & Learning and student protests]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53272</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/15/on-agnes-callard-on-the-art-of-governing-teaching-learning-and-student-protests/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really liked and admired Agnes Callard’s essay, “Beyond Neutrality: The university’s responsibility to lead” in The Point (September 29, 2024) [HT Dailynous]. My post is, despite some quibbles, primarily about amplifying a point Callard (Chicago) makes. I do so not just because there is considerable overlap between our positions (recall here and here), but also because she advances the discussion on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by umanwizard in "World conker champion found with steel chestnut, cleared of cheating"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41844648</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41844648"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T03:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this game well-known enough in Britain and Ireland that readers will know what on earth is being alleged just from reading this article? Or are you expected to have to google it?
Apparently it’s a game where you take turns swinging a chestnut on a string and trying to hit the opponent’s chestnut and break it. Yes, I can see how a steel fake chestnut would be an advantage here, though I’m amazed it wouldn’t be instantly obvious to even a casual observer that the look and sound were wrong. So maybe I’m still missing something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>umanwizard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jstrieb in "Gettiers in software engineering (2019)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842593</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842593"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T22:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relevant (deleted, as far as I can tell) tweet:
> When I talk to Philosophers on zoom my screen background is an exact replica of my actual background just so I can trick them into having a justified true belief that is not actually knowledge.
https://old.reddit.com/r/PhilosophyMemes/comments/gggqkv/get...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jstrieb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by londons_explore in "Turn your Android phone into a modern ham radio transceiver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842346</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842346"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T21:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The radio simply plugs into the USB C port on your Android smartphone and transforms it into a fully-fledged handheld radio transceiver.
When I saw the headline I was hoping someone had hacked the qualcomm modem and turned it into a software defined radio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>londons_explore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One personal website is enough for me]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8669</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/one-personal-website-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure disassociated always rates as a personal website, with its informational content style. But it’s owned personally by me, and I personally write the content, so on that basis it’s a personal website. A lot of what I post are my thoughts on the many and various things happening online and in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JumpCrisscross in "Google commits to buying power generated by nuclear-energy startup Kairos Power"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841798</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841798"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> it’s a power purchase agreement from something that may never be built! No different from Microsoft’s previous fusion power purchase agreement
A frequent complaint from utilities has been AI companies refusing to sign PPAs. They want the option of picking up and leaving if someone else offers a better deal down the road, leaving the utility stuck with overbuilt infrastructure costs.
> virtue signalling
This term has lost whatever meaning it ever had if we're using it to refer to binding contracts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JumpCrisscross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oulipo in "Bike Manufacturers Are Making Bikes Less Repairable"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841449</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841449"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Founder of Gouach, the repairable (and fireproof!) e-bike battery mentioned in the article, happy to answer any question!
- we salvaged 100s of discarded e-bike batteries
- we found that 90% of components were like new
- batteries were thrown away because of the spot-welding and the glue which prevents repairability
- we spent 2 years (and 5 patents) to design a robust, safe, and easy to assemble system that requires nothing but a screwdriver
Our batteries have been in use since 2 years in the streets of France, on micro-mobility e-bikes, in the harshest possible conditions (rain, snow, cold, heat, shocks), and we're very happy with their performances!
We're now opening it to the general public (for conversion kits, and to replace old batteries that are no longer manufactured)
We plan to open-source at least part of the embedded software, so people can write extensions (to let their battery "talk" with any e-bike system, and share it — using WASM embeddable code — to other people on the web!)
Let's fight planned obsolescence!
(and if you're looking for a new battery, there's 25% off on https://get.gouach.com)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oulipo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by daxfohl in "Scale Ruins Everything"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841448</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41841448"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given that we've been throwing cash at every conceivable idea for the last ten plus years, yet when speaking of unicorns we still have to refer back to airbnb and uber, seems like we're well past "peak unicorn" and well into the "horse with a mild concussion" era.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daxfohl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigation of a Workbench UI Latency Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/faa017b4653d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/investigation-of-a-workbench-ui-latency-issue-faa017b4653d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Hechao Li and Marcelo Mayworm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I hate my degree]]></title>
        <id>https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/i-hate-my-degree/</id>
        <link href="https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/i-hate-my-degree/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:10:54.371Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I started my magister degree in programming, and it fucking sucked from the very beginning of the bachelors, to be honest. I constantly regret "my" choice (my dad is a programmer, and I sorta wanted to make him proud, but there was no pressure from him or anybody else) to start all this. I long for history, literature, philosophy, languages and human psychology constantly. I try to self-study some of this, but university studying takes most of my time and mental capacity. IT just feels like it is not for me. I want to understand our situation as humans on this tiny planet. I feel this void inside of me every day. I feel like this year I will eventually fail my studies due to numerous mental breakdowns. Fuck it, I will be someone else in the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating custom Amazon EKS worker node builds using EC2 Image Builder]]></title>
        <id>0f6921caef075cd4bf67b783cc1704da9240aca9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/automating-custom-amazon-eks-worker-node-builds-using-ec2-image-builder/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers who are building their “Golden Image” Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) using EC2 Image Builder may wish to extend their Image Builder pipelines to build out their Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) worker nodes as well. In this blog, we will show you how to do this and provide you with AWS CloudFormation templates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brad Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zhovner in "Busy Status Bar"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41839748</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41839748"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Pavel Zhovner here, Flipper Devices CEO. 
Yes it's our product, but it's not ready for announcement yet, so we keep it secret.
Right now, we are working on implementing Matter smart home protocol and will slightly change the product concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zhovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: What’s App, AWS Lambda, Load Balancers, AWS Console, and more (Oct 14, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>802232dd71f635b36fd40d9d7a982433d951aad6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-whats-app-aws-lambda-load-balancers-aws-console-and-more-oct-14-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, AWS hosted free half-day conferences in London and Paris. My colleagues and I demonstrated how developers can use generative AI tools to speed up their design, analysis, code writing, debugging, and deployment workflows. These events were held at the GenAI Lofts. These lofts are open until October 25 (London) and November 5 (Paris). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On being a great gift-giver]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/on-being-a-great-gift-giver/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/on-being-a-great-gift-giver/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are great at giving gifts. The kinds of gifts that squeeze your heart make you feel seen. I'm trying to become one of those people, but my friend Simon already is.
If you're reading this you're probably aware that I run a blogging platform that I care for deeply. And it's the main thing I speak about when someone asks after my day. I rattle on about a challenging bug I'm trying to squash, complain about cheeky script-kiddies rattling the latches on all the doors and windows looking for an exploit, or mention an email I received from a blogger letting me know they see the love and effort I put into my work.
Simon hears all of this, and on my 32nd birthday gave me a gift that really hit home.
I keep a mostly-up-to-date list of nice messages about Bear that I've received from users over the past few years. It helps me remember why I do what I do, and makes me feel all warm and fuzzy whenever I need some extra motivation.
Knowing this, Simon conspired with a friend who owns a 3D printer and designed and created a little desktop bear that can hold a message board. He then wrote each of these messages out by hand (suffering only minor carpel tunnel) on sticky notes which the bear now carries like a human bear directional.

It now sits on my desk, next to my computer where I get to see it every work day, right when and where I need a shot of good vibes.
These are the kinds of gifts I want to learn how to give. Ones that make the receiver feel like they've been listened to and understood. That don't cost much money but are priceless at the same time.
I'm grateful and inspired. Thanks Simon (I know you're subscribed to my blog). And thanks to everyone who has sent me a kind email over the past few years. I appreciate you all.
Enjoyed the article? I write about 1-2 a month. Subscribe via email or RSS feed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The European Central Bank and the return of history]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45647</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/14/the-european-central-bank-and-the-return-of-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T09:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of the post-World War II ´Pax Americana, an almost eighty-year period of peace for European countries allied with the USA, will soon lead the EU to end the prohibition of monetary financing of governments by the European Central Bank (ECB). This might take the shape of the ECB providing credit to an entity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US just lost a war and nobody noticed]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53266</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/14/the-us-just-lost-a-war-and-nobody-noticed/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T07:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the eight decades following the end of World War II, the US has taken part in dozens of land wars, large and small. The outcomes have ranged from comprehensive victory to humiliating defeat, but all have received extensive coverage. By contrast, the US Navy’s admission of defeat in its longest and most significant campaign […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy is Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/privacy-is-politics/</id>
        <link href="https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/privacy-is-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to having an opinion, every cornerstone of a community becomes a droughtless wellspring. No matter where you go, opposing arguments will follow. That is the nature of opinions—there will always be one slightly different from another. Amazingly, even in areas where opinions shouldn’t take precedence over fact, people will still hold their personal beliefs over them. I think that’s just plain ignorance.
One of these communities is the Land of OPSEC. The world of information security, simply put. An area of knowledge that should, without a doubt, be centered around the obvious fact of the matter. Easily. Want to be secured? Don’t use that—use this. Is this thing compromised? Update to this.
Right? Sort of. The world of digital security is probably one of the most politically mot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by matrix2003 in "Why does FM sound better than AM?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41832921</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41832921"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone gave me an analogy some time ago that made a lot of sense.
If you shine a flashlight through a tree blowing in the wind and vary the brightness to convey information, the signal can get distorted pretty easily.
However, if you have a constant brightness source and vary the color, it’s a lot easier to figure out what the source is trying to convey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>matrix2003</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProRata: an AI chatbot that pays for the knowledge it disseminate]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/prorata-ai-chatbot-pays-knowledge-idisseminate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ProRata is an AI chatbot that pays the content producers whose work is used to format answers to questions put to it. Yes, you read that correctly. The technology is being backed by American investor and entrepreneur Bill Gross, writes Fred Vogelstein, for Crazy Stupid Tech: But it will do something none of the others […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michaelmior in "CRLF is obsolete and should be abolished"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41831072</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41831072"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> various protocols (HTTP, SMTP, CSV) still "require" CRLF at the end of each line
What would be the benefit to updating legacy protocols to just use NL? You save a handful of bits at the expense of a lot of potential bugs. HTTP/1(.1) is mostly replaced by HTTP/2 and later by now anyway.
Sure, it makes sense not to require CRLF with any new protocols, but it doesn't seem worth updating legacy things.
> Even if an established protocol (HTTP, SMTP, CSV, FTP) technically requires CRLF as a line ending, do not comply.
I'm hoping this is satire. Why intentionally introduce potential bugs for the sake of making a point?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaelmior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation is called “Productivity Growth”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45643</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/13/automation-is-called-productivity-growth-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker It is more than a bit bizarre reading pieces that talk about automation or job-killing AI as something new and alien. These are forms of productivity growth. They allow more goods and services to be produced for each hour of human labor. Productivity growth is usually thought of as a good thing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ChuckMcM in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41830516</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41830516"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T18:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty impressive. The engineering team at SpaceX is really something. Some thoughts;
The 'chopsticks catch' was amazing to watch. Seems like it adds a lot of risk and clearly the booster needs additional fire suppression systems :-) perhaps the tower could mount something that sprays the booster like the barges have for the F9 boosters.
The heatshield held out for a much longer time, the asymmetric heating on the flaps was interesting. I had guessed that all four flaps would have equivalent heating based on an approach that was basically that side of the rocket perpendicular to the flow but it seems like that isn't the case. Still it seems like they are close to having something workable here.
The detonation at the end was pretty spectacular too, but I suspect that structurally the tanks failed as the rocket hit the water vs anything that was an engineering failure. Engineering it to be strong enough to land on water would presumably compromise the cargo to orbit number.
The use of Starlink was really interesting. The ability to get live video for the entire re-entry is pretty game changing for engineering. I'd guess there are even more 'views' than they showed (there would be if I were running things :-)) but overall that capability is something that really helps evaluate the changes made.
I can easily imagine that flight 6 will be nominal end to end without any unintended damage. That would enable, perhaps, one of their 'massive' Starlink missions to test cargo delivery. It will also start to give us some better numbers on exactly how much cargo Starship can put in orbit in 'full reuse' mode  which is essential if they want to create a fueling station on orbit for the Artemis program.
Again, hats off to engineering at SpaceX, y'all did good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ChuckMcM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 songs to get to know me]]></title>
        <id>https://tbskyen.bearblog.dev/100-songs-to-get-to-know-me/</id>
        <link href="https://tbskyen.bearblog.dev/100-songs-to-get-to-know-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I posted this image over on the bluesky, and it got like 100 likes, so now here we are. Rather than spam this as a 100 post thread, let's do it in a format which is suited for it: the blog.
These songs are in no particular order, except the order I am finding them in my playlists and deciding to put them on here.
1. ABBA - Lay All Your Love On Me


I genuinely don't quite know if my enjoyment of ABBA is something I came by honestly, or something which is simply genetically engineered into my Scandinavian soul. I remember hearing my mom blasting their songs on the home stereo in my childhood, and the association has put permanent nostalgia blinders on me for all of ABBA's greatest hits. Still, I think the beat is undeniable and the mournful tone of the chorus adds some real melancholy to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by magicalhippo in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41829231</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41829231"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First off, the booster was going about 1250 km/h when it started its landing burn, it relied purely on drag to get it slowed down to that speed.
Going by the telemetry of the seconds before the landing burn and noting the speed vs time, it seems drag was around 40 m/s^2 when it was going at around 3000 km/h. Since drag depends on velocity squared though, it had reduced to just above 10 m/s^2 just before the engines lit at 1250 km/h, and so would quickly become negligible once the engines lit.
Going by Wikipedia, the Super Heavy[1] has 3400000 kg of fuel at launch, so 3% of that is about 102000 kg. For the landing burn, it used 13 Raptor v3 engines[2] to scrub speed. Each Raptor flows about 650 kg/s max, so 3% fuel is enough for about 12 seconds for the 13 engines.
The empty mass of the Super Heavy is about 275000 kg, so about 377000 kg before the landing burn with 3% fuel.
Using the sea-level vs vacuum performance of the Raptor v2 engines, one can estimate that each Raptor v3 produces about 2.45 NM of force at sea-level. So 13 of them would produce about 31.85 MN of force.
Using Newton's second law, F=ma, this gives an initial deceleration of about 84 m/s^2 and about 104 m/s^2 when empty. If we do a rough spreadsheet integration, we get that a burn of roughly 4 seconds is needed to scrub the speed assuming no other forces.
Now, comparing this with reality, the full 13 engines were lit for a little over 5 seconds.
In my simplified calculations I was assuming full throttle the whole way, which obviously isn't realistic, and I also assumed 3% fuel. So over all I think that's a pretty decent estimation.
[1]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SpaceX_Super_Heavy#Engines
[2]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SpaceX_Raptor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>magicalhippo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: punch card loom]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53264</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/13/sunday-photoblogging-punch-card-loom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kids today probably don’t know about punched cards, but when I was at school we all had to play around with them a bit as we learnt about state-of-the-art computing …. But the technology derives from weaving, and from the Jacquard loom of 1804.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>