<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-01T06:29:00.428Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-01T06:29:00.428Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death and the Cinema]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272587</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/death-and-the-cinema.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T06:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of film, even films about death, will hopefully come as a distraction from turbulent news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Squashing the Perfection Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://sreekarscribbles.com/squashing-the-perfection-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://sreekarscribbles.com/squashing-the-perfection-bug/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:19:18.684Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love my blog! I really do! I want to write every day. But I don't. Why? Because of the Perfection Bug!
"You need to share a unique thought"
"Your idea should be worth penning"
"You need to write in great detail"
Buzz, buzzz, buzzzz....the perfection bug keeps buzzing in my ear.
But today, I decided to squash that bug!
I don't need unique thoughts. I don't need amazing ideas. I don't need to explain things in detail.
All I need is a thought (which can be ordinary) and a bunch of words to share it. That's it! That's all I need to write on my blog.
So, see you again tomorrow with an ordinary thought and a bunch of words!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dmd in "IRS Direct File to open to all 50 states and D.C. for 2025 tax season"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40538563</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40538563"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[94% of Americans make less than $200k a year. Not everything is meant for "software engineers in California".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dmd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/31/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272554</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-31-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler, politics and pandemics; aftermath of Trump's conviction, including medical exam; Biden and the youth vote; CDC knew Covid was airborne January 30, 2020 ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by macrael in "IRS Direct File to open to all 50 states and D.C. for 2025 tax season"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40537914</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40537914"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:26:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's SUCH a win that they managed to roll this out to a small set of tax situations and states to start. Every government project I've been on has required creativity in defining an MVP that doesn't include shipping to everyone. This was cited consistently as one of the great successes of this project, they were able to ship something that successfully filed 150k taxes b/c they were able to scope things down to something doable in 9 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>macrael</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsflash: Inequality in Neoliberal America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Newsflash-Inequality-in-Neoliberal-America</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Newsflash-Inequality-in-Neoliberal-America"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If anyone is perplexed or surprised why Americans are so upset about the economy, they should look no further than the Income Distribution and Dynamics in America (IDDA) recent report by the Federal Reserve Board of Minneapolis and its data site that looks at the stagnation of American income and economic mobility in America. It unfortunately confirms what we already know—the neoliberal state benefits unevenly and in ways that confound an ability to challenge it.. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Inequality, 
Neo-liberalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schultz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify custom contact center insights with Amazon Connect analytics data lake]]></title>
        <id>b44f4d90bbfa2e0d08f57e4bdcf5b0d09dfc7e16</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-custom-contact-center-insights-with-amazon-connect-analytics-data-lake/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Connect's analytics data lake centralizes customer data for powerful performance analysis without complex pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luke Roberts: &ldquo;Raspberries&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/raspberries</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/raspberries"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[J.H. Prynne’s ‘Poems 2016-2024’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Authorizes Ukraine to Make “Limited” Strikes on Russia With US Weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272549</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/biden-authorizes-ukraine-to-make-limited-strikes-on-russia-with-us-weapons.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden Administration doubles down yet again against Russia, even as the Collective West is running out of options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Single Sign On (SSO) to manage project teams for Amazon CodeCatalyst]]></title>
        <id>fbcf566b2175883fe6c6b7622cccf1911f785fd5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/using-single-sign-on-sso-to-manage-project-teams-for-amazon-codecatalyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T14:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst is a modern software development service that empowers teams to deliver software on AWS easily and quickly. Amazon CodeCatalyst provides one place where you can plan, code, and build, test, and deploy your container applications with continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) tools. CodeCatalyst recently announced the teams feature, which simplifies management of space and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Konaka Satyapal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Philip-J-Fry in "Spotify won't open-source Car Thing, but starts refund process"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40534912</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40534912"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are they just banking on people not caring enough or knowing about the refund process? Clearly it can't be better off for them to refund hundreds of thousands maybe even 1m+ people.
We need laws that step in to make this impossible. Hardware should be designed so that it can be reused. Make it so that people can just reflash the memory at a minimum. There's no reason for something like this to become e-waste. And the excuse being Spotify wanting to protect their brand should not stand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip-J-Fry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back on Bear Blog - for life]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-blog-life/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-blog-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:15:23.670Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I decided to start blogging again after a long absence, Bear was the platform I fell in love with. I published the first post, It's alive!, on February 16, 2023, while on vacation in Chiang Mai, Thailand.
After about half a year, I went on a blogging tool spree. Why? I'm not sure why. Maybe because of my love and fascination for the web.
I tried many different platforms. Eventually, there were three left:
Bear
Pika
Scribbles
They are all fantastic! If you're on one of them today and find it to be the right blogging tool for you, congratulations. You made a great choice!
For me, Bear ended up being the winner. I will write a separate post on this later, but basically, it was the combination of simplicity and customization that won me over forever.
When I say "forever," I mean for the rest of my life. I decided to upgrade to the lifetime plan. Partly because it's a great deal, but also to keep me from looking elsewhere. This is my home, and I'm very happy to have found my way back.
I look forward to writing many more posts, but more importantly, I look forward to reading what other "Bears" publish in this beautiful community.
Happy blogging!
Follow: email · rss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending local traffic management load balancing to Layer 4 with Spectrum]]></title>
        <id>66599d35bdbaa8000a84c512</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/extending-local-traffic-management-load-balancing-to-layer-4-with-spectrum"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is adding support for all TCP and UDP traffic to our local traffic management (LTM) load balancing solution, extending the benefits of LTM to more than just HTTP(S) applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Ward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Discount Window Stigma Be Cured?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30230</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/can-discount-window-stigma-be-cured/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core responsibilities of central banks is to act as “lender of last resort” to the financial system. In the U.S., the Federal Reserve has been operating as a lender of last resort through its “discount window” (DW) for more than a century. Historically, however, the DW has been plagued by stigma—banks’ reluctance to use the DW, even for benign reasons, out of concerns that it could be interpreted as a sign of financial weakness. In this post, we report on new research showing that once a DW facility is stigmatized, removing that stigma is difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivier Armantier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking of Pursuing a PhD in Economics? Info on Graduate School and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30228</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/thinking-of-pursuing-a-phd-in-economics-info-on-graduate-school-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Becoming a PhD economist can provide a fulfilling and financially secure career path. However, getting started in the field can be daunting if you don’t know much about the preparation you’ll need and the available job opportunities. If you’re wondering what it means to be an economics researcher or how to become one, please read on. We’ll review how to prepare for a career in economics research, what an economics PhD program entails, and what types of opportunities it might bring. Economic education is a core component of the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s mission to serve the community. To empower would-be economists, this post provides information for students who seek a career in economics research. We hope this information will be helpful to students interested in economics, regardless of their background and economic situation.  This information is most applicable to students applying to programs in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasey Chatterji-Len and Anna Kovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/31/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272537</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-31-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our decolonizing daliy links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Debunking to “Pre-bunking”: EU Opens Up Another New Front in Its War on Information]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272426</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/just-before-eu-elections-von-der-leyen-commission-goes-all-in-on-orwellian-and-dicksensian-narrative-control.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Perhaps if you think of information as a virus, instead of treating an infection once it has taken hold -- that is, debunking -- it is much better to vaccinate so that the body is inoculated." Welcome to prebunking.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hassan Ould Moctar: &ldquo;Hors Camp&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hors-camp</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hors-camp"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War and migration in the Sahel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Conviction Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272520</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/donald-trump-conviction-open-thread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T09:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump was convicted on all 34 counts in his New York "hush money" trial. What next?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vasco in "A man ordered to hide his boat painted the boat on his fence"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532255</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532255"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T07:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American land of the free is being able to bring a gun to school but getting a fine because your grass is too tall. These HOA type stories are always so funny. It blows my mind people buy in places with rules like these.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vasco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by low_tech_love in "Japan's push to make all research open access"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532049</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532049"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term “open access” is misleading and carefully engineered to generate good will, when in fact it should be termed “pay to publish” (as argued quite nicely by Brian McGill [1]). As it stands today, OA is mostly a public money sink, a big scheme to drain public money from European countries. Not only are we paying a ridiculous, ungodly amount of money for people to host PDFs on a website, but the entire idea of publishers competing for the quality of their research output (in order to get submissions) has also basically been eradicated and turned meaningless. Reviewers are pushed to accept papers instead of rejecting them, because a rejected paper makes no money, and now we are left with a deluge of noise that passes for scientific literature. I sincerely pity the PhD student who needs to run a serious, systematic literature review in 2024. Hell sounds more attractive.
If you want open access, ditch the publishers and fund volunteer expert communities to edit and publish their own papers. You can’t have the cake and eat it too.
[1] https://dynamicecology.wordpress.com/2024/04/29/the-state-of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>low_tech_love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by toast0 in "Engineering for Slow Internet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532038</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40532038"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I bet that WhatsApp is one of the rare services you use which actually deployed servers to Australia. To me, 200ms is a telltale sign of intercontinental traffic.
So, I used to work at WhatsApp. And we got this kind of praise when we only had servers in Reston, Virginia (not at aws us-east1, but in the same neighborhood). Nowadays, Facebook is most likely terminating connections in Australia, but messaging most likely goes through another continent. Calling within Australia should stay local though (either p2p or through a nearby relay).
There's lots of things WhatsApp does to improve experience on low quality networks that other services don't (even when we worked in the same buildings and told them they should consider things!)
In no particular order:
0) offline first, phone is the sou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>toast0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who By Fire? The Burning of Rafah’s Tent People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324075</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/who-by-fire-the-burning-of-rafah/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In eight months of war, Israel has killed thirty times more children in Gaza than Russia has killed Ukrainian children in two years and years months of war. Gaza’s population is just 1/15th the size of Ukraine's. But instead of sanctioning Israel, Biden and Blinken have threatened to sanction the one agency that’s tried to hold it accountable: the ICJ. Every atrocity Israel gets away with encourages it to do something even more grotesque. More
The post Who By Fire? The Burning of Rafah’s Tent People appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can’t Turn Back the Clock on Genocide: “Easily 200,000 Deaths in Gaza.”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324137</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/you-cant-turn-back-the-clock-on-genocide-200000-deaths-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Amal Nassar lay in pain on a bed at the Al-Awda Hospital in the Nuseirat refugee camp in northern Gaza, the echoes of explosions and artillery fire could be heard all around her. It was mid-January and she had made her way to the embattled hospital to give birth to a baby girl she  More
The post You Can’t Turn Back the Clock on Genocide: “Easily 200,000 Deaths in Gaza.” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by padolsey in "Engineering for Slow Internet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40531956</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40531956"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of this resonates. I'm not in Antartica, I'm in Beijing, but still struggle with the internet. Being behind the great firewall means using creative approaches. VPNs only sometimes work, and each leaves a signature that the firewall's hueristics and ML can eventually catch onto. Even state-mandated ones are 'gently' limited at times of political sensitivity. It all ends up meaning that, even if I get a connection, it's not stable, and it's so painful to sink precious packets into pointless web-app-react-crap roundtrips.
I feel like some devs need to time-travel back to 2005 or something and develop for that era in order to learn how to build things nimbly. In deficit of time travel, if people could just learn to open web tools and use its throttling tool: turn it to 3g, and see if their webapp is resilient. Please!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>padolsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Attack on the USS Liberty Symbolizes Israel’s Duplicity and Deceit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324151</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/the-attack-on-the-uss-liberty-symbolizes-israels-duplicity-and-deceit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-seven years ago during the Six-Day War (June 8, 1967), Israeli Defense Forces (IDF) brutally attacked a U.S. naval intelligence ship that was seconded to the National Security Agency (NSA) for intercepting communications in the Middle East.  Thirty-four American sailors were killed in the attack, and 171 were wounded by unmarked Mirage fighter aircraft using cannons and rockets.  Israeli boats fired machine guns at close range at those helping the wounded, including a Soviet naval vessel that was trying to rescue U.S. sailors; they also machine-gunned life rafts that survivors had dropped in hopes of abandoning the ship.  The Israelis immediately called the disaster a “random accident.” It wasn’t “random” and it wasn’t an “accident,” but the NSA investigation of the assault remains classified to this day. More
The post The Attack on the USS Liberty Symbolizes Israel’s Duplicity and Deceit appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boris Kagarlitsky and the Future of the Russian Left]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324128</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/boris-kagarlitsky-and-the-future-of-the-russian-left/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T06:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boris Yulyevich Kagarlitsky has had a torrid time with Russia’s notorious carceral regime—most recently on February 13, 2024 when prosecutors allied with one Kremlin faction had him re-imprisoned for a five-year term—albeit, he would insist, not nearly as severe as the systemic torture suffered by the late liberal opposition leader Alexei Navalny, killed on February 16 at the ‘Polar Wolf’ Artic Circle penal colony. Since the early 1980s, Boris has been repeatedly prosecuted for articulating left-wing ideals. More
The post Boris Kagarlitsky and the Future of the Russian Left appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Climate Change, Centrism Means a Slow Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324029</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/on-climate-change-centrism-means-a-slow-death/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To listen to Republicans, one might imagine that Democrats are Big Oil’s worst enemy, fighting to curb climate change on behalf of the good people of Florida and the rest of the nation. But much Democratic opposition exists in the form of incentives for green energy industries, for example, those built into the Inflation Reduction Act. In terms of actually holding climate polluters accountable, other than Biden’s budgetary proposal to end tax breaks (which is, after all, only a proposal), and a pause on natural gas permits, Democratic challenges have come in the form of “homework assignments for companies, and requests for Justice Department investigations,” wrote Axios reporter Ben German. More
The post On Climate Change, Centrism Means a Slow Death appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Bad to Worse: Tariffs on Chinese Green Tech Cause Massive Treasuries Dump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324154</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/from-bad-to-worse-tariffs-on-chinese-green-tech-cause-massive-treasuries-dump/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, after egregious theft of foreign reserves and promiscuous abuse of sanctions, Joe “Not the Climate President” Biden slapped huge tariffs on Chinese green tech and guess what? Beijing turned around May 18 and dumped $53 billion-worth of U.S. Treasuries for gold. Are alarm bells going off in federal financial centers and huge efforts underway  More
The post From Bad to Worse: Tariffs on Chinese Green Tech Cause Massive Treasuries Dump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Untold ICC Story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324144</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/the-untold-icc-story/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even the most optimistic of political analysts did not expect that the International Criminal Court’s Chief Prosecutor would be uttering these words: “I have reasonable grounds to believe that Benjamin Netanyahu (…) and Yoav Gallant (…) bear criminal responsibility for (…) war crimes and crimes against humanity …” Aside from the two Israelis, Karim Khan has included three Palestinians  More
The post The Untold ICC Story appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soaking Sunak Calls the Sodding Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324158</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/soaking-sunak-calls-the-sodding-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a pitiful sight.  Soaked and literally washed-out, the feeble thin British Prime Minister, Rishi Sunak, made an announcement that caught many in his party by surprise.  On July 4, the United Kingdom will be going to the polls.  Necks will find themselves in nooses and placed in the guillotine – metaphorically speaking.  The stretch to slaughter has  More
The post Soaking Sunak Calls the Sodding Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Media, Social Media, and the New Civil War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324285</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/mass-media-social-media-and-the-new-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How close are we to being in the movie? Leila and I went to the Baghdad Theater, down the road from our apartment in Portland, Oregon, to see the new film, Civil War, a few weeks ago.  There were a few pieces of dialogue where I wished I could have been on the writing team  More
The post Mass Media, Social Media, and the New Civil War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rovics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Deadly Force” Controversy Destroys Trump’s Immunity Argument]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/deadly-force-controversy-destroys-trumps-immunity-argument/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All politicians contradict themselves, but few so shamelessly as Donald Trump. Recently, Trump’s lawyer, D. John Sauer, lobbied the Supreme Court for “presidential immunity” in Trump’s criminal trial concerning his involvement in the Capitol insurrection. Sauer claimed in his arguments that presidents enjoy immunity for actions even as drastic as assassinating political opponents. This week,  More
The post “Deadly Force” Controversy Destroys Trump’s Immunity Argument appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Underhill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump and Kennedy Say They’d Free Ross Ulbricht. Biden Can Do That Right Now.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324288</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/trump-and-kennedy-say-theyd-free-ross-ulbricht-biden-can-do-that-right-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While panhandling for votes at the Libertarian National Convention over Memorial Day weekend, two non-Libertarian presidential candidates — Donald Trump and Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. — promised to free political prisoner Ross Ulbricht if elected. That promise is a big deal to Libertarians. Ulbricht, 40, is about a decade into his two life sentences, without  More
The post Trump and Kennedy Say They’d Free Ross Ulbricht. Biden Can Do That Right Now. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unfinished Journey of Palestinian Statehood]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324025</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/the-unfinished-journey-of-palestinian-statehood/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 22, Palestine was recognized as a state by Norway, Ireland, and Spain, bringing the number of countries recognizing Palestine as a state to over 140 of the 193 members of the United Nations. Yet, Palestine is still not a legal state. Moreover, the current political consensus is that the best solution to the  More
The post The Unfinished Journey of Palestinian Statehood appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping the Parallels of US Conflict: From Vietnam to the War on China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324204</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/mapping-the-parallels-of-us-conflict-from-vietnam-to-the-war-on-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 4th, 1964, President Lyndon B. Johnson stood in front of the American public and stated, “We Americans know, as do others though some may forget, the risk of spreading conflict. […] I shall immediately request Congress to pass a resolution to make it clear that our government is united in its determination to  More
The post Mapping the Parallels of US Conflict: From Vietnam to the War on China appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Gaza, Israel Trials New Face of America’s Imperial Laboratory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324141</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/in-gaza-israel-trials-new-face-of-americas-imperial-laboratory/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Saturday, October 7 2023, a significant shift occurred in the Palestinian-Israeli narrative. A normalised, gradual genocide over 76 years of Zionist colonialism, peppered by savage episodes of “mowing the lawn”, obscured by liberal Zionist propaganda and backed by imperial Washington, became an unapologetic, even gleeful mass murder of Palestinians, grotesquely captured on video for the world  More
The post In Gaza, Israel Trials New Face of America’s Imperial Laboratory appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peace No More: A Prayer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324150</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/peace-no-more-a-prayer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t believe in peace anymore. I used to think of myself as a pacifist. Now I’m not so sure. Today I understand what the slogan “No Justice, No Peace” means. But I want more than justice. I would be ok with nearly anything if it stopped the genocide in its tracks. “Does that mean  More
The post Peace No More: A Prayer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fred Baumgarten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End Rent-a-Halo Bullshit: Separate Piety and Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324041</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/end-rent-a-halo-bullshit-separate-piety-and-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The First Amendment of the Constitution specifies, “Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof.” In Washington, the “free exercise thereof” perennially includes politicians exploiting religion to sanctify themselves and all their power grabs. One of the most brazen if not most shameless “free exercise thereof” examples  More
The post End Rent-a-Halo Bullshit: Separate Piety and Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine: Still Not the Good War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/ukraine-still-not-the-good-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian bogeyman is played out. The threat of a Russian empire is as empty as Joe Biden’s scolding of Israel’s slaughter in Gaza or Donald Trump’s protestations of innocence. This doesn’t mean that I support the current government in Moscow. Nor does it mean its war in Ukraine is something I support. It does  More
The post Ukraine: Still Not the Good War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electoral Outcome Means a Worrying Future for South Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324197</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/electoral-outcome-means-a-worrying-future-for-south-africa/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:48:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although there are still many votes to be counted the broad outlines of the South African election are clear. There are four key factors for the left to consider. One is that, outside of some largely rural provinces, support for the African National Congress (ANC), the party of Nelson Mandela, is now in steep decline.  More
The post Electoral Outcome Means a Worrying Future for South Africa  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imraan Buccus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Oil & Gas – Hello Thermal Bricks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324139</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/goodbye-oil-gas-hello-thermal-bricks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of energy struggles with the nearly impossible task of getting off fossil fuels. This requires thinking outside of the box, something revolutionary bustling with energy that bails us out of sluggish fossil fuels that emit too much CO2 into the atmosphere and rapidly overheats the planet. The CO2/global warming relationship, joined at the  More
The post Goodbye Oil & Gas – Hello Thermal Bricks appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of MoMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323912</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/in-praise-of-moma/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I think the big difference between a place like the Museum of Modern Art and a more historical or universal institution is that those institutions start with the premise that they are about history and we start with the premise that we’re ahistorical, that history is a byproduct of what we do. If we do  More
The post In Praise of MoMA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Kids These Days”: Ending the American Tradition of Demonizing the Young]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324182</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/kids-these-days-ending-the-american-tradition-of-demonizing-the-young/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:43:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“History is hard to know, because of all the hired bullshit, but even without being sure of “history” it seems entirely reasonable to think that every now and then the energy of a whole generation comes to a head in a long fine flash, for reasons that nobody really understands at the time—and which never  More
The post “Kids These Days”: Ending the American Tradition of Demonizing the Young appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicky Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Prehistoric Humans Discovered Fire Making]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324148</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/how-prehistoric-humans-discovered-fire-making/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In ancient Greek myth tells the story of Prometheus, who, after molding humans out of clay and teaching them the fine arts of civilization, defied the Olympian Gods by stealing the secret of fire and offering it to humans. Prometheus paid dearly for this act of transgression that doted humankind with unprecedented technological know-how ultimately transforming  More
The post How Prehistoric Humans Discovered Fire Making  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Barsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prescribed Burning: an Overrated Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324052</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/prescribed-burning-an-overrated-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Deschutes National Forest plans to ramp up prescribed burns across Central Oregon. However, the Forest Service exaggerates the presumed benefits of prescribed burning and ignores the problems. One of the most important issues is that  most wildfires never encounter a fuel reduction, whether from thinning or prescribed burns. So, even if prescribed burns were  More
The post Prescribed Burning: an Overrated Strategy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lethal Workplaces: Deaths on the Job Continue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324163</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/lethal-workplaces-deaths-on-the-job-continue/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:40:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National Council for Occupational Safety and Health (National COSH) announced “The Dirty Dozen” employers of 2024 recently. Who are the Dirty Dozen? They are members of an employer class, a tiny minority of the population, which put the vast majority of workers and communities at-risk due to unsafe practices, leading to preventable illnesses, injuries  More
The post Lethal Workplaces: Deaths on the Job Continue appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Sandronsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are We Kafkaesque?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324035</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/why-are-we-kafkaesque/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the late 1980s, still during the communist era, while visiting Prague, a friend gave me Franz Kafka’s ‘The Castle’ in Czech. It was an edition from the 1960s, the decade leading up to the Prague Spring, when publishing and reading Kafka was allowed in Czechoslovakia, albeit for a short time. After the Russian invasion  More
The post Why Are We Kafkaesque? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monika Zgustova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tower of Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324198</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/tower-of-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Johann Sebastian Bach’s last pupil, Johann Gottfried Müthel (1728–88) spent the final two decades of his life as a church organist in the Baltic city of Riga, far to the northeast of the three central German cities (Erfurt, Gotha, and Leipzig in the Lutheran—and Bach family—heartland) and two Bavarian ones (bi-confessional Augsburg and Catholic Munich)  More
The post Tower of Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Flags Over the Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324157</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/red-flags-over-the-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s highest court is supposed to be impartial — especially when it comes to our elections and constitutional rights. Unfortunately, Supreme Court Justice Samuel Alito has been sending not very subtle signals that he’s aligned with former President Donald Trump’s MAGA movement — and the exclusionary Christian nationalism that motivates many of Trump’s followers. Americans learned recently  More
The post Red Flags Over the Supreme Court appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Montgomery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irish American Punk Musician Mat Callahan Takes Deep Dive into Black American Music and Song]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324153</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/irish-american-punk-musician-mat-callahan-takes-deep-dive-into-black-american-music-and-song/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a white guy and so is my friend and comrade, Mat Callahan, both of us reinventing ourselves in the aftermath of the Black Lives Matter movement, like other white guys who have wanted to stay relevant. Callahan and I both grew up in lefty families listening to Paul Robeson, Odetta and Leadbelly and learning  More
The post Irish American Punk Musician Mat Callahan Takes Deep Dive into Black American Music and Song  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animals Self-Medicate With Plants, Behavior People Have Observed and Emulated for Millennia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323978</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/animals-self-medicate-with-plants-behavior-people-have-observed-and-emulated-for-millennia/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A goat with an arrow wound nibbles the medicinal herb dittany. O. Dapper, CC BY When a wild orangutan in Sumatra recently suffered a facial wound, apparently after fighting with another male, he did something that caught the attention of the scientists observing him. The animal chewed the leaves of a liana vine – a  More
The post Animals Self-Medicate With Plants, Behavior People Have Observed and Emulated for Millennia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrienne Mayor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Uses of Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324171</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/31/donald-trump-and-the-uses-of-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a wide-ranging interview with a Time Magazine reporter this past April, Donald Trump said he expected victory in the coming presidential election, but he wouldn’t rule out the possibility of political violence if victory didn’t materialize. As he explained, “I don’t think we’re going to have that [political violence]. I think we’re going to  More
The post Donald Trump and the Uses of Violence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Israel Kill Public Support for America’s Bipartisan Consensus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272460</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/will-israel-kill-public-support-for-americas-bipartisan-consensus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T05:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a tiny silver lining in the Israel genocide in Gaza?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by coolgoose in "Things you wish you didn't need to know about S3"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40531553</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40531553"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T04:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of them are interesting points, but I am not sure I agree with the complaint the file system is case sensitive.
That's how it should be and I am annoyed at macos for not having it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coolgoose</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[who's afraid of a big bad word?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/big-bad-word/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/big-bad-word/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T03:03:42.726Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I got coffee with a college friend who I last saw in July of 2023. In the months since then, she has not only quit her job, but also somehow gotten engaged AND married (in a courthouse wedding) without telling any of us. What is going on? Life is going 80 in a school zone and I don’t have my seat belt on. I haven't even met her boyfriend (now husband) yet.
This is the third friend I grew up with to get married, and with all of them I struggle to use the right terms to refer to their partners. It's not that I don't know the words. First fiancée, then husband and wife. I'll start sentences fully intending to use the most up-to-date term but midway through 'husband' will catch in my mouth and 'boyfriend' will slip out instead.
Most of this can be chalked up to unfamiliarity. I've been u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by LeoPanthera in "Steam's Last Stand"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40530992</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40530992"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T02:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know about the post title rule but I would be surprised if anyone clicks on this not assuming it's about the video game digital distribution service and storefront.
That said, here's a lovely video from YouTuber "Aging Wheels" about a (working!) scale model of a British steam truck: https://youtu.be/PFKa8K9qZBQ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LeoPanthera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jennie Bastian - Jennie Bastian, founder of Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jennie-bastian-jennie-bastian-founder-of-communication?v=1717108670</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jennie-bastian-jennie-bastian-founder-of-communication?v=1717108670"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jennie Bastian
Title: Jennie Bastian, founder of Communication
Date: May 21 2024
Source: Retrieved on May 30 2024 from https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/65de9ee46569fa0017d9fc9d.

MK: Hello and welcome to THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES, a podcast about queer and neurodivergent kids living out anarchy and youth liberation. 
 Here at THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES we believe that youth autonomy is not only crucial to queer and trans liberation, but to anarchy itself. Governance is inherently based on projecting linear narratives of time and Development and gender onto our necessarily asynchronous and atemporal queer lives, and youth and teens are at the center of this form of oppression. 
 Our goal with the podcast is to create a space by and for youth that challenges all forms of control a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cate Moses - Cate Moses, Artist and Housing Advocate]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cate-moses-cate-moses-artist-and-housing-advocate?v=1717108373</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cate-moses-cate-moses-artist-and-housing-advocate?v=1717108373"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cate Moses
Title: Cate Moses, Artist and Housing Advocate
Date: April 23 2024
Source: Retrieved on May 30 2024 from https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/65de9ee46569fa0017d9fc9d.

 MK: Hello and welcome to THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES, a podcast about queer and neurodivergent kids living out anarchy and youth liberation. 
 Here at THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES we believe that youth autonomy is not only crucial to queer and trans liberation, but to anarchy itself. Governance is inherently based on projecting linear narratives of time and Development and gender onto our necessarily asynchronous and atemporal queer lives, and youth and teens are at the center of this form of oppression. 
 Our goal with the podcast is to create a space by and for youth that challenges all forms of control and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temperance Blyck - Temperance Blyck, The Youth-Liberationist Lockdown Activist]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/temperance-blyck-temperance-blyck-the-youth-liberationist-lockdown-activist?v=1717108254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/temperance-blyck-temperance-blyck-the-youth-liberationist-lockdown-activist?v=1717108254"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Temperance Blyck
Title: Temperance Blyck, The Youth-Liberationist Lockdown Activist
Date: April 23 2024
Source: Retrieved on May 30 2024 from https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/65de9ee46569fa0017d9fc9d.

 MK: Hello and welcome to THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES, a podcast about queer and neurodivergent kids living out anarchy and youth liberation. 
 Here at THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES we believe that youth autonomy is not only crucial to queer and trans liberation, but to anarchy itself. Governance is inherently based on projecting linear narratives of time and Development and gender onto our necessarily asynchronous and atemporal queer lives, and youth and teens are at the center of this form of oppression. 
 Our goal with the podcast is to create a space by and for youth that challenge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isabelle Santin - Isabelle Santin of Chosen Few Software]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/isabelle-santin-isabelle-santin-of-chosen-few-software?v=1717107905</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/isabelle-santin-isabelle-santin-of-chosen-few-software?v=1717107905"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Isabelle Santin
Title: Isabelle Santin of Chosen Few Software
Date: April 9 2024
Source: Retrieved on May 30 2024 from https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/65de9ee46569fa0017d9fc9d.

MK: Hello and welcome to THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES, a podcast about queer and neurodivergent kids living out anarchy and youth liberation. 
 Here at THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES we believe that youth autonomy is not only crucial to queer and trans liberation, but to anarchy itself. Governance is inherently based on projecting linear narratives of time and Development and gender onto our necessarily asynchronous and atemporal queer lives, and youth and teens are at the center of this form of oppression. 
 Our goal with the podcast is to create a space by and for youth that challenges all forms of control a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skye-Gia Garcia - Skye-Gia Garcia of OutReach LGBTQ+]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/skye-gia-garcia-skye-gia-garcia-of-outreach-lgbtq?v=1717107663</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/skye-gia-garcia-skye-gia-garcia-of-outreach-lgbtq?v=1717107663"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Skye-Gia Garcia
Title: Skye-Gia Garcia of OutReach LGBTQ+
Date: March 5, 2024
Source: Retrieved on May 30 2024 from https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/65de9ee46569fa0017d9fc9d.

MK: Hello and welcome to THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES, a podcast for and about queer and neurodivergent kids and teens living out anarchy and youth liberation. 
 Here at THE CHILD AND ITS ENEMIES we believe that youth autonomy is not only crucial to queer and trans liberation, but to anarchy itself. Governance is inherently based on projecting linear narratives of time and Development and gender onto our necessarily asynchronous and atemporal queer lives, and kids, teens, and everyone else affected by anti-child ageism are at the center of this form of oppression. 
 Our goal with the podcast is to create a s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by engineers_unite in "Unexpected anti-patterns for engineering leaders"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40529067</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40529067"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T21:46:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have seen Will Larson's techniques applied/ forced in multiple organizations and have found that his view of the engineering world just does not work. I sense that there is a cult of personality around him that leads to engineering ivory towers.
Most orgs that I've seen follow his writing or ideas have ended up in conflict with the business and one another, isolated on a corporate island, and then gutted by layoffs.
I don't like to throw an author/engineer under the bus but I do not know why this guy has a following. I have never seen his methods result in happy engineers and delivered value.
My summary of this article (for managers):
1. Micromanage early and often
2. Measure, and whatever you're measuring, act like it's truth and that you know best.
3. Listen to the curmudgeons and the naysayers because they are the true sources of knowledge.
Edit- as I mention in a reply, try https://pragprog.com/titles/rjnsd/the-nature-of-software-dev... Ron Jeffries' "The Nature of Software Development". Incremental value, engineers leading delivery, constant feedback cycles, flexibility. I've followed the tenets of this book in many orgs, and they lead to measurable value, happy engineers, and successful orgs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>engineers_unite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Adnate wins Archibald Packing Room Prize for Baker Boy painting]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7730</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/matt-adnate-wins-archibald-packing-room-prize-baker-boy-painting/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Adnate has been named the 2024 winner of the Archibald Prize’s Packing Room Prize, with his portrait of Indigenous Australian rapper Baker Boy, AKA Danzal Baker. As the name suggests, the prize is awarded by the staff of the packing room at the Art Gallery of New South Wales (AGNSW), which administers the Archibald. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ebolyen in "Don't DRY Your Code Prematurely"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40528380</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40528380"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know, that sounds like a complex kind of ingest which could be arbitrarily subtle and diverge over time for legal and bureaucratic reasons.
I would kind of appreciate having two formats, since what are the odds they would change together? While there may never be a 3rd format, a DRY importer would imply that the source generating the data is also DRY.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ebolyen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by blizdiddy in "What We're Working on in Firefox"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40527968</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40527968"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> More streamlined menus that reduce visual clutter and prioritize top user actions so you can get to the important things quicker
Oh no, more of this.
What about less used options? How much slower? How much less discoverable?
Desktop applications are already for power users almost by definition, let’s not slow them down for the sake of reducing “clutter”. Absolutely annoying trend of the last 15 years or so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blizdiddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272451</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics, Trump convicted on all 34 counts, yellow waders for Merchan's jury instructions, H5N1 breakout scenario, "Decolonize the gut!", "They were careless people...." ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly adopt new AWS features with the Terraform AWS Cloud Control provider]]></title>
        <id>7410c16db7d84ca3276967fb363607aab174008c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/quickly-adopt-new-aws-features-with-the-terraform-aws-cloud-control-provider/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS customers using Terraform as their IaC tool can now benefit from faster time-to-market by building cloud infrastructure with the latest AWS innovations that are typically available on the Terraform AWS CC Provider on the day of launch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Welly Siauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by joshstrange in "After 6 years, I'm over GraphQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525950</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525950"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought into the hype and I feel bad for the company where I implemented it. One true endpoint to rule them all and cause endless headaches in the process.
With most tech that I screw up I assume that "I wasn't using it right" but with GraphQL I'm not sure how anyone could. The permissions/auth aspect alone is a nightmare. Couple that with potential performance issues (N+1 or just massive amounts of data) and I want nothing to do with GraphQL anymore. Everything we attempted to fix our permissions issues just caused more problems. It would break existing queries and debugging GraphQL sucked so much.
If you only live on the frontend and someone else is responsible for the backend GraphQL then I understand why you might like it. From that perspective it's amazing, you can get as little or as much as you want with the specific fields you want. No waiting on the backend team to write an endpoint. However even then you end up saving queries as files or abstracting them (maybe IDE support has improved but it wasn't great last time I was using it ~5 years ago) and now you just have REST endpoints by another name.
At one point we considered whitelisting specific queries and that's when I knew we had gone too far and made a mess for ourselves. If we had taken the time to just write REST endpoints instead we would have gotten way more done and had way fewer grey hairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joshstrange</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by haswell in "Don't DRY Your Code Prematurely"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525690</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525690"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the #1 issues I’ve seen with DRY over the years seems to stem from a misunderstanding of what it means.
DRY is not just about code duplication, it’s about information/knowledge duplication, and code happens to be one representation of information.
Hyper focusing on code duplication quickly gets into premature optimization territory, and can result in DRYing things that don’t make sense. Focusing on information duplication leaves some leeway for the code and helps identify which parts of the code actually need DRY.
The difference is important, and later editions of the Pragmatic Programmer call this out specifically. But the concept of DRY often gets a bit twisted in my experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>haswell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hardwaregeek in "Don't DRY Your Code Prematurely"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525596</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40525596"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:28:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important to remember that all best practices are not created equal. I'd prioritize readability over DRY. I'd prioritize cohesion over extensibility. When people talk about best practices, they don't talk about how a lot of them are incompatible, or at least at odds with each other. Writing code is about choosing the best practices you want to prioritize as much as it's about avoiding bad practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hardwaregeek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Learn About Machine Learning on AWS]]></title>
        <id>a32ec7509a82a646ef6004dc3614ea1555925212</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-learn-about-machine-learning-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:01:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A data-driven approach empowers businesses to make informed decisions based on accurate predictions and forecasts, leading to improved operational efficiency and resource optimization. Machine learning (ML) systems have the remarkable ability to continuously learn and adapt, improving their performance over time as they are exposed to more data. This self-learning capability ensures that organizations can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kiney in "After 6 years, I'm over GraphQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40523957</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40523957"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T14:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unpopular opinion: I'm actually a fan of singe page specific endpoints. You get much easier debugging, easier to audit security, easier performance optimization an the imho pretty small price to pay is that it's "not elegant" and a bit of backend code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kiney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global South Suffering Due to Powerful Nations’ Elite-Serving Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272445</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/global-south-suffering-due-to-powerful-nations-elite-serving-policies.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank projects the worst slowdown in over four decades in 2024. This is mainly due to Western powers’ contractionary policies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by llm_trw in "I got tired of hearing that YC fired Sam, so here's what actually happened"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40523177</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40523177"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>multi-million dollar a year non-profit
At 24 I ended up as the chair of a not for profit that stood on top of $30 million of real estate _because no one else wanted to_. Getting quorum was impossible because we needed three out of five board members to show up to a meeting.
People have this idea it's mustache twirling villains running these things. It's usually the idiot thats about to burn out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>llm_trw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disrupting FlyingYeti's campaign targeting Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>66583c6f7d1754000b5c0dde</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/disrupting-flyingyeti-campaign-targeting-ukraine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April and May 2024, Cloudforce One employed proactive defense measures to successfully prevent Russia-aligned threat actor FlyingYeti from launching their latest phishing campaign targeting Ukraine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cloudforce One</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Kropotkin - A Russian Village]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-a-russian-village?v=1717071658</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-a-russian-village?v=1717071658"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Kropotkin
Title: A Russian Village
Date: 1902
Notes: Published in Northern Europe, pp. 109–122.
Source: Retrieved on 30th May 2024 from www.libertarian-labyrinth.org

 The first impression produced upon a stranger by a village in Great Russia is undoubtedly gloomy. The small, one-storied cottages have neither flowers in front nor clean, white-curtained windows. They look depressingly dark. The unwhitewashed walls are built of thick logs, if there are woods in the neighborhood, or else of rough stone. The windows, of which there are never more than three, are small, with tiny panes of glass,—for glass is expensive. 
 The straw roofs are unsightly, as in most cases they are unthatched and are merely made out of bundles of straw held together with straw ropes. Sometimes, when f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Kropotkin - Lending Libraries and Cheap Books]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-lending-libraries-and-cheap-books?v=1717071331</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-lending-libraries-and-cheap-books?v=1717071331"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Kropotkin
Title: Lending Libraries and Cheap Books
Date: January 1904
Notes: Published in The Nineteenth Century vol. 55, no. 323, pp. 69–78.
Source: Retrieved on 30th May 2024 from www.libertarian-labyrinth.org

 Much has been written lately in condemnation of the free libraries, on the ground that they were chiefly used by those who cared only for light reading, and that the more serious books were rarely in demand. It is quite true that out of each six books taken during the year from the free library five will be novels. But it would be quite unfair to take no notice of the considerable number of more serious books that are read as well. Taking, for instance, the annual report of our Bromley Library, I see that during the last twelve months more than seven thousand books…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Kropotkin - The Higher Education of Women in Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-the-higher-education-of-women-in-russia?v=1717071212</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-the-higher-education-of-women-in-russia?v=1717071212"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Kropotkin
Title: The Higher Education of Women in Russia
Date: January 1898
Notes: Published in The Nineteenth Century vol. 43, no. 251, pp. 117–134.
Source: Retrieved on 30th May 2024 from www.libertarian-labyrinth.org

 THE Russian educated woman is known to some extent in this country for the part which she took in the struggles for political freedom. Very little is known, however, about the hard, and often really heroic, struggles which Russian women have sustained simply to obtain the right to a better education; still less about the wonderful organizing powers which they have displayed in the creation and maintenance of their educational institutions. 
 If women have to struggle hard for their rights in this country, one can easily imagine the resistance they had to ov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare acquires BastionZero to extend Zero Trust access to IT infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>6657afb17d1754000b5c0d82</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-acquires-bastionzero"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce that BastionZero, a Zero Trust infrastructure access platform, has joined Cloudflare. This acquisition extends our Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA) flows with native access management for infrastructure like servers, Kubernetes clusters, and databases]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenny Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Kropotkin - Intensive Farming in Flanders]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-intensive-farming-in-flanders?v=1717071056</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-intensive-farming-in-flanders?v=1717071056"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Kropotkin
Title: Intensive Farming in Flanders
Date: July 1915
Notes: Published in The Contemporary Review vol. 108, no. 595, pp. 105–112.
Source: Retrieved on 30th May 2024 from www.libertarian-labyrinth.org

I.
 THE necessity of growing more foodstuffs in this country has perhaps never been so evident as it is now. That the population of these islands does not obtain from its land all that it could is no longer contested. Thus the question arises—Cannot we take advantage of the considerable numbers of Belgians, especially from Flanders, to whom we are giving hospitality, to learn something about their methods of intensive farming? Could not, let us say, several County Councils, especially in those counties where there are patches of a lighter soil, establish a number of sm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Kropotkin - The Wife of Number 4,237]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-the-wife-of-number-4-237?v=1717070746</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-kropotkin-the-wife-of-number-4-237?v=1717070746"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Kropotkin
Title: The Wife of Number 4,237
Date: 1886
Notes: Based on Sophie Kropotkin’s own experience with her husband at Clairvaux prison. Translated for Liberty by Sarah E. Holmes.
Source: Retrieved on 30th May 2024 from www.libertarian-labyrinth.org

I.
 The train had just arrived at the station of N—–, an out-of-the-way place on one of the branches of the South-Eastern system. The few travellers alighted—three men and a woman—and stood on the platform, waiting till the way was deal- to cross to the other side and make their way out. 
 The men belonged in the vicinity and knew each other. They talked together, while the woman—a young brunette, thin and poorly dressed in black—stood apart, leaning on the railing. Her eyes roved over the surrounding country and seemed to s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neom in "I got tired of hearing that YC fired Sam, so here's what actually happened"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40522394</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40522394"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T11:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ran a multi-million dollar a year non-profit and had a full-time job. It's not unusual to chair or "run" a non-profit and have a regular job, non-profits are actually set up to make this easy to do. If that non-profit somehow mystically turned into a for-profit enterprise, for a multitude of reasons (some less obvious) I would have clearly had to pick one or the other. If said non-profit had commercialized transformer as a service, I'd have quit DigitalOcean (double so if I was well vested).
Just to make it fair with the situation: I honestly don't know if I would have proactively quit one or the other. Depending on the workloads, I may very well have tried to moonlight both for a while, I'm unsure.
I don't think this tweet by Paul is weird at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0-bad-secrotrs in "After 6 years, I'm over GraphQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40522307</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40522307"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T11:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aside from all the valid points listed in the blog I found out that the frontend engineers in my company save some queries in central library and reuse them even if they don't need all the field returned by this array just to save themselves the time they spend writing queries so they are basically using GraphQL as REST at the end and now we have the worst of both worlds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0-bad-secrotrs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272420</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-29-2024-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T10:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's warbling links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atsjie in "After 6 years, I'm over GraphQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40521939</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40521939"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T10:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worked on two GraphQL projects; I was quickly cured from the hype. I recognize a lot of points in this article.
In both these projects the GraphQL had started small. I came in during a more mature phase of these projects (2 and 4 years). That's where the requirements are harder, more specific, and overall complexity has grown. Adoption and demand on the API were growing quickly. Hence you logically spend more time debugging, this is true for any codebase.
But GraphQL has everything in it to make such problems even harder. And both these projects had clear signs of "learning-on-the-go" with loads of bad practices (especially for the N+1 problem). Issue descriptions were much vaguer, harder to find in logs and performance issues popped up in the most random places (code that had been running and untouched for ages).
Fun fact; in both these projects the original devs who set it up were no longer involved. Probably spreading their evangalism further elsewhere.
RPC and REST are just more straightforward to monitor, log, cache, authorize and debug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atsjie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwaway_5753 in "I got tired of hearing that YC fired Sam, so here's what actually happened"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40521793</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40521793"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T09:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people here bending over backwards to try to interpret this maximally negatively.
Probably because the "Sam Altman is an amoral, power hungry mastermind who was run out of all his previous gigs" is a more interesting narrative than whatever is actually happening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway_5753</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding people because of what you suspect they might think]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52730</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/30/avoiding-people-because-of-what-you-suspect-they-might-think/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T09:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something that’s bothered me for a while is the relationship between politics and friendship. Not just close friendship but also people who you are happy to hang out with socially. Some topics – I’d include Brexit, trans rights and Israel/Palestine – are especially divisive in that people who disagree on these seem to find it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zellyn in "How Waymo outlasted the competition and made robo-taxis a real business"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40520939</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40520939"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T06:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems silly. It’s been obvious even to casual observers like myself for years that Waymo/Google was one of the only groups taking the problem seriously and trying to actually solve it, as opposed to pretending you could add self-driving with just cameras in an over-the-air update (Tesla), or trying to move fast and break things (Uber), or pretending you could gradually improve lane-keeping all the way into autonomous driving (car manufacturers). That’s why it’s working for them. (IIUC, Cruise has pretty much also always been legit?)
Don’t even get me started on the “didn’t take psych 102: Attention and Memory”-level cluelessness required to believe a human can safely pay attention well enough in a vehicle that reliably tricks you into believing it’s autonomous to take over in the split seconds before a disaster…
I find it hard to believe that the Tesla and Auto Manufacturer positions aren’t knowingly deceptive. I mean, what are they going to say? “It’s too hard so we’re just waiting for Waymo or Cruise to license their tech once it works”?
I’m gonna stop here before I start mocking geohot… I seriously can’t believe the journalists who wrote those early stories were willing to risk their lives like that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zellyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i'm alive, what a thing to be]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/im-alive-what-a-thing-to-be/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/im-alive-what-a-thing-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T01:40:06.149Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not normally a person thankful for life. I've been existing, not living, for a long time. I wake up, do what I have to do to keep my scholarship and my body in decent condition, and go to sleep. Repeat. My days have a rhythm I don't necessarily enjoy, because college life is the same stressful day over and over again, with a little respite here and there. And it's like, God, I'm 20 years old. I should be at the club.
But life goes on regardless, so here I am, at 9 a.m., eating a bowl of thick oatmeal and writing this post. I don't know what exactly made me write this. The oatmeal? My 2024 planner slowly approaching the halfway mark? The sunlight filtering through the curtains? Maybe it's the fact that I don't have anything to go to today except lunch with a friend. Being able to take it slow in the morning, enough to think about things like this, is rare.
I'm alive. That's something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[free your mind]]></title>
        <id>https://sh0zone.com/mind/</id>
        <link href="https://sh0zone.com/mind/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T01:17:37.526Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by khazhoux in "Google releases smart watch for kids"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40519047</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40519047"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T01:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> This constant tracking of kids is unnecessary and dangerous. Generations of kids survived without their parents needing to know their location at all times.
This topic is always so alarmist.  I have kids and a spouse.  We all have Find My and Location Sharing on our phones.  I don't FrEaK oUt that my kids are going to die if I'm not tracking their every movement.  But it's nice to glance at Find My app and see if the kids are still hanging out at Starbucks or they got to school on time.  It's convenient to see which corner of the park they're at when I need to go pick them up.  I can see if my wife's still at Whole Foods and send her a message to pick up baru nuts.  They can see if I'm still at work or headed home.
This idea of helicopter parents vs free-range glory is a false dichotomy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>khazhoux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I love bearblog]]></title>
        <id>https://stern.bearblog.dev/i-love-bearblog/</id>
        <link href="https://stern.bearblog.dev/i-love-bearblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the iron laws of people being creative on the internet is that it’s only a matter of time until the haters arrive.
Yesterday on Twitter, I saw post after post mocking the increasing popularity of bearblog, the “bear”-bones blogging platform that simply gives people a blank slate and lets them go at it. One post derided certain bearbloggers as “Mini Navals” -- essentially, amateurish wannabes in their early 20s regurgitating the wisdom of Naval without any life experience. Another mocked the entire activity of writing short essays and taking screenshots of them. "Put white text on a dark blue background. The essay does not even need to be good. Follow the trend..."
To the contrary - I'm loving the trend. Who cares if a few posts are cliché or badly written or a little amateurish. Sure, there’s some middling stuff on bearblog. But I’ve encountered dozens of essays that are genuinely superb. My favorite writer is Prakhesar, a Canadian who’s turned his life around in the last couple years and has taken to bearblog to tell the world about it.
In this age of spammy ads and cookie banners, the internet has become an overgrown forest. Amidst it all, bearblog stands tall as a quiet, "old-internet" venue -- a corner of the web well worth preserving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "Google releases smart watch for kids"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40517658</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40517658"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T22:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ugh, I threw up a little in my mouth just from the headline.
This constant tracking of kids is unnecessary and dangerous. Generations of kids survived without their parents needing to know their location at all times.
And yes, I totally admit, some kids (very few actually depending on the locale) didn't survive. But we've traded this false sense of "safety" for kids that are so risk averse it is seriously negatively affecting their development. I highly recommend the writings of Jonathan Haidt - he not only has great arguments but also has a lot of data to back up his conclusions.
Kids don't need more tech, they need less of it (and FWIW, most adults, too).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy birthday WordPress, twenty-one and going strong]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7725</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/happy-birthday-wordpress-twenty-one-going-strong/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a bit late to the party, but such is life in the twenty-first century. The other day WordPress (WP), the CMS that powers disassociated turned twenty-one (Facebook link)*. I’ve been on-board since 2007. You’ll only find a handful of posts from those days though, I rebooted my website in 2021, after taking a slightly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[more bus rides with friends!]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/bus-rides-friends/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/bus-rides-friends/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T19:40:27.800Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently read Kristin's post where she notes that a lot of blogs have a very serious tone to them, and laughed because it was something I clocked too, at least in my own posting behavior recently!
I think I naturally like to reflect, but I'd noticed that whenever I came on here, I found myself endeavoring to write Thoughtful Posts about Realizations and Things That Matter1, because a lot of the posts I read were (either intentionally or naturally) Thoughtful Posts about Realizations and Things That Matter. That's not necessarily bad, but I'm happy for the reminder to unclench. Honestly, I personally prefer reading the day-to-day, thesis-less stuff myself.2
Last Sunday I went on an overnight staycation with my friends at a small villa on the outskirts of the city! It started out a little …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wmf in "Google releases smart watch for kids"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515345</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515345"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartwatches may be an overlooked answer to the kid phone conundrum. Watches have the communication and location tracking that parents demand without the distraction of phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wmf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shooker435 in "I sold TinyPilot, my first successful business"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515340</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515340"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mindset assumes that the only measure of success is monetary. If he left Google to try and get richer than staying at Google, then sure, he probably lost.
However, he kept trying again before job hunting or returning to big tech. This tells me the monetary factor was smaller than something else.
You mention the underrated educational experience in your last sentence, but there's so much more than that. He was probably never worried about his autonomy, being laid off, working with (or for) people he didn't want to work with, corporate politics, or anything else corporate bureaucracy introduces. This likely freed up his brain to be more creative and actually be used to 100% of its capacity.
I believe the obsession with TC in tech is highly problematic and there are a lot of talented folks optimizing for promotions via internal politics, rather than solving real problems for real people.
I also wish healthcare wasn't tied to employment, but that's a post for another time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shooker435</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sandofsky in "Kino: Pro Video Camera"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515201</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40515201"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry you ran into that. I distinctly remember testing the 13 mini, due to notch layout issues, so this is unexpected. As soon as the crash reports come in, we’ll dig into that.
Unfortunately, while we had a QA person on this, and nearly 100 beta testers, the iPhone camera APIs are a mine field. We’ll get a fix out as soon as we have details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sandofsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS analytics services streamline user access to data, permissions setting, and auditing]]></title>
        <id>3d2c5cbd28c5ac61507b809afe28f8c149527f4a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-analytics-services-streamline-user-access-to-data-permissions-setting-and-auditing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline data access with trusted identity propagation: simplify sign-in, define fine-grained permissions, and audit using actual user identities across selected AWS analytics services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by foobiekr in "Codestral: Mistral's Code Model"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513335</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513335"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's some irony in the fact that people will ignore this license in exactly the same way Mistral and all the other LLM guys ignore the copyright and licensing on the works they ingest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>foobiekr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by analyte123 in "Codestral: Mistral's Code Model"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513224</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513224"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The license for this [1] prohibits use of the model and its outputs for any commercial activity, or even any "live" (whatever that means) conditions, commercial or not.
There seems to be an exclusion for using the code outputs as part of "development". But wait! It also prohibits "any internal usage by employees in the context of the company's business activities". However you interpret these clauses, this puts their claims and comparisons on completely unequal ground. They only compare to other open-weight models, not GPT-4 or Opus, but a normal company or individual can do whatever they want with the Llama weights and outputs. LangChain? "Your favourite coding and building environment"? Who cares? It seems you're not allowed to integrate this with anything else and show it to anyone, even as an art project.
[1] https://mistral.ai/licenses/MNPL-0.1.md]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>analyte123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by piltdownman in "Ottawa wants the power to create secret backdoors in networks for surveillance"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513148</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40513148"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada has the power to backdoor telecom networks for surveillance. All host nations do for their infrastructure as part of the RAN Architecture
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lawful_interception
What Canada seems to actually want is a way of doing this without legal oversight or recourse to traditional legal gatekeeping like warrants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>piltdownman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Powers: &ldquo;Capital&#8217;s Emirates&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/capitals-emirates</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/capitals-emirates"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T14:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UAE and US hegemony.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking Stock: Dollar Assets, Gold, and Official Foreign Exchange Reserves]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30121</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/taking-stock-dollar-assets-gold-and-official-foreign-exchange-reserves/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global central banks and finance ministries held nearly $12 trillion of foreign exchange reserves as of the end of 2023, with nearly $7 trillion composed of U.S. dollar assets. Nevertheless, a narrative has emerged that an observed decline in the share of dollar assets in official reserve portfolios represents the leading edge of the dollar’s loss of status in the international monetary system. Some market participants have similarly linked the apparent increase in official demand for gold in recent years to a desire to diversify away from the U.S. dollar. Drawing on recent research and analytics, this post questions these narratives, arguing that these observed aggregate trends largely reflect the behavior of a small number of countries and do not represent a widespread effort by central banks to diversify away from dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Douglass, Linda S. Goldberg, and Oliver Z. Hannaoui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa: hanging on]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/South-Africa-hanging-on</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/South-Africa-hanging-on"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T10:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa has a general election today with 28m citizens registered to vote. Since the end of the apartheid regime three decades ago, the African National Congress (ANC) has won all the elections with substantial majorities. But this time there is the possibility that the ANC will poll less than 50% of those voting. 
English

/ 
Poverty, 
South Africa, 
Inequality, 
Precarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the Theil inequality index to show and analyse increased colonial exploitation]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45383</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/29/using-the-theil-inequality-index-to-show-and-analyse-increased-colonial-exploitation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T09:26:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some time ago, I delved into the unique advantages of the Theil index of inequality over the Gini index, when data is available. The Theil index offers a distinct advantage in its ability to provide a consistent quantitative deconstruction of inequality. It does so by utilizing various concepts such as class, region, gender, or any […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mediocre by whose standards?]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/mediocre-by-whose-standards/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/mediocre-by-whose-standards/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T09:20:45.127Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a tweet that rubbed me the wrong way.
It stated: "Mediocre people often have a clear tell: you'll often see them hanging out with other mediocre people, probably because the A+ folks avoid them."
This reeks of the kind of elitist, self-congratulatory attitude that plagues certain circles. Who determines what makes someone "mediocre" or an "A+"? By what metrics are we judging the worth and value of human beings? The premise that accomplished people inherently avoid those deemed "mediocre" is flawed and perpetuates an unhealthy way of viewing the world and those around us.
Excellence has nothing to do with shutting others out or surrounding yourself with a self-selected elite group. In fact, I would argue the most exceptional people seek out a diversity of viewpoints and backgrounds. They don't just associate with some narrowly defined cohort of "A+ folks." The insinuation that the company you keep is the mark of your mediocrity is short-sighted at best.
Perhaps this tweet was merely an attempt at provocation...
 and I've all fallen for the bait.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Meltzer Commission on the IFI at the US Congress in 2000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Meltzer-Commission-on-the-IFI-at-the-US-Congress-in-2000</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Meltzer-Commission-on-the-IFI-at-the-US-Congress-in-2000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 high memory U7i Instances for large in-memory databases]]></title>
        <id>8c871b2347245a09a7506da5264f862fb0203d42</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-high-memory-u7i-instances-for-large-in-memory-databases/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T23:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash unparalleled power with U7i instances: up to 32 TiB DDR5 memory, 896 vCPUs, and unmatched performance for in-memory databases like SAP HANA, Oracle, and SQL Server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASBO - Solidarity and its Discontents?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/asbo-solidarity-and-its-discontents?v=1716936084</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/asbo-solidarity-and-its-discontents?v=1716936084"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T22:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: ASBO
Title: Solidarity and its Discontents?
Subtitle: Riots, Rebellion and Repression in Bristol 2011-2023
Date: 01/24
Source: https://bangupandsmash.noblogs.org/downloads/



The media, the schools, the judges, the cops, politicians, surveillance, technology, work. All have their role to play in repression. [1]
 Concepts and practices such as repression and solidarity have become amorphous and widespread. (I would also add ‘abolition’ to this stack of buzz words, but that might just be my 2p).[2] As with any word that conveniently describes a complex phenomenon (see also gentrification, ‘burn-out’, ‘trauma’, ‘affinity’ etc.) they are both a help and a hindrance. All these words are difficult to discuss because they combine personal experiences with repressive practices deliberatel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 26, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240528</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240528"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sasha k, Wolfi Landstreicher, Leila - Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sasha-k-wolfi-landstreicher-leila-introduction?v=1716931094</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sasha-k-wolfi-landstreicher-leila-introduction?v=1716931094"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T21:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: sasha k, Wolfi Landstreicher, Leila
Title: Introduction
Subtitle: Killing King Abacus
Date: 2000
Notes: This article originally appeared in Killing King Abacus #1
Source: Retrieved on May 28, 2024 from https://writerror.com/texts/Killing-King-Abacus-Introduction

Killing King Abacus
 To Kill King Abacus is to create relations without measure. If we aim to destroy capitalism we cannot reproduce its necrophilic logic which reduces relationships to numbers. To Kill King Abacus is to destroy the social net which privileges mediated transactions and images over direct relations. Because money is a general equivalent and thus is nearly limitless in its applications, it conquers other signifiers of value; capitalism transforms other value systems into itself. To Kill King Abacus is to dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Starbucks gives you lemon lattes, go co-work at McDonalds]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7713</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/starbucks-gives-lemon-lattes-co-work-at-mcdonalds/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Meerkamper, writing at Spacing, laments the apparent demise of the once omnipresent commercial third place, a kind of neutral zone between home and work, such as a cafe, where people gather. Or where remote workers can set up shop for the day. Coffee houses are one of the earliest examples of ‘Third Places,’ a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An art deco delight by night in the Sydney suburb of Randwick]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7719</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/photo-art-deco-delight-night-sydney-suburb-randwick/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Randwick is a large suburb located about five kilometres south east of downtown Sydney, Australia. It is home to the Prince of Wales hospital, Royal Randwick Racecourse, a thriving commercial and retail hub, large bus and light rail depots, the historic Ritz Cinemas, and arguably, the University of New South Wales (UNSW). Even though UNSW […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Platform Explained Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7123</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/data-platform-explained-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T18:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out Data Platform Explained Part I, where we started sharing the journey of building a data platform, its building [...]
The post Data Platform Explained Part II  appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus - Errico Malatesta: A Brief Biography]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-errico-malatesta-a-brief-biography?v=1716910492</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-errico-malatesta-a-brief-biography?v=1716910492"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T15:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus
Title: Errico Malatesta: A Brief Biography
Date: 2020
Notes: A brief biographical statement used to preface a reader for the DSA LSC Political Education Working Group's Malatesta Reader, which was used in a series of study circles in 2020 to explore Malatesta's "Anarchy," "Towards Anarchy," and " An Anarchist Programme".

 Errico Malatesta was born to a family of middle-class landowners in Santa Maria Capua Vetere, Italy on 14 December 1853. More distantly, his ancestors ruled Rimini as the House of Malatesta. The first of a long series of arrests came at age fourteen, when he was apprehended for writing an "insolent and threatening" letter to King Victor Emmanuel II . 
 Malatesta was introduced to Mazzinian Republicanism while studying medicine at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports of a death exaggerated]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52718</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/28/reports-of-a-death-exaggerated/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a metaphor. There’s an elderly person you’ve known for years.  Not a close relative, no, but someone whose career you’ve followed.  You feel tremendous respect for them, maybe some affection. They’re getting old and frail, but they’ve kept active.  Now and then you might see an article or something, and you’ll think, huh: still […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turning a rotten brain into a blog]]></title>
        <id>https://fatine.bearblog.dev/turning-a-rotten-brain-into-a-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://fatine.bearblog.dev/turning-a-rotten-brain-into-a-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:39:12.771Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I came across a content creator who stated that the antidote to the overconsumption of media content or any sort of information is creation, and it struck a chord with me.
My name is Fatine, I am a 23-year-old student, and that is all you need to know for now.
My consumption tendencies are not unique to me. The fact that Gen Z is a highly connected generation is undeniable, but I have come to the conclusion that it is not something to combat; the aim should be to counterbalance it. One has got to find a good habit that is a byproduct of consumption but makes it profitable. I think writing ticks all the boxes, given the fact that you must absorb a considerable amount of valuable information in order to produce coherently written thoughts.
During these past six months, I went through episodes of overstimulation that triggered the urge to go on long rants about specific topics. These topics were mainly recognized patterns from day-to-day observations and café discussions, all linked, in my opinion, to social media phenomena.
"Dump it" is a self-discovery journey where I try to turn months of introspection and café conversations into concise paragraphs, backed by research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Exchange‑Traded Products Improve Bitcoin Trading?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30080</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-exchange-traded-products-improve-bitcoin-trading/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin exchange-traded products (ETPs) began trading in the U.S. on January 11, 2024. For investors, these ETPs purport improved liquidity and price efficiency, and more convenient access to bitcoin trading compared to other means of trading bitcoin in spot markets. Proponents also cite bitcoin holdings as a portfolio diversification opportunity due to historically low correlation with traditional financial securities. Others argue that bitcoin remains a speculative asset and that ETPs increase its interconnections with the traditional financial system. In this post, we examine the initial performance, trading costs, and price efficiency of spot bitcoin ETPs in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Armstrong, Asani Sarkar, and Leslie Conner Warren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anark - A Modern Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anark-a-modern-anarchism?v=1716865569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anark-a-modern-anarchism?v=1716865569"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T03:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anark
Title: A Modern Anarchism
Date: 2022
Notes: Originally published in video format on the YouTube channel Anark, this piece combines the three-part essay A Modern Anarchism by Daniel Baryon into one document.
Source: Retrieved on 5/27/2024 from https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-1-anarchist-analysis https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-2-anarchy and https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-3-revolution

Part 1: Anarchist Analysis
Introduction
 We stand now at a turning point, wherein many roads sprawl out in front of us. With unprecedented access to information, the atlas seems to lie within our hands. But, at this crossroads, the popularizers of these many paths shout over one another to persuade new travelers, only to find that most travelers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creative environments, are they a place or a time, or both?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7702</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/creative-environments-place-time-both/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your mission, should you choose to accept it: write about creative environments. Let’s have a go. A creative environment, as far as I can tell, is not necessarily a place. Not one I can put my finger on, at least. Nor is it a particular time. My creative ideas, if that’s what they can be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: LlamaIndex support for Amazon Neptune, force AWS CloudFormation stack deletion, and more (May 27, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>1bf9fbbce923c6324942d76ec84a66ab6cd7527a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-llamaindex-support-for-amazon-neptune-force-aws-cloudformation-stack-deletion-and-more-may-27-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Dr. Matt Wood, VP for AI Products at Amazon Web Services (AWS), delivered the keynote at the AWS Summit Los Angeles. Matt and guest speakers shared the latest advancements in generative artificial intelligence (generative AI), developer tooling, and foundational infrastructure, showcasing how they come together to change what’s possible for builders. You can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whipping up disaster: how Brazil became a lab for financial agro-investments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Whipping-up-disaster-how-Brazil-became-a-lab-for-financial-agro-investments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Whipping-up-disaster-how-Brazil-became-a-lab-for-financial-agro-investments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T18:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Agro is pop, agro is tech, agro is everything” states a popular slogan in adverts broadcast on Brazil's largest TV channel since 2016. Financed by agribusiness, these advertisements portray a virtuous cycle, showcasing images of contented rural workers amidst soybean, corn, cotton, and sugar cane plantations, as well as happy urban families. They are all content because they can feed, clothe themselves, and fuel their cars, thanks to the agro-industry. 
English

/ 
Brazil, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GRAIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eunice Minette Schuster - Native American Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eunice-minette-schuster-native-american-anarchism?v=1716826080</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eunice-minette-schuster-native-american-anarchism?v=1716826080"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eunice Minette Schuster
Title: Native American Anarchism
Subtitle: A Study of Left-Wing American Individualism
Date: 1932
Notes: What is meant by ‘Native American’ in the title is ‘local to America’, not ‘indigenous American’. The text undoubtedly still contains many OCR errors that are hard to find without reading the entire book. Finally, some text appears missing through errors in how the book was originally published, such as a paragraph ends naturally with a period at the end of page 112, but then begins half-way through a sentence at the beginning of page 113 (“exchange and recognized that money”).
Source: <archive.org/details/nativeamericanan0000schu>

Preface
 The writer has attempted in the following study to delineate the character and form of native American anarchism an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohammed Bamyeh & Uri Gordon - The No State Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mohammed-bamyeh-uri-gordon-the-no-state-solution?v=1716820647</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mohammed-bamyeh-uri-gordon-the-no-state-solution?v=1716820647"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mohammed Bamyeh & Uri Gordon
Title: The No State Solution
Subtitle: A Dialogue with Palestinian sociologist Mohammed Bamyeh & Israeli political scientist Uri Gordon
Date: January 28 2024
Notes: This zine is a transcription of The No State Solution: A Dialogue with Palestinian sociologist Mohammed Bamyeh & Israeli political scientist Uri Gordon, a live and recorded event which took place on January 22, 2024 in unceded Lekwungen territory in so-called occupied “Victoria, BC, Canada.” While a few grammatical errors have been fixed, we did our best to stay true to the original transcript of our speakers. It is not to be confused with Shuli Branson’s No State Soluton (2023).
Source: Retrieved on May 19 from https://anarchistnetwork.info/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/ANVI-NoStateSolution.pd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Duane Rousselle - After Post-Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-after-post-anarchism?v=1716819512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-after-post-anarchism?v=1716819512"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Duane Rousselle
Title: After Post-Anarchism
Date: 2012
Source: <archive.org/details/RousselleAfterPostAnarchism_201610>

 For Soren, 
who taught me the value of a leap. 
 “What we are dealing with here is another version of the Lacanian ‘il n’y a pas de rapport’: if, for Lacan, there is no sexual relationship, then, for Marxism proper, there is no relationship between economy and politics, no meta-language enabling us to grasp the two levels from the same neutral standpoint, although—or, rather, because—these two levels are inextricably intertwined.” 
 — Slavoj Zizek 
Afterword
 Children from around the ages of five through seven are believed to have already acquired an understanding of the social norms surrounding sexuality. Immediately following this period of development, the ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Loadenthal - The Politics of Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/michael-loadenthal-the-politics-of-attack?v=1716818479</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/michael-loadenthal-the-politics-of-attack?v=1716818479"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Michael Loadenthal
Title: The Politics of Attack
Subtitle: Communiqués and Insurrectionary Violence
Date: 2017
Notes: Originally published as the authors dissertation.
Source: <manchesteruniversitypress.co.uk/9781526114440/>

 CONTEMPORARY ANARCHIST STUDIES 
 A series edited by 
 Laurence Davis, University College Cork, Ireland
 Uri Gordon, University of Nottingham, UK
 Nathan Jun, Midwestern State University, USA
 Alex Prichard, Exeter University, UK
Contemporary Anarchist Studies promotes the study of anarchism as a framework for understanding and acting on the most pressing problems of our times. The series publishes cutting-edge, socially engaged scholarship from around the world – bridging theory and practice, academic rigor and the insights of contemporary activism. 
 The top…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Graeber - The Democracy Project]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-democracy-project?v=1716817696</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-democracy-project?v=1716817696"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Graeber
Title: The Democracy Project
Subtitle: A History, a Crisis, a Movement
Date: 2013
Source: <archive.org/details/isbn_9780812993561>

 Democracy has been the American religion since before the Revolution —from New England town halls to the multicultural democracy of Atlantic pirate ships. But can our current political system, one that seems responsive only to the wealthiest among us and leaves most Americans feeling disengaged, voiceless, and disenfranchised, really be called democratic? And if the tools of our democracy are not working to solve the rising crises we face, how can we —average citizens— make change happen? 
The Democracy Project tells the story of the resilience of the democratic spirit and the adaptability of the democratic idea. It offers a fresh take o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudolf de Jong - Ferdinand Domela Nieuwenhuis: Anarchist and Messiah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-de-jong-ferdinand-domela-nieuwenhuis-anarchist-and-messiah?v=1716817339</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-de-jong-ferdinand-domela-nieuwenhuis-anarchist-and-messiah?v=1716817339"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rudolf de Jong
Title: Ferdinand Domela Nieuwenhuis: Anarchist and Messiah
Date: 1971
Notes: In this historical essay the redeemer of the Dutch proletariat is reviewed against the background of his own day and age. Author Rudolf de Jong (born 1932) studied political and social-science, and since 1960 works at the International Institute for Social History in Amsterdam. He has published books on the Spanish Civil War and articles on anarchism, Latin America, and Spain. A summary of his essay on Provos and anarchists appeared in the Autumn 1967 issue of Delta. The present article is translated by Elizabeth Wentholt-Haig. 
 Text digitalized by Forum voor Georganiseerd Anarchisme.
Source: Delta, A review of arts life and thought in the Netherlands, winter 1970-71

 When the students occ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global warming and the threat of cheap Chinese EVs]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45379</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/27/global-warming-and-the-threat-of-cheap-chinese-evs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T11:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker Suppose the G-7 finance ministers sat down and worked out a plan to spend tens of billions of dollars a year to subsidize developing countries in their transition to a green economy. Many of us might think this is a good idea since global warming poses a real threat to the planet. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Boggs - Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carl-boggs-marxism-prefigurative-communism-and-the-problem-of-workers-control?v=1716806355</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carl-boggs-marxism-prefigurative-communism-and-the-problem-of-workers-control?v=1716806355"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Carl Boggs
Title: Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control
Date: 1977
Source: Boggs, Carl. 1977. “Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control”. Radical America 11 (November), 100; cf. Boggs Jr., Carl. Revolutionary Process, Political Strategy, and the Dilemma of Power. Theory & Society 4,No. 3 (Fall), 3. Republished in Class Against Class www.oocities.org. Republished again in libcom.org.

 A conspicuous deficiency of the Marxist tradition has been the failure to produce a theory of the state and political action that could furnish the basis of a democratic and non-authoritarian revolutionary process. The two most widely-tested strategies for advancing revolutionary goals — Leninism and structural reformism — provide no real al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even if it avoids civil war, Israel's final crisis looks cataclysmic!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Even-if-it-avoids-civil-war-Israel-s-final-crisis-looks-cataclysmic</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Even-if-it-avoids-civil-war-Israel-s-final-crisis-looks-cataclysmic"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T08:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2021, commenting on Albert Einstein's prophetic warnings of Israel's disastrous future as early as 1948, we concluded our text with the following observation and, at the same time, prediction: 
English

/ 
Palestine, 
Israel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections of a conflicted impostor]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T00:51:56.738Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah... how difficult it is to admit this, but I failed. Actually, I don't know if it's difficult, if I'm afraid, or if I just lack courage, despite many people saying that fear is the absence of courage, so this might be redundant.
I always thought I was a very intelligent guy and ahead of my time, especially when I was around 18 years old or younger. I remember people always saying that I was very mature for my age, because I had values that were already lost, and even my culture was from generations much earlier than mine. When technology was still a novelty, and servers were something only large or well-structured companies had, I was basically a master, and I was still a minor... I remember setting up LANs for acquaintances or friends to play games, and even setting up a server (more li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The search for the distant Planet Nine continues]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7689</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/search-distant-planet-nine-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weird stuff is happening out on the remote boundary of the solar system. Beyond the orbit of Pluto. You name it, it’s going on out there. Irregularities. Anomalies. Clustering of apsidal lines. Perihelia. And — saving the best for last — a surprising prevalence of retrograde Centaurs. These anomalies include the apparent clustering of apsidal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICQ to close on 26 June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7695</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/icq-close-26-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T20:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASL? Another artefact of the early days of the (mainstream) internet will soon be no more. Instant messaging service, ICQ, launched in 1996, will cease operating, as of Wednesday 26 June 2024. ICQ (I seek you, get it?) allowed users to chat to pretty much anyone who let them. I can’t remember when I stopped […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unbearable lightness of a simple photoblog]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T12:06:45.108Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love having collection of photos I like on the internet. I can access them whenever I want. Yet, I do not really like instagram.
Although I have it, mostly I use it to interact and stay in contact with my friends. Because, for most people, staying in contact via instagram is the norm. It is not the norm for me but I do not really have power as one person.
But it does not mean that I can not have my own taste of photo blog.
Luckily I've found a very nice photoblog generator on Github made by Anders Jensen-Urstad. He is such a nice guy that he even helped me, via email, by answering my questions about how to set the generator up because I couldn't get something rights at first. This is his photoblog by the way.
It is just exactly what I wanted. Lightweight, super fast, no tracking, privacy friendly and content-first approach. So I just went right away and built my own. Once you open it, you will see the latest uploaded photo. At the bottom navigation, there are older, newer, home, archive and contact buttons.
Right now it is only on Github page because I still could not decide a name for the blog, which domain and hosting service to use. I'm still looking for a privacy friendly, reliable service. Once I decide these, I will have proper domain name later.
I found some services from this list on PrivacyTools.io. Apart from these, I found Porkbun, Mythic Beasts, Nixi Host and Nearly Free Spech. I will need to dig these up and see the best one. (I'm addicted to the act of researching these kind of things :') )
If you have any suggestions of domain and hosting service, I really appreciate it. I want to use the domain for my Bearblog blog in the future, too.
For now, it is what it is.   ¯\( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)/¯
Here is one of the songs I listened to while writing this post]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in negotiation: Re-positioning public health in the Pandemic Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T09:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021 during the Covid-19 pandemic, the WHO World Health Assembly established an international body to negotiate a convention, agreement, or other international instrument to strengthen pandemic prevention, preparedness, and response. The negotiations have been difficult. Furthermore, the focus on public health in the Pandemic Agreement remains fragile before the World Health Assembly starting on the 27th of May 2024. 
English

/ 
Health, 
WHO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abbe Brown, Alison McCallum, Amitabha Sarkar, Chloe Stephenson, Corrado Piroddi, Lynda Gilby, Meri Koivusalo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Kilmainham Gaol]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52720</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/26/sunday-photoblogging-kilmainham-gaol/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T07:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Writing]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/on-writing/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/on-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost a month ago I had a problem. Information overload. I had filled up all my free time with audiobooks and podcasts. Every free moment I was consuming information. It was getting frustrating. My general productivity was going down as well. So I quit cold turkey.
This wasn't the first time I had done this. At first, it was uncomfortable but I got used to my company. Like meeting an old friend after a long time. The ideas just started flowing and I needed an outlet, I found one in writing.
My writing process is simple. I spend time with myself as much as I can. I let the ideas flow till I feel almost compelled to write them down. It is like the compulsion and excitement of picking up the controller of your favorite video game. Sometimes though I don't feel like writing a post but I push through and kinda get myself in that state because consistency is important.
All of this was not planned. I let myself flow with life instead of overthinking and getting in my own way. A lot of this creative stuff is undefined and weird. Yes, your process needs some essence of discipline and consistency. But you just kinda let it flow in a sense. And get out of your own way as fast as possible.
The last part sounds all woo-woo to my logical brain but this has been my experience with the art of writing so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do the work]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T18:43:27.312Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of well-meaning advice on the internet, including this blog. Gives you some new insights. Maybe some insights you knew and had to relearn. It makes you feel good. And you move on to the next advice without ever implementing it. I know, I have been there.
Just do the work is probably another advice people will read, feel good about, and move on. But as a recovering productivity addict, I have to say this - 'Stop reading all kinds of cool things about how to do great work, feel good about yourself for a few days or hours, and not change a single thing in your life'.
There is a lot of alpha in just doing the work. If you are not doing the work. JUST DO THE WORK. All the nifty tricks and mental models and whatnot are just icing on the cake. They are supposed to make the 'Just do the work' part easier with time. But you gotta get started.
Start in a dumb inefficient way but start. You are better than the guy reading about all this and not doing anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>