<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-27T01:36:49.488Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-27T01:36:49.488Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Migrating to the cloud with AWS]]></title>
        <id>59dc679b0c05157308218c9126cc3375da8e04e1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-migrating-to-the-cloud-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, businesses are increasingly turning to the cloud for its scalability, agility, and cost-effectiveness. Migrating your data center to the cloud can be a daunting task, but with the right approach and tools, it can be a successful journey. This Let’s Architect! blog post will guide you through the process of migrating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Federica Ciuffo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the universe exist before the Big Bang? Maybe…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7915</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/did-the-universe-exist-before-the-big-bang-maybe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened, or was there, before the Big Bang that is said to have brought the universe into being? Was there nothing, to which something came? It is the question of the ages. In his recent documentary series, Universe, British physicist Brian Cox posits that the universe existed before the Big Bang. How long this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/26/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274012</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-26-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silky Shah]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326618</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/silky-shah/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Joshua Frank and Erik Wallenberg interview Silky Shah, author of Unbuild Walls: Why Immigrant Justice Needs Abolition (Haymarket, 2024).  Silky has been working as an organizer on issues related to racial and migrant justice for over two decades. Originally from Texas, she began fighting the expansion of immigrant jails on the US-Mexico border in the aftermath of 9/11. In 2009, she joined the staff of Detention Watch Network, a national coalition building power to abolish immigrant detention in the United States, and now serves as its executive director. More
The post Silky Shah appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methodological fetishism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45459</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/26/methodological-fetishism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Beyond the significant financial expenses required to conduct RCTs … critics have raised concerns about considerable opportunity costs associated with their privileged status in programme and policy assessment. These costs result from how an over-emphasis on experimental evaluations in evidence generation systematically undermines alternative research methods potentially better equipped to answer questions about causal mechanisms (or the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Book From an MIT Whiz Kid]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/mit-whiz-kid/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/mit-whiz-kid/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you just want to pick up the book, here you go!
It's May 8th, 2022 and the market has officially left "easy-mode" and entered into a straight grind down. Gone are the days of just buying $NIO at the end of the day because it closed up at least 1 ATR on elevated rvol and you'll wake up with it a couple points higher, just cause!
Now, we are seeing the high flyers that are up in the air getting hit on earnings and selling off aggressively. The r*tarded trade that Tim and I are taking in our joint account is shorting earnings day 1 under premarket lows and it's working! We aren't crushing it, but it's working. We are covering everything at 1:1, often reshorting into vwap vs high of day and taking them overnight. Additionally, we are pressing names under earnings day 1 on day 2 and that’s a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) for speed and scale]]></title>
        <id>d4565ed778c5a0e98b15e9b099d374724e2830bf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/optimizing-amazon-simple-queue-service-sqs-for-speed-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SQS boosts performance, scaling capabilities, and energy efficiency without impacting existing behavior - a behind-the-scenes look at AWS's continuous improvement journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Is Nowhere Near Ready for Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274003</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/the-u-s-is-nowhere-near-ready-for-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is cooking our collective gooses. What can be done to reduce the damage?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare incident on June 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>667b4709a4598c000bd7048c</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-june-20-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new DDoS rule resulted in an increase in error responses and latency for Cloudflare customers. Here’s how it went wrong, and what we’ve learned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lloyd Wallis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/26/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273978</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-26-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T10:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our freedom-loving daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie: The ‘Israel Lobby’ Works for the US Military Industrial Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273977</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/rob-urie-the-israel-lobby-works-for-the-us-military-industrial-complex.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T10:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why even cynical interpretations of the source of Israel power in US policy are generally not cynical enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Union ‘Effects’ on Hourly and Weekly Wages: A Half-Century Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273990</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/union-effects-on-hourly-and-weekly-wages-a-half-century-perspective.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T10:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with union power diminished, union members still benefit from higher weekly pay than non-members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is EU’s Fuzzy Natural Gas Math Leading to Major Minuses in the Caucasus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273936</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/is-eus-fuzzy-natural-gas-math-leading-to-major-minuses-in-the-caucasus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T10:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Armenia-Azerbaijan peace process gets tangled up with the EU’s desperate ploys to kick Russian gas reliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate and environmental crisis: Sorcerer's apprentices at the World Bank and the IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Ecology/Climate, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libertarian Communist Group - Towards a Programme]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Libertarian Communist Group
Title: Towards a Programme
Date: 1977
Notes: Another, earlier TOWARDS A PROGRAMME text can be found on <www.thesparrowsnest.org.uk/collections/public_archive/15788.pdf>

Preface (2004)
 This document was originally drafted by members of the Anarchist Workers’ Association, (A.W.A.) following a resolution passed at the 1976 [?] A.W.A. conference, which called for the A.W.A. to agree a clearer definition of its theory and strategy. At that time the A.W.A. had groups and members in England and Scotland, and a sympathiser or two in Ireland, and published the monthly newspaper ‘Anarchist Worker’. The text below was adopted as a ‘provisional’ rather than as a definitive text by the tendency whose members went on to publish ‘Libertarian Communist’, and renamed t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Release of Julian Assange: Plea Deals and Dark Legacies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326537</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/the-release-of-julian-assange-plea-deals-and-dark-legacies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the longest sagas of political persecution is coming to its terminus. That is, if you believe in final chapters. Nothing about the fate of Julian Assange seems determinative. His accusers and inquisitors will draw some delight at the plea deal reached between the WikiLeaks founder’s legal team and the US Department of Justice.  More
The post The Release of Julian Assange: Plea Deals and Dark Legacies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US is Mired in a Cold War Model From the 1950s]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326503</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/the-us-is-mired-in-a-cold-war-model-from-the-1950s/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden administration is in denial regarding the dangerous Cold War that currently exists between the United States, China, and Russia that qualifies as Cold War II.  The current Cold War promises to be more dangerous, more costly, and more implacable than its predecessor, which dominated the 1950s and early 1960s.  Fortunately, the administrations of John F. Kennedy and Richard M. Nixon lessened the impact of the Cold War in the wake of the Cuban missile crisis, and the U.S. failure in Vietnam, respectively. More
The post The US is Mired in a Cold War Model From the 1950s appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An AI Hell on Earth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326501</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/an-ai-hell-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venture capital and military startup firms in Silicon Valley have begun aggressively selling a version of automated warfare that will deeply incorporate artificial intelligence (AI). Those companies and their CEOs are now pressing full speed ahead with that emerging technology, largely dismissing the risk of malfunctions that could lead to the future slaughter of civilians, not to  More
The post An AI Hell on Earth? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Hartung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza and Gazans Can’t Disappear]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326423</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/gaza-and-gazans-cant-disappear/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you sense that there is less and less news reaching us from the occupied Palestinian territories, expressly from Gaza? Do you feel what I fear: – that moral outrage by the world public has been spent? That those millions of creative, passionate calls for a ceasefire have been exhausted? Or, that there’s simply nothing new to report, nothing that could possibly supersede the last massacre, the last failed negotiation, the last thwarted aid delivery? More
The post Gaza and Gazans Can’t Disappear     appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>B. Nimri Aziz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congress’s Nuclear Addiction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/congresss-nuclear-addiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “ADVANCE Act,” a bill to promote nuclear power, was passed 88-to-2 by the U.S. Senate last week. The ADVANCE stands for “Accelerating Deployment of Versatile, Advanced Nuclear for Clean Energy.” The only senators voting against it were Edward Markey of Massachusetts and Bernie Sanders of Vermont. It was approved in the House of Representatives  More
The post Congress’s Nuclear Addiction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air Pollution Is Killing Millions and Rising Exponentially—A Shift in Agriculture Can Solve It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326493</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/air-pollution-is-killing-millions-and-rising-exponentially-a-shift-in-agriculture-can-solve-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1958, geochemist Charles David Keeling set up the Mauna Loa Global Monitoring Laboratory in Hawaii, which measured carbon dioxide (CO2). Keeling believed that CO2 levels were rising and wanted to prove it. Mauna Loa was a perfect location to obtain precise readings since it was located at an elevation of more than 13,000 feet in the  More
The post Air Pollution Is Killing Millions and Rising Exponentially—A Shift in Agriculture Can Solve It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmy Videle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No to Nuclear NATO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326418</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/no-to-nuclear-nato/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With so-called U.S. or NATO nuclear weapons in potentially eight nations in Europe — and perhaps South Korea as well, at least on U.S. submarines docked there to please certain war-crazed South Koreans — there could soon be more nations in the world with “U.S.” nuclear weapons than nations with anybody else’s. More
The post No to Nuclear NATO appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Swanson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Water, Climate, Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326509</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/water-climate-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“For Fanon, then, the right to indifference, or to ignorance, does not exist.” The doctor’s task “was to rise up in revolt, become indignant, show alarm… not to dissimulate the real”. Mbembe Necropolitics Weather whiplashing, unprecedented heat waves, drought, and forest fires, are in the news. Storytelling may begin in the middle of an action  More
The post Water, Climate, Violence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Judith Deutsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: I Don’t Want to Set the World On Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326409</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/letter-from-london-i-dont-want-to-set-the-world-on-fire/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a child, I loved making fires. I would be so happy out in the open just clearing some space and setting one up with some wood or paper as my tinder. Twigs and sticks, ideally bone-dry, would then be added. A spark or match or lighter would get the smoke going, followed by more  More
The post Letter from London: I Don’t Want to Set the World On Fire appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conn Hallinan: He Knew What Side He was On]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326492</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/conn-hallinan-he-knew-what-side-he-was-on/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s note: I was distressed to learn of Conn Hallinan’s death last week. I’d heard from our mutual friend, P. Sainath, in the fall that Conn hadn’t been well, but the news still came as a jolt. Conn started writing for CounterPunch in 2003. His first story was a blistering attack on Ariel Sharon (The  More
The post Conn Hallinan: He Knew What Side He was On appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Bacon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024’s violent tornado season has been one of the most active on record]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326411</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/2024s-violent-tornado-season-has-been-one-of-the-most-active-on-record/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spring 2024 was unnerving for people across large parts of the U.S. as tornado warnings and sirens sent them scrambling for safety. More than 1,100 tornadoes were reported through May − a preliminary number but nearly twice the 30-year average at that point and behind only 2011, when deadly tornado outbreaks tore across the southeastern  More
The post 2024’s violent tornado season has been one of the most active on record appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Gallus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minding the Debate: What’s Happening to Our Brains During Election Season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326505</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/26/minding-the-debate-whats-happening-to-our-brains-during-election-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of us are convening watch parties and others deliberately will not tune in. Either way, the June 27 presidential debate is the real start of the election season, when more Americans start to pay attention. It’s when partisan rhetoric runs hot and emotions run high. It’s also a chance for us, as members of  More
The post Minding the Debate: What’s Happening to Our Brains During Election Season appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Burrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[você quer jogar comigo?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/jogo-bonito/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/jogo-bonito/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T01:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I was walking on the sidewalk with my soccer ball looking for a patch of grass to play on1 when I noticed someone walking towards me and gesturing at my ball. I hesitated, because tossing your ball to a stranger by a busy street isn't the most prudent idea, but eventually the child in me won. The ball bounced once on the concrete before landing at his feet.
Thump thump thump. Chest, thigh, right foot, left foot, pass, repeat. We juggled the ball back and forth on the sidewalk for a minute before I mouthed I have to go and pointed with my thumb. After he returned my ball, we smiled at each other and went our separate ways.
Not a single word was exchanged during our keep-up session. And yet the memory's been keeping me warm since. I love that the ball can turn strangers into friendly ones, that you can play with someone for hours without knowing the first thing about them and still have a blast. In that regard soccer stands alone among all my hobbies.
This should be the plot for the next Mission: Impossible movie.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Street]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T01:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is intended to be the most basic of rundowns in getting a top job offer for Carnegie Mellon SCS freshman.
While the following may sound annoyingly prestige-oriented, and compensation-driven, it is bluntly intended to reflect the realities of an increasingly competitive professional landscape. There is a lot of yapping, beware. Get some Tsaocaa boba and settle in.
About me, for context, I grew up low-income in a suburban town with immigrant parents that never attended high school. I took up to Calc AB in high school, and I only knew basic web development coming into CMU. I graduated from Carnegie Mellon University this semester. My highest offer this year included a total compensation of $550k. I had offers from trading firms, two FAANGs, tiktok.
CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Stre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Netflix Reliability with Service-Level Prioritized Load Shedding]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e735e6ce8f7d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/enhancing-netflix-reliability-with-service-level-prioritized-load-shedding-e735e6ce8f7d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Quality of Service techniques at the application level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ye Old Blogroll, a trove of links to blogs, personal websites]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7911</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ye-old-blogroll-trove-links-blogs-personal-websites/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My thanks to Ray for recently adding disassociated to Ye Old Blogroll, a directory of small and independent websites and blogs. Directory websites like Ray’s are invaluable when it comes to promoting the work of Indie and Small Web writers and bloggers, which is often overshadowed by all sorts of things, including some of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[about me]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm boon.
appreciate you for being here.
i've always wanted to be an astronaut but i found myself making bits fly instead. i love that which is aesthetic and i take great pride in designing beautiful distributed systems. i enjoy dota, strawberries, and software (in that order).
i like to think reasonably, objectively, creatively, simply, and always with the future in mind. i'm very strongly opinionated, but i love nothing more than being corrected correctly. i love learning experiences.
the majority of my posts will probably be irrelevant to you, especially since i enjoy yapping, but peruse at your leisure.
always happy to chat on twitter.
see you sometime,
boon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse, an IndieWeb arts community by Chris Shaw]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7899</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-artocalypse-indieweb-arts-community-chris-shaw/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse is a subscription based community for artists on IndieWeb, created by Chris Shaw at uncountable thoughts. This a great cross-promotional idea, showcasing the work of artists, while also spreading the word about IndieWeb. I dare say some of the participating artists will already have followings elsewhere, and their membership of Artocalypse will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 forces data backup to OneDrive, possible workaround]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7893</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/windows-11-forces-data-backup-onedrive-possible-workaround/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe it’s time to start a Windows 11 is going just great website, similar to Molly White’s Web3 is Going Just Great. I say this after reading about another instance of heavy-handedness on Microsoft’s part, at Neowin: Quietly and without any announcement, the company changed Windows 11’s initial setup so that it could turn on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/25/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273958</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-25-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T18:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics; the debates; Hillary Clinton's forthcoming book; counting and scripting in the caring professions; mask bans spread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21409</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/25/developer-tools/the-key-to-a-happy-rust-c-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of Rust at Meta goes all the way back to 2016, when we first started using it for source control. Today, it has been widely embraced at Meta and is one of our primary supported server-side languages (along with C++, Python, and Hack). But that doesn’t mean there weren’t any growing pains. Aida [...]
Read More...
The post The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Nosferatu" theme for bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/nosferatu-theme-for-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/nosferatu-theme-for-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to share a new Bear Blog theme paying homage to the classic vampire film, Nosferatu. I was inspired to create this one after watching the trailer for the upcoming 2024 remake. The theme has an atmospheric aesthetic that evokes the haunting tone of the original movie. I've designed this theme to be ideal for blogs focused on horror, Gothic literature, or film reviews. The font treatment is also ideal for long-form book reviews or essays. I hope you enjoy exploring the CSS and customizing it to your liking. Now, if you'll excuse me, I think I hear rats scratching in the walls...
Demo: nosferatu.bearblog.dev 
static.mgx.me/css/nosferatu-v1.0.0.css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equally different]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/equally-different/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/equally-different/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I launched the July Reply blog challenge. I like the idea and hoped there would be a lot of interest, but so far, it's been lukewarm.
For the past few weeks, I have posted something new every day. Many of the texts that I've been proud of have barely gotten any attention at all.
“Why am I even doing this for?”
I heard myself thinking that today. It's so incredibly stupid and ridiculous that it's embarrassing to even mention it.
I'm doing this because I love it. If others like it too, great, but that's not the main purpose.
No one likes everything we do, whether we're a small blogger or the biggest artist in the world. On the other hand, we will always think that our latest creations are our best. Why else would we continue?
We are all different—equally different.
You're sitting on the world's best joke, looking forward to the laughter, but you're met with the reaction: “Is that all?”
Different.
You tell someone about the greatest movie ever made and then ask what they thought: “It wasn't to my taste, so I turned it off after half an hour."
Different.
You like watching football. I hate sports.
Different.
What a wonderful diversity!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite Warnings, Israel Looks Set to Jump Off Lebanon Ledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273950</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/despite-warnings-israel-looks-set-to-jump-off-lebanon-ledge.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel looks like it is about to bite off way more than it can chew in instigating a hot war with Lebanon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices working with self-hosted GitHub Action runners at scale on AWS]]></title>
        <id>c54a5e17bad2934e3e0477995d7d86a4bf854ecd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-working-with-self-hosted-github-action-runners-at-scale-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview GitHub Actions is a continuous integration and continuous deployment platform that enables the automation of build, test and deployment activities for your workload. GitHub Self-Hosted Runners provide a flexible and customizable option to run your GitHub Action pipelines. These runners allow you to run your builds on your own infrastructure, giving you control over the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shilpa Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/25/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273814</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-25-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T10:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our zingy daily links: Praising grim fairy tales, PPE destruction, moar heat records, global tax splat, China v. Treasury rules,US carrier to Koreas, Venezuela, Assange deal, Bibi deal defiance, Russia Crimea beach attack uproar, Dems v. Biden exit rumors, Aussie censorship, Nvidia plunge, unions organizing nationally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Frets As Chinese Company Cosco Wraps Up Construction of South America’s Largest Deep Sea Port]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273815</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/chinese-company-cosco-is-close-to-finishing-construction-of-south-americas-largest-deep-sea-port-and-washington-is-not-happy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Due to its potential size and volume of operations, Peru's Chancay mega-port is destined to become a nerve centre of international trade." And it will be exclusively controlled by Cosco.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In France, a Bold New Take on ‘Liberté, Egalité, Fraternité’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326291</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/in-france-a-bold-new-take-on-liberte-egalite-fraternite/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France has rendered unto the world, over the past quarter-century, a distinct public service. Thanks to the trailblazing research of three French scholars — Thomas Piketty, Emmanuel Saez, and Gabriel Zucman — we know much more about the world’s maldistributed wealth than ever before. Could France now be on the brink of making another significant  More
The post In France, a Bold New Take on ‘Liberté, Egalité, Fraternité’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Workers Are Winning as the Nation Adds Jobs, Manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326394</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/how-workers-are-winning-as-the-nation-adds-jobs-manufacturing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Ralston went into bargaining with Transco last fall intending to negotiate one of the strongest union contracts in his three decades with the company. Carmakers urgently wanted to get new vehicles to market. The railroads needed to get more autoracks—enclosed rail cars used to transport vehicles—into service. And Ralston said he and his co-workers,  More
The post How Workers Are Winning as the Nation Adds Jobs, Manufacturing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Answering the Call to Fight Injustice: An Interview with Barbara Smith]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326431</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/answering-the-call-to-fight-injustice-an-interview-with-barbara-smith/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barbara Smith is one of the leading intellectuals and activists who developed the traditions of Black feminism. A part of a group of Black lesbian socialists, she co-authored the groundbreaking “Combahee River Collective Statement.” A prolific writer, she has published many books and articles that have emphasized the interlocking nature of systems of oppression under  More
The post Answering the Call to Fight Injustice: An Interview with Barbara Smith appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Victory for the Disposables: The Sentencing of the Hindujas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326442</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/victory-for-the-disposables-the-sentencing-of-the-hindujas/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his seminal work on modern slavery, Kevin Bales does away with certain, antiquated concepts.  In its insidious, older form, one focused on the concept of natal alienation, slaves were chattels and assets, outrightly owned.  Each slave system was distinct and protean, if marked by certain universal features. The universal feature of ownership, at least when it  More
The post Victory for the Disposables: The Sentencing of the Hindujas appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lock Them Both Up!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326446</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/lock-them-both-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the 2016 election Trump fanatics chanted “Lock her up,” referring to Hillary Clinton.  The tables have now turned.  Trump is a convicted criminal and Biden violates international law. In one of the most twisted forms of logic ever to appear in politics, liberals believe that screaming “Trump is a fascist” somehow proves that Biden is not.  If  More
The post Lock Them Both Up! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Fitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Armed Vs. Peaceful Resistance – What You Need to Know about Muqawama in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326417</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/armed-vs-peaceful-resistance-what-you-need-to-know-about-muqawama-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The word Muqawama in Palestinian lexicon does not need elaboration beyond the immediate meaning it generates among ordinary Palestinians. Only recently, and specifically after the Oslo peace accords and the sudden infusion of western-funded NGOs, did such terms as ‘peaceful resistance’ and ‘non-violent resistance’ begin to emerge within some circles of Palestinian intellectuals. These phrases,  More
The post Armed Vs. Peaceful Resistance – What You Need to Know about Muqawama in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Property Law, Settler-Colonialism, and the Vatican]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326414</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/property-law-settler-colonialism-and-the-vatican/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newsflash!  Property law in the U.S. is not rooted in the Constitution. America’s legal foundation for property law (possession), “anti-Indian law,” and the concept of nation-states is religious, not secular. Where did this deep sense of entitlement, hierarchy, and dominion over unknown lands and its original sovereign peoples originate? How was this wilderness continent, upon  More
The post Property Law, Settler-Colonialism, and the Vatican appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Labor Price of Gas is at Trumpian Levels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326410</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/the-labor-price-of-gas-is-at-trumpian-levels/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media have told us endlessly how people can no longer afford things due to higher prices and the fact that wages have risen more doesn’t matter. I wouldn’t want to disagree with the experts, but suppose we just did a little calculation about how much time it takes a typical worker to earn enough  More
The post The Labor Price of Gas is at Trumpian Levels appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran’s Trial to Highlight BAE Systems, Inc. Complicity in Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326416</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/veterans-trial-to-highlight-bae-systems-inc-complicity-in-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:08:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ENDICOTT, NY – On Wednesday, June 26, 2 pm, in Endicott Village Court, 225 Jefferson Avenue, Jack Gilroy, an 89-year-old former machine gunner in occupied Austria, will tell the court why he was compelled to deliver a letter to weapons manufacturer, BAE Systems, and should not be convicted of trespass. Gilroy, a member of Veterans For Peace  More
The post Veteran’s Trial to Highlight BAE Systems, Inc. Complicity in Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veteran’s Trial Will Highlight Weapons Manufacturers’ Complicity in Gaza Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326471</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/veterans-trial-will-highlight-weapons-manufacturers-complicity-in-gaza-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Wednesday, June 26, Jack Gilroy, an 89-year-old veteran, will tell a court in Endicott, New York why he was compelled to deliver a letter to weapons manufacturer BAE Systems, protesting their weapons shipments to Israel, and why he should not be convicted of trespassing. “This case is not about trespass,” said Jack Gilroy, who  More
The post Veteran’s Trial Will Highlight Weapons Manufacturers’ Complicity in Gaza Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerry Condon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Straw Men and Strange Bedfellows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326429</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/25/straw-men-and-strange-bedfellows/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my college days I was a Goldwater Republican. My roommate and I saw eye-to-eye. Today he is a conservative Republican, and I am a progressive Democrat. We remain close friends, but this divide troubled me. I asked him to help me understand why the right harbors so much animosity towards the left. He responded  More
The post Straw Men and Strange Bedfellows appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Topper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put your Palace Cinema wine glass in the cup-holder carefully]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7882</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/put-palace-cinema-wine-glass-cup-holder-carefully/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether they are a part of an on-going series of light-hearted clips by Australian cinema group Palace Cinemas, remains to be seen, but the two I’ve caught to date, on their Instagram page, have been pretty witty. The first is in response to the apparent problem of patrons nicking the cinema’s wine glasses. Why would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i gave my depression one month]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/i-gave-my-depression-one-month/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/i-gave-my-depression-one-month/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:28:45.709Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Towards the end of May, I promised myself I would give this life my all for one month. Just for one month, I told myself. If I still can't find myself gaining control of depression, then I can give up, but at least I would have given up contently knowing I tried.
Last night, I was unable to sleep (unfortunately, insomnia seems to be a common side effect in antidepressants). I stared up the ceiling aimlessly, and pondered, A month has passed. Even more. I am still the same. What changed?
I was clearly anxious and upset throughout the day, because I skipped work too. I told myself I deserved a break, but deep down I knew I was lying to myself. The break was an excuse. I actually wanted to run from work and people and from existing in general. Because, after a month, I felt like nothing chang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping keep customers safe with leaked password notification]]></title>
        <id>6675c883a4598c000bd703c6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/helping-keep-customers-safe-with-leaked-password-notification"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help protect against account compromise via credential stuffing attacks, Cloudflare will notify dashboard users when we detect that a password was found in an external data breach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Galow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive scaling of Amazon ECS services using Amazon ECS Service Connect Metrics]]></title>
        <id>dddca191d6a2df5df6c28c233a33652b924833c9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/proactive-scaling-of-amazon-ecs-services-using-amazon-ecs-service-connect-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post discusses Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) Service Connect, a capability that provides a secure and scalable way to connect different Amazon ECS service deployments. This enables seamless communication between micro-services while reducing the operational overhead. It provides features such as service discovery, load balancing, and network traffic metrics. This post primarily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Nalpet Ramakrishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging AI for efficient incident response]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21393</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/24/data-infrastructure/leveraging-ai-for-efficient-incident-response/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing how we streamline system reliability investigations using a new AI-assisted root cause analysis system. The system uses a combination of heuristic-based retrieval and large language model-based ranking to speed up root cause identification during investigations. Our testing has shown this new system achieves 42% accuracy in identifying root causes for investigations at their [...]
Read More...
The post Leveraging AI for efficient incident response appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Claude 3.5 Sonnet in Amazon Bedrock, CodeCatalyst updates, SageMaker with MLflow, and more (June 24, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>7dacc08a7aef106cc0797e9788dead147aa616ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-5-sonnet-in-amazon-bedrock-codecatalyst-updates-sagemaker-with-mlflow-and-more-june-24-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I had the opportunity to try the new Anthropic Claude 3.5 Sonnet model in Amazon Bedrock just before it launched, and I was really impressed by its speed and accuracy! It was also the week of AWS Summit Japan. JAWS-UG, a Japanese AWS user group, held various sessions with AWS Heroes and Community Builders at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using machine learning to detect bot attacks that leverage residential proxies]]></title>
        <id>66722bd6a4598c000bd700f0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/residential-proxy-bot-detection-using-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare's Bot Management team has released a new Machine Learning model for bot detection (v8), focusing on bots and abuse from residential proxies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob AminAzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feedle, A Search Engine For Blogs]]></title>
        <id>https://linkage.lol/feedle-a-search-engine-for-blogs/</id>
        <link href="https://linkage.lol/feedle-a-search-engine-for-blogs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of folks who blog are always on the lookout for other bloggers to follow. BearBlog has a discover feed that lists recent and recent top posts. Many bloggers maintain a blogroll where they suggest the writing of people they like to others. I've found some good stuff there. (Note - Quit putting Daring Fireball in your blogroll. Everyone in the universe who needs to know about that blog already reads it). A few months ago, I found Feedle, a search engine for blogs and podcasts that allows you to add your own blog to its database. It's a good resource to find people who are well versed in the things you are interested in. Check it out.
Feedle, A World of Feeds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciphering the Disinflation Process]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30281</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/deciphering-the-disinflation-process/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. inflation surged in the early post-COVID period, driven by several economic shocks such as supply chain disruptions and labor supply constraints. Following its peak at 6.6 percent in September 2022, core consumer price index (CPI) inflation has come down rapidly over the last two years, falling to 3.6 percent recently. What explains the rapid shifts in U.S. inflation dynamics? In a recent paper, we show that the interaction between supply chain pressures and labor market tightness amplified the inflation surge in 2021. In this post, we argue that these same forces that drove the nonlinear rise in inflation have worked in reverse since late 2022, accelerating the disinflationary process. The current episode contrasts with periods where the economy was hit by shocks to either imported inputs or to labor alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Heise and Ayşegül Şahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Compromised Cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16687</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/catching-compromised-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slack uses cookies to track session states for users on slack.com and the Slack Desktop app. The ever-present cookie banners have made cookies mainstream, but as a quick refresher, cookies are a little piece of client-side state associated with a website that is sent up to the web server on every request. Websites use this […]
The post Catching Compromised Cookies appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Slama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The economic crisis and unfolding disaster in Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45445</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/24/the-economic-crisis-and-unfolding-disaster-in-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The population of Argentina is suffering. The purchasing power of people who still have a job is down (a lot), and unemployment must have doubled (it was 5,7% in the last quarter of 2023) if it has not tripled. Less government spending, less consumer spending, and, no doubt, less private investment means that Argentina is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday’s Jamaal Bowman Primary Hits Close to Home for Me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326380</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/tuesdays-jamaal-bowman-primary-hits-close-to-home-for-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T06:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American Israel Public Affairs Committee has been around over 60 years, but it only began intervening in Democratic primaries in a big way last election cycle. AIPAC’s move came on the heels of a string of corporate Democrats losing primary contests to progressive “Squad” members, such as Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez in 2018, and Bowman two years later.  More
The post Tuesday’s Jamaal Bowman Primary Hits Close to Home for Me appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember the Palestinian Doctors Killed by Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326396</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/remember-the-palestinian-doctors-killed-by-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first week of June 2024, the Palestine office of the World Health Organization (WHO) released figures about the atrocious attacks on health care facilities and workers in Gaza since October 7, 2023. Thus far, according to the WHO, the Israelis have attacked 464 health care facilities, killed 727 health care workers, injured 933 health  More
The post Remember the Palestinian Doctors Killed by Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quibbling About Killing: Netanyahu’s Spat with Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326398</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/quibbling-about-killing-netanyahus-spat-with-washington/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, is unhappy.  Not so much with the Palestinians, whom he sees as terroristic, dispensable and a threat to Israeli security.  Not with the Persians, who, he swears, will never acquire a nuclear weapon capacity on his watch.  His recent lack of happiness has been directed against the fatty hand that feeds him and his country’s war making capabilities. More
The post Quibbling About Killing: Netanyahu’s Spat with Washington appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Think Trump’s Bad?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326302</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/you-think-trumps-bad/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poland is supposed to be one of the politically sane places in Europe right now. The far-right Law and Justice Party lost national elections last year to a centrist coalition and exited power after eight long years of democratic repression. Donald Tusk, who’d previously been the president of the European Council, once again became the  More
The post You Think Trump’s Bad? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Buy The Tariff Lie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326399</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/dont-buy-the-tariff-lie/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If he returns to the White House,” Bloomberg reports, “Donald Trump has pledged to enact a 10% across-the-board tariff on imports that he says will raise billions of dollars in revenue to pay for more tax cuts.” He’s even floated the idea, per CNBC, of an “all tariff policy” and elimination of the federal income  More
The post Don’t Buy The Tariff Lie appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rescinding Dr. Segal: Mt. Irony in the Age of Resurrected US McCarthyism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326357</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/rescinding-dr-segal-mt-irony-in-the-age-of-resurrected-us-mccarthyism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resurrection of McCarthyism in the US has returned in full force since October 7th. Careers have been truncated, protests have been muffled and employment opportunities curtailed. MSNBC cancelled the Mehdi Hasan Show in November. In June, Briahna Joy Gray was canned by The Hill, where she co-hosted the Rising web series. 30% of students  More
The post Rescinding Dr. Segal: Mt. Irony in the Age of Resurrected US McCarthyism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Crowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the trap of good memories]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I struggle with this thing, of remembering certain people in such a golden light. Before this seems like a post talking about not-so-good people, it's not. It's about perfectly nice people.
The thing is, the way I tend to remember people is by how they made me feel. Few people in my life have made me feel like a real, raw person when talking to them. But some have. Some of these people are miles away, and have maybe always been miles away, both geographically and otherwise.
It's a really painful thing, because as these memories I hold go further and further back in my memory, I don't know what I want anymore. All I really want is to feel the way they made me feel again. Not so easy though, is it?
We've both grown in separate ways, and I'm grateful for where I am in my life, I think I've done pretty alright for myself so far. No matter what I do though, it does feel like there's a certain hole in my life, somewhere I'm lacking greatly. The remedy is so far though. Maybe it doesn't even exist, not anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Extensions are all you need]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to extend GitHub Copilot by using the Chat and Language Model APIs in your Visual Studio Code extension. Get inspired by early adopters and their extensions.
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A book about ferns: the truth of the three-hour Gilligan’s Island cruise]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7876</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/book-ferns-truth-three-hour-gilligans-island-cruise/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gilligan’s Island was a slapstick American TV series which ran from 1964 to 1967. Despite its popularity, the show was cancelled shortly before filming of a fourth series commenced. I first saw reruns of Gilligan’s quite some time later. A number of movies, featuring most of the original cast, were made between 1978 and 1982. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We can’t have a new paradigm as long as people think the old one was free-market fundamentalism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45437</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/23/we-cant-have-a-new-paradigm-as-long-as-people-think-the-old-one-was-free-market-fundamentalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The belief in free-market fundamentalism runs very deep. When I say that, I don’t mean that support for the concept runs deep, I mean the belief that we had been pursuing free-market policies in the years before the Trump and Biden presidency runs very deep. I was reminded of this fact in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Selfish Woes About Dark Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a fan of having dark mode on my site because I have a hard time choosing colors that speak to me. I like to keep things minimalistic with my colors, and for me, it’s just much easier to do with a white background. However, I know (and acknowledge) the importance of having one, and so I pushed myself to do some tinkering on the blog this morning. Besides, my eyeballs also hate me when I look at my site at night, and so I’m sure it’s the case for other people too.
I subscribe to a lot of blogs via RSS reader, but I do take the extra step to launch their site to read the post. I have a deep appreciation for those who take the time to design their site the way they want, and so I want to read their posts the way it was meant to be read. It’s kind of like: listening to an album in order because I know that the artist ordered it a specific way for people to listen to. At the same time, it’s OK if you want to shuffle the playlist if you as the consumer want to, just like it’s OK for those who read my posts to do so via an RSS feed.
Anyways, this is just a quick post to say that, if your preference is dark mode, it is now available on here. I’ll revisit my site again at night time to test out the color contrasts (since I worked on this during daytime) to see if it makes sense, or if my eyeballs are still straining to read things.
Due to this, I’ve also gone ahead and created a Changelog for my site, so I can keep track of the little (and big) changes I make on here.
Side note:
I typically do have my screens on dark mode, and so if the sites/blog I read have dark mode, I read those in dark mode. It’s a weird thing for me to want my site in a lighter background, but I do struggle with it sometimes. Thanks to those who have put up with probably burning your retinas reading my posts if you weren’t doing so in an RSS reader. I appreciate you.
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Anthropic's Claude 3.5 Sonnet  All You Need -  Vibe check]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro
Source
    
I have been subbed to Claude Opus for a few months (yes, I am an earlier believer than you people). Couple of days back, I was working on a project and opened Anthropic chat. Then I realised it was showing "Sonnet 3.5 - Our most intelligent model" and it was seriously a major surprise.
I have been playing with with it for a couple of days now. Wrote some code ranging from Python, HTML, CSS, JSS to Pytorch and Jax. Made it do some editing and proof-reading. So far it's been smooth sailing. Maybe we haven't hit a wall yet (Ok I am not important enough to comment on this but you gotta remember it's my blog).
But why vibe-check, aren't benchmarks enough? Oversimplifying here but I think you cannot trust benchmarks blindly. There can be benchmark data leakage/overfitting to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Narbonne Cathedral (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52793</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/23/sunday-photoblogging-narbonne-cathedral-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T06:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Rooum - Anarchism is about individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T14:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Donald Rooum
Title: Anarchism is about individuals
Date: 1986
Notes: From the 1986 centenary issue of Freedom, pp. 56–57
Source: Retrieved on 2024-06-21 from https://files.libcom.org/files/freedom-centenary.pdf

 There is no such thing as human society. 
 A lot of muddled thinking rests on the error that because ‘society’ is a useful noun, it must refer to a thing. It is one of those nouns like ‘journey’ and ‘tennis’, which refers not to a thing but to a relationship between things. The statement ‘human society exists’ is simply a less cumbersome way of saying ‘human individuals relate to each other in certain complicated ways’. The question, ‘what is the purpose of human society?’ means the same as, ‘why do human individuals associate in the way they do?’. 
 Human craving for soci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The day I talked to my crush.]]></title>
        <id>https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/</id>
        <link href="https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T13:44:53.532Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was exciting, to say the least. I had an exam that day, and people usually finish their exams and go on their way. The problem was I had never talked to my crush before, so I couldn't exactly call her up to meet me. I finished my exam really early—about an hour and a half early—so that I wouldn't miss her.
Let's cut back to the morning of that day. I had already prepared what I wanted to say to her. But since I might talk non-stop, I decided to go with a letter (yeah, I'm old school that way—don't judge me). I woke up and did my morning routine (yes, I do have a routine). Then I wrote what I wanted to say, put it in an envelope, and went to the gym because I was too excited and nervous.
Now back to the scene where I'm waiting in the corridor for her to come out of the exam hall. Man, I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fault-isolated, zonal deployments with AWS CodeDeploy]]></title>
        <id>6bdb1a94f1d30c014904a2d39161cd2f38f4fcfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/fault-isolated-zonal-deployments-with-aws-codedeploy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post you’ll learn how to use a new feature in AWS CodeDeploy to deploy your application one Availability Zone (AZ) at a time to help increase the operational resilience or your services through improved fault isolation. Introducing change to a system can be a time of risk. Even the most advanced CI/CD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Haken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways Amazon Q simplifies AWS CloudFormation development]]></title>
        <id>325586d795e23aaa06a2c511ac9f946c1213c70b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-ways-amazon-q-simplifies-aws-cloudformation-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction As a builder, AWS CloudFormation provides a reliable way for you to model, provision, and manage AWS and third-party resources by treating infrastructure as code. First-time and experienced users of CloudFormation can often encounter some challenges when it comes to development of templates and stacks. CloudFormation offers a vast library of over 1,250 resource […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shape Rotation 101: An Intro to Einsum and Jax Transformers]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/einsum-new/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/einsum-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T04:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acknowledgements
First, I would like to acknowledge my friends and kind internet strangers who helped me with this post.
This post heavily adapts from the following -
Tested Jax Transformer code via xjdr |  Github Link
Einstein summation in pytorch
Einstein summation in numpy
Basic guide to einsum
Big thanks to _xjdr, Felix, Pushkar and Tokenbender for proof-reading.
Intro
I have been “delving” into jax and einsum notation lately in my quest to become a shape-rotator.
This post is divided into two parts. In the first part, we go through einsum notation basics. The second part is about understanding simple transformer code in jax which uses a lot of einsum.
From your end, I want some brains (no I am not a zombie, I just want your attention). I also assume knowledge of numpy basics, matrix m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost my notebook... And a fresh start.]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/lost-my-notebook-and-a-fresh-start/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/lost-my-notebook-and-a-fresh-start/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, new corner of the internet I've just found!
I found this place in the most fun way, I found a zine that was (I can only assume) planted in the library I work at by
veronique.ink! I thought it was the coolest thing I've ever seen, the coolest idea. Initially I didn't realize it was a website link that was written on the page, but an instagram handle, so I was struggling to find them for only a second before I found the sense to type it into google.
I recently lost my notebook, or at least can't find it in the mess of my room. Usually I write my random thoughts in there, as I figured I had become above the notes app and was looking for reasons to stay off my phone. Of course, as soon as I lose my means of documenting my ideas, all sorts of events pass me by with nowhere to write about them. I've only just finished high school, recently lost my grandmother, and all sorts of change is crashing my way, and now I need to just stew in it..? Or worse, take to my notes app??
Then lo and behold, there's the zine just sitting on the shelf. Scrolling through these websites here, I figured maybe it was a sign. Or I'm just bored and want a new hobby. Only God knows. So anyway, I'm hoping I'll still find my notebook once I get around to cleaning my room. Maybe then I can even publish those thoughts in there! For now I'll just write them straight from screen to the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark clouds over Europe with a few sunny patches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Dark-clouds-over-Europe-with-a-few-sunny-patches</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Dark-clouds-over-Europe-with-a-few-sunny-patches"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are publishing here a transcript of an interview with Éric Toussaint by journalist and publisher Mario Hernandez for the radio programme “Metropolis”, broadcast on June 13, 2024 on Radio del Pueblo (People's Radio), AM 830, in the city of Buenos Aires. 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Mario Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the UEFA Euro 2024 football games are impacting local Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>667596a1a4598c000bd70354</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-uefa-euro-2024-football-games-impact-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how UEFA Euro 2024 is shifting Internet traffic patterns during games across Europe with insights into traffic drops and cybersecurity concerns during national team games]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exam-ining recent Internet shutdowns in Syria, Iraq, and Algeria]]></title>
        <id>66747b7aa4598c000bd70245</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/syria-iraq-algeria-exam-internet-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar to actions taken over the last several years, governments in Syria, Iraq, and Algeria have again disrupted Internet connectivity nationwide in an attempt to prevent cheating on exams. We investigate how these disruptions were implemented, and their impact]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dustin Illingworth: &ldquo;Private Riddles&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/private-riddles</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/private-riddles"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yoko Tawada and Paul Celan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ilan Pappé: &ldquo;The Collapse of Zionism&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-collapse-of-zionism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-collapse-of-zionism"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six signs of breakdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edwin F. Ackerman: &ldquo;Transforming Mexico&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/transforming-mexico</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/transforming-mexico"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claudia Sheinbaum’s new regime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Militarist Initiative, Anonymous - The left of capital is sabotaging the anarchist movement: let’s fight back!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anti-militarist-initiative-anonymous-the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-l?v=1718919809</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anti-militarist-initiative-anonymous-the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-l?v=1718919809"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anti-Militarist Initiative, Anonymous
Title: The left of capital is sabotaging the anarchist movement: let’s fight back!
Date: June 2024
Source: https://antimilitarismus.noblogs.org/post/2024/06/14/the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-lets-fight-back/

 Soon after the escalation of the war in Ukraine, two completely different tendencies began to emerge under the banner of anarchy. One tendency insists that all inter-state wars are wars of the bourgeoisie against the proletariat, and therefore our participation in them cannot benefit the interests of the exploited class. The other tendency focuses on material, ideological and propaganda work in support of Ukraine’s state war effort and it sees such an approach as a pragmatic step for future self-organization. 
 R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections on the fear of failure and seeking recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-the-fear-of-failure-and-seeking-recognition/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-the-fear-of-failure-and-seeking-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
I don't know... Lately, I've been thinking a lot about my fear of failure (or maybe I've already failed?), seriously.
I'm a very hardworking person... I have courses from prestigious universities (currently over 95 courses), I know four languages and am fluent in three, and I have certifications that many people would love to have, but every day I feel like I'm failing more.
I work in the technology sector (and IT has more branches than medicine). Specifically, I specialize in databases and server infrastructure. I even have my own setup at home, including cloud, Git, blog, documentation, and various other things. Recently, I became unemployed because I lost my freelance contracts with companies, and on the same day my last contract ended, I took all my savings and paid off what I coul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeArtifact adds support for Rust packages with Cargo]]></title>
        <id>154d6b6a2483f420a12068e91b98f67bb15db6b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-codeartifact-adds-support-for-rust-packages-with-cargo/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeArtifact now supports Rust packages, enabling secure storage and management of Rust crates within your organization's private repositories, mitigating legal and security risks from external package sources while ensuring efficient collaboration across teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging about blogging versus adding value through your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7868</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/blogging-about-blogging-versus-adding-value-through-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less blogging about blogging: The majority of my posts are either platform explanations/justifications or organizational posts. Stuff like, “I’m moving the Archives here” or “I’ve added a ton of Links there.” Other times it’s simple announcements about me moving my blog someplace new. So, why do I feel the need to talk about this? This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy OS, an experimental Linux distro, by Barry Kauler]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7866</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/easy-os-experimental-linux-distro-barry-kauler/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m in the process of migrating my OS away from Windows. I’ve been running Linux Mint, considered to be a user-friendly, Windows-like distribution of the Linux family of OS’s, on a backup device for almost two weeks now. It’s been a learning curve naturally, but so far, so good. In the meantime though, the word […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burritos power Guzman Y Gomez to hot sharemarket debut]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7862</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/burritos-power-guzman-y-gomez-hot-sharemarket-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares in Australian founded Mexican food restaurant Guzman Y Gomez (GYG: it’s not only an initialism, it’s a ticker code) had a stellar debut on their first day of trading on the ASX, with one market pundit describing the launch as “the hottest float on the stock market in years“: Its shares opened at $30, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Peaky Blinders military unit helping to defend Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7860</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/peaky-blinders-military-unit-defend-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathryn Diss and Mathew Marsic, writing for ABC News: For Commander Anton, it’s difficult to imagine returning to his quiet life before the war. The 33-year-old former builder is now a battle-hardened soldier who risks his life every day, just kilometres from the Russian border. He is part of an elite squad of soldiers who […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the death of mgx]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/the-death-of-mgx/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/the-death-of-mgx/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:29:53.294Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bearblog.dev allows for open discussion and exchange of ideas in a low-stakes way. Putting my thoughts into writing on Bear means there are chances that some readers may open it and engage with it. At that moment, they are actively interpreting and making sense of it based on their own background. I find it liberating to release my raw text entries into the world and see what resonates or sparks new internal discussions for others. There is also a sense of relief in getting ideas that have been swirling in my mind out in the open. Once published, it feels like a task completed. While I don't necessarily stay involved in conversations about my posts, I appreciate seeing the ripple effects as others reflect on or debate the topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3.5 Sonnet model now available in Amazon Bedrock: Even more intelligence than Claude 3 Opus at one-fifth the cost]]></title>
        <id>362d245ccfb6f0d5062ec50122393c4a6f14ee2a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-5-sonnet-model-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock-the-most-intelligent-claude-model-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This powerful and cost-effective model outperforms on intelligence benchmarks, with remarkable capabilities in vision, writing, customer support, analytics, and coding to revolutionize your workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: With the New Popular Front against the deadly fascist threat!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-With-the-New-Popular-Front-against-the-deadly-fascist-threat</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-With-the-New-Popular-Front-against-the-deadly-fascist-threat"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When, just after the announcement of the results of the European elections, French President Macron surprised everyone by deciding to dissolve the Parliament and to call general elections for June 30, it was obvious that he aspired to repeat, once again, the successful blackmail thanks to which he had won his two presidential elections: to find himself alone against Marine Le Pen and her far-right party, thus forcing left-wing voters to vote for him in the absence of a left-wing alternative (...)
English

/ 
France, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper:  Fungal banking]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52776</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/20/occasional-paper-fungal-banking/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So in the last couple of decades we’ve discovered that many plants rely on networks of soil fungi to bring them critical trace nutrients. This is a symbiotic relationship: the fungal network can access these nutrients much better than plants can, and in return the plants provide the fungus with other stuff — particularly energy, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recap of the Data Engineering Open Forum at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6b4d4410b88f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-recap-of-the-data-engineering-open-forum-at-netflix-6b4d4410b88f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A summary of sessions at the first Data Engineering Open Forum at Netflix on April 18th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>