<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-24T01:33:04.564Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-24T01:33:04.564Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telstra redundancies, AI robots come in, the future is now]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/telstra-redundancies-ai-robots-future-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s largest telecommunications company, Telstra, announced this week it was making about three thousand employees, or ten percent, of its workforce redundant. About three hundred people were sent home straightaway — hopefully with some sort of pay-out — while the remainder will depart between now and the end of the year. This is terrible news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build bases on the Moon, instead of going for a week]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7671</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/build-bases-moon-instead-going-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA is dead set keen to return to the Moon. But their current plan, called Artemis, is dead set crazy, writes Polish-American entrepreneur and writer, Maciej Cegłowski: You don’t have to be a rocket scientist to wonder what’s going on here. If we can put a man on the moon, then why can’t we just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272083</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics;  can the Democrats allow Trump to take office, White House issues corrections, Marijuana policy ("and boogie they will") ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by boochiboo12 in "Daylight Computer – New 60fps e-paper tablet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40457491</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40457491"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T17:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi yall, founder of Daylight here.
Happy to answer any questions you have. Long time lurker, so this is pretty cool to finally take part :)
I made this because I wanted the eye-strain free and minimalist qualities of my kindle/Eink applied to so much more of what I do on a computer.
Lack of speed and ghosting felt like it made traditional Eink impossible to do most computing tasks. So we focused on making the most Paperlike epaper display that has no ghosting and high refresh rate - 60 to 120fps. We started working on this in 2018.
We developed our own custom epaper display tech we call LivePaper. We focused on solving the tradeoffs RLCDs traditionally have - around reflectance %, metallic-look / not Paperlike enough, viewing angle, white state, rainbow mura, parallax, resolution, size, lack of quality backlight, etc.
First proof of concept in late 2021, and then it took us 2.5 years to get it into production.
And we built a whole android tablet around it.
It’s essentially our attempt at making a remarkable tablet on steroids / kindle on steroids. Definitely some trade offs, but on the whole we think it’s worth it. (& on twitter a bunch of early customers seem to think so too)
Note: it’s 60fps epaper, not off the shelf Eink. We spent years developing what we think is the best epaper display in the world and it’s exclusively manufactured by our display factory in Japan.
There’s still many cases where traditional Eink is going to be better (bistability, viewing angle, white state color, etc), but we feel for more general purpose computers you can code on and do google docs on and do fast multitouch amongst a thousand other things, the speed and lack of ghosting totally makes it worth it.
Think of it as a Godzilla sized pebble watch with a decade of improvement
Or think of it as a gameboy advanced, advanced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>boochiboo12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmull in "OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40455846</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40455846"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, here are some things that aren't really being disputed:
* OpenAI wanted an AI voice that sounds like SJ
* SJ declined
* OpenAI got an AI voice that sounds like SJ anyway
I guess they want us to believe this happened without shenanigans, but it's bit hard to.
The headline of the article is a little funny, because records can't really show they weren't looking for an SJ sound-alike. They can just show that those records didn't mention it. The key decision-makers could simply have agreed to keep that fact close-to-the-vest -- they may have well understood that knocking off a high-profile actress was legally perilous.
Also, I think we can readily assume OpenAI understood that one of their potential voices sounded a lot like SJ. Since they were pursuing her they must have had a pretty good idea of what they were going after, especially considering the likely price tag. So even if an SJ voice wasn't the original goal, it clearly became an important goal to them. They surely listened to demos for many voice actors, auditioned a number of them, and may even have recorded many of them, but somehow they selected one for release who seemed to sound a lot like SJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G7: Whether or not to maintain the suspension of Ukrainian debt payments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the G7 discussing Ukraine's debt? 
English

/ 
G7 / G20, 
Debt in Northern countries, 
Ukraine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[沈阳 photo dump（mostly 老北市）]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:19:59.869Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some photographs from the Chinese city of 沈阳 (Shenyang).

I could spend all day browsing these five-story malls. This one boasted restaurants, cafes, daycares, basketball courts, go-karting, and live fish.

Fine dining in 沈阳. These are the food models in the lobby. My mom fighting with my aunt and uncle-in-law to first pay the bill, and when she loses that battle, to order fewer items. Lots of 客气 to go around. 

Although it may look the part, those flowers are not lavender. You can't see it here, but the whole time we were in Shenyang it looked as though it were snowing. I later learned that the "snow" was actually the seed hairs of the willow and the poplar trees. It looks cool until the fuzz gets in your eyes, on your clothes, everywhere. (source)
老北市
A popular night market in 沈阳 which runs every night. If you're there at the right time, you can catch the show with flying drone-powered phoenixes shooting fireworks from their wings. Sadly I don't have any good photos of that show — my senses were overwhelmed for most of the night (in a good way).










Night markets have been ruined for me forever. How can anything measure up to that? Not to mention we passed two markets en route to 老北市 that also looked better than anything I'd ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masks Work, Our Comprehensive Review Has Found]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272067</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/masks-work-our-comprehensive-review-has-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, a rigorous study on mask use shows definitively that masks do indeed work, as in reduce transmission of respiratory diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272059</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our crepuscular daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das: The Economic Costs of  Modern War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271986</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/satyajit-das-the-economic-costs-of-modern-war.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How economic, military and political costs and consequences are intersecting in the Ukraine and Israel-Palestine conflicts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skill Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:37:22.552Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term skill issue is thrown around Twitter a lot. It comes from gaming culture. If you can't beat a level. It is a skill issue. Just level up and win. If you think about it, it is a powerful term. It gives power to the player.
Applied to life everything is a skill issue. Can't do the perfect juggle? Skill issue. Can't write awesome distributed performant code? Skill issue. Can't convince a penguin to try your awesome new ice cream? You guessed it. Skill issue. It is a powerful mindset. Gives you extreme ownership.
But there is a catch. Do you take ownership of other people's shitty behavior? No. You can take ownership of the triggers and environment you perhaps created to lead to that shitty behavior. Especially if you are in positions of power to have a big impact(ie: manager/CEO). Otherwise, constant shitty behavior is their burden to bear. Avoid such people. People rarely change and you don't need the negativity in your life.
Here the skill issue is effectively able to isolate and weed out the negativity. This is purely in a professional context. In a more personal context, things are a lot more messy. I don't have an answer for that which works. A skill issue on my end. Need more life experience to resolve it.
Make everything a skill issue and just level up!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272061</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/why-corporations-choose-lawlessness-to-fight-unions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers at companies like Apple and Starbucks face armies of union-busting lawyers advising employers to repeatedly violate labor laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by omnicognate in "OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451982</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451982"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T08:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Comments full of people reading the headline and assuming that what OpenAI did here is fine because it's a different actress, but that's not how "Right of publicity" (*) laws work. The article itself explains that there is significant legal risk here:
> Mitch Glazier, the chief executive of the Recording Industry Association of America, said that Johansson may have a strong case against OpenAI if she brings forth a lawsuit.
> He compared Johansson’s case to one brought by the singer Bette Midler against the Ford Motor Co. in the 1980s. Ford asked Midler to use her voice in ads. After she declined, Ford hired an impersonator. A U.S. appellate court ruled in Midler’s favor, indicating her voice was protected against unauthorized use.
> But Mark Humphrey, a partner and intellectual property lawyer at Mitchell, Silberberg and Knupp, said any potential jury probably would have to assess whether Sky’s voice is identifiable as Johansson.
> Several factors go against OpenAI, he said, namely Altman’s tweet and his outreach to Johansson in September and May. “It just begs the question: It’s like, if you use a different person, there was no intent for it to sound like Scarlett Johansson. Why are you reaching out to her two days before?” he said. “That would have to be explained.”
* A.K.A. "Personality rights": https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Personality_rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>omnicognate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collapse of the Thwaites Glacier Has Accelerated]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272054</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/collapse-of-the-thwaites-glacier-has-accelerated.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The timetable for the collapse of the Thwaites Glacier is collapsing, and why that matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oxygen_crisis in "WinDirStat – Windows Directory Statistics"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451333</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451333"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WizTree is famously almost 50x faster than WinDirStat (on normal Windows NTFS drives) by reading the Master File Table (MFT) instead of walking the tree to measure each file.
WizTree isn't open-source like WinDirStat but "free as in beer" with optional donations.
There's also a fork of WinDirStat patched to read the MFT but I don't know anyone who's tried it: https://github.com/ariccio/altWinDirStat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oxygen_crisis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by serial_dev in "OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451129</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40451129"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know, to me, it's just sounds like they know how to cover all their bases.
To me, it sounds like they had the idea to make their AI sound like "her". For the initial version, they had a voice actor that sounds like the movie, as a proof of concept.
They still liked it, so it was time to contact the real star. In the end, it's not just the voice, it would have been the brand, just imagine the buzz they would have got if Scarlett J was the official voice of the company. She said no, and they were like, "too bad, we already decided how she will sound like, the only difference is whether it will be labelled as SJ or not".
In the end, someone probably felt like it's a bit too dodgy as it resemblance was uncanny, they gave it another go, probably ready to offer more money, she still refused, but in the end, it didn't change a thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>serial_dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critics of Campus Protests are Weaponizing Anti-Semitism to Undermine Student Resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323656</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/critics-of-campus-protests-are-weaponizing-anti-semitism-to-undermine-student-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College campuses and universities across the country have organized some of the largest peace activities and anti-war protests since 1969. As the social movement points in specific directions in calling for Palestinian liberation, over 100 schools scattered across the United States from American to Yale University have participated and issued their own sets of “Five  More
The post Critics of Campus Protests are Weaponizing Anti-Semitism to Undermine Student Resistance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ICC is Doing Its Job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323530</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/the-icc-is-doing-its-job/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ICC is doing its job. It's doing what it is supposed to do. We cannot only apply international law when it is convenient. And the independent panel of international legal experts the ICC appointed to help with this case unanimously – unanimously – agreed with the charges. More
The post The ICC is Doing Its Job appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernie Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear White Friends: Can You Smell the Yellow Roses of Dier al-Balah?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323361</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/dear-white-friends-can-you-smell-the-yellow-roses-of-dier-al-balah/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Family and neighbors and community and country come first, right? Right. But what happens when that country happens to be the most powerful in the world, spending its entire time since 1947 maintaining world hegemony, with catastrophic consequences for the people of the Global South? Then our communities occupy not only the land within US borders; they occupy Afghanistan, Iraq, Yemen, Syria and all of the other countries that have suffered under our imperialism. Maybe most of all, Palestine. More
The post Dear White Friends: Can You Smell the Yellow Roses of Dier al-Balah? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Priti Gulati Cox – Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For Many American Jews Protesting for Palestinians, Activism is a Journey Rooted in Their Jewish Values]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323517</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/for-many-american-jews-protesting-for-palestinians-activism-is-a-journey-rooted-in-their-jewish-values/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Rebekah and many other American Jews, the cultural memory of the Holocaust, and the common refrain “Never Again,” inspires their activism for Palestinian rights. “Growing up in Hebrew schools, you grow up with the nightmarish Holocaust films,” she stressed. “The conclusion of this education should have been clear: ‘You can’t do it to another group of people!’” More
The post For Many American Jews Protesting for Palestinians, Activism is a Journey Rooted in Their Jewish Values appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atalia Omer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grizzly Hunting is Trophy Hunting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323484</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/grizzly-hunting-is-trophy-hunting/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A final decision on the petitions to remove the grizzly bear from the list of threatened species and the protections of the Endangered Species Act (delisting) may come in June or early July. Currently, authority over grizzly bear management is vested in the U.S. Fish & Wildlife Service. If the petitions are approved, management will  More
The post Grizzly Hunting is Trophy Hunting appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Bader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rages of Equivalence: The ICC Prosecutor, Israel and Hamas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323532</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/the-rages-of-equivalence-the-icc-prosecutor-israel-and-hamas/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legal world was abuzz.  The diplomatic channels of various countries raged and fizzed.  It had been rumoured that Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, along with his cabinet colleagues, had been bracing themselves for a stinging intervention from the International Criminal Court, a body they give no credence or respect to. Then came the words from the Prosecutor of  More
The post The Rages of Equivalence: The ICC Prosecutor, Israel and Hamas appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Keep the Affordable Care Act Working, But Can’t Afford to See a Doctor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323534</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/i-keep-the-affordable-care-act-working-but-cant-afford-to-see-a-doctor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love my job. Every day I get to answer phone calls from some of the tens of millions of Americans who rely on the Affordable Care Act and help them get the healthcare benefits they need. Even though I do an essential job, my employer — the federal call center run by Maximus in  More
The post I Keep the Affordable Care Act Working, But Can’t Afford to See a Doctor appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Charles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi Dies in Helicopter Crash, Leaving Behind a Polarizing Legacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323536</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/iranian-president-ebrahim-raisi-dies-in-helicopter-crash-leaving-behind-a-polarizing-legacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ebrahim Raisi, the Iranian President, and the country’s foreign minister were tragically found deceased on May 20, 2024, shortly after their helicopter crashed in foggy conditions. In response, Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei swiftly appointed a relatively unknown vice president as the interim leader. According to Iran’s Constitution, the First Vice President assumes the presidency  More
The post Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi Dies in Helicopter Crash, Leaving Behind a Polarizing Legacy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Housing, Not Handcuffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323557</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/housing-not-handcuffs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 22nd, the Supreme Court heard oral arguments for Grants Pass v. Johnson, a case that focuses on whether unhoused — the term that has generally replaced “homeless” — people with no indoor shelter options can even pull a blanket around themselves outdoors without being subject to criminal punishment. Before making its way to the  More
The post Housing, Not Handcuffs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LIZ THEOHARIS - SHAILLY GUPTA BARNES</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump Has Poisoned the Well]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323554</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/donald-trump-has-poisoned-the-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In ancient times, it was common practice to poison sources of fresh water before the arrival of an invading army to diminish its strength. That practice has now been revived by Donald Trump to sap his adversaries’ strength, and has been widely used by his followers, with detrimental effects on the quality of political discourse  More
The post Donald Trump Has Poisoned the Well appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Regrets, We’ve had a Few]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323349</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/letter-from-london-regrets-weve-had-a-few/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A beleaguered Rishi Sunak set out plans last week to increase food security in this country by decreasing our dependence on food from abroad by growing it ourselves. I was already on it, Prime Minister. On the kitchen window-sill was a small pot of soil once hosting a parsley plant, from which a few weeks  More
The post Letter from London: Regrets, We’ve had a Few appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Calls the Shots with Russia and Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323549</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/china-calls-the-shots-with-russia-and-europe/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:28:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putin the Supplicant Xi Jinping’s balancing act with Russia and the West took on a new challenge with Vladimir Putin’s arrival in Beijing on May 16. It was roughly the 40th such meeting of these supposedly old friends. Once again Xi had to demonstrate loyalty to Russia in its war in Ukraine while also showing sensitivity  More
The post China Calls the Shots with Russia and Europe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Wine Mogul David Trone Crashed and Burned His Senate Bid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323345</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/how-wine-mogul-david-trone-crashed-and-burned-his-senate-bid/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the closing weeks of Maryland’s Democratic Senate primary, wine mogul David Trone was lighting both his money and campaign on fire. The race came down to which he’d burn through first. As his early lead gave way in the homestretch before the May 14 election, Trone’s desperation began to show. In a May 1 interview with  More
The post How Wine Mogul David Trone Crashed and Burned His Senate Bid appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Trump’s Corporate Tax Cuts Sparked Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323253</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/23/how-trumps-corporate-tax-cuts-sparked-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T04:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next year, when key provisions of President Trump’s 2017 tax breaks to the wealthy and corporations expire, we have an opportunity to get our money back. I’m not just talking about all the foregone tax revenue we’ve lost because the rich have paid so little since 2017 — though we should get that back, too.  More
The post How Trump’s Corporate Tax Cuts Sparked Inflation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsay Owens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by julianeon in "US Justice Department to seek breakup of Live Nation-Ticketmaster"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447979</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447979"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T23:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Live Nation-Ticketmaster is not a monopoly then there is no such thing as a monopoly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>julianeon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tedivm in "Leaked OpenAI documents reveal aggressive tactics toward former employees"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447810</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447810"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have worked for multiple startups (Malwarebytes, Vicarious, Rad AI, Explosion AI, Aptible, Kenna Security). Not once have I seen an exit agreement that stated they would steal back my vested equity if I didn't sign. This is definitely not "standard restrictions".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tedivm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by NotSammyHagar in "Leaked OpenAI documents reveal aggressive tactics toward former employees"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447762"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This reads like more than standard restrictions. I hate those like everyone, they are just intended to chill complaints in my opinion with enough question to scare average people without legal expertise (like me, like most devs), just like non-competes used to seemingly primarily be used to discourage looking at other jobs, separate from whether it was enforceable - note the recent FTC decision to end non-competes.
About 5 months ago I had a chance to join a company, their company had what looked like an extreme non-compete to me, you couldn't work for any company for the next two years after leaving if they had been a customer of that company.
I pointed out to them that I wouldn't have been able to join their company if my previous job had that non-compete clause, it seemed excessive. Eventually I was in meetings with a lawyer at the company who told me it's probably not enforceable, don't worry about it, and the FTC is about to end non-competes. I said great, strike it from the contract and I'll sign it right now. He said I can't do that, no one off contracts. So then I said I'm not working there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NotSammyHagar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tedivm in "Leaked OpenAI documents reveal aggressive tactics toward former employees"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447613</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447613"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If this really was a mistake the easiest way to deal with it would be to release people from their non disparagement agreements that were only signed by leaving employees under the duress of losing their vested equity.
It's really easy to make people whole for this, so whether that happens or not is the difference between the apologies being real or just them just backpedaling because employees got upset.
Edit: Looks like they're doing the right thing here:
> Altman’s initial statement was criticized for doing too little to make things right for former employees, but in an emailed statement, OpenAI told me that “we are identifying and reaching out to former employees who signed a standard exit agreement to make it clear that OpenAI has not and will not cancel their vested equity and releases them from nondisparagement obligations” — which goes much further toward fixing their mistake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tedivm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mateus1 in "Leaked OpenAI documents reveal aggressive tactics toward former employees"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447526</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40447526"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What surprises me about these stories surrounding openAI is how they apologize while lying and downplaying  any blame. Do they expect anybody to believe they didn’t know about clawback clauses?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mateus1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running clubs, the IndieWeb of the dating realm?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7657</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/running-clubs-indieweb-dating-realm/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Marshall, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Run South Yarra co-founder Tom Adair is wary of any suggestion that run clubs are the new Tinder, yet relationships are born here, and side-by-side chats while jogging, he notes, are definitely less pressurised than face-to-face interactions. (Plus, you can always pick up the pace and scoot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michael9423 in "One-third of Amazon warehouse workers are on food stamps or Medicaid"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40445715</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40445715"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actually, it's the opposite. At the level of automation we've reached, labor is worth, per hour, way more than 100 years ago. The problem is just that this value is siphoned off by shareholders who do not have to work to receive the monetary value that should go to the worker. So the issue is simply in how corporations are set up and how the stock market is designed.
The entire system is designed to drain as much value out of hardworking people into the pockets of those who do not work, but simply own shares.
Being able to buy and sell shares is not problematic per se, but there should be rules in place that give all workers of a publicly traded company better access to owning parts of said company. In other words, all workers of a rich company should be (relatively spoken) rich, corresponding to the value they provided to the company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michael9423</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by notaustinpowers in "Windows Recall sounds like a privacy nightmare"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40445595</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40445595"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fact that it ensures to not take a snapshot of DRM content but also explains that it doesn't hide PASSWORDS in snapshots is INSANE to me!
God forbid it takes a screenshot of Bridgerton but my bank account password, that's fair game!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>notaustinpowers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16644</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/balancing-old-tricks-with-new-feats-ai-powered-conversion-from-enzyme-to-react-testing-library-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of frontend development, one thing remains certain: change is the only constant. New frameworks emerge, and libraries can become obsolete without warning. Keeping up with the ever-changing ecosystem involves handling code conversions, both big and small. One significant shift for us was the transition from Enzyme to React Testing Library (RTL), prompting […]
The post Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergii Gorbachov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/22/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272027</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-22-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics, Stefanik files ethics complaint against Merchan, Greenhalgh publishes ginormous, magisterial study, stomps anti-maskers and droplet dogmatists, "trust your immune system." ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable data management at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21235</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/data-infrastructure/composable-data-management-at-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, Meta’s data management systems have evolved into a composable architecture that creates interoperability, promotes reusability, and improves engineering efficiency.  We’re sharing how we’ve achieved this, in part, by leveraging Velox, Meta’s open source execution engine, as well as work ahead as we continue to rethink our data management systems.  Data is at [...]
Read More...
The post Composable data management at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21222</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/security/post-quantum-readiness-tls-pqr-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the internet (like most digital infrastructure in general) relies heavily on the security offered by public-key cryptosystems such as RSA, Diffie-Hellman (DH), and elliptic curve cryptography (ECC). But the advent of quantum computers has raised real questions about the long-term privacy of data exchanged over the internet. In the future, significant advances in quantum [...]
Read More...
The post Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 7thpower in "Sal Khan is pioneering innovation in education again"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40441616</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40441616"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a high school dropout and who learned math using Khan Academy after never having completed more than pre-algebra in middle school.
Sal Khan’s work changed my life and allowed me to build a foundation in not only math, but also finance and economics, that allowed me to feel confident enough to go to college. I did not have a support system or people in my life who could teach me these things, but I had the internet and patience, which meant I had opportunities that did not exist even a few years before (this was in 2014).
Now I work in AI and generally have a life I could not have dreamed of. Every time I go to the grocery store to buy something and don’t have to worry about my card being declined, it feels like magic. Even years later.
If I had been in that situation a few years earlier, my life would be very different.
I’m excited to live in a world where my daughters and countless others will have a tutor that can help them maximize their potential throughout their lives. I’m excited not only for them, but for society. What a time to be alive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>7thpower</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Gaza Starvation Ploy Intensifies With Seizure of Rafah Crossings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272024</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/israel-gaza-starvation-ploy-intensifies-with-seizure-of-rafah-crossings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rafah operation is speeding the pace of genocide in Gaza.  That looks to be its primary aim.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans in the Labor Market: 2024 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29773</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/veterans-are-doing-better-in-the-labor-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans constitute a significant segment of the male labor force, and understanding labor market disparities between veterans and non‑veterans is an important component of studying disparities in the economy as a whole. In a previous Liberty Street Economics post, we have shown that even relative to a group of comparable non-veterans, veterans have lower employment and labor force participation rates. One year later, we see that veterans continue to experience lower labor market attachment and the employment gap has widened, though the earnings gap has closed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Dan Garcia, and Maxim Pinkovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding Regional Services configuration flexibility for customers]]></title>
        <id>66448139abf9e2000aee8587</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/expanding-regional-services-configuration-flexibility-for-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're happy to announce expanded capabilities that will allow you to configure Regional Services for an increased set of defined regions to help you meet your specific requirements for being able to control where your traffic is handled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is generally available: a unified interface for managing and scaling your generative AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>664cf64607441c000a06e4ed</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-gateway-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is an AI ops platform that provides speed, reliability, and observability for your AI applications. With a single line of code, you can unlock powerful features including rate limiting, custom caching, real-time logs, and aggregated analytics across multiple providers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Liao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/22/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271982</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-22-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T10:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our blistering daily links: moar cat bird flu victims, coffee drinking decline, Taiwan factory kill switches, police getting DNA via false Covid tests, AfD, Netanyahu doubles down on genocide, Zelensky meltdown, Trump beats Biden $ haul, Supremes, confused Fed, private equity v. pet owners]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gresham’s Law Comes for Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272018</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/greshams-law-comes-for-science.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T09:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Science publication has become so corrupted that entire journals have been shut down over running fake research. How did we get here?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A genuine selfmade billionaire]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52714</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/22/a-genuine-selfmade-billionaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that no-one deserves to be a billionaire. In the public realm, defenders of wealth concentration often come up with an example of a person who has created all their wealth themselves – the selfmade billionaire. They didn’t get their money from inheritance or some other form of luck, but from entrepreneurial instincts and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wolfensohn switches on the charm (1995-2005)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who is Pro-Israel California Rep. Jared Huffman—Really?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323426</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/who-is-california-rep-jared-huffman-really/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T06:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protestors probe his political psyche and we follow the money Northern California congressperson Jared Huffman, 60, held his annual “Hootenanny” campaign fundraiser at Lagunitas Brewery in Petaluma, California. Press were denied entry to the private party, but the real story was outside, as CounterPunch discovered. The fundraising event did not go karmically well for the  More
The post Who is Pro-Israel California Rep. Jared Huffman—Really? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Byrne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Hedge-Fund Driven Neoliberal University]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323257</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/welcome-to-the-hedge-fund-driven-neoliberal-university/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the spirit of ruthless equity firms and asset-stripping hedge fund managers, pedagogies of conformity, silencing, and ethical abandonment now proliferate under the guise of budget cuts or overt attempts to transform higher education into white nationalist indoctrination centers. Universities are now viewed as businesses, students as clients, and faculty as a serf-like, casual labor force. Furthermore, administrative leadership has regressed, modeling itself after hedge fund managers and embracing a market-driven ideology that believes the irrational belief that the market to solve all problems and control not only the economy but all aspects of social life. More
The post Welcome to the Hedge-Fund Driven Neoliberal University appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Assange Case: A Flicker of Hope in the UK High Court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323473</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/the-assange-case-a-flicker-of-hope-in-the-uk-high-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was faint, but there was more than just a flicker of hope.  In the tormented (and tormenting) journey the WikiLeaks founder and publisher, Julian Assange, has endured, May 20, 2024 provided another pitstop.  As with many such stops over the years, it involved lawyers.  Many of them. The occasion was whether the UK High Court of Justice  More
The post The Assange Case: A Flicker of Hope in the UK High Court appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Obstacle to Free and Fair Elections in Venezuela is the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323256</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/the-biggest-obstacle-to-free-and-fair-elections-in-venezuela-is-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For all the hullabaloo about “free and fair elections” in Venezuela by the US government, its sycophantic corporate press deliberately ignores the elephant in the room – namely, the so-called sanctions designed to make life so miserable that the people will acquiesce to Washington’s plan for regime change. As Foreign Policy puts it, “Venezuelan President  More
The post The Biggest Obstacle to Free and Fair Elections in Venezuela is the US appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[apartment hunting, and finding meaning in living alone]]></title>
        <id>https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/</id>
        <link href="https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:38:01.193Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fall, I'll be moving to a new city to pursue graduate studies. I thought it'd be a good idea to move in a few months early to get a feel for the area - and also avoid fighting over good areas around campus, especially if I wait too long.
Next week I'm flying out to visit some apartments. It dawned upon me that this would be the first time where I live truly alone - no housemates, roommates, parents, pets - it'll be just me, in a new city. I'm excited of course, but also quite scared. The thought of being free and landing into a new city is something amazing, but for the first time, I'm really on my own.
I moved back with my parents to save on rent a year ago. And while I do appreciate them for their generosity, I think it's time for me to leave; I've been paying rent with my mental health, something a lot of Asian kids can relate to. I also feel restricted when I came back to the city where I attended high school. It was like I'm in purgatory: suffering for some time before entering heaven (a place of my own).
It's a big step, despite something I'm excited for. Yet very scary. But if I'm scared to do it, it's exactly because I'm scared that I should do it.
I think I'm ready now. Ready to take that big leap, into a new home, nearly a thousand miles away from where I grew up.
The (paper) journal I've kept since 2020 is reaching the last few pages, appropriately. It's as if it knew that my journey here was coming to an end, and a new one will begin soon.
I'll be buying a new notebook once in Seattle. Only appropriate when closing a chapter, no?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. King’s Words on Vietnam Still Ring True for Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323385</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/dr-kings-words-on-vietnam-still-ring-true-for-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Israeli troops continue their assault in Rafah, increasing the death toll and displacing – yet again – hundreds of thousands of Gazans, there’s much to be learned from recalling Dr. Martin Luther King’s visionary words on Vietnam 57 years ago. Breaking his silence on a war that by then had claimed over 20,000 American  More
The post Dr. King’s Words on Vietnam Still Ring True for Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Security: Productivity Growth and the Scary Stories About Rising Retiree to Worker Ratios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323280</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/social-security-productivity-growth-and-the-scary-stories-about-rising-retiree-to-worker-ratios/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of the release of the 2024 Social Security Trustees Report, we have seen a wave of columns and news articles telling us that we won’t have enough workers to support a growing population of retirees. The story is that all of us baby boomer types are now retiring and the later generations  More
The post Social Security: Productivity Growth and the Scary Stories About Rising Retiree to Worker Ratios appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Nadir of Human Behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323383</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/the-nadir-of-human-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It was the best of times, it was the worst of times, it was the age of wisdom, it was the age of foolishness, it was the epoch of belief, it was the epoch of incredulity, it was the season of light, it was the season of darkness, it was the spring of hope, it  More
The post The Nadir of Human Behavior appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Judith Deutsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Student Debt Crisis Would Likely Worsen Under a Second Trump Administration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323264</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/22/why-the-student-debt-crisis-would-likely-worsen-under-a-second-trump-administration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T04:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crisis of student debt has reached proportions never before seen in the United States. Collectively, students owed $1.6 trillion in federal student loans at the end of 2023. However, that total is slightly lower than it was two years prior, thanks to some proactive actions from the Biden administration. The administration has pursued a  More
The post Why the Student Debt Crisis Would Likely Worsen Under a Second Trump Administration appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Richwine – Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do I have to write my own Anki cards?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.memothon.com/why-do-i-have-to-write-my-own-anki-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.memothon.com/why-do-i-have-to-write-my-own-anki-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T01:14:11.309Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You really shouldn't have to write your own Anki cards today.
There's a really common sentiment that using pre-made or llm generated decks can't replace creating your own.
This is probably true. Writing your own flashcards forces you into a state where you have to actually think and organize the concepts together in your head into things that are digestible.
Often the flashcards that people create are not conducive to review. It's hard to create cards that aren't easy to remember the "shape" of later on instead of actually remembering the content. And drilling one small piece of the puzzle doesn't fill in the rest of the pie.
LLMs are sophisticated enough now to generate variations on flashcards on-demand. But nobody has wired up LLMs natively with spaced repetition for learning. It seems like everyone has stopped at "generate 100 flashcards for me based on this pdf," which does result in flashcards that aren't going to help you remember things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bragr in "Show HN: Pls Fix – Hire big tech employees to appeal account suspensions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40435890</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40435890"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T00:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is commercial bribery in most places.
>California Code, Penal Code - PEN § 641.3
>(a) Any employee who solicits, accepts, or agrees to accept money or any thing of value from a person other than his or her employer, other than in trust for the employer, corruptly and without the knowledge or consent of the employer, in return for using or agreeing to use his or her position for the benefit of that other person, and any person who offers or gives an employee money or any thing of value under those circumstances, is guilty of commercial bribery.
>(b) This section does not apply where the amount of money or monetary worth of the thing of value is two hundred fifty dollars ($250) or less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bragr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental selling point of all productivity advice is getting more done in less time. It's a good hook. I have over the years consumed a lot of content around productivity. It took me a long time to realise I was making a fundamental mistake.
I assumed I would stumble upon some specific protocol that I can follow perfectly and my life is set. So I have tried it all. All kinds of wake-sleep times. Journaling. All kinds of productivity apps and timing techniques. Trying to get as much damn sunlight in my little eye holes within x minutes of waking up(yes, I had a Huberman era). Nothing worked.
The fundamental mistake in all of this is I thought of my mind as some unmotivated child that I could be strict with and discipline into getting stuff done. But if you have ever taught young children( I have) you will know that discipline and fear only get you so far. Getting them interested in the topic changes the game.
This realisation drastically changed my life. I can get my mind interested in doing things through self-programming. Everyone is different on how to do this. Many of these routines and techniques that we hear about are just outcomes of effective self-programming unique to that individual. Each of us needs to find our unique way.
How to program your mind? You can introspect and the documentation of your mind will reveal itself to you. Also, there are some ways you can make the mind more malleable to programming. I have given a framework I follow for this in my 'Hacking Hardwork' post.
There is no golden technique that will save you. Only you can save yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by panarky in "Sam Altman is showing us who he really is"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40434884</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40434884"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T22:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altman would have us believe it's all just an innocent misunderstanding but without actually saying so:
"We cast the voice actor behind Sky’s voice before any outreach to Ms. Johansson."
Is he trying to suggest the company did not try to make the voice sound like her without her permission?
The statement sounds like it's written by a lawyer to be technically true while implying something that is actually false.
These are weasel words.
He sounds sneaky, evasive and intentionally deceptive.
We should not give a sneaky, deceptive and manipulative person this much power over our future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>panarky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My 2001: A Space Odyssey remake joke post trained Google AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7631</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2001-a-space-odyssey-remake-joke-post-trained-google-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two and bit years ago, I spotted an entry on Fandom about a “remake” of the Stanley Kubrick sci-fi classic, 2001: A Space Odyssey. Being a 2001 fan, I naturally wrote about it. I’ve had a lot of fun with the post ever since. People stumble upon it every now and again, and link to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth wins NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of year 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7637</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/she-is-the-earth-wins-nsw-premiers-literary-awards-book-year-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth, a work of verse, written by Yankunytjatjara (South Australia) poet Ali Cobby Eckermann, was named the NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of the year, on Monday 20 May 2024. Award judges were unstinting in their praise of Eckermann’s writing: She is the Earth is a stunning verse novel that takes the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by constantcrying in "Show HN: Pls Fix – Hire big tech employees to appeal account suspensions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40433333</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40433333"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seems insane. Surely every single company would fire you for doing that. If you put this in its proper term it is "corruption" and you should definitely worry about the legal implications of doing this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>constantcrying</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An indie guide to the IndieWeb, by Wing Pang]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7641</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-guide-indieweb-wing-pang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based product designer Wing Pang, whom I wrote about last week, has published a comprehensive guide to the IndieWeb. Coming from a design background, joining the IndieWeb was an incredibly exciting and rewarding, yet maze-like journey. To be honest, almost every step of the way was like a leap! But I’ve learnt so much […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring fair bandwidth allocation for Amazon EKS Workloads]]></title>
        <id>6094b32da7c2d5cacc202444ec0b024d73ee06c4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/ensuring-fair-bandwidth-allocation-for-amazon-eks-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Service Vendor (ISV) users often offer their end-user solutions hosted on a multi-tenant architecture to reduce cost and operational management. However, this approach can lead Kubernetes clusters to resource exhaustion or network starvation issues that impact neighboring workloads. By default, Kubernetes provides capabilities to enforce resource availability such as CPU and memory to prevent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jpgvm in "Gordon Bell has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40433060</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40433060"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:54:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gordon was the first investor in my first startup, the first guy that believed in us.
Even though I only met him later in his life he was still sharp as a tack, never lost the mind of the engineer. Sometimes it's best not to meet your heroes but Gordon lived up to the hype and then some.
Super gentle, generous with his time, the consummate gentleman.
One of my fondest memories from my startup years was enjoying dinner with Gordon and his wife in Sydney, she made the most amazing cookies. To this day I don't think I have had a better cookie haha.
Visited the computer history museum with him once for a bit of a VIP tour I guess. So many stories about PDPs and all the friends he made along the way.
Thanks for all the stories and memories old man, you have earned your rest.
RIP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jpgvm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, bringing back the blogosphere one blog at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7643</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/blog-of-the-day-bringing-back-blogosphere-one-blog-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, yes, styled as Blog of the .Day, a collaboration between James of James’ Coffee Blog, and Joe Crawford, will highlight a new blog every day. Aside from casting the spotlight daily on a blog, another goal of the project is to bring the term blogosphere back into popular usage. For those […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by evmar in "The curious case of the missing period"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40432486</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40432486"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> A portion of this code implemented a SMTP client.
If I wanted to root cause this, the real problem is right there.  Implementing protocols correctly is hard and bugs like in the post are common.  A properly implemented SMTP client library, like one you would pull off the shelf, would accept text and encode it properly per the SMTP protocol, regardless of where the periods were in the input.  The templating layer shouldn't be worrying about SMTP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "How to Turn Off AI Overview in Google and Set "Web" as Default"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40431495</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40431495"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T17:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your loss, I will keep expanding my brain with the wisdom of Googles powerful AI
https://imgur.com/a/g4qOU9a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pants2 in "What UI density means and how to design for it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40430177</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40430177"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This explains exactly why physical restaurant menus are so much better vs mobile site menus. If I'm viewing the menu of a restaurant on my phone, I always look in Google Maps for someone who took a picture of the menu, because it's a dense UI. Every "mobile friendly" menu site is able to show maybe 5 items on the page at once, so it takes many pages of scrolling to see everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pants2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouth Dildos]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:41:59.234Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People that use mouth dildos annoy the shit out of me. Either commit and smoke a cigarette, or give it up.
I hate smoking. I think it's fucking disgusting and I don't understand why anyone would want to do it. I especially hate it when there's a gaggle of smokers huddled around the front door of a pub, tooting away on their fags. It's vile and I don't want my pink fluffy lungs affected by that shit.
But do you know what I hate more than smoking?
Mouth dildos.
What the fuck is a mouth dildo?
-- Everyone
This is a mouth dildo:

Not only do you look ridiculous putting that stupid fucking contraption in your mouth, but the plumes of flavoured vapour that bellow from these things make you look even more like an utter cunt.
I don't want to be subjected to the cherry ice cream vapour pouring from your mouth dildos, seemingly by the bucket load. At least smokers are committing, knowing they're gonna kill themselves, have decided to enjoy it while they're here.
But you mouth dildo fuckers are the worst. We don't want to smell your stupid fucking vape. So put it away because you look (and smell) like a dick head.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Changing Landscape of Corporate Credit]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29223</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/the-changing-landscape-of-corporate-credit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firms’ access to credit is a crucial determinant of their investment, employment, and overall growth decisions. While we usually think of their ability to borrow as determined by aggregate credit conditions, in reality firms have a number of markets where they can borrow, and conditions can vary across those markets. In this post, we investigate how the composition of debt instruments on U.S. firms’ balance sheets has evolved over the last twenty years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Boyarchenko and Leonardo Elias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Mr. Mitsotakis criminalizes, threatens and represses students who defend international legality!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If some people think they can repeat what they've seen in other countries and occupy universities, pitch tents and make a mess, they're deeply mistaken”. This - so eminently delicate - statement by the Greek Prime Minister, which followed the brutal “evacuation” of the law faculty on Tuesday May 14 (28 arrests), can only surprise the uninformed: the Greek state and its governments have always had a soft spot for anything to do with apartheid and apartheid regimes! Today Israel, formerly South (...)
English

/ 
Greece, 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SilverBirch in "The OpenAI board was right"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40425855</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40425855"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It really is incredible how something as small and simple as this gives such incredible bad vibes. This is like early 2010s facebook vibes. It's just... if they're going to steal her voice, what would they do to yours?
But it also points to a wider problem in OpenAI's existence. They're built on theft. If you wrote something on the internet in the last 20 years, they've stolen it. They've stolen it, they're put it into their little magic box and now they want to sell it back to you. OpenAI is amazing technology, and once the equity of the company is redistributed back to the content owners who actually provided the value, it'll be great to see what they can do from there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SilverBirch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by trustno2 in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40424722</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40424722"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altman wants to be a part of AI regulation in the same way Bankman Fried wanted to be a part of cryptocurrency regulation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trustno2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dead End of Liberal American Zionism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323343</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-dead-end-of-liberal-american-zionism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant number of American Jews are now willing to challenge the Zionist project while pointing out that it is inherently fated to suppress the human rights of non-Jews in Palestine. Speaking at a protest near Sen. Chuck Schumer’s home in Brooklyn last month, Naomi Klein said: “We don’t need or want the false idol of Zionism. We want freedom from the project that commits genocide in our name.” More
The post The Dead End of Liberal American Zionism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abba Solomon - Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empire Stumbling Toward Irrelevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323274</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/empire-stumbling-toward-irrelevance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To a working family “camping” on the street or a homeless single mother, this is what political collapse feels like.  The UK is #1 in homelessness, the USA “leads” the developed world in percentage of its population living on the street.  Meanwhile, endless billions are borrowed and sent abroad to senselessly genocide millions.  These sure signs of Imperialist decline can’t be ignored forever.    More
The post Empire Stumbling Toward Irrelevance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Noon at LA’s City Council]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323374</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/high-noon-at-las-city-council/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the classic 1952 Western High Noon, Katy Jurado portrays Helen Ramirez, former lover of Will Kane (Gary Cooper), the outnumbered, embattled Marshal at Hadleyville, who is being menaced by a looming shootout with a gang of gunslingers. Ramirez confronts Will’s newlywed, Amy Fowler (Grace Kelly), telling the bride that she should pick up a  More
The post High Noon at LA’s City Council appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Race to End Fossil Fuel Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323175</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-race-to-end-fossil-fuel-production/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given all this Green rhetoric and crude (oil) action, it’s hard to find examples around the world where people are actually doing something to end fossil fuel production. One of those places is Ecuador, which held a referendum last August about keeping oil under the ground of a certain plot of land in the Yasuní national park. “Yasuní is the most important park in Ecuador,” observes Esperanza Martínez, of Acción Ecológica in Ecuador. “It has been recognized as the most biodiverse region in the world, and it’s also home to many indigenous peoples.” More
The post The Race to End Fossil Fuel Production appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black MAGA Is Still MAGA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323381</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/black-maga-is-still-maga/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider Donald Trump to be in a racial bind when it comes to election 2024. After all, he needs Black voters to at least defect from Joe Biden in swing states, if not actually vote for him. Yet, more than ever, he also needs his white nationalist base to believe that a second Trump term  More
The post Black MAGA Is Still MAGA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clarence Lusane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power, or the Purpose of the Police]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323408</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/power-or-the-purpose-of-the-police/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What can we gain from a better understanding of the police as an American institution? A new documentary digs deep into the history, philosophy, and legality of US policing, tying historical injustices to the contemporary use and abuse of state violence. Following much praise for Power at Sundance and CPH:DOX earlier this year, Oscar-nominated director Yance Ford (Strong Island) brings his  More
The post Power, or the Purpose of the Police appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francis Brodsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Solidarity Triumphs Over Corporate Greed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323409</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/how-solidarity-triumphs-over-corporate-greed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Management at Amfuel tried to bully Jo Tucker and her 200 co-workers—most of them Black women, a number of them single moms—into accepting dozens of unnecessary concessions in a new contract. For four years, however, the manufacturing workers in Magnolia, Arkansas remained strong and resolute as the company tried to break the union and wear them  More
The post How Solidarity Triumphs Over Corporate Greed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Business of Obesity and Shame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323412</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-big-business-of-obesity-and-shame/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturers of new weight loss drugs are salivating at the prospect of profit. What Americans eat, how they diet and exercise, the sugar content of their sodas, and the high fructose corn syrup in their processed foods have long been objects of endless gambling on Wall Street. Now, with drugs like Mounjaro, Wegovy, and Ozempic,  More
The post The Big Business of Obesity and Shame appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ocodo in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40423772</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40423772"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T03:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altman has proven time and again that he is little more than a huckster wrt technology, and in business he is a stone cold shark.
Conman plain and simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ocodo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by windexh8er in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40423483</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40423483"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:43:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing about the situation is that Altman is willing to lie and steal a celebrity's voice for use in ChatGPT.  What he did, the timeline, everything - is sleazy if, in fact, that's the story.
The really concerning part here is that Altman is, and wants to be, a large part of AI regulation [0].  Quite the public contradiction.
[0] https://www.businessinsider.com/sam-altman-openai-artificial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>windexh8er</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by npunt in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421850</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421850"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T23:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people cheat on (relatively) small things, it's usually an indication they'll cheat on big things too]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>npunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nickthegreek in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421712</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421712"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T23:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This statement from scarlet really changed my perspective. I use and loved the Sky voice and I did feel it sounded a little like her, but moreover it was the best of their voice offerings. I was mad when they removed it. But now I’m mad it was ever there to begin with. This timeline makes it clear that this wasn’t a coincidence and maybe not even a hiring of an impressionist (which is where things get a little more wishy washy for me).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nickthegreek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by anon373839 in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421564</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421564"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, that statement lays out a damning timeline:
- OpenAI approached Scarlett last fall, and she refused.
- Two days before the GPT-4o launch, they contacted her agent and asked that she reconsider. (Two days! This means they already had everything they needed to ship  the product with Scarlett’s  cloned voice.)
- Not receiving a response, OpenAI demos the product anyway, with Sam tweeting “her” in reference to Scarlett’s film.
- When Scarlett’s counsel asked for an explanation of how the “Sky” voice was created, OpenAI yanked the voice from their product line.
Perhaps Sam’s next tweet should read “red-handed”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anon373839</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aaronharnly in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421334</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421334"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, this confirms that OpenAI have been shooting from the hip, not that we needed much confirmation. The fact that they repeatedly tried to hire Johansson, then went ahead and made a soundalike while explicitly describing that they were trying to make it be like her voice in the movie … is pretty bad for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aaronharnly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Kharkow - The Advice Led to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ilya Kharkow
Title: The Advice Led to Hell
Date: May 16, 2024
Source: https://actionweek.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/16/rady-vedou-do-pekla-ilya-kharkow/#more-1104

 I wrote about how difficult it was to get from Kyiv to Lviv on the first day of a full-scale war in the novel THE MINING BOYS. But when I finally got there, it only got worse. 
 The people who sheltered me sincerely did not understand why I did not want to defend the country with weapons in my hands. My hope to go to Europe seemed like a betrayal to them. At the same time, I had to hide from them not only my fear, but also my culture and my orientation. 
 These same people advised me to voluntarily join the territorial defense. Their acquaintances, who also didn’t want to fight, deliberately signed up there so they wouldn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The health benefits of giving up drinking coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/health-benefits-giving-up-drinking-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with many things we consume, the science on coffee can be conflicted. One decade caffeine consumption is a no-no, the next it seems coffee is quite beneficial. Regular readers will know I’m a coffee drinker, but in — what I consider to be — moderation: two (large serve) cups per day. But some people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "ICC prosecutor seeks arrest warrants against Sinwar and Netanyahu for war crimes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418956</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418956"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: if you're going to comment in this thread, please review the site guidelines (https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html). Make sure that your comment is following them, and that you are posting in the intended spirit: intellectually curious, respectful conversation.
"Respectful" here means respectful to the people who are wrong (in your view) and most respectful to the people who are most wrong (in your view). If you can't do that, that's ok, but please don't post until you can. Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive - https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html.
Hellish flamewars in deep subthreads are not ok. I'm going to lower the bar for banning accounts that do this, so please don't do this. If you're hotly indignant, step away from the keyboard until that changes. Nobody 'wins' on the internet anyway, and it's not worth destroying this community for. Not to mention your heart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by isoprophlex in "Introducing Copilot+ PCs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418816</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418816"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Their "copilot" brand is so weird and... muddled.
There's the AI code assistant thing that github actually started, there's the horrible chatbot maker GUI demoware, there's AI stuff you might be able to do with your sharepoint (if only you could get hold of the right ms sales rep to take your money), there's an app that does genai things on your personal MS account... And now there's a Surface rebrand?
That org chart meme about Microsoft being little fiefdoms pointing guns at eachother never stops being relevant.
[1] https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-copilot/microsoft-...
[2] https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2023/05/0...
[3] https://copilot.microsoft.com/
And [4] the meme itself, as you really can't convince me the above is the result of a coherent company-wide strategy https://i.insider.com/51dfec8469bedd5e19000017]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>isoprophlex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I'm blogging again]]></title>
        <id>https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/</id>
        <link href="https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:55:38.443Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the glory days of the internet, when social media was just becoming mainstream, I used to blog regularly. I would write and publish a post anywhere from 1 - 3 times a week.
I didn't monetize my blog and I had no dreams of my personal site becoming a business. It was simply a place for me to share things that were on my mind and lessons learned from books I was reading.
Fast forward many years and what we have is the current state of the internet.
Everything is an ad. Everyone is an influencer. And the algorithms determine what we see and dictate what we post. And for some reason they insist on the entire population becoming video producers.
It's an endless game that I lost my taste for long ago.
That's why I'm attempting to blog again. I need somewhere to get my thoughts and opinions out without distraction and without too much tech.
If the internet stresses you out as much as it does me, might I suggest starting your own blog?
Or heck, maybe just quit the social internet altogether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;A Reprieve for Assange&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism as ‘espionage’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Application Load Balancer IPv6, Amazon S3 pricing update, Amazon EC2 Flex instances, and more (May 20, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3ec4a6e752f974d277f95d9da7228e9f5bba4ba4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-application-load-balancer-ipv6-amazon-s3-pricing-update-amazon-ec2-flex-instances-and-more-may-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is in full swing around the world, with last week’s events in Bengaluru, Berlin, and  Seoul, where my blog colleague Channy delivered one of the keynotes. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon S3 will no longer charge for several HTTP error codes – A customer reported […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O povo pelo povo e o RS acaba em menos de seis meses]]></title>
        <id>https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/o-povo-pelo-povo-e-o-rs-acaba-em-menos-de-seis-meses/</id>
        <link href="https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/o-povo-pelo-povo-e-o-rs-acaba-em-menos-de-seis-meses/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:31:41.361Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A direita, os anarcocapitalistas (embora este termo seja discutível) e a extrema-direita brasileira, diante do crime ambiental praticado no Rio Grande do Sul, conseguiram emplacar uma bela história: o povo pelo povo.
É muito importante salientar como o povo brasileiro se uniu para ajudar o povo do Rio Grande do Sul. É reconfortante observar que o próprio povo, especialmente os mais pobres, uniu-se no próprio RS para ajudar os outros. Voluntários que não têm muito em casa saem às 5h para atender 12h em um abrigo onde as pessoas perderam tudo. Isso é significativo, especialmente após o período de 2018 a 2023, em que o Brasil parecia uma poça de sangue (e ainda parece, em certa medida), pois mostra que o povo ainda é solidário, mesmo que precise de uma tragédia para uni-los.
O problema é que …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruptions Have Eased, But Remain a Concern]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30028</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/supply-chain-disruptions-have-eased-but-remain-a-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain disruptions became a major headache for businesses in the aftermath of the pandemic. Indeed, in October 2021, nearly all firms in our regional business surveys reported at least some difficulty obtaining the supplies they needed. These supply chain disruptions were a key contributor to the surge in inflation that occurred as the economy recovered from the pandemic recession. In this post, we present new measures of supply availability from our Business Leaders Survey and Empire State Manufacturing Survey that closely track the New York Fed’s Global Supply Chain Pressure Index (GSCPI). We will begin publishing these data on a monthly basis starting in June. These indexes indicate that supply availability had generally been improving since early 2023, but over the past couple of months, improvement has stalled. This trend is concerning since our May Supplemental Survey indicates that between a third and a half of businesses in the region are experiencing difficulties obtaining supplies, and many are reducing operations and raising prices to compensate, though to a lesser extent than a few years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel and Richard Deitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Godfrey Wood: &ldquo;Battle Machine&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrospectives on Podemos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSGE models — a total waste of time]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45375</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/20/dsge-models-a-total-waste-of-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll While one can understand that some of the elements in DSGE models seem to appeal to Keynesians at first sight, after closer examination, these models are in fundamental contradiction to Post-Keynesian and even traditional Keynesian thinking. The DSGE model is a model in which output is determined in the labour market as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchy In Action - Anarchy in the Haitian Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchy-in-action-anarchy-in-the-haitian-revolution?v=1716166084</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchy-in-action-anarchy-in-the-haitian-revolution?v=1716166084"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchy In Action
Title: Anarchy in the Haitian Revolution
Source: Retrieved on 19 May 2024 from anarchyinaction.org/index.php?title=Anarchy_in_the_Haitian_Revolution

 Following many years of hidden and small-scale resistance, African slaves in the French colony of Saint Domingue (or San Domingo) rose up in 1791 against their colonizers and slave masters. By 1804, they abolished slavery, expelled the French colonizers, and established the independent republic of Haiti. Haiti was the name given to the Caribbean island by the Tainos before colonizers arrived, slaughtered the entire indigenous population, and imported African slaves. 
 While the 1776 and 1789 revolutions of the USA and France were grounded in exclusionary “citizens’ rights,” the Haitian Revolution stood out for a com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Completing the largest migration in Kubernetes history]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since as early as Kubernetes v1.7, the Kubernetes project has pursued the ambitious goal of removing built-in cloud provider integrations (KEP-2395).
While these integrations were instrumental in Kubernetes' early development and growth, their removal was driven by two key factors:
the growing complexity of maintaining native support for every cloud provider across millions of lines of Go code, and the desire to establish
Kubernetes as a truly vendor-neutral platform.
After many releases, we're thrilled to announce that all cloud provider integrations have been successfully migrated from the core Kubernetes repository to external plugins.
In addition to achieving our initial objectives, we've also significantly streamlined Kubernetes by removing roughly 1.5 million lines of code and reduci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What has happened to cover versions of popular songs?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7624</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-happened-cover-versions-popular-songs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, Australian radio station Triple J, invites a band or musician to record a cover of a song, for their Like A Version show. Anything goes here. About two years ago, Sydney based Australian DJ Dave Winnel performed a cover of Africa, by Toto, not the sort of music you’d usually hear on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World, I guess?]]></title>
        <id>https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/</id>
        <link href="https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:28:15.910Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay... exhales
Here we go.
Hi, I'm Meï ! And welcome to this blog. Or this attempt at a blog.
It's been a few weeks since I felt a lot of nostalgia for the Internet of old, the one I discovered as a lil' kid, on my tenth birthday, circa 2007.
A friend, Seeker, began working on his own blog a few months back. I really liked his articles about DIY and Game Dev, and on a whim asked him his tech stack with the intent of setting something up for myself.
I used to write quite a bit a few years ago. Especially when I got to the big city after high school. Welcome to Fucktopia1 was a small series detailing my new life far from the countryside.
As of late, I've been trying to get back into writing. Essays to recommend some games, some small fictions, and lore for TTRPGs, I've been slowly but surely getting back into it. But I didn't really manage to find a public, even for the essays in places (well, Discord servers in this case) dedicated to the exact IP I was trying to promote.
This built up as a bit of frustration, and is another of the reasons I felt like doing a blog. I wanted to be more open to the world, able to write in a place anyone could read if they stumble on the place.
So once again, here we go!
1. As a note, the "Fucktopia" is a reference to Souillon's comic book "Hello Fucktopia". Couldn't find a listing in English, sorry! It's available in French & Spanish, at least..
My small rules of writing
Try to write regularly. Not necessarily everyday, but I should strive for a post per week at least.
Focus! I'm super prone to tangents and often stray off-topic. A post should be on a single subject, unless this is a post consciously made for tangents and chaos.
No stressing over this. I already stress over too much, let's keep this place as my comfy Internet place.
Let's hope it goes well. And I hope you'll enjoy this blog and its topics.
Fan-art of Cyberpunk Bartender Action: VA-11 HALL-A, by rnna_7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Pézenas]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52709</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/19/sunday-photoblogging-pezenas-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T07:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Generalist]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bear in a circus is interesting. So is a juggler and a man on the unicycle. A bear on a unicycle juggling swords on the other hand is something extremely unique. Something you would pay good money to see. A smart generalist is kinda like that.
A smart generalist is a person who is 80/20 across multiple fields. This means they have reached 80 Percent understanding/capability across multiple fields leveraging around 20 percent of the effort that would typically be needed to fully master it. It makes them unique.
The primary skill of a smart generalist is the ability to get from 0 to 80 in a new field quickly. They can quickly identify high ROI leverage points of a subject. It is a learned skill. They also have strong convictions that anything can be learned and learned fast. Even things considered 'tough' by society.
On the other hand, we have the cracked specialists. People really good at one thing. Getting to the frontiers and advancing human knowledge. Creating absolutely beautiful works in that 'one thing'.
It is a sliding scale. We all lie somewhere between a specialist and a generalist. But we could all do some good to realise we are not limited. We can do multiple things if we want to. It is easy to be hemmed in. To define your identity as 'Software Engineer' or 'Writer' or 'XYZ'. That is what school teaches -'Specialisation'. But humans are versatile. We are the OG general intelligence. Capable of adapting and doing multiple things.
Don't forget the 'General' in General Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To my Sunflower]]></title>
        <id>https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/</id>
        <link href="https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:26:07.405Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little bird came to see me,
What’s you name? - I asked.
And he chirped the following words:
Leave a comment or Stay in touch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[don't skip the openings]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:35:12.065Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the absolute worst thing someone can tell me about their anime viewing preferences has nothing to do with the kind of show they watch but how they watch it.
image from director nakayama ryū's chainsaw man (2022).
skipping openings just because you're on a binge can so easily rob you of what i'd argue are the best narrative and collective highs a series can offer.[^1]
from a purely functional standpoint, they give us time to breathe and process what exactly we're watching. take, for example, the three versions of shippuden's penultimate opening— blood circulator. each variant denotes which point of the story you're at, and primes you for what's to come. (if you pay attention, you'll notice they lead into each other seamlessly! so neat.)
sometimes it's instinctual and more about building ant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>