<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-01-08T12:50:08.790Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-01-08T12:50:08.790Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/8/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285054</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-8-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T11:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our dastardly daily links: Varoufakis for Star Trek, cold snaps, LA inferno, China wobbles? EU v. Trump, Israel truce violations, Western media calls for more Ukraine deaths, Exxon sues critics, Cybertruck bomber's ChatGPT advice, jobs debate, Greenwald v. AOC, DoJ sue rental price-fixers,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is a US-Türkiye Deal Involving the Kurds in the Works?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285164</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/is-a-us-turkiye-deal-involving-the-kurds-in-the-works.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T11:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Erdogan’s hand weakens and the US-Israel look towards Iran, signs point to Türkiye backing down.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe Races to Refill as Gas Reserves Dwindle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285179</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/europe-races-to-refill-as-gas-reserves-dwindle.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T10:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at another act of European self-destruction in the name of harming Russia, here on the gas supply front.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haitian Exodus from Springfield, Ohio Might Be a Sign of Things to Come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349327</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/haitian-exodus-from-springfield-ohio-might-be-a-sign-of-things-to-come/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T07:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Telegraph recently reported that ahead of President-Elect Donald Trump’s inauguration later this month, thousands of Haitian immigrants have already left or are planning to leave Springfield, Ohio. The Haitian community has been living in fear for months, and their flight could reverse some of the economic and social gains that the rust belt town has won by virtue of its immigrant community’s hard work and cultural contributions. What is happening in Springfield could be a harbinger in similar places once Trump occupies the Oval Office. More
The post Haitian Exodus from Springfield, Ohio Might Be a Sign of Things to Come appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Slager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaire Round-Up, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349313</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/349313/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the close of 2024 there were 813 billionaires in the United States with a combined total wealth of $6.72 trillion, according to an analysis of the Forbes wealth data. The total number of billionaires has remained constant since the outlet published its 38th annual World’s Billionaire List on April 2, 2024. But the combined  More
The post Billionaire Round-Up, 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chuck Collins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genocidal President, Genocidal Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349529</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/genocidal-president-genocidal-politics/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When news broke over the weekend that President Biden just approved an $8 billion deal for shipping weapons to Israel, a nameless official vowed that “we will continue to provide the capabilities necessary for Israel’s defense.” Following the reports last month from Amnesty International and Human Rights Watch concluding that Israeli actions in Gaza are genocide, Biden’s decision was a new low for  More
The post Genocidal President, Genocidal Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Army; Travel to Exotic, Distant Lands; and Radicalize]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349531</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/join-the-army-travel-to-exotic-distant-lands-and-radicalize/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been popular to see political and religious radicalisation as something oddly separable from institutions of state. State institutions are meant to cope and cure the condition, not foster it.  Like some errant form, it takes place because of popular trends, messages floating in the detritus of the internet and the disrupting buzz and slurry of  More
The post Join the Army; Travel to Exotic, Distant Lands; and Radicalize appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from Iraq, Libya, and Syria: Resistance, Betrayal, and Collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349487</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/lessons-from-iraq-libya-and-syria-resistance-betrayal-and-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tumultuous collapses of Iraq, Libya and Syria offer stark parallels and contrasts, shedding light on the complex interplay of foreign intervention, internal strife and the fragile dynamics of power in the Middle East. At the heart of anti-colonialism lie two principles which, at first glance, seem to stand in direct opposition. The first calls  More
The post Lessons from Iraq, Libya, and Syria: Resistance, Betrayal, and Collapse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sukant Chandan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haiti and American Neocolonialism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349538</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/haiti-and-american-neocolonialism/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Haiti is best understood in the contexts of the modern world as an American neocolonial protectorate. Besides US policy in Cuba, which includes a genocidal blockade depriving the Cuban people of precious resources needed to function society, it’s hard to find another case of such an ongoing and sustained assault from the largest empire in  More
The post Haiti and American Neocolonialism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Inskeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans’ Rage at Insurers Goes Beyond Health Coverage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349433</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/americans-rage-at-insurers-goes-beyond-health-coverage/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My book “Delay, Deny, Defend: Why Insurance Companies Don’t Pay Claims and What You Can Do About It” was thrust into the spotlight recently, after UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson was shot and killed in what authorities say was a targeted attack outside the company’s annual investors conference. Investigators at the scene found bullet casings inscribed  More
The post Americans’ Rage at Insurers Goes Beyond Health Coverage appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Feinman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Negative Spaces of the Trump Era]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349477</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/in-the-negative-spaces-of-the-trump-era/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expression “punch-drunk,” Google informs me, means “stupefied by or as if by a series of heavy blows to the head.” Google’s Oxford Language entry then offers a not-terribly-illuminating example of the term’s use: “I feel a little punch-drunk today.” Right now, a better one might be something like: “After November 5, 2024, a lot of people have been feeling  More
The post In the Negative Spaces of the Trump Era appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revising NYT History on Democrats Losing the Working Class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349314</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/revising-nyt-history-on-democrats-losing-the-working-class/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times had a lengthy piece giving a story on how the Democrats lost the support of working-class voters over the last three decades. The essence of the argument is that working-class voters were angered by Democrats’ support of “free trade” and the bailouts of the financial industry in the financial crisis. While  More
The post Revising NYT History on Democrats Losing the Working Class appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invest in Immigrants, Don’t Deport Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349549</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/08/invest-in-immigrants-dont-deport-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Immigrants across America are quaking in their boots as they fear being arrested by federal agents and deported from the country – all because they sought refuge from a bad life in search of a better future. Donald Trump blames President Biden for encouraging mass migration, and he is pledging to close the border and  More
The post Invest in Immigrants, Don’t Deport Them appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chloe Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy and Debt: Has the Link been Broken?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Democracy-and-Debt-Has-the-Link</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Democracy-and-Debt-Has-the-Link"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
Histoire Jubi EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Democrat?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285145</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/what-is-a-democrat.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T05:39:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where does a Democrat fit in the political food chain?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new AWS Asia Pacific (Thailand) Region]]></title>
        <id>3acab191e810ab04e856c629a911bcd01c319944</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-new-aws-asia-pacific-thailand-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T02:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS launches Asia Pacific (Thailand) Region with 3 Availability Zones, accelerating cloud adoption. Strategically located to meet data residency needs, it drives innovation across industries. Early AWS adopters in Thailand share transformative success stories. Get started now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Accessibility Testing at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17358</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/automated-accessibility-testing-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T20:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, customer love is our first priority and accessibility is a core tenet of customer trust. We have our own Slack Accessibility Standards that product teams follow to guarantee their features are compliant with Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG). Our dedicated accessibility team supports developers in following these guidelines throughout the development process. We…
The post Automated Accessibility Testing at Slack appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nstormann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer time forming La Nina possibly coming to Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9060</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/summer-time-forming-la-nina-possible/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T20:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Saunders writing for ABC News: Your average La Niña forms in winter, peaks in late spring, then gradually weakens through summer. However, the current edition has not played by the rule book — for only the second time in 75 years, its onset has arrived in the middle of summer. This is something I’ve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 1/7/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285147</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/200pm-water-cooler-1-7-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Trump to change "Gulf of Mexico" to "Gulf of America"; "FBI Is Still Hiding Details of Russiagate": Aaron Maté; HPMV in China ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by davidw in "Ending our third party fact-checking program and moving to Community Notes model"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42625676</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42625676"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T18:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ideological bits are:
* Dana White added to the board.
* "Move our trust and safety and content moderation teams out of California, and our US content review to Texas. This will help remove the concern that biased employees are overly censoring content." - like people being in Texas makes them more objective?!
The actual mechanisms of running a social media network at scale are tricky and I think most of us would be fine with some experimentation. But it looks pretty political in the broader context, so maybe it's just a way of saying that certain kinds of 'content' like attacking trans people is going to be ok now.
I can't quite FB entirely, but Threads looks like a much less interesting option with Blue Sky being available and gaining in popularity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davidw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "Ending our third party fact-checking program and moving to Community Notes model"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42625568</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42625568"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T18:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to hear an informed take from anybody who thinks that Facebook's fact-checkers were a better product feature than Community Notes.
All of the articles I'm seeing about this online are ideological, but this feels like the kind of decision that should have been in the works for multiple quarters now, given how effective Notes have been, and how comically ineffective and off-putting fact-checkers have been. The user experience of fact-checkers (forget about people pushing bogus facts, I just mean for ordinary people who primarily consume content rather than producing it) is roughly that of a PSA ad spot series saying "this platform is full of junk, be on your guard".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Abishek_Muthian in "Nvidia's Project Digits is a 'personal AI supercomputer'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42623030</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42623030"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T14:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm looking at my Jetson Nano in the corner which is fulfilling its post-retirement role as a paper weight because Nvidia abandoned it in 4 years.
Nvidia Jetson Nano, A SBC for "AI" debuted with already aging custom Ubuntu 18.04 and when 18.04 went EOL, Nvidia abandoned it completely without any further updates to its proprietary  jet-pack or drivers and without them all of Machine Learning stack like CUDA, Pytorch etc. became useless.
I'll never buy a SBC from Nvidia unless all the SW support is up-streamed  to Linux kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abishek_Muthian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Has Happened to Our Grand Experiment, the Internet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285141</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/what-has-happened-to-our-grand-experiment-the-internet.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T14:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AI threatening to crapify online life and even generate geopolitical chaos, Congress needs to reinstate the Office of Technology Policy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/7/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285025</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-7-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our anti-fragile daily links: Oat milk hazards? China new virus assessment, Biden drillling ban, Trudeau quits, France looting of Africa, EU leaders + Starmer v. Musk, Finkelstein on Gaza defeat, China currency wars? Trump v. hush money sentencing, private credit worries, Tesla revenues fall]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYT Readies Terrain for Incoming Trump Administration’s Long-Telegraphed Intervention in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285080</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/nyt-lays-groundwork-for-trump-administrations-long-telegraphed-intervention-in-mexico.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media's role in selling the next military adventure should never be underestimated, even in this media-skeptic age.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental and climate debt: Who is responsible?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Environmental-and-climate-debt-Who-is-responsible</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Environmental-and-climate-debt-Who-is-responsible"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T11:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concepts of climate debt and ecological debt are central to successfully achieving the ecological bifurcation. The ecological debt owed by States – and in particular the wealthiest States and major corporations – of the North to the populations of the Global South must be recognized. That recognition must take the form of cancellation of the debt of the countries of the Global South and paying of reparations by the States of the North. The latter must compel the wealthiest interests to (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Natural Resources, 
Ecology/Climate, 
EN Dette écologique et climatique : Qui est responsable ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE: Nations Aren’t Corporations and ‘Efficiency’ Means Austerity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/doge-nations-arent-corporations-and-efficiency-means-austerity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T10:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why DOGE, if implemented on the scale intended, will be a train wreck for the great majority of Americans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Health Insurers Limit Coverage of Prosthetic Limbs, Questioning Their Medical Necessity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285111</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/health-insurers-limit-coverage-of-prosthetic-limbs-questioning-their-medical-necessity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T10:17:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another type of example of how health insurers screw patients.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banana Road From South America to China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349206</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-banana-road-from-south-america-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T07:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November, Álvaro Noboa, the father of Ecuador’s president Daniel Noboa, had a heart attack. He was hastily taken to a clinic in Guayaquil, his hometown, and then after he was stabilized, flown to a hospital in New York. Álvaro Noboa unsuccessfully ran for president five times (1998, 2002, 2006, 2009, and 2013), but it  More
The post The Banana Road From South America to China appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A War Against Meaning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349228</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/a-war-against-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our ability to make and tell stories is what makes us human. That’s also how we deal with suffering and pain and loss. But stories have an arc; there is a return from the abyss. Terrible, tragic things happen, even things which we might never heal from, but people change and adapt and weave the terrible into the story of their life. People die, but their influence lives on, their memory is celebrated and valued by those who knew and loved them. People suffer but they learn something and grow from their experiences, somehow, however awful they are. ‘Your gift will come from your wound,’ as the storytellers say.  More
The post A War Against Meaning appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Glazebrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unbearably Short Life of an Anti-War Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349387</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-unbearably-short-life-of-an-anti-war-movement/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The thing that is to be supported, and the force that is to support it should stand in geometrical proportion to each other” cardinal Richelieu, cited by Henry Kissinger “Nothing is thoroughly real, therefore everything is permitted” – Hassan I. Sabbah, Persian leader of the assassins, in Vladimir Bartol’s novel Alamut. Even if it had  More
The post The Unbearably Short Life of an Anti-War Movement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arturo Desimone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiation Smokescreen: How the U.S. and Antisemites Became Key Enablers of Israeli Genocide in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349389</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/negotiation-smokescreen-how-the-u-s-and-antisemites-became-key-enablers-of-israeli-genocide-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The devastation in Gaza continues to escalate, with ceasefire negotiations used as part of a calculated strategy and a smokescreen until Israel completes its ethnic cleansing of northern Gaza. Crucial to the success of this plan is the unwavering complicity of the Biden administration, which has embraced and amplified Israeli narratives, shielded it from accountability,  More
The post Negotiation Smokescreen: How the U.S. and Antisemites Became Key Enablers of Israeli Genocide in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Unknown or No Direction Home: The Enigma of Bob Dylan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349372</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/a-complete-unknown-or-no-direction-home-the-enigma-of-bob-dylan/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bob Dylan is back in the news again. A countercultural hero to people who grew up some five decades ago, yet also, perhaps not surprisingly, given his paradoxical character, someone who hated the role into which he had been cast and someone who has been incorporated in the literary establishment by virtue of his Nobel  More
The post A Complete Unknown or No Direction Home: The Enigma of Bob Dylan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John S. Auerbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Military to Prison Pipeline: Trading One Uniform for Another]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349221</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/the-military-to-prison-pipeline-trading-one-uniform-for-another/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like old soldiers around the country, a group of former service members gathered in Crest Hill, Illinois to remember fallen comrades on Memorial Day, 2024. Several months later, The Veteran, a newspaper published by Vietnam Veterans Against the War, ran a photo of the event they attended. It shows a multi-generational group of men–white, Black  More
The post The Military to Prison Pipeline: Trading One Uniform for Another appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Early - Suzanne Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the World Hides Liability for Climate Deaths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349368</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/how-the-world-hides-liability-for-climate-deaths/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly half the world’s children “live in countries where risks to their health and safety due to the effects of climate change are extremely high,” according to UNICEF. By 2050, almost all children globally will be “exposed to heat waves,” resulting in the rise of specific health issues, especially for smaller children, adds the agency. Rich nations’ inability  More
The post How the World Hides Liability for Climate Deaths appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Berke, Carter Dillard, Beatrix Homler and Rei Stone-Grover</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Would Surprise America’s Rich in 2025? Not Getting Richer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349259</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/what-would-surprise-americas-rich-in-2025-not-getting-richer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new year has begun with old news: The world is continuing to become colossally more unequal — with the United States leading the way. In 2024, wealth trackers at Bloomberg have just reported in a year-end review, “the world’s 500 richest people got vastly richer.” Of the world’s 15 richest individuals, the Bloomberg data  More
The post What Would Surprise America’s Rich in 2025? Not Getting Richer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Jimmy Carter Pardoned Draft Resisters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349392</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/why-jimmy-carter-pardoned-draft-resisters/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T06:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The passing of Jimmy Carter has been duly noted in ubiquitous remembrances and commentaries on his four-year presidency, 1977-1981. Carter is lauded more for his post-presidential humanitarian projects, while his presidency is deemed a mixed bag by left and right alike. For many Vietnam War resisters – myself included, it is more personal. Jimmy Carter’s  More
The post Why Jimmy Carter Pardoned Draft Resisters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerry Condon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tlaloc’s Cornstalks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349418</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/07/tlalocs-cornstalks/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T05:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee, the all-wise priest The all-wise priest, Lee All eyes on the all-wise Presley El-vise Presley Annually concocts for us Coquito, little coconut Coquito, not Cocijo Which is lightning, yes In Zapotec — Who As Lightning gods will do Created this world From his breath And lightning bolt tongue Infusing the realms His lightning/electricity Beating  More
The post Tlaloc’s Cornstalks appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Sperber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dewitt in "How I program with LLMs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42619022</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42619022"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T03:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One interesting bit of context is that the author of this post is a legit world-class software engineer already (though probably too modest to admit it). Former staff engineer at Google and co-founder / CTO of Tailscale. He doesn't need LLMs. That he says LLMs make him more productive at all as a hands-on developer, especially around first drafts on a new idea, means a lot to me personally.
His post reminds me of an old idea I had of a language where all you wrote was function signatures and high-level control flow, and maybe some conformance tests around them. The language was designed around filling in the implementations for you. 20 years ago that would have been from a live online database, with implementations vying for popularity on the basis of speed or correctness. Nowadays LLMs would generate most of it on the fly, presumably.
Most ideas are unoriginal, so I wouldn't be surprised if this has been tried already.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dewitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Title Launch Observability at Netflix Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/19ea916be1ed</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/title-launch-observability-at-netflix-scale-19ea916be1ed?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T01:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: Navigating Ambiguity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3: A Survey of Analytics Engineering Work at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e67f0aa82183</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/part-3-a-survey-of-analytics-engineering-work-at-netflix-e67f0aa82183?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the last in a multi-part series sharing a breadth of Analytics Engineering work at Netflix, recently presented as part of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eigenvalue in "Stimulation Clicker"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614385</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614385"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, that was amazing. This is honestly a better piece of contemporary art (in terms of making you think about modern life and what is happening to our environment, the impact on ourselves, our kids, etc.) than most of what you might see at a fancy art gallery or a contemporary art museum in NYC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eigenvalue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zdc1 in "Stimulation Clicker"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42614326"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T19:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finished the game without cheating. I felt like a frog being slowly boiled (and it really does feel like you're boiling at the end). It's quite the journey...
I love how everything here isn't even farfetched. It's just standard YouTube and TikTok content. The red notification bubbles were also a nice touch, I felt myself really drawn to those, and if I think back, I guess that's the earliest example I can recall of where these patterns all started: Facebook's little red notification bubble]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zdc1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forecast 2025: roaring or tepid?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Forecast-2025-roaring-or-tepid</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Forecast-2025-roaring-or-tepid"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to make some forecasts on what will happen to the world economy and its major countries in 2025. Many people reckon that it is waste of time making such forecasts as they are never accurate and quite often the opposite happens. Of course, forecasts are wrapped in error, given the many variables involved that drive economies. Weather forecasts are still difficult to make and meteorologists are dealing with physical events and not (at least directly) with human actions. Nevertheless, (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Debt crisis, 
Recession]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup: 2025 Tech Predictions, Llama 3.3 70B, Stable Diffusion 3.5 Large, custom billing view, and more (January 6, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>4fa89b3af496404ca2ee8f7c6b9813035cee90e6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/happy-new-year-aws-weekly-roundup-2025-tech-predictions-llama-3-3-70b-stable-diffusion-3-5-large-custom-billing-view-and-more-january-6-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy New Year! We are witnessing technology augment human ingenuity in inspiring ways. In the coming years, using technology for positive impact will redefine the way we think about success. Amazon CTO, Dr. Werner Vogels, offers five forward-looking tech predictions for 2025, and beyond: The workforce of tomorrow is mission-driven A new era of energy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize your container workloads for sustainability]]></title>
        <id>7d5701991d02108aba8dd83e32c2ee4765f604d5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/optimize-your-container-workloads-for-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T18:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog was authored by Karthik Rajendran, Senior Solutions Architect (AWS) and Isha Dua, Senior Solutions Architect (AWS).  The software architect’s job is mostly one of trade-offs, weighing the considerations of different approaches and then choosing the one that strikes the best balance. Some architects are surprised to find that, in the AWS Cloud at least, architecting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hamandcheese in "3blue1brown YouTube Bitcoin video taken down as copyright violation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612966</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612966"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T17:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems like a huge abuse of the copyright system to me. It sounds to me like ChainPatrol doesn't actually have any IP to protect, but they are instead deputizing YouTube's copyright system to fight what they deem to be crypto scams. Absolutely wild if true.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hamandcheese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wil421 in "3blue1brown YouTube Bitcoin video taken down as copyright violation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612650</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612650"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T17:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is 2030. After the AI bot wars, FaceBook and Google have been crippled. They let AI automation control their content and it was deleted after OpenAI GPT10 discovered vulnerabilities in automated copyright strikes.
Taco Bell won the franchise war and is the only restaurant remaining.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wil421</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by catgary in "Justin Trudeau promises to resign as PM"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612168</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42612168"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T16:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it’s worth noting that the weekend before this, local residents of Ottawa had basically “stormed” one of the trucker convoy camps to unblock a road. There were genuine concerns that the residents of Ottawa were ready to take matters into their own hands, and it would be a bloodbath. Not to mention the blockade in Alberta where they were found with guns and a pipe bomb, with their communications indicating they were planning to murder the RCMP officers on site!
Declaring the Emergency acts was overwhelmingly popular in Canada and remains one of the most popular things Trudeau ever did. The moves to restrict access to banking affected less than 20 people (and I think they were generally funnelling money from international propaganda groups or committing similar financial crimes).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>catgary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by csense in "Justin Trudeau promises to resign as PM"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42611968</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42611968"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T16:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patio11 has some good coverage of Trudeau's handling of the trucker protest against the government's handling of COVID-19 [1].
Whatever you think of the truckers' position or protest tactics, any punishment for their actions ought to go through the laws and court system.  Trudeau instead essentially told the banking system "You can't do business with those people, they're terrorists."  Patio11's words of what happened next:
"The assistant deputy finance minister...said...'The intent was not to get at the families', and when a democratic government starts a sentence that way something deeply #*&$#ed up has happened."
I'm not on the pulse of Canadian politics, so I don't really know what sins or political circumstances have led Trudeau to this point, or if he has any redeeming qualities.  Personally, I'm glad to see him gone.
[1] https://www.bitsaboutmoney.com/archive/debanking-and-debunki...
(You'll have to Ctrl+F trucker as this blog doesn't seem to have  for headings, as is customary on e.g. Wikipedia.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csense</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by armada651 in "Apple squandered the Holy Grail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42610957</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42610957"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T14:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Word processors like MacWrite absolutely transformed the ways that everyone used computers.
MacWrite was released 5 years after WordPerfect, which itself is predated by WordStar. I don't get why Apple fans have this obsession with pretending Apple invents these things.
Apple refines what others have attempted before, that's what they're good at. Part of the reason people are disappointed with Apple these days is because of this fantasy image of Apple as an inventor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>armada651</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by padolsey in "Hitting OKRs vs. Doing Your Job"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42608823</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42608823"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T08:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now having worked in a few smaller teams since my time at FB, I realize how marvellous it is to not have to worry about OKRs, performance reviews and all that malarkey. It was so draining to run yourself as a mini PR/brand within one's team (/one's department) and market oneself (one's team) to your manager (/your company).
So much mental bandwidth was spent.
I also, from a systems-thinking POV, just fundamentally reject the value in OKRs as a meaningful proxy for the value you (/your team) are producing unless you are an entirely mechanistic function. By mechanistic I mean you have a clear discrete InputOutput expectation. Every single time an element of human activity is reduced to a metric, you lose something, and if you do it enough times, you've effectively produced a metric that is completely distinct from the thing you intended on measuring in the first place. For example: let's say you're in the suicide prevention team at FB, and your OKR is 'number of suicides averted'. Well, that sounds good, but unbeknownst to you, perverse incentives have kicked in and invisibly imbued your metric-chasing experiments a dark undertone. A new risk model might start flagging more content as potentially suicidal to boost numbers, leading to over-intervention that could traumatize users or waste resources. Or perhaps the surface we use to measure success, a UX or user activity metric, might actually be uncorrelated with crisis aversion or... and this is where it hits: the thing that's instrumental in crises is social media itself. The metric becomes a game, and it games _you_. Your team thinks you're doing X, but you're really doing Y. Because you're disattached from the real problem and comforted by incredibly lossy proxies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>padolsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Transition Travesty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/the-transition-travesty/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T07:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark the current scene.  A politically defunct, King Lear-like Joe Biden continues to make big and small policy decisions after his intended successor’s platform narrowly but clearly lost at the ballot box, even as President-elect Donald Trump conducts an incipient shadow presidency through a torrent of legal maneuvers, social media pronouncements and interviews, sounding more Caesarian by the day.  More
The post The Transition Travesty appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Medish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Will Mexico’s New President Deal With Trump, Migration and Drug Cartels?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349225</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/how-will-mexicos-new-president-deal-with-trump-migration-and-drug-cartels/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June 2024, Mexicans elected a female president, Claudia Sheinbaum to replace Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador. Arguably, Mexico is Washington’s most significant foreign policy partner, playing a central role in two issues that Donald Trump manipulated to win the 2024 presidential election: migration and drugs. More
The post How Will Mexico’s New President Deal With Trump, Migration and Drug Cartels? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Un]Happy New Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349272</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/unhappy-new-year/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honestly, as 2025 begins, isn’t it finally time to reimagine American history? So, what do you think of this: George Trump, Abraham Trump, Ulysses S. Trump, Franklin D. Trump, Dwight D. Trump, John F. Trump, Lyndon B. Trump, and even Richard M. and George W. Trump. And yes, of course, on January 20th, Donald J.  More
The post [Un]Happy New Year appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letters from Gaza – ‘Alhamdulillah. We Are Not Okay’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349278</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/letters-from-gaza-alhamdulillah-we-are-not-okay/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 14 months, I have received hundreds of messages from family members throughout the Gaza Strip. The nature of the messages often conveyed a sense of urgency and panic but, at times, contentment in God’s will. Some of those who wrote these notes have been killed in Israeli strikes, like my sister, Dr.  More
The post Letters from Gaza – ‘Alhamdulillah. We Are Not Okay’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans and Violence: Chicken or Egg?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349266</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/veterans-and-violence-chicken-or-egg/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I need to cleanse my mind of the brothers I’ve lost,”  Master Sergeant Matthew Alan Livelsberger (US Army) allegedly wrote in an explanatory note on his phone before shooting himself inside a Tesla Cybertruck packed with fireworks and gas tanks set to detonate outside a Las Vegas casino, “and relieve myself of the burden of  More
The post Veterans and Violence: Chicken or Egg? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gutting the Right to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349269</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/gutting-the-right-to-know/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I usually refrain from criticizing opinions issued by the Montana Supreme Court (the Court). I cannot stand silent, however in the face of the Court’s recent evisceration of Montana’s fundamental constitutional Right to Know, Article II, section 9. This provision guarantees that “No person shall be deprived of the right to examine documents or to  More
The post Gutting the Right to Know appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James C. Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frail Egos and Sandpit Colonialism: Australia, the United States and Invading Iraq]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349273</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/frail-egos-and-sandpit-colonialism-australia-the-united-states-and-invading-iraq/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former Australian Prime Minister John Howard is in the news again.  The release of Australian cabinet documents from 2004 – a supposed treat for historians of Australian history each new year – has been given a typically modest, calm and boringly anodyne treatment in media outlets. One topic featured should have caused continued sharp intakes of breath  More
The post Frail Egos and Sandpit Colonialism: Australia, the United States and Invading Iraq appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Must Keep Up Our Courage:  Ending Yoon Suk Yeol’s Legacy of Betrayal and Dismantlement of Korea’s Sovereignty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349322</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/we-must-keep-up-our-courage-ending-yoon-suk-yeols-legacy-of-betrayal-and-dismantlement-of-koreas-sovereignty/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than 44 hours Koreans have braved freezing snowstorms to demand the arrest of the elusive Yoon Suk Yeol, who has barricaded himself inside his official residence in defiance of constitutional and legal authority.  Yoon, extolled by Washington as a “champion of democracy,” has vanished from public view behind hastily erected barricades manned by  More
The post We Must Keep Up Our Courage:  Ending Yoon Suk Yeol’s Legacy of Betrayal and Dismantlement of Korea’s Sovereignty appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simone Chun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Center Has Collapsed: What Now?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349280</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/the-center-has-collapsed-what-now/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who brought down the center? We the left, of course! Hey, Hurray! We the virtuous. We showed those Dems. Kicked those hypocrites where it hurts. Three Hurray’s! Well … WE didn’t do any such thing. The Arab American voters in Michigan, Palestinian American voters all over, Muslim-Americans all over, all kinds of decent people with  More
The post The Center Has Collapsed: What Now? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>REZA FIYOUZAT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stock Market and Budget Projections: Do the Numbers Add Up?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349211</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/06/stock-market-and-budget-projections-do-the-numbers-add-up/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T06:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a while since we’ve had Mr. Arithmetic here, but with Donald Trump coming back to the White House, we may need him around. The immediate reason for consulting his expertise is the projections for big stock market gains in 2025. It seems the median forecast is for the S&P 500 to rise by  More
The post Stock Market and Budget Projections: Do the Numbers Add Up? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bee_rider in "In my life, I've witnessed three elite salespeople at work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42606745</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42606745"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T01:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I know a good salesman when I see one. I was, briefly, the No. 1 telemarketer in the United States.
Oh neat, how?
> Unlike many of my less successful colleagues, I quickly learned to take yes for an answer; though we were legally required to read a long list of mandatory disclosures to all our sales, I noticed that this often broke the spell and gave people an opening to back out or “wait and ask the wife about it.” As soon as I heard a yes, I said, “Great choice!” and transferred them to confirmation. My manager occasionally came by and reminded me that it was technically illegal to skip my disclosures, but he made commission off my commission, and his tone made it clear that I could do as I pleased as long as I kept putting up numbers.
[…]
> I was one of the first to go, technically for not making my required disclosures—about cancellation fees, international rates, all that fine print nobody ever bothered to recite—on a sale.
So, he and his boss did crime together for a while and then eventually their scam stopped working and he got fired.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bee_rider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rambles.NET, a webzine founded by Tom Knapp in 1999]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9054</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/rambles-net-webzine-founded-tom-knapp-1999/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T20:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rambles.NET is an online magazine founded by Tom Knapp in 1999, and still going strong over twenty-five later. Knapp himself continues to contribute. Rambles is another example of Indie Web in its original inception; I think a Facebook page is the only hint of social media present. I had a crack at publishing a webzine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie Web makes all of us property owners online]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9051</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-web-property-owners-online/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T19:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American engineer and product manager Den Delimarsky offers another way of looking at the core Indie Web tenets of owning your own website domain, and owning your own content. See yourself as a property owner, rather than a renter. If any of your online presence is on social media channels, you’re leasing the space, you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inauguration insurance, another form of cookie insurance?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9049</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/inauguration-insurance-cookie-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-05T19:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Ellis writes about buying a plate of cookies he had no intention of eating, from an entrepreneurial twelve-year old neighbour going door to door, who was selling them. Why would anyone pay out good money for something they’re not going to consume? Ellis describes the gesture as cookie insurance: Lastly, I bought cookies I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists to explore life creation from basic chemicals + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-to-explore-life-creation-from-basic-chemicals-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-to-explore-life-creation-from-basic-chemicals-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T16:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European scientists launch MiniLife project to create lab-made life, companies in Australia start mandatory climate disclosures, and discontent shapes global elections as incumbents lose votes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Path TCP: revolutionizing connectivity, one path at a time]]></title>
        <id>6ZxrGIedGqREgTs02vpt0t</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/multi-path-tcp-revolutionizing-connectivity-one-path-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Path TCP (MPTCP) leverages multiple network interfaces, like Wi-Fi and cellular, to provide seamless mobility for more reliable connectivity. While promising, MPTCP is still in its early stages,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marek Majkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BJones12 in "Why Canada Should Join the EU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583575</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583575"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Europeans could learn from Canada how to allow immigration in a fashion that the population embraces rather than tolerates
Clearly the author is ignorant. Canadians are sick of immigration. Young Canadians doubly so. Racism is becoming more acceptable by the day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BJones12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by antics in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583334</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42583334"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T07:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You are catching a lot of flak for this, but there is one thing you are right about. If you make tens of millions of dollars, and can't figure out what to do with those resources, you shouldn't be calling your coworkers NPCs. You're the NPC.
I truly mean this in an entirely non-judgemental way. I wish the author luck in achieving his dream of becoming high agency rather than simply high freedom. I wish it for everyone who wants it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>antics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pech0rin in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42581844</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42581844"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T03:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the most childish thing I’ve read. And shows a lot about he doesn’t have any people relying on him or community to support. He takes one hike and throws away 60m. Doesn’t try to find anything interesting to do at Atlassian just calls his coworkers NPCs. This is zero-empathy Peter Pan syndrome at its worse.
Sad how he just goes adventure hopping to try and find meaning. The problem is no matter where you are you are also there. Time to look inward and not outward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pech0rin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by akamaka in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580494</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580494"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T00:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I should work for Elon and Vivek at DOGE and help America get off its current crash to defaulting on its own debt
I’ve got an idea: take some good economics courses so that you learn how government spending actually works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>akamaka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by madrox in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580321"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T23:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't think you have to have Fuck You Money to get to this point. Most people eventually become disillusioned with work enough that they reevaluate what matters to them. Getting a very profitable exit is just one way to trigger that experience.
In my experience, a lot of people who get into this state start self-sabotaging hard as a way of rejecting what feels, ironically, like losing control. Sudden freedom can feel foreign and lot like your world got forcibly taken away from you. I'm not surprised the author is turning down opportunities and breaking off with his girlfriend. It's a way of taking back control.
When this happened to me, I pivoted hard from getting satisfaction out of what I built to getting satisfaction out of developing people. Now I take great pride out of the careers I've nurtured...a lot more than what I've built, in most ways. I've heard others express similar ideas in different ways, like "I now enjoy making other people rich."
No matter what, I encourage the author to use this time to build connections instead of destroying them (real connections...not work or SF acquaintances). Something I did not read in this essay is how he grew closer to anyone (in fact, I read the opposite). No path out of this valley involves traveling alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madrox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cj in "I am rich and have no idea what to do"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580224</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42580224"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T23:28:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t think his problem is money.
I think his problem is his identity (founder of Loom) suddenly disappeared.
Now he needs to develop a new identity.
This is especially difficult for single founders without kids (in the sense that people with spouse/kids already derive much of their identity from those 2 things).
Selling a company isn’t all that different from going through a divorce (in the sense that your identity needs to be completely rebuilt from scratch)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: A Survey of Analytics Engineering Work at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4f1f53b4ab0f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/part-2-a-survey-of-analytics-engineering-work-at-netflix-4f1f53b4ab0f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T21:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second in a multi-part series sharing a breadth of Analytics Engineering work at Netflix, recently presented as part of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scop in "Advent of Code 2024 in pure SQL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577887</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577887"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T19:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I reacted to this title the way I react a new menu item at Taco Bell: a strange mixture of desire, shame, and admiration for human ingenuity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Tell HN: Impassable Cloudflare challenges are ruining my browsing experience"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577504</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42577504"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T18:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The "unsubscribe" button in Indeed's job notification emails leads me to an impassable Cloudflare challenge.
That's a CAN-SPAM act violation.
FTC: "Tell recipients how to opt out of receiving future marketing email from you. Your message must include a clear and conspicuous explanation of how the recipient can opt out of getting marketing email from you in the future. Craft the notice in a way that’s easy for an ordinary person to recognize, read, and understand. Creative use of type size, color, and location can improve clarity. Give a return email address or another easy Internet-based way to allow people to communicate their choice to you. You may create a menu to allow a recipient to opt out of certain types of messages, but you must include the option to stop all marketing messages from you. Make sure your spam filter doesn’t block these opt-out requests."[1]
Experian was recently fined for making it hard to opt out of their marketing emails.
The actual regulation text:
§ 316.5 Prohibition on charging a fee or imposing other requirements on recipients who wish to opt out.
Neither a sender nor any person acting on behalf of a sender may require that any recipient pay any fee, provide any information other than the recipient's electronic mail address and opt-out preferences, or take any other steps except sending a reply electronic mail message or visiting a single Internet Web page, in order to:
(a) Use a return electronic mail address or other Internet-based mechanism, required by 15 U.S.C. 7704(a)(3), to submit a request not to receive future commercial electronic mail messages from a sender; or
(b) Have such a request honored as required by 15 U.S.C. 7704(a)(3)(B) and (a)(4).
That seems to cover it. File a CAN-SPAM act complaint (spam@uce.gov). Send a copy to the legal department of the sender.
[1] https://www.ftc.gov/business-guidance/resources/can-spam-act...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most visited DevOps and Developer Productivity blog posts in 2024]]></title>
        <id>84ca02a5b48a54f88f390089a009976e87922bea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/the-most-visited-devops-and-developer-productivity-blog-posts-in-2024-copy/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we kick off 2025, I wanted to take a moment to highlight the top posts from 2024. Without further ado, here are the top 10 DevOps and developer productivity blog posts of 2024. Announcing CDK Migrate A single command to migrate to the AWS CDK – This blog post announces the general availability of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re:Invent 2024 DevOps and Developer Productivity Playlist]]></title>
        <id>c0274ae9899bf1d6fa6f868d7f7e54714956d4a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/reinvent-2024-devops-and-developer-productivity-playlist/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dust has settled after another re:Invent. I once again had the privilege of organizing the DevOps and Developer Productivity (DOP) track along with Jessie VanderVeen, Krishna Dalal, Megan Sattler and countless others. For 2024, the DOP track included 60 sessions. If you weren’t able to attend, I have compiled a list of the on-demand […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes with Stream Live, Cloudflare’s live streaming service]]></title>
        <id>chVlt8JAjFduvvOJ5c1yl</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/behind-the-scenes-with-stream-live-cloudflares-live-streaming-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about Stream Live’s design, and how it leverages the distributed nature of Cloudflare’s network, rather than centralized locations as many other live services do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Boutette</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>