<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-30T06:33:40.896Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-30T06:33:40.896Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Looming Nuclear Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332068</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/a-looming-nuclear-catastrophe-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no greater strategic madness than the belief that nuclear superiority must be maintained at each rung of the nuclear ladder in order to maintain deterrence.  U.S. weapons technology was a major driver of escalation dominance throughout the 1950s and 1960s along with the belief that the Soviet Union would move to a level of nuclear conflict that the United States could not counter.  “Dr. Strangelove or How I Stopped Worrying and Learned to Love the Bomb” parodied these fears, and the arms control and disarmament developments of the 1970s and 1980s helped to defuse them.  Sadly, the Biden administration has taken a step that suggests a return to escalation dominance, which will spiral a Pentagon budget that will soon reach $1 trillion per year. More
The post A Looming Nuclear Catastrophe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332169</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/death-camp/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2007, when the State of Israel implemented its still-ongoing blockade of Gaza, several different monikers have emerged to describe the conditions for Palestinians living in the territory under the ongoing Israeli siege.  Now, after 11 months of the murderous Israeli assault on the people of Gaza, it is necessary once again to revise what the State of Israel has imposed on the territory.  What the state of Israel has created in the Gaza Strip is nothing less than a death camp akin to what the Nazis created for the massacre of Jews and other so-called enemies of the Reich. More
The post Death Camp appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Fields</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election Years Are Dangerous Times for People of Color]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332089</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/election-years-are-dangerous-times-for-people-of-color/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As he runs for reelection in 2024, former president Donald Trump has made the outlandish claim that “millions of people [have crossed the United States border] …from prisons, jails and mental institutions to come into our country and destroy our country.” His statement was a combination of two tropes that are often deployed by those seeking political  More
The post Election Years Are Dangerous Times for People of Color appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Genocide With a Smile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332066</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/roaming-charges-genocide-with-a-smile/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True to form, Trump has now taken to calling Kamala Harris “low IQ” and “stupid,” racist tropes he draws on whenever he’s confronted by minorities, women or both. But for all her faults, Harris isn’t stupid. In fact, she’s demonstrated her ability to swiftly master and deftly deploy the finer points of Clintonian triangulation, the strategy of political bait-and-switch that prioritizes running against the core issues held by her own party, even policies she once enthusiastically promoted as signature features of her own previous campaigns. Pulling this off required some pretty adroit political gymnastics, where Harris had to completely reverse herself without showing the strain over long-held positions on fracking, immigration, asylum, a human rights-based foreign policy, student loan forgiveness, torture, the death penalty, and a single-payer health care system. But she sold these policy retreats so smoothly that the Democratic base eagerly embraced her joyful politics of austerity, aggressive policing and genocide with a smile. More
The post Roaming Charges: Genocide With a Smile appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Reproductive Justice Without Palestinian Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332094</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/no-reproductive-justice-without-palestinian-liberation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following speech was given at Union Park at the March on the DNC on Monday, August 19th. Chicago for Abortion Rights is out here today because we REFUSE to allow the Democrats to use abortion rights and trans rights as a bargaining chip to force us to vote for their imperialist agenda. We refuse the  More
The post No Reproductive Justice Without Palestinian Liberation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Medley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break on Through: Finding The Doors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332156</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/break-on-through-finding-the-doors/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was at university when I first heard the Doors.  It was springtime, coming on summer.  I was living on campus, my first year, and I was eighteen.  I was in a housemate’s room, waiting for him to get back for some reason I don’t recall now.  The building we lived in was a little  More
The post Break on Through: Finding The Doors appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Do the Candidates Stand on War? Someplace Very Vague]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332149</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/where-do-the-candidates-stand-on-war-someplace-very-vague/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since a prerequisite for the American presidency is being ready, willing and able to slaughter lots of foreigners, it would be nice to know where the candidates stand on war, especially for those of us against it. We know where Joe “Proxy War” Biden stands. He’s all in. We can only pray that Kamala “Military  More
The post Where Do the Candidates Stand on War? Someplace Very Vague appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 7 Has a Prehistory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/october-7-has-a-prehistory/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In belatedly disposing of teaching materials long after retiring, I came across a cutting from the Guardian Weekly (that convenient pre-internet medium for far-flung colonials, comprising articles from the UK Guardian, the Le Monde and the Washington Post). The cutting was a review of David Montgomery’s The Fall of the House of Labor; the issue, 22 May 1988. But wait, there’s something on  More
The post October 7 Has a Prehistory appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Derogators: The Geneva Conventions Turn 75]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332148</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/beware-the-derogators-the-geneva-conventions-turn-75/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 12, 1949, the four Geneva Conventions were adopted, laying the basis of a normative standard in international humanitarian law.  As Balthasar Staehelin, personal envoy of the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) president to China, stated at an anniversary event at the Swiss Embassy in Beijing, “In the past 75 years, the four Geneva Conventions  More
The post Beware the Derogators: The Geneva Conventions Turn 75 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tasty Bacon or Fellow Being? The Paradox of How We Relate to the Intelligence and Emotions of Pigs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/tasty-bacon-or-fellow-being-the-paradox-of-how-we-relate-to-the-intelligence-and-emotions-of-pigs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pigs are fascinating animals. Science shows they can solve challenging problems, love to play, display wide-ranging emotions, and have unique personalities. In short, they are both intelligent and sentient—capable of feeling. It’s clear that it is illogical and immoral to treat pigs as mere objects. In 2015, I reviewed an essay notable for its summary and distillation  More
The post Tasty Bacon or Fellow Being? The Paradox of How We Relate to the Intelligence and Emotions of Pigs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Bekoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump IPOs His Presidency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332026</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/trump-ipos-his-presidency/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does anyone think Donald Trump is actually running for president? Granted, he’s the Republican nominee and is on the ballot in all fifty states, but the only election day that interests Trump is the one around September 20. On that day (or perhaps a few days later) the lockout period on his Trump Media  More
The post Trump IPOs His Presidency appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Venezuela Elections of 28 July 2024:  What and Whom to Believe?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332163</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-venezuela-elections-of-28-july-2024-what-and-whom-to-believe/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our media rush to issue sensational headlines and frequently make premature judgements, which, when false, are seldom corrected. With regard to the Venezuelan elections of 28 July, we are expected to believe that Nicolas Maduro rigged them. But why do we tend to think that way?  Why do the journalists of the New York Times, WaPo,  More
The post The Venezuela Elections of 28 July 2024:  What and Whom to Believe? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh Confidential: Notes on the 2024 Quota Reform Movement and July Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332158</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/bangladesh-confidential-notes-on-the-2024-quota-reform-movement-and-july-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction As recent as August 2024, a culmination of social, political, and economic challenges has caused turmoil in Bangladesh. In this article, exclusive for Counterpunch, Daniel Falcone shares insights and commentary gathered from scholars, researchers and activists in the country (that wish to remain private). They provided a summary of several important issues currently impacting  More
The post Bangladesh Confidential: Notes on the 2024 Quota Reform Movement and July Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DNC Protests: Freedom That Extends Beyond the Platitudes of the Democratic Party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332095</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-dnc-protests-freedom-that-extends-beyond-the-platitudes-of-the-democratic-party/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a pro-Palestine encampment at my local college in May, I booked a ticket to the DNC. The president of the college had just been forced to resign for “insubordination” for having the audacity to meet with demonstrators and listen to their demands. The student movement to oppose genocide and settler colonialism inspired me to  More
The post The DNC Protests: Freedom That Extends Beyond the Platitudes of the Democratic Party appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Prosecution of Trayon White]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332115</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-prosecution-of-trayon-white/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images of Trayon White in the passenger seat of a car, allegedly pocketing envelopes of cash on multiple occasions, have been splashed across the media. And now the 40-year-old DC councilmember, a protégé of the late Marion Barry, faces federal bribery charges and up to 15 years in prison. ly pocketing envelopes of cash on  More
The post The Prosecution of Trayon White appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Erdan’s War on the UN: The Brutal Wish of Failed Israel Diplomat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332084</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/erdans-war-on-the-un-the-brutal-wish-of-failed-israel-diplomat/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Departing Israeli Ambassador to the United Nations, Gilad Erdan clearly had an unpleasant experience at the world’s largest international institution. In an interview published in the Israeli newspaper Maariv on August 20, the disgruntled envoy said that “the UN building should be closed and wiped off from the face of the earth.” Whether Erdan has  More
The post Erdan’s War on the UN: The Brutal Wish of Failed Israel Diplomat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tribes and Greens Rally Against Uranium Mining Near Grand Canyon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332180</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/tribes-and-greens-rally-against-uranium-mining-near-grand-canyon/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I just want to remind people that this is about nuclear war, genocide and the ongoing colonialization of our land and the ongoing takeover of our resources and we are tired of being a resource colony. We are not a sacrifice zone.” – Leona Morgan, Diné, co-founder of Haul No!   On Saturday, Aug. 24, members  More
The post Tribes and Greens Rally Against Uranium Mining Near Grand Canyon  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hatch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bobby’s Bounce: RFK Jr’s Lesser-Evilism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332133</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/bobbys-bounce-rfk-jrs-lesser-evilism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oops. I didn’t see that one coming. So, let’s talk about RFK Jr.’s decision to help Donald Trump win the presidential election. Because, to be clear, Bobby is not just—excuse me, not even dropping out of the race. He could have done that, correctly denouncing the Democratic party’s anti-democratic legal and electoral tactics that made  More
The post Bobby’s Bounce: RFK Jr’s Lesser-Evilism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Kavanagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ghost of Torquemada and the DAV]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332048</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-ghost-of-torquemada-and-the-dav/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The July/August 2024 issue of Disabled American Veterans Magazine featured a profile on Vietnam vet and former Chicago police superintendent Terry Hillard, who had been named Disabled American Veteran of the Year. The piece was written by Matt Saintsing. In his long police career, I wondered if Hillard had ever encountered Vietnam vet and notorious Chicago police  More
The post The Ghost of Torquemada and the DAV appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Levy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards A New History of Venetian Art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332056</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/towards-a-new-history-of-venetian-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venetian painting has long been famous, and so much has been commented on. Early in the nineteenth century, Hegel, who never got to Italy, offered some evocative notes. Later in that century, Walter Pater published a famously suggestive account of the school of Giorgione. In 1970, Sydney J. Freedberg’s massive volume history of sixteenth-century Italian  More
The post Towards A New History of Venetian Art appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dispatch on American Political Dystopia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332161</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/dispatch-on-american-political-dystopia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is seemingly no end to the lethal and dystopian absurdity of  US-American political life right now. Donald “Poisoning Our Blood” Trump not only walks free but has a decent shot of being re-elected to the most dangerous job on Earth. What the fascist fuck! Hey, so what if he’s a malignant narcissist, a fascist,  More
The post Dispatch on American Political Dystopia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Star is Born, the Kamala Harris Version]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332013</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/a-star-is-born-the-kamala-harris-version/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bradley Cooper’s production of A Star is Born was reflected in the Democratic Party’s national convention. In the film, Ally (Lady Gaga) is a small town, struggling singer/songwriter. She impresses a country rock music star, Jackson Maine (Bradley Cooper), who invites her to join him at one of his concerts. He coaxes her on stage  More
The post A Star is Born, the Kamala Harris Version appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Necessity Drives Us Together]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332119</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/necessity-drives-us-together/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future is community. That might seem like a paradoxical way to begin a piece on the potential for break-up and conflict in the U.S. But it is the fundamental insight into how we navigate through whatever is coming. And that is highly uncertain. There are multiple scenarios for how a U.S. future might unfold.  More
The post Necessity Drives Us Together appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Public Lands are Slipping Away]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332117</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/our-public-lands-are-slipping-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our public lands, our sacred birthright and legacy to posterity are under serious and potentially life-ending threats. In the most extreme example, the State of Utah has filed a lawsuit against the federal government to take control of national public lands in Utah. Straight out of Project 2025. Utah claims that 18.5 million acres of  More
The post Our Public Lands are Slipping Away appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Bader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In and Out of California’s Prisons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332155</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/in-and-out-of-californias-prisons/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I was due to go to a parole board hearing in mid-2022, when a coworker at a California state prison mentioned a recent seminar from the Creating Restorative Opportunities and Programs,” said Lamar Simms of Sacramento. That was then for him. Today, Simms is a wage-earning service worker in Oakland, Calif., and a recent graduate of CROP’s Ready  More
The post In and Out of California’s Prisons appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Sandronsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris and Fortifying Black-Palestinian Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332050</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/kamala-harris-and-fortifying-black-palestinian-solidarity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past month, as Kamala Harris’s campaign for the US presidency has gained momentum, hopes she would take a strong stance on the genocide in Gaza have dwindled. Her candidacy has brought disillusionment among supporters of the Palestinian cause, and with it, growing tensions between anti-genocide activists and Harris supporters. The tension was reflected in a bitter exchange earlier this  More
The post Kamala Harris and Fortifying Black-Palestinian Solidarity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Notebooks of Sonny Rollins]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332044</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-notebooks-of-sonny-rollins/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Notebooks of Sonny Rollins Edited by Sam V.H. Reese Published in 2024 by New York Review Book Sonny Rollins did something highly unusual in modern entertainment: he ascended to the top of his field and then dropped off the radar. Vanished. Disappeared. The legend is Rollins was dissatisfied with his sound and looking for  More
The post The Notebooks of Sonny Rollins appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve O’Keefe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Presidential Election Farce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332154</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-presidential-election-farce/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s difficult to view the presidential election as anything but fluff with about 10 weeks left until November. In the US, the electorate has been viewed by the power elite of the military-industrial-investment-government complex as passive non-actors in the elite’s relentless campaign for power and greed. The point in this presidential election is to scare  More
The post The Presidential Election Farce appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For the Love of Gaza, Bring Back the Students So They Can Bring the War Home Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332077</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/for-the-love-of-gaza-bring-back-the-students-so-they-can-bring-the-war-home-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was born and raised in Bellefonte, Pennsylvania, a small-town cowering in the shadow of a vast college metropolis known simply as State College and I fucking hate State College. I hate State College because nine months out of the year State College is the home of Penn State University, a massive tax-funded corporation that  More
The post For the Love of Gaza, Bring Back the Students So They Can Bring the War Home Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicky Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary in a Carbon Trap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332091</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/canary-in-a-carbon-trap/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although I rarely mention it in print, I have had a very common airway disease since I was very small. Neither the worst nor the most mild version in my case. But bad enough to cause me to miss over 30 days of high school each year as a teenager—and to force me to explain  More
The post Canary in a Carbon Trap appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Pramas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Heath and the demise of western Marxism]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53089</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/30/53089/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T01:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am very pleased that our very own Chris Bertram has responded to Joseph Heath’s very entertaining and polemical “John Rawls and the death of Western Marxism,” a widely shared Substack post [HT: Dailynous]. Chris has made some important corrections to the public record, and the comments on his post are extending that. As it happens, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eieio in "The secret inside One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396053</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396053"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T22:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[author here :)
this is my favorite story from running the site, and possibly the best story I've ever been a part of. I'm not a big crier but I have cried so many times thinking and trying to write about it over the past 2 months. And of course, the process of discovery (and going from panic to excitement) was pretty crazy too.
One of my favorite things about this is that it validated one of the core beliefs I have when making these things - that you need constraints for the small group of people that are jerks, but that for the most part those constraints are fodder for the largely-good and very creative folks that play around on the internet.
Happy to answer any questions folks have!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eieio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asolove in "The secret inside One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41395709</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41395709"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This part is so important:
> The adults in my life were largely not mad at me. They asked me to knock it off, but also made me a t-shirt. I don’t think I’d be doing what I do now without the encouragement that I received then.
Teena need a place to be moderately mischievous, with semi-real social outcomes, but also some boundaries and help to not take it too far.
And adults who aren’t authorities over them except insofar that they have cool talents the kids want to learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asolove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dusk, a novel by Robbie Arnott, being published in October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8373</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dusk-novel-robbie-arnott-published-october-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dusk, the new novel by Hobart based Australian author Robbie Arnott, is being published on Tuesday 8 October 2024. In the distant highlands, a puma named Dusk is killing shepherds. Down in the lowlands, twins Iris and Floyd are out of work, money and friends. When they hear that a bounty has been placed on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oasis regroup, this is not the second coming we were waiting for]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8371</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/oasis-regroup-unwanted-second-coming/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T20:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backbeat, the word is on the street, Oasis, the old nineties Britpop act — that was, in the words of co-founder Noel Gallagher — bigger than the Beatles, is set to play a series of reunion concerts. Honestly, I was more excited when in 2011, the Stone Roses, an even older act, announced they were* […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277562</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Kamala's stint at McDonalds: Fact or fiction?; Kennedyon healthy food, and on the environment.; Section 230 decision: "The business model of Big Tech is over.";]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VyseofArcadia in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393216</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393216"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Hilarious that the entire TSA system is vulnerable to the most basic web programming error that you generally learn to avoid 10 minutes
The article mentions that FlyCASS seems to be run by one person. This isn't a matter of technical chops, this is a matter of someone who is good at navigating bureaucracy convincing the powers that be that they should have a special hook into the system.
What should really be investigated is who on the government side approved and vetted the initial FlyCASS proposal and subsequent development? And why, as something with a special hook into airline security infrastructure, was it never security audited?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VyseofArcadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by macNchz in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393163</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393163"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What was surprising to me was that they didn't immediately do pre-dawn raids on the pentesters' homes and hold them without a lawyer under some provision of an anti-terror law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>macNchz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by UniverseHacker in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393115</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393115"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hilarious that the entire TSA system is vulnerable to the most basic web programming error that you generally learn to avoid 10 minutes into reading about web programming- and that every decent quality web framework automatically prevents.
It is really telling that they try to cover up and deny instead of fix it, but not surprising. That is a natural consequence of authoritarian thinking, which is the entire premise and culture of the TSA. Any institution that covers up and ignores existential risks instead of confronting them head on will eventually implode by consequences of its own negligence- which hopefully will happen to the TSA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>UniverseHacker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by woodruffw in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392938</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392938"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TSA's response here is childish and embarrassing, although perhaps unsurprising given the TSA's institutional disinterest in actual security. It's interesting to see that DHS seemingly (initially) handled the report promptly and professionally, but then failed to maintain top-level authority over the fix and disclosure process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>woodruffw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be My Buddy]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/be-my-buddy/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/be-my-buddy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been considering starting a supporters page for a while, but I've been feeling conflicted...
I don't want to launch it just for the sake of it. While I want it to add some value, I don't want it to feel like a cheaper experience for those who don't want to or can contribute financially.
The solution became Birming Buddies ($1/month or one-time tip).
This gives you early access to new add-ons and palettes for the Bearming theme. You'll also be mentioned on the Birming Buddies page, and your name will be highlighted in blog challenges that you participate in.
Additionally, you'll have the opportunity to comment and make suggestions for theme features when new posts are made on the Ko-fi supporters page.
I hope this adds value for those who wish to contribute, while still allowing everyone else to continue using this blog and the theme without restrictions.
Thank you so much for your support!
PS. Despite the Birming Buddies name, I consider anyone who visits my blog a true buddy. You're awesome!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nsagent in "Judges rule Big Tech's free ride on Section 230 is over"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392867</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392867"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current comments seem to say this is rings the death knell of social media and that this just leads to government censorship. I'm not so sure.
I think the ultimate problem is that social media is not unbiased — it curates what people are shown. In that role they are no longer an impartial party merely hosting content. It seems this ruling is saying that the curation being algorithmic does not absolve the companies from liability.
In a very general sense, this ruling could be seen as a form of net neutrality. Currently social media platforms favor certain content, while down weighting others. Sure, it might be at a different level than peer agreements between ISPs and websites, but it amounts to a similar phenomenon when most people interact on social media through the feed.
Honestly, I think I'd love to see what changes this ruling brings about. HN is quite literally the only social media site (loosely interpreted) I even have an account on anymore, mainly because of how truly awful all the sites have become. Maybe this will make social media more palatable again? Maybe not, but I'm inclined to see what shakes out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nsagent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jehna1 in "OpenAI is good at unminifying code"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41390033</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41390033"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T12:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author of HumanifyJS here! I've created specifically a LLM based tool for this, which uses LLMs on AST level to guarantee that the code keeps working after the unminification step:
https://github.com/jehna/humanify]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jehna1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277548</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T10:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our high-flying daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie:  Kamala Harris is the New Face Being Put on America’s Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277504</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/rob-urie-kamala-harris-is-the-new-face-being-put-on-americas-wars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T10:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unvarnished assessment of what a Kamala Harris presidency would amount to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - Anti-Communist communists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-anti-communist-communists?v=1724924772</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-anti-communist-communists?v=1724924772"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T09:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: Anti-Communist communists
Subtitle: Or: on capitalization and capitalism
Date: August 28, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 29th August 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 It feels like two years ago but it was probably five. I drove from one side of North Carolina to another side of North Carolina because the “neo-confederates” were planning some kind of armed march through some small town and we needed all the numbers we could get to confront them. It worked, and we outnumbered them, and the people in town seemed grateful for our presence. 
 After a few hours, it devolved into a strange shouting match alongside a rural road. The confederates on one side of the road, the anti-fascists on the other. We probably called them Nazis. They called us communists. 
 “I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Joseph Heath’s account of the trajectory of analytical Marxism]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53079</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/29/on-joseph-heaths-account-of-the-trajectory-of-analytical-marxism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been much attention online to a piece by Joseph Heath arguing that analytical Marxism disappeared because the analytical Marxists all turned into Rawlsian liberals. At a certain level of resolution (blurred, zoomed out) the argument has something going for it. But at that level, all it amounts to is the claim that this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activists Link Climate Change, Gaza in a Campaign Targeting Citigroup]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277543</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/activists-link-climate-change-gaza-in-a-campaign-targeting-citigroup.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protesters are pushing Citigroup to divest from fossil fuels and companies that are sending arms to Israel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Poverty Reduction Under Capitalism Is a Myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277540</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/why-poverty-reduction-under-capitalism-is-a-myth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T07:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A full-throated critique of the claim that capitalism benefits the poors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by broodbucket in "HDMI Forum rejects AMD's HDMI 2.1 open-source driver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387420</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387420"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T04:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>On the one hand, this move ensures the quality and consistency of HDMI experience.
Does it though? Does it really?
I don't understand this move from HDMI Forum. They're handing a win to DisplayPort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>broodbucket</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gstar in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387112</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387112"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incidentally, if you root your tablet you can just change the build.MODEL to "MyAir5" and everything will work on a third party tablet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gstar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gstar in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387108</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387108"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMFG; I am in Perth, I have the same system, the very same problem and solved it almost the same way and was in the process of writing it up.
The system uses RS422, with a base64 encoded AES key in the aaservice binary, and I was contemplating building an esp32 based open source implementation of the controller.
That's a crazy weird coincidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gstar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ranebo in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386992</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386992"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have no idea how true this is :).  I had to upgrade everything, the old site didn't even have SSL.  But this annoyed me so much I wanted others to know how to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ranebo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by redact207 in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386671</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386671"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T02:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that this man resurrected his blog after 10 years just to write this. Anger and spite are strong motivators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>redact207</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommending for Long-Term Member Satisfaction at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac15cada49ef</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/recommending-for-long-term-member-satisfaction-at-netflix-ac15cada49ef?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T01:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jiangwei Pan, Gary Tang, Henry Wang, and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending August 25, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240828</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240828"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GitOps for Stateful Workload Management with vSphere CSI driver on on-premises Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>ed82f2e2617bb8ba0abe2dbd4214f8982ac7d851</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-gitops-for-stateful-workload-management-with-vsphere-csi-driver-on-on-premises-kubernetes-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T22:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the de-facto standard for container orchestration, providing powerful capabilities for deploying and managing stateless workloads. However, users running stateful applications on Kubernetes face unique challenges, especially in VMware environments. A key issue is that the virtual disks used by stateful apps can’t be attached to pods as easily as ephemeral storage. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elamaran Shanmugam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I Become a Vaishnavite?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53071</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/should-i-become-a-vaishnavite/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK guys, here’s the deal. Last night I had a decently long dream in which Vishnu appeared to me personally, blue but golden with godly light and so on, to explain to me that he was real, and that I should worship him but not necessarily his avatars, more just him, (though I objected that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[404 Media are not going anywhere, but yes they are]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8368</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/404-media-not-going-anywhere-but-they-are/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What we learned in our first year of 404 Media, by 404 Media. Has it really been a year? Here we are a year later, and we are very proud and humbled to report that, because of your support, 404 Media is working. Our business is sustainable, we are happy, and we aren’t going anywhere. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The photorealistic AI-generation revolution is here]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8363</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/photorealistic-ai-generation-revolution-here/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Welch, a writer for The Verge, on the new “reimagine” feature, that shipped with Google’s recently launched Pixel 9 smartphones. Long story short, “reimagine” allows someone to edit/enhance any photo, anyway they choose: With a simple prompt, you can add things to photos that were never there. And the company’s Gemini AI makes it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignacy Jóźwiak - Interview with Denys Pankratov, organizer of the Crane Operators Union of the Lviv Region — Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignacy-jozwiak-interview-with-denys-pankratov-organizer-of-the-crane-operators-union-of-the-lvi?v=1724876882</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignacy-jozwiak-interview-with-denys-pankratov-organizer-of-the-crane-operators-union-of-the-lvi?v=1724876882"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignacy Jóźwiak
Title: Interview with Denys Pankratov, organizer of the Crane Operators Union of the Lviv Region — Ukraine
Subtitle: Comrades from the Polish trade union OZZ IP, a member of the International Labour Network of Solidarity and Struggles give a voice to trade unionists from Ukraine
Date: March 5, 2022
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from laboursolidarity.org

 We met Denys and members of the Crane Operators Union in spring 2021, during online meetings and exchange of experience between unionised operators in Poland and Ukraine. At the time, protests were underway in both countries over pay rises and improved workplace safety in this sector. Ukrainian operators regularly informed about our actions and expressed solidarity in their social media. We wrote about the s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitney Kimball - Revenge: Spectrum Workers on Strike Build Their Own ISP]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/whitney-kimball-revenge-spectrum-workers-on-strike-build-their-own-isp?v=1724876594</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/whitney-kimball-revenge-spectrum-workers-on-strike-build-their-own-isp?v=1724876594"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Whitney Kimball
Title: Revenge: Spectrum Workers on Strike Build Their Own ISP
Date: April 14, 2021
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from gizmodo.com

 If, for any number of reasons, you’d like to burn telecoms to the ground and build a new internet service provider on their smoldering remains, good news for you. New York City Spectrum workers, who’ve weathered an anguishing four-year strike, have built their own internet service provider. If the city throws its support behind it, People’s Choice Communications could liberate New Yorkers from cable gangsters once and for all. 
 The city itself is almost constantly fighting Spectrum. With its rise to dominance in New York, Gov. Andrew Cuomo has tried to evict it; attorneys general had to chase it around for allegedly defrauding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Le Tréhondat - “I, Kostya, Ukrainian high school student, member of the Direct Action union”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/patrick-le-trehondat-i-kostya-ukrainian-high-school-student-member-of-the-direct-action-union?v=1724876246</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/patrick-le-trehondat-i-kostya-ukrainian-high-school-student-member-of-the-direct-action-union?v=1724876246"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Patrick Le Tréhondat
Title: “I, Kostya, Ukrainian high school student, member of the Direct Action union”
Subtitle: Interview by Patrick Le Tréhondat
Date: April 19, 2023
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from laboursolidarity.org

Please introduce yourself to our readers
 My name is Kostya, I am a student of the second grade. [Kostya lives in the Volyn region in northwestern Ukraine.] 
How did you experience the beginning of the war?
 In fact, I sensed that a full-scale invasion would soon occur, but I did not expect it to be so large and destructive. I remember the beginning very well. My mother asked me to buy food, which was practically non-existent, and told me to stay at home. The first week was very scary, nobody knew what was going to happen. We were just hoping for the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volodya Vagner - Builders in Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/volodya-vagner-builders-in-solidarity?v=1724876004</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/volodya-vagner-builders-in-solidarity?v=1724876004"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Volodya Vagner
Title: Builders in Solidarity
Subtitle: A rambunctious Russian-speaking union shakes up Sweden’s labor movement
Date: August 16, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from meduza.io

 Sweden is usually outside of The Beet’s purview, but the migrant workers at the heart of its growing shadow economy are not. In the construction sector in particular, many of these migrants hail from the countries that emerged from the Soviet Union’s collapse and they still use Russian as their lingua franca. To fight for their rights and combat exploitation, hundreds of these workers have formed Builders in Solidarity (Solidariska Byggare, in Swedish). Freelance journalist Volodya Vagner reports on this rapidly growing Russian-speaking union shaking up the Swedish labor movement. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur C Clarke predicts some of the future in 1964]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8358</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/arthur-c-clarke-predicts-future-1964/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking in 1964, the late British author and futurist made numerous predictions, mainly relating to advances in technology, many of which were prescient. Clarke called artificial intelligence (no surprise there, coming from the co-writer of the 1968 movie, 2001: A Space Odyssey). He also foresaw the internet, working from home, and a favourite of mine, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Minute Park, One Million Checkboxes, win Tiny Awards 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8355</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/one-minute-park-one-million-checkboxes-tiny-awards-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Minute Park by Elliott Cost, has been named winner of the main prize of the Tiny Awards 2024, while One Million Checkboxes by Nolen Royalty, took out the multiplayer player gong. One is your lucky number this year. Held annually since last year, 2023, the Tiny Awards recognise excellence in non-commercial websites designed by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[$HIMS is doing it!]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/hims-is-doing-it/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/hims-is-doing-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subscribe to receive weekly updates!
Before I start, I must say, I am a user of $HIMS when it comes to their preventative "hair-loss" lineup. I wish I had an affiliate link to plug to help hedge this trade, but I'm shit out of luck.
Okay, so what's the trade? Why do I think it's a pretty damn good opp, and what is going on?
Well, $HIMS is down 32.54% in the past month and has a current enterprise value of just over 3 billion with a market cap of 3.2 billion. Staircase up and elevator down type of action... somewhat.

Back on June 18th of this year, we had an enterprise value of 5.13B before quickly drifting on off after allegations that the company's GLP-1 weight-loss drugs were sourced from a "shady supplier." This has raised concerns about the quality and safety of their products.
Here's…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Insights with High-Quality Dashboards at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7186</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/08/unlocking-insights-with-high-quality-dashboards-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a lot of dashboards at Spotify. Our Insight teams and analysts from across the company are constantly whipping [...]
The post Unlocking Insights with High-Quality Dashboards at Scale appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aj7 in "A dishwasher can make or break a restaurant (2017)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41382859</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41382859"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a PhD in Physics from Berkeley. Still, in the strictest real estate sense, my best and highest use is as a dishwasher.
I was managing a small optics factory in Livermore. We made laser mirrors to order there — any wavelength, any reflectivity, any angle, any polarization, you name it. I was working my ass off and was unmarried at the time. Thanksgiving came around and I had nowhere to go. But I hooked up with a church in San Jose that had a dinner for poor people and went as a volunteer. After serving the dinner, I wandered back into the dish room. I immediately went over to the sink and kicked out the lady who was pretending to work. I then washed all the dishes and left.
Comes one year later.  I’m in the exact same situation.  I call up that church.  The lady says, “Oh, that’s very nice of you.  But we don’t need any more volunteers, we have enough.”  Oh shit.  What to do.  I found my old replica army parka I had bought in a Cambridge surplus store 20 years earlier. I went as a poor person. I didn’t want to be alone.
The first thing I found out is that poor people are herded, controlled, treated like children. We had to wait outside the church in the mild cold until permitted to enter, in a kind of line. So I sit down.  I will never forget the beatific smiles of the volunteers that served us.  This was performance art, and they were the stars.  Everyone on the supplicant end noticed this, I’m sure. So the meal ends. I walk back into the dish room, survey the situation, once again kick out whoever was pretending to do the dishes, do the dishes, and leave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aj7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Dad]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/dear-dad/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/dear-dad/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Dad,
Today marks the first anniversary of your passing. Not a day goes... eeh, what’s that you said?
"I know, you don't have to rub it in."
Haha! Your sense of humor is intact. That's still one of the first things people mention when your name comes up: your wonderful sense of humor, and how incredibly kind you were.
You truly treated everyone with the same care and respect.
I still remember the incident in the garden from when I was little. A drug addict had wandered in and fallen asleep there. Mom and all of us kids stood at a safe distance, nervously watching as you helped him. Before staggering off, he turned around with tears of gratitude and asked:
"Are you a priest?"
That’s the kind of person you were. A helping hand and a life saver. A true hero.
As you know, your other son turns 50 today. But this day is not about birth or death. It’s a day of celebration and love. A day of unity, no matter the realm of residence.
Thank you for the long and wonderful time you gave us. Thank you for all the lovely memories that keep your spirit alive. Thank you for all the beautiful things you passed on to us.
I'll end with your last words:
I love you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memories of the Last Few Days]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/memories-of-the-last-few-days/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/memories-of-the-last-few-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re finally back home.
I’ve had a really good few days (since Friday) break. We did a lot in a relatively short amount of time.
So many indicators of a memorable time.
Tan lines in random places to indicate getting that much needed Vitamin D.
Photographs that froze time to be remembered and printed.
(Enamel) Pins added to my collection of places visited.
Stickers. All of the stickers, even though pins have replaced that obsession.
A couple of library cards to show that even during vacation, I still think about all of the books to be read in the future.
Memories of full bellies because we ate a lot of really yummy food.
I’m still processing everything. I’ll be posting all of the photos in the future, whether it be on here, or on the photoblog.
Last day of my very short “vacation” today.
I woke up this morning after having dreamt of work, with tears in my eyes. Is it respectable for me to throw a tantrum to show that I really don’t want to go back to work tomorrow?
Probably not. For today, I’m going to try really hard to just not think about it.
Vacation is not over until it’s over.
28/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277508</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics; The DNC was a superspreading event, and adopted a eugenicist masking policy; Boeing door plug debacle reveals shop floor fiasco; Vermeer's tronie. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AWS Parallel Computing Service to run HPC workloads at virtually any scale]]></title>
        <id>a5b458691b849a5cf02d12c1cf9dca72099fe15e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-aws-parallel-computing-service-to-run-hpc-workloads-at-virtually-any-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T17:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Parallel Computing Service, run HPC workloads at virtually any scale effortlessly; leverage Slurm and managed clusters to accelerate simulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is getting ready for post-quantum cryptography]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21662</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/28/security/post-quantum-cryptography-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T16:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Quantum Apocalypse is coming. The advent of quantum computers has raised real questions about the future of data privacy over the internet.  Someday, advances in quantum computing will make it possible to decrypt sensitive data that was encrypted using today’s complex cryptography systems. In the latest episode of the Meta Tech Podcast you’ll meet Sheran [...]
Read More...
The post Meta is getting ready for post-quantum cryptography appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fritz Brupbacher - Bakunin and his Confession]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fritz-brupbacher-bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724856892</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fritz-brupbacher-bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724856892"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T14:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fritz Brupbacher
Title: Bakunin and his Confession
Date: 1929
Notes: Original title: *Bakunin e la sua Confessione
 Fritz Brupbacher 
 Témoins, III, n. 10–11, autunno-inverno 1955–56 
 via: finimondo.org/node/2118 
 Michael Bakunin: Der Satan der Revolte 
 by Fritz Brupbacher First published in 1929
Source: Retrieved on August 28, 2024 from https://www.elephanteditions.net/library/bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724822630

I
 
 For most contemporaries, Michail Bakunin is unknown. If a certain number of people only know him by name, that is enough to hate and slander him. But there are some who love him with fervour. 
 Once Bakunin was truly a great name. While one would search in vain in the edition of the great encyclopedic dictionary published in 1866 for the name of Karl Marx, tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Poverty Grows as Super-Rich Get Richer Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277500</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/global-poverty-grows-as-super-rich-get-richer-faster.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T14:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oxfam gives an update on the ever-widening gap between our money overlords and the poor, and how their enrichment is increasing poverty.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "Diffusion models are real-time game engines"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41378523</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41378523"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T11:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Apparently there’s more cause, effect, and sequencing in diffusion models than what I expected
To temper this a bit, you may want to pay close attention to the demo videos. The player rarely backtracks, and for good reason - the few times the character does turn around and look back at something a second time, it has changed significantly (the most noticeable I think is the room with the grey wall and triangle sign).
This falls in line with how we'd expect a diffusion model to behave - it's trained on many billions of frames of gameplay, so it's very good at generating a plausible -next- frame of gameplay based on some previous frames. But it doesn't deeply understand logical gameplay constraints, like remembering level geometry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277441</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our ravishing daily links: fundamentalists' brains? Long Covid in kids, 25 F temp increases coming? China rare earths clampdown, Macron authoritarianism, Ukraine ballsitic misiles, Wilkerson on US decline, Trump + Harris agree debate rule, moar Durov, Stoller on antitrust, Burning Man richfest, strikes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G.A. Cohen on the output bias]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53064</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/g-a-cohen-on-the-output-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Originally drafted for a conference at Frankfurt in 2018 to mark the 40th anniversary of Karl Marx’s Theory of History: A Defence. I’ve done a bit of editing of my conference script and added a few footnotes etc, but it isn’t necessarily produced to the scholarly standards one might require of a journal article.) In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer Review: What Does It Really Mean Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277485</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/peer-review-what-does-it-really-mean-today.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why peer review is not what you might think it is, and what can be done to remedy that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distortions and Distractions of the Democratic National Circus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277483</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/on-the-distortions-and-distractions-of-the-democratic-national-circus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-targeted rant about the offensive shallowness and neglect of concrete material needs of voters that the Democratic Party now embodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polar Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://wait.lol/polar-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://wait.lol/polar-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[:root {
  --image-border: rgba(0,0,0,0.1);
  --image-shadow: rgba(0,0,0,0.1);
}
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  :root {
    --image-border: rgba(255,255,255,0.2);
    --image-shadow: rgba(255,255,255,0.1);
  }
}
.app-image {
  box-shadow: 0 4px 8px var(--image-shadow);
  border: 1px solid var(--image-border);
}
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  .app-image {
    box-shadow: 0 4px 8px var(--image-shadow), 0 0 0 1px var(--image-border);
  }
}
sup { font-size: 0.6em; }
.footnotes { font-size: 0.8em; color: #666; }
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  .footnotes { color: #aaa; }
}
.image-container {
  display: flex;
  justify-content: space-between;
  gap: 10px;
  margin: 60px 0;
}
.image-container img {
  width: calc(50% - 5px);
  height: auto;
  object-fit: cover;
  cursor: p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The (Electoral) Politics of Age Gaps]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53062</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/the-electoral-politics-of-age-gaps/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’ nomination locks in another Boomer presidency. This single generation — those born in the nineteen years between 1946 and 1964 — is guaranteed another presidency. 36 consecutive years, not counting the Biden Interregnum (he’s technically too old). Despite being a Boomer, you may have noticed that she’s the young, exciting candidate. Yes, the generational […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "Thoughts on the Durov Arrest"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41376204</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41376204"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This analysis leaves out the fact that Pavel Durov is, with Telegram, in approximately the same position Ladar Levison was with Lavabit. Unlike Meredith Whitaker, Durov actually is in a position to furnish documents to the French government, where he has citizenship. He's in that position because he has repeatedly made deliberate product decisions, to the bafflement of cryptographers around the world, to keep himself in that position.
If you literally have plaintext documents responsive to criminal inquiries in a jurisdiction you are subject to, we don't reach the "internet censorship wars". You're in a place not dissimilar to a 1970s telephone company; the "random people can't simply declare themselves above the law wars". Don't be in that place. Encrypt end-to-end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vessenes in "Diffusion models are real-time game engines"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41375657</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41375657"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T03:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, this is surprising. Apparently there’s more cause, effect, and sequencing in diffusion models than what I expected, which would be roughly ‘none’. Google here uses SD 1.4, as the core of the diffusion model, which is a nice reminder that open models are useful to even giant cloud monopolies.
The two main things of note I took away from the summary were: 1) they got infinite training data using agents playing doom (makes sense), and 2) they added Gaussian noise to source frames and rewarded the agent for ‘correcting’ sequential frames back, and said this was critical to get long range stable ‘rendering’ out of the model.
That last is intriguing — they explain the intuition as teaching the model to do error correction / guide it to be stable.
Finally, I wonder if this model would be easy to fine tune for ‘photo realistic’ / ray traced restyling — I’d be super curious to see how hard it would be to get a ‘nicer’ rendering out of this model, treating it as a doom foundation model of sorts.
Anyway, a fun idea that worked! Love those.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vessenes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook operates a little differently in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8351</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/facebook-operates-differently-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Swan, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Rampant celebrity cryptocurrency scam ads are as Australian as Tim Tams, koalas or the Great Barrier Reef, according to American Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen, who says the tech giant’s lack of focus on Australia has let scams run wild on its platform compared with other markets. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zbowling in "Microsoft donates the Mono Project to the Wine team"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371554</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371554"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T19:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked on Mono a lot back in the early 2000s (back in the SVN days before it moved to Git, even). This move makes a lot of sense. Things evolved a lot over the years. Mono's legacy goals, which are to be a portable CLR (.NET) runtime for platforms that Microsoft didn't care about, don't make much sense today.
Mono made a lot of sense for running places where full .NET didn't, like in full AOT environments like on the iPhone where you can't JIT, or for random architectures that don't matter anymore but once did for Linux (Alpha, Itanium, PPC, MIPs, etc.). When Microsoft bought Xamarin (which itself was born out of the ashes of the Novell shutdown of the Mono effort) and started the DotNET Core efforts to make .NET more portable itself and less a system-provided framework and merge in a lot of the stuff Mono did a single more focused project made more sense.
Mono was still left out there to support the edge cases where DotNET Core didn't make sense, which was mostly things like being a backend for Wine stuff in some cases, some GNOME Desktop stuff (via GTK#, which is pretty dead now), and older niche use cases (second life and Unity still embed mono as a runtime for their systems). The project was limping, though, and sharing a standard library but different runtimes after much merging. Mono's runtime was always a little more portable (C instead of C++) and more accessible to experiment with, but we need that less and less, but it's still perfect for Wine. So, having it live on in Wine makes sense. It's a natural fit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zbowling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pif in "Why is the Oral-B iOS app almost 300 MB? And why is Colgate's app even bigger..?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371345</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371345"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T18:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My question is: why do an Oral-B app and a Colgate app even exist?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by silverquiet in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369889</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369889"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years back it started showing me obvious political ragebait. I ignored it and then it started showing me pictures of women whose nipples were obviously showing through their clothing, which was an improvement, but still not the reason I signed up for Facebook. I've always understood it as the algorithm is looking for engagement and will try some lowest common denominator tactics to engage in it. As someone who just wanted to see the odd picture of a friend or relative, I don't have much use for Facebook these days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>silverquiet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by object-a in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369244"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's funny because Facebook's news feed in the last couple years is unusable, filled with AI slop and clickbait. Twitter similarly requires aggressive use of block + mute to eliminate scams, clickbait, and other content I'm not interested in.
I don't know if this is due to their changes in moderation policy, or if AI has overwhelmed them, but I vastly preferred the old news feeds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>object-a</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Malidir in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369086</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369086"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Pavel's interview with Tucker Carlson, he mentions how he (VK) met with Zuckerberg, and he told them new features they were planning.  And Zuck nicked them all.
Zuck is on a major PR campaign drive, I would not trust a word he says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malidir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21618</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/27/security/privacy-aware-infrastructure-purpose-limitation-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we’ve been diligently working to incorporate privacy into different systems of our software stack over the past few years. Today, we’re excited to share some cutting-edge technologies that are part of our Privacy Aware Infrastructure (PAI) initiative. These innovations mark a major milestone in our ongoing commitment to honoring user privacy.  PAI offers [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BurningFrog in "Nuclear reactors a mile underground promise safe, cheap power"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41368420</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41368420"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Existing nuclear reactors are already extremely safe, and they still can't be built because of safety concerns.
The "you can't be 100% sure" argument is impossible to defeat, and I don't think this design will move the needle.
It also provides the argument that wanting to bury reactors 1 mile deep shows how incredibly dangerous nuclear power really is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BurningFrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Getting Multiple Library Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read a lot. Probably more than a lot of people, but still not as much as some.
When you read a lot, libraries can become your best friend. Although I would love to buy all of the books, it's just not sustainable. As much as I love having a physical collection, there are times when just borrowing a book over buying it, makes more sense.
I loved visiting libraries growing up. There was one next to my middle school that I would go to after school. I remember getting lost in the pages of a book, tucked in a corner between shelves.
I went to libraries less and less growing up. Then e-books happened. I still read a lot, and found myself buying most of the e-books I read. At some point, I got a Kindle Unlimited subscription. Despite its name, the book selection really wasn't unlimited, especially if you read outside of the genre of their book offerings.
Enter Libby.
If you haven't heard of it, Libby is a game changer for anyone who loves reading. All you need is a library card, and suddenly you have access to the library's entire e-book collection.
I started a Libby account with a local library card to start with. Simple enough, right? But then I had an epiphany: as long as I'm a California resident, I can get different library cards across the state. Now that is the real game changer. More library cards = even more selection of books.
Now, every time I visit a new California town, I try to stop by their library to get a card. Yesterday, we visited a new town for my birthday. We passed a library while roaming around town. Guess what I did?
I got myself yet another library card.
Thinking about collecting all of the cards up and down California at this point. A librarian Thanos, if you will.
27/31 - Blaugust
💬 Community Echoes
Multiple Library Cards and Libby by Noisy Deadlines
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do You Do for Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/what-do-you-do-for-fun/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/what-do-you-do-for-fun/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Wonder Woman
People in the first world take having fun very seriously. We sure spend enough money on it. Some kinds of fun are pricing themselves out of the middle-class range. Tickets and all that goes with them (parking, food, souvenirs) to major league sports and top-tier concerts can easily take a family outing into four figures. A day at a Disney theme park for a family of four is well over $1000.
I've never been to a Disney Park, and my last concert was 15 years ago. I guess I'll die without seeing Bruce Springsteen. I heard the other day that he's reached billionaire status, and I'm not giving a billionaire any of my dough to be entertained for three hours, no matter how good a showman he is. I enjoy amateur and minor league sports. Hell, I like watching my grandson's socce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irrationality and mass paranoia invade our societies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T08:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“But why are they attacking us? What have we done to them to make them hate us and bomb us like this?”. These are surprising and thought-provoking questions from ordinary Russians living in the Kursk region, asked by reporters sent to cover the advance of Ukrainian troops into this Russian territory. And they are all the more surprising given that these Russians do not live in Vladivostok or Siberia, but practically straddle the Russian border with Ukraine, just a few dozen kilometers from (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Palestine, 
Antifascism, 
Ukraine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price Gouging Part Two]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45576</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/26/price-gouging-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford When you are only concerned with one thing and have only one tool things can go awry quite easily.  So it is with our price theory friends.  They bask in the rigor of their thinking and look askance at the inability of regular folks to grasp the point of the logic of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first six months of Vision Pro by Michael Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8348</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/first-six-months-vision-pro-michael-ball/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Ball, writing about the first six-months of Apple’s spatial computing, and — whether Apple likes it or not — virtual reality headset, Vision Pro: The Vision Pro is clearly the most ambitious of their product launches since the iPhone, the first to be wholly developed under the purview of CEO Tim Cook (though various […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ndesaulniers in "DOJ sues realpage for algorithmic pricing scheme that harms renters"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41360283</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41360283"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies are culluding to suppress wages by algorithm, too.  Look up a company called Aon, and their product called Radford Data & Analytics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ndesaulniers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SeptemBest: A Quality Blog Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/septembest-blog-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/septembest-blog-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know what you’re thinking:
“Not another blog challenge!”
But hear me out...
There’s been a debate lately about the existence or non-existence of blog challenges. The criticism has been that quantity takes precedence over quality. Even though there haven’t been any requirements for daily posts, it’s sort of become the norm to post every day.
With that in mind, I propose a kind of anti-challenge for the month of September. A "challenge" where quality comes first – and only.
The idea is to blog in the way you normally do. Whether that’s one post every two weeks or two a day doesn’t matter. Then, at the end of September, you choose the text that you think was your "best" during the month.
The post that...
...you are most proud of.
...was the hardest to write.
...is the most personal.
...best represents you.
...made you think in new ways.
Or whatever you base "best" on. Your favorite, simply put.
Why this challenge?
As a reader, perhaps someone visiting your blog for the first time, it gives a good picture of who you are as a blogger. This no-pressure approach might also lead your writing into new unexplored territory. Diving back into the ideas and perspectives that resonated with you most can offer fresh and valuable insights.
If you want to join SeptemBest, as I’ve chosen to call it, contact me and I’ll add you to the list below. Then come back to me on October 1st with your “winning text,” and it will be added here along with the rest of the contributions.
Please note: I really want to emphasize that this is not a competition, despite the name. The idea is for it to be a fun, low-pressure, and interesting exploration on a personal level.
Participants (⭐️ = Birming Buddies)
Robert Birming
Alexandra
Netigen
Nikki
Jd
Jedda
Brandon
Dominik
Shrutarshi Basu
Lou Plummer ⭐️
Jason Kratz
Barry Sampson]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: S3 Conditional writes, AWS Lambda, JAWS Pankration, and more (August 26, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>4cb2b61c9474efcc91420feeff2904beeee6b491</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-s3-conditional-writes-aws-lambda-jaws-pankration-and-more-august-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS User Group Japan (JAWS-UG) hosted JAWS PANKRATION 2024 themed ‘No Border’. This is a 24-hour online event where AWS Heroes, AWS Community Builders, AWS User Group leaders, and others from around the world discuss topics ranging from cultural discussions to technical talks. One of the speakers at this event, Kevin Tuei, an AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scrlk in "NSA releases 1982 Grace Hopper lecture"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41359832</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41359832"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great quote at 45:26 regarding vertical vs. horizontal scaling: https://youtu.be/si9iqF5uTFk?t=2726
> "Now back in the early days of this country, when they moved heavy objects around, they didn't have any Caterpillar tractors, they didn't have any big cranes. They used oxen. And when they got a great big log on the ground, and one ox couldn't budge the darn thing, they did not try to grow a bigger ox. They used two oxen! And I think they're trying to tell us something. When we need greater computer power, the answer is not "get a bigger computer", it's "get another computer". Which of course, is what common sense would have told us to begin with."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scrlk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RETINAS: Real-Time Infrastructure Accounting for Sustainability]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21592</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/26/data-infrastructure/retinas-real-time-infrastructure-accounting-for-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are introducing a new metric— real-time server fleet utilization effectiveness —as part of the RETINAS initiative to help reduce emissions and achieve net zero emissions across our value chain in 2030. This new metric allows us to measure server resource usage (e.g., compute, storage) and efficiency in our large-scale data center server fleet in [...]
Read More...
The post RETINAS: Real-Time Infrastructure Accounting for Sustainability appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your Next Experiment by Learning Better Proxy Metrics From Past Experiments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/64c786c2a3ac</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/improve-your-next-experiment-by-learning-better-proxy-metrics-from-past-experiments-64c786c2a3ac?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Aurélien Bibaut, Winston Chou, Simon Ejdemyr, and Nathan Kallus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Lap Around the Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/another-lap-around-the-sun/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/another-lap-around-the-sun/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:41:42.947Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating another year of being alive.
That's it.
That's the post.
A reflection post upcoming at some point, but not today.
Today, the plan is to bask in the sun, spend the day in one of the cutest towns, and enjoy the sound of the waves crashing on the shore.

...and of course, snapping photos of all of the things
26/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use This Curse on Your Worst Enemy]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/use-this-curse-on-your-worst-enemy/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/use-this-curse-on-your-worst-enemy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I have one favorite thing in the whole world to think about, it's me. Left to my own devices, I am definitely my own favorite thing to contemplate. I'm constantly evaluating whether I feel good enough and if not, what I can do to rectify that situation. Do I need a snack? Maybe some cell phone time is called for. Maybe I am working too hard, and I need a break. Are people treating me with enough respect? Are my co-workers doing their fair share of tasks? Are raises coming up? Will I get what I deserve?
If I had the power to do one thing to my worst enemy, I would make that bastard as self-centered as possible, because brothers and sisters, let me tell you, a self-centered existence is a miserable existence. Until I was 43, the answer to the internal question "Do I feel good enough?" was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithmic Macroprudential Risk, and a legal case related to possible rent inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53048</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/26/algorithmic-macroprudential-risk-and-a-legal-case-related-to-possible-rent-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to The New York Times (23 August), The Justice Department “filed an antitrust lawsuit on Friday against the real estate software company RealPage, alleging its software enabled landlords to collude to raise rents across the United States.” I am not an expert in law or anti-trust, but there is another (systemic risk management) angle to this story that the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by red_admiral in "Australian employees now have the right to ignore work emails, calls after hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41354732</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41354732"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the Swiss implementation of this. A manager _can_ contact an employee on a Sunday, but then the employee is immediately on weekend-rate overtime even if they just got an email with "deal with this next week". So, many companies have systems that hold back e-mail sent outside of working hours until the next working day unless specially authorised and costed.
Never underestimate an economics-based solution to a legal problem, a.k.a. "if you really want to ban it, tax it".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>red_admiral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mquander in "Removing stuff is never obvious yet often better"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353884</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353884"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T03:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know if this calculator was good or bad, but the rationale sounds superficially ridiculous.
> Visitors who didn't see the calculator were 16% more likely to sign up and 90% more likely to contact us than those who saw it. There was no increase in support tickets about pricing, which suggests users are overall less confused and happier.
Of course if you hide the fact that your product might cost a lot of money from your users, more of them will sign up. Whether they are better off depends on whether they end up getting a bill they are unhappy with later at some unspecified future date, or not. That's not something you will figure out from a short-term A/B test on the signup page. So this seems like totally useless evidence to me.
I see this dynamic frequently with A/B tests. For example, one of my coworkers implemented a change that removed information from search result snippets. They then ran an A/B test that showed that after removing the information, people clicked through to the search result page more often. Well, obviously, it makes sense that they might click through more often, if information they wanted which was previously in the snippet, now requires them to click through. The question of which is actually better seemed to have been totally forgotten.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mquander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by steelframe in "Australian employees now have the right to ignore work emails, calls after hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353270</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353270"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've dabbled in management a few times in my career. This meant attending manager-only meetings and trainings. I'll never forget one time when a manager in a focus group said something along the lines of, "The tech sector is going through a rough patch, so we can turn the screws on our employees and they'll have to take it because they will have a hard time trying to find a job somewhere else." This is at a company where most of the employees are on work visas, so losing their job can very rapidly escalate into having to leave the country in short order.
After I picked my jaw up off the floor I realized I simply lacked the scruples I'd need to be "one of them." I also started looking into every legal protection I had available to me in my jurisdiction.
I know not every manager is like that. I'd like to think I wasn't. But there are enough of them that think that way that legal protections often need to be there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steelframe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jawns in "Police Chief Says Cops Have a 5th Amendment Right to Leave Body Cameras Off"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352340</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352340"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T23:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In general, courts have held that Fifth Amendment protections against self-incrimination pertain to testimonial evidence, not broadly to any possible evidence that might be incriminating.
The Fifth Amendment does not extend to physical evidence or other non-testimonial evidence, even if such evidence is potentially incriminating. For example, courts have held that things like blood samples, fingerprints, handwriting samples, and even video or audio recordings do not fall under the protection of the Fifth Amendment because they are not considered testimonial in nature.
The report notes that it is the police chief, not a lawyer representing him, who is making the preposterous argument that the Fifth Amendment justifies his conduct.  Any lawyer who tried to make that argument would be made a laughing stock.
Indeed, I would think that this internal affairs report, where the chief is essentially admitting that he knew he'd done something wrong and was trying to prevent incriminating evidence from being recorded, would be pretty damning in front of a jury, because it establishes that he was well aware of the recklessness of his conduct.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jawns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by koverstreet in "Linux Pipes Are Slow"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352339</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352339"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T23:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my sideprojects is intended to address this: https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/
The idea is a syscall for getting a ringbuffer for any supported file descriptor, including pipes - and for pipes, if both ends support using the ringbuffer they'll map the same ringbuffer: zero copy IO, potentially without calling into the kernel at all.
Would love to find collaborators for this one :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>koverstreet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The asterism: the proposed new symbol for the fediverse. So say we]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8342</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/asterism-proposed-new-symbol-fediverse/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asterism, ⁂, a typographic symbol made up three stars, is being proposed as the new symbol for the fediverse. If the fediverse needs a symbol, it’s not half bad. Does the web have a symbol? I’m not even sure. But for those who came in late, the fediverse can be defined thusly: The fediverse […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Years and Still Settling In]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/two-years-and-still-settling-in/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/two-years-and-still-settling-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks two years since closing on our house in the San Francisco Bay Area (California). It feels both like it just happened yesterday, and a lifetime ago.
Buying this house was not the easiest. During the entire nightmare of a process, I remember thinking that I wanted to blog about it (I wasn’t writing yet then) in detail, so that all first time homebuyers could avoid the stress we endured. Also, no one ever teaches you any of this in school, so I’m not exactly sure how anyone could know the process until they’re knees deep in it already.
Yes, there are plenty of articles out there about the house buying process, but it still doesn’t truly prepare you for the real thing. At least it didn’t for us.
I want to caveat that this house was not my first house. In 2012, I bought my first hou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-Thing Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://matanabudy.com/one-thing-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://matanabudy.com/one-thing-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:46:58.541Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love apps that do only one thing but do it well. I don’t need an app to solve all my problems in one interface. This usually leads to one of the following:
The app solves many problems I have, but it solves each one poorly.
The app solves some problems I have and some that I don’t, making parts of it useless to me.
I don’t want what they call a Super-app. I want an app designed to solve something specific, one that has been thoughtfully crafted to address a particular need. This doesn’t mean that I want an app for every little thing. The “one thing” could also be a big thing; it just needs to be focused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragorn Eloff - Do Anarchists Dream of Emancipated Sheep?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aragorn-eloff-do-anarchists-dream-of-emancipated-sheep?v=1724591914</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aragorn-eloff-do-anarchists-dream-of-emancipated-sheep?v=1724591914"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T13:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aragorn Eloff
Title: Do Anarchists Dream of Emancipated Sheep?
Subtitle: Contemporary Anarchism, Animal Liberation and the Implications of New Philosophy
Source: Chapter from ‘Anarchism and Animal Liberation: Essays on Complementary Elements of Total Liberation’ (ISBN: 0786494573). <academia.edu>

 Everything fits together, from the bird whose brood is crushed to the humans whose nest is destroyed by war. 
 —Louise Michel 
 In this essay I explore the relations between contemporary anarchism and animal rights/liberation through the lens of Deleuze/Guattari-inflected complex systems theory. Specifically, I look at the liberalism and normative practices endemic to the mainstream animal rights movement, engaging with some of the more salient critiques that have emerged from Leftist an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reclaim the Night!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Reclaim-the-Night</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Reclaim-the-Night"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T12:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the sun is rising in the east, rain is pouring, and tides are visiting to and fro in the Ganges, nothing can diminish the spark that was raised against the heinous rape that happened at one of the most premium medical colleges, known as R. G. Kar Medical College, in Kolkata. Yes, Kolkata, known as the safest city in India, to all the people throughout the nation is experiencing turmoil after decades over a shivering issue. On August 9, a postgraduate trainee doctor found rape and (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
India, 
Feminisms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salmali Das, Sankha Subhra Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Perfect Blogger]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/the-perfect-blogger/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/the-perfect-blogger/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time thinking about blogging; about my own blog and those of the people I read regularly and the ones I discover as I explore. Every once in a while I discover a real gem where someone's efforts are all at once entertaining, thought provoking, inspiring and original. I'll often be stricken with a pang of jealousy. "I want to write like that", I'll tell myself, knowing that I won't. Alas, I write like me. I might get some inspiration or an idea for a day's entry from one of my favorite bloggers, but I'm never going to be them.
The writing I like the best is the personal kind. I like knowing what makes people tick. As much as I like reading well written technical pieces that tell me how to do cool things with my MacBook and my iPhone, I like it best when I find out what it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auraj - People’s uprising against an autocratic state]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/auraj-people-s-uprising-against-an-autocratic-state?v=1724575985</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/auraj-people-s-uprising-against-an-autocratic-state?v=1724575985"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Auraj
Title: People’s uprising against an autocratic state
Subtitle: The present, past and future of Bangladesh
Date: 24 July 2024
Notes: The writer is a member of the anarchist group Auraj network. Auraj (which means “anarchy” in Bangla) is an anarchist network of Bangladeshi students and other people from different professions. Auraj has published various translations of Anarchist thinkers such as Bakunin, Kropotkin, Rudolf Rocker, and others in Bangla. Auraj also frequently publishes articles on Bangladesh’s political and economic scenario. Auraj has shown solidarity with the recent labor movements (movements of garment workers, jute mill workers), student movements, and civil rights movements in Bangladesh. Although members of Auraj have individually taken part directly in many…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Photoblogging: Tempio del Valdier, Frasassi Caves, Italy.]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53034</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/25/sunday-photoblogging-tempio-del-valdier-frasassi-caves-italy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Ronzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confederación Nacional del Trabajo - CNT on the re-foundation of the IWA]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/confederacion-nacional-del-trabajo-cnt-on-the-re-foundation-of-the-iwa?v=1724573647</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/confederacion-nacional-del-trabajo-cnt-on-the-re-foundation-of-the-iwa?v=1724573647"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Confederación Nacional del Trabajo
Title: CNT on the re-foundation of the IWA
Subtitle: CNT-E’s XI Congress agreements on internationalism
Date: 5 April 2016
Source: Retrieved on 25th August 2024 from www.cnt.es

 The CNT would like to announce and explain the agreements made during our December 2015 Congress with regards to the current International Workers’ Association (IWA). We believe that it is necessary to explain our position on the drift of our international, so that this internal situation can be made publically known in order to openly and quickly begin the process of its re-foundation. 
 In the CNT we consider international solidarity to be critical in this historical moment, marked by the global organization of capitalism. As expected, the economic crisis has served as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an internal CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.chay.dev/create-an-internal-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.chay.dev/create-an-internal-cli/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assumed Audience: programmers who know their way around a terminal.
One useful way to capture and preserve institutional knowledge in a dev team is to grow a collection of useful snippets, scripts, or workflows. This is why almost every repo out there has some way to write and run tasks via Makefiles, bash scripts, or language-specific toolings like scripts in package.json for Javascript, or mix tasks for Elixir.
What about org-wide things, like installing useful tools, generating boilerplate code, or running complex AWS commands that no one remembers? Some companies like Slack and Shopify have their own internal CLI. The modern terminal Warp has a pretty sick feature for documenting and sharing workflows.
It's quite easy to get started with your very own CLI. Let's create one right now fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did you lose your AirPods?]]></title>
        <id>https://alexyancey.com/lost-airpods/</id>
        <link href="https://alexyancey.com/lost-airpods/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T23:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend found some AirPods on the ground and tapped them to his phone, revealing only the serial number and the last four digits of the owner's number. He turned to me for help.
All Out
Could I really brute-force spam all phone numbers ending in 1234 and find the right owner? This seemed a bit impractical, so I had to think of ways to whittle the number down to something more manageable.
Area Code
I started with the assumption that the owner lived near me in the Portland metropolitan area. With that, I restricted the search to our local area code*. Sure, they could be from out of town, but hey, let's give it a shot.
999 numbers is a manageable list, but I wanted to trim the number a bit more. Sure, sending a thousand SMS messages isn't much to a determined spammer, but I didn't want to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Robson: &ldquo;To Be Continued&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/to-be-continued</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/to-be-continued"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wei Shujun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish packages to AWS CodeArtifact using Amazon CodeCatalyst Actions]]></title>
        <id>e8258fd18a1ab4295fa19354682af40f46311ed2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/publish-packages-to-aws-codeartifact-using-amazon-codecatalyst-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst is a unified software development service for development teams to quickly build, deliver and scale applications on AWS while adhering to organization-specific best practices. Developers can automate development tasks and innovate faster with generative AI capabilities, and spend less time setting up project tools, managing CI/CD pipelines, provisioning and configuring various development environments […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Shahzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How empirical is ’empirical’ macroeconomics?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45572</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/23/how-empirical-is-empirical-macroeconomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T18:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll At a first glance, DSGE models seem to imply total ignorance because representative agents (or representative groups of agents with limited heterogeneity) featuring objective utility functions populate the literature. At a second glance, however, it becomes obvious that “methodological individualism” prevails and even dominates. To understand this dominance one only has to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>