<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-27T01:35:11.978Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-27T01:35:11.978Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections of a conflicted impostor]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T00:51:56.738Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah... how difficult it is to admit this, but I failed. Actually, I don't know if it's difficult, if I'm afraid, or if I just lack courage, despite many people saying that fear is the absence of courage, so this might be redundant.
I always thought I was a very intelligent guy and ahead of my time, especially when I was around 18 years old or younger. I remember people always saying that I was very mature for my age, because I had values that were already lost, and even my culture was from generations much earlier than mine. When technology was still a novelty, and servers were something only large or well-structured companies had, I was basically a master, and I was still a minor... I remember setting up LANs for acquaintances or friends to play games, and even setting up a server (more li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The search for the distant Planet Nine continues]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7689</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/search-distant-planet-nine-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weird stuff is happening out on the remote boundary of the solar system. Beyond the orbit of Pluto. You name it, it’s going on out there. Irregularities. Anomalies. Clustering of apsidal lines. Perihelia. And — saving the best for last — a surprising prevalence of retrograde Centaurs. These anomalies include the apparent clustering of apsidal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICQ to close on 26 June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7695</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/icq-close-26-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T20:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASL? Another artefact of the early days of the (mainstream) internet will soon be no more. Instant messaging service, ICQ, launched in 1996, will cease operating, as of Wednesday 26 June 2024. ICQ (I seek you, get it?) allowed users to chat to pretty much anyone who let them. I can’t remember when I stopped […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[all the bells and whistles]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/all-the-bells-and-whistles/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/all-the-bells-and-whistles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T19:34:54.498Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[guyssssss... look at the blog!!!! we got a newsletter now! it's just for me send out notifs about new blog posts and some other stuff, probably more personal stuff for my buddies :p also, check out the reply via email link at the ends of my posts.
I've been looking around this website as much as i can (very difficult btw) to find interesting blog layouts and generally read the room and determine the culture bearbloggers have going on here. I'll be honest, and sorry to offend if I do, but this seems like a very serious website... imma keep doing what I do on here of course, but a lot of the posts I've read have a very sterile voice to them. I hope more friends come on here and we can liven up the space a bit more. let's smile and laugh you guys <3
I'm still enjoying many of the blogs on here, especially those ran by women. not to be reese witherspoon "women's stories matter. they just matter." but women's stories really do matter and I really enjoy reading about other women's lives on this website. blogging gives a space to introspect and reflect on our lives, and I enjoy hearing other women's voices and beliefs. I'm hoping to hear more queer voices, too.
to my dear friends who actually read my blog, I hope you guys will come on here one day, too. I think you're all so wonderful anyway, and I love to read more from you guys.
thank you to all the now-strangers that are also reading this blog, I really appreciate you and the grace you've given me to feel more welcomed on this website. if you like it here, feel free to subscribe to the newsletter <3
love love love you guys! byeeee~
Reply via email
subscribe to the newsletter so you never have to miss a post ᯓ★]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crazygringo in "Google Meet rolls out multi-device adaptive audio merging"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40484206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40484206"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T18:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just want to say that this is really actually kind of mind-blowing from an audio engineering perspective.
Outputting audio from multiple laptops in the same room is easy. Perfectly syncing it is harder. Implementing echo cancellation across all of that is quite a bit trickier than regular single-device echo cancellation.
But then treating all the laptop microphones as a kind of microphone array, having to deal with sync issues and phase issues and background noise issues... that's hard core.
Kudos to the engineering team on this one. This is actually pretty amazing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crazygringo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pclmulqdq in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482505</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482505"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T14:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as I can tell, the issue with this is:
OP runs a casino/gambling site.  Gambling is a regulatory mess (I have spent far too long dealing with this as an RNG supplier), and so it's very hard to comply with every jurisdiction, and each one needs you to prove compliance to operate in that jurisdiction.*  Gaming companies spend a lot on compliance and tracking, but since the internet is the internet, it's pretty hard to enforce perfectly, so some countries and ISPs take this into their own hands.
Due to that, IPs hosting gambling and gaming sites often get regionally blocked by internet providers or otherwise flagged as hosting illegal content.  Those regional blocks consequently affect the reputation score of the IP, and if you are a traffic aggregator like Cloudflare, can cause other customers to have issues.  One of the most aggressive and annoying regulatory environments for gambling companies is the US, so it's very possible Cloudflare has had some trouble due to gambling use of their IPs in states in the USA.
Cloudflare wanted them to use the BYOIP features of the enterprise plan, and did not want them on Cloudflare's IPs. The solution was to aggressively sell the Enterprise plan, and in a stunning failure of corporate communication, not tell the customer what the problem was at all.  The message from Cloudflare should have been "Enterprise plan + BYOIP or ban, and maybe we'll work with you on price" but it was instead "you would really like the Enterprise plan."
*As an aside - we're lucky in that respect being a tech supplier with relatively uniform rules, but our customers (the gaming companies) get the short end of the stick here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pclmulqdq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jrochkind1 in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482106</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482106"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been hearing stories from developers/entrepeneurs about Cloudflare being very weird to deal with:
"We'd like to talk to you about an enterprise plan."
"No thanks, I'm fine with the free plan."
"Based on your traffic, we'd like to talk to you about an enteprrise plan."
"Is there a traffic limit on the free plan?"
"No, there is no limit. But based on your traffic, we require you to get an enteprirse plan."
[Gives up and gets an enterprise plan]
[6 months later]
"Based on your traffic, we'd like to talk to you about up'ing your enteprise plan to a new monthly pay."
"Is there a cap to traffic in our current plan? I don't see that in our terms."
"No, there is no cap to traffic in cloudflare plans, but based on your traffic, we're going to require you to pay more per month than you are currently paying."
"OK, can you tell me the traffic limit in our current or new plan? So I know what I'm paying for and when I'm approaching it?"
"No. But you need to pay more."
[Wash, rinse, repeat, every 6-12 months]
It seems like while cloudflare technically does not charge for egress, in fact for large egress it's just a game of chicken between the customer and a salesperson every 6-12 months, with the salesperson trying to figure out the most they can manage to get without losing the customer? I mean, I guess that is standard for enteprise sales, but I think usually you at least have some terms to know what you've got for how long without a renegotiation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jrochkind1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unbearable lightness of a simple photoblog]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T12:06:45.108Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love having collection of photos I like on the internet. I can access them whenever I want. Yet, I do not really like instagram.
Although I have it, mostly I use it to interact and stay in contact with my friends. Because, for most people, staying in contact via instagram is the norm. It is not the norm for me but I do not really have power as one person.
But it does not mean that I can not have my own taste of photo blog.
Luckily I've found a very nice photoblog generator on Github made by Anders Jensen-Urstad. He is such a nice guy that he even helped me, via email, by answering my questions about how to set the generator up because I couldn't get something rights at first.
It is just exactly what I wanted. Lightweight, super fast, no tracking, privacy friendly and content-first approach. So I just went right away and built my own. Once you open it, you will see the latest uploaded photo. At the bottom navigation, there are older, newer, home, archive and contact buttons.
Right now it is only on Github page because I still could not decide a name for the blog, which domain and hosting service to use. I'm still looking for a privacy friendly, reliable service. Once I decide these, I will have proper domain name later.
I found some services from this list on PrivacyTools.io. Apart from these, I found Porkbun, Mythic Beasts, Nixi Host and Nearly Free Spech. I will need to dig these up and see the best one. (I'm addicted to the act of researching these kind of things :') )
If you have any suggestions of domain and hosting service, I really appreciate it. I want to use the domain for my Bearblog blog in the future, too.
For now, it is what it is.   ¯\( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)/¯
Here is one of the songs I listened to while writing this post]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/26/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-26-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T10:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘To Be America’s Friend Is Fatal’: A Current Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272203</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/to-be-americas-friend-is-fatal-a-current-overview.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T10:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, to be America’s enemy is largely beneficial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in negotiation: Re-positioning public health in the Pandemic Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T09:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021 during the Covid-19 pandemic, the WHO World Health Assembly established an international body to negotiate a convention, agreement, or other international instrument to strengthen pandemic prevention, preparedness, and response. The negotiations have been difficult. Furthermore, the focus on public health in the Pandemic Agreement remains fragile before the World Health Assembly starting on the 27th of May 2024. 
English

/ 
Health, 
WHO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abbe Brown, Alison McCallum, Amitabha Sarkar, Chloe Stephenson, Corrado Piroddi, Lynda Gilby, Meri Koivusalo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clues From Bird Flu’s Ground Zero on Dairy Farms in the Texas Panhandle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272199</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/clues-from-bird-flus-ground-zero-on-dairy-farms-in-the-texas-panhandle.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T09:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failures is the US response to the bird flu outbreak are piling up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Kilmainham Gaol]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52720</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/26/sunday-photoblogging-kilmainham-gaol/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T07:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism Attacks Argentine Workers and You May be Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322913</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/26/capitalism-attacks-argentine-workers-and-you-may-be-next/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T06:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Marcel Strauß.
As always when a representative of the right wing tells you he or she is campaigning to bring “freedom,” be afraid. Very afraid. For “freedom” in these cases means freedom for the richest financiers and industrialists to do whatever they want.
For them, “Freedom” is for capital, not for human beings without capital to invest. Today’s exhibit is the offensive against working people that is taking place in Argentina, where the new extreme right president, Javier Milei, is determined to see how far capitalist ideology can be pushed. So far, Argentines have pushed back but Milei, cheered on by domestic and international big business leaders, is nothing if not determined to ram through his austerity packages. And he has shown no inclination to allow mere democracy to stand in his way.
Nonetheless, there is no surprise here. President Milei ran on a program of extreme austerity, brandishing a chainsaw at his election rallies. Unfortunately, enough Argentines bought his siren songs, or were desperate enough to try anything given the country’s punishing inflation, to elect him, ending a one-term period in executive office by the ordinarily dominant Peronists. Alas, doing something new for the sake of doing something new, when it is aimed at you, rarely works. And here there is actually nothing new. President Milei simply promoted standard hard right ideology, albeit promoting it with unusual vigor. Snake oil is snake oil, as Argentine working people are already finding out.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Capitalism Attacks Argentine Workers and You May be Next appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Dolack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaming Soros for Campus Protests is Anti-Semitic — Just Ask Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323613</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/26/blaming-soros-for-campus-protests-is-anti-semitic-just-ask-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Ed Rampell.
From The New York Post to The Wall Street Journal, right-wing pundits have lined up to malign students across the United States who have rightfully criticized their schools for supporting the ongoing Israeli genocide in Gaza. As the genocide continues to unfold — claiming the lives of 35,562 Palestinians, including 15,000 children, according to Al Jazeera at the time of this writing — students, faculty and staff have brought overdue scrutiny to the complicity of their universities, whose endowments are altogether valued at more than $839 billion per the National Association of College and University Business Officers and invested extensively in the Israeli economy, including weapons manufacturers profiting directly from Palestinian death. Rather than accept that students oppose their tuition dollars being spent to kill Palestinians, right-wing pundits have instead accused them of being “paid protesters” in the employ of philanthropist George Soros.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Blaming Soros for Campus Protests is Anti-Semitic — Just Ask Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudan Portrait – Kordofan (1985)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323797</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/26/sudan-portrait-kordofan-1985/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T04:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of displacement and climate crisis almost no one is talking about Sudan. Sudan, according to the United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs (UNCHA), “is now today world’s largest displacement crisis: Almost 9 million people – 9 million people – have been forced to flee to other parts of Sudan or  More
The post Sudan Portrait – Kordofan (1985) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Cantarow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atum47 in "Helen Keller on her life before self-consciousness (1908)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40479185</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40479185"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T01:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This reminded me of a story my professor once told us back in college. I was studying sign language and she is deaf. She told us growing up in the old days they didn't had specialized schools for deaf people (since they could read?!) so she attended regular school and was not doing ok. She struggled a lot until she finally got the attention that she needed from a teacher who was able to instruct her in sign language (which believe you or not is Brazil's second official language). Before that she told us she was not able to have complex thoughts. She didn't know her father had a name, for instance. She thought his "name" was daddy. She is a brilliant woman and I'm glad I attended her class and also, that she was able to find someone who helped her, growing up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atum47</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dataflow in "Why is x & -x equal to the largest power of 2 that divides x?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40478558</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40478558"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T23:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Short explanation:
1. The largest power of 2 that divides x is just 2^(number of trailing zeros in x)
2. Crucial observation: -x == ~x + 1
3. ~x flips all the bits of x bits, so none of the bits of ~x match those of x. (i.e. (x & ~x) == 0)
4. When you do +1, all the trailing 1's flip AGAIN, becoming zero like they were in x. The next highest 0 (say it was the n'th) also flips, becoming 1... like it was in x.
5. Crucial observation: The n'th 0 did NOT match the corresponding bit in x prior to the increment, therefore it MUST match after the increment. All higher bits stay as-is.
6. This leaves only the n'th bits matching in x and ~x + 1, isolating the highest power-of-2 divisor of x when you AND them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dataflow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zogrodea in "Google scrambles to manually remove weird AI answers in search"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40477060</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40477060"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T18:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This approach to remove bad search suggestions manually reminded of a different approach Google once took, where they weren’t satisfied with manually tweaking search results but rather wanted to tweak the algorithm that produces these results when there were bad results.
'Around 2002, a team was testing a subset of search limited to products, called Froogle. But one problem was so glaring that the team wasn't comfortable releasing Froogle: when the query "running shoes" was typed in, the top result was a garden gnome sculpture that happened to be wearing sneakers. Every day engineers would try to tweak the algorithm so that it would be able to distinguish between lawn art and footwear, but the gnome kept its top position. One day, seemingly miraculously, the gnome disappeared from the results. At a meeting, no one on the team claimed credit. Then an engineer arrived late, holding an elf with running shoes. He had bought the one-of-a kind product from the vendor, and since it was no longer for sale, it was no longer in the index. "The algorithm was now returning the right results," says a Google engineer. "We didn't cheat, we didn't change anything, and we launched."'
https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=14009245]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zogrodea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do the work]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T18:43:27.312Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of well-meaning advice on the internet, including this blog. Gives you some new insights. Maybe some insights you knew and had to relearn. It makes you feel good. And you move on to the next advice without ever implementing it. I know, I have been there.
Just do the work is probably another advice people will read, feel good about, and move on. But as a recovering productivity addict, I have to say this - 'Stop reading all kinds of cool things about how to do great work, feel good about yourself for a few days or hours, and not change a single thing in your life'.
There is a lot of alpha in just doing the work. If you are not doing the work. JUST DO THE WORK. All the nifty tricks and mental models and whatnot are just icing on the cake. They are supposed to make the 'Just do the work' part easier with time. But you gotta get started.
Start in a dumb inefficient way but start. You are better than the guy reading about all this and not doing anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelnos in "Tmux is worse-is-better"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476695</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476695"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like "parsing each keystroke twice" is pretty low on the list of things that wastes CPU cycles and drains my laptop battery. I cannot at all get worked up over this, getting to the point I'd pull out the word "poison" to describe it.
It's nice that Kitty does most of what tmux does built in, but as the author points out, that's not really all that helpful for anyone who does any work over ssh.
And to me, bundling all that into a terminal emulator is bloat. Terminals should be terminals. If I want a multiplexer on top of that, I will... use a multiplexer on top of that.
I am potentially sympathetic to the idea that tmux and screen make it harder for terminal developers to add new features to their terminals. I don't really know enough about the issues involved to form an opinion. But from the perspective of a regular user, I do not want a multiplexer in my terminal app. When I need one, I prefer to reach for an app-agnostic multiplexer like tmux or screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelnos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by j2kun in "Tmux is worse-is-better"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476638</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476638"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T17:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> remote persistence
This is the real reason I actually need tmux. I often lose connection to a server for various reasons and don't want to lose my vim session or whatever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>j2kun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lukev in "Google scrambles to manually remove weird AI answers in search"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476299</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40476299"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T17:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like there's some semantic slippage around the meaning of the word "accuracy" here.
I grant you, my print Encyclopedia Britannica is not 100% accurate. But the difference between it and a LLM is not just a matter of degree: there's a "chain of custody" to  information that just isn't there with a LLM.
Philosophers have a working definition of knowledge as being (at least†) "justified true belief."
Even if a LLM is right most of the time and yields "true belief", it's not justified belief and therefore cannot yield knowledge at all.
Knowledge is Google's raison d'etre and they have no business using it unless they can solve or work around this problem.
† Yes, I know about the Gettier problem, but is not relevant to the point I'm making here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lukev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Strikes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323713</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/25/three-strikes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T14:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was the week of rebukes for Israel: On Monday, the ICC requested arrest warrants for Netanyahu and Gallant, on Wednesday three European nations, Ireland, Spain and Norway, recognized Palestinian statehood and on Friday the ICJ ordered Israel to halt its military operations in Rafah, open the border crossings for humanitarian aid and allow international investigators into Gaza. Has the international community finally run out of patience with Israeli intransigence? 
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Three Strikes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/25/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272122</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-25-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T10:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bouncy daily links: child artist, ICJ v. Israel Rafah offensive, Covid causing heart disease rise? Germany depends on Chinese arms, UK snap elections, Macron New Caledonia failing, Trump underwhelming Bronx rally, voters reject Biden econ happy talk, childbirth/abortion debate, moar social media censorship]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Headlines 2 Weeks Ago, Labor Market “Suddenly” Weakens as Unemployment Claims “Spike”: It Just Got Unwound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272171</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/remember-headlines-2-weeks-ago-labor-market-suddenly-weakens-as-unemployment-claims-spike-it-just-got-unwound.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T07:38:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wee unpacking of unemployment data to show how Fed rate cut cheerleaders are still ahead of themselves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Remains Painfully Dependent on China for Silicon and Solar Panels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272168</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/u-s-remains-painfully-dependent-on-china-for-silicon-and-solar-panels.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T06:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another own goal in the US economic war against China. We chose to make ourselves dependent and don't like where we are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics anon?]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T06:39:49.586Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics enough before indulging in optimization
hacks? Don't tell me you are already watching videos on how to do xyz thing fast instead of focusing on basics.
First step of optimization should be to profile if you are milking the basics enough or not.
Leveling up in anything boils down to a few simple processes. I repeat simple but hard to execute - doing minimum viable research to get started, understanding the basics, doing the thing and focusing.
Minimum viable research - finding the correct resources, enough to get started with, finding a mentor or a teacher. The emphasis is to get enough to get started. This is pretty easy especially for knowledge work given we have internet and chatgpt. The basics are more or less similar across most resources plus as you progress…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Should Stop Attacking the International Criminal Court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Biden-Should-Stop-Attacking-the-International-Criminal-Court</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Biden-Should-Stop-Attacking-the-International-Criminal-Court"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T05:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ICC seeking arrest warrants for Israeli leaders is a major step forward for international law. US officials' attacks on the ICC are a major step backward for US global standing. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Palestine, 
Israel, 
Human Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Branko Marcetic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on friendships as a 20-something]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/on-friendships-as-a-20-something/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/on-friendships-as-a-20-something/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T03:51:39.699Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in college. I've been in college for one year now, after taking a gap year + I-don't-think-I'm-gonna-do-college year. I got incredibly lucky in my spring semester of last year, my first semester of college as a whole, to have very nice professors and cool classmates. I especially lucked out with my public speaking class, in which I made two new friends. we haven't had any more classes together since, but we still hang out at least once or twice a month.
it's funny because the first friend I made was because she heard me say my birthday and her birthday is the day after mine. we then exclaimed, chatted a bit more about what we have in common, and we figured out that her brother is dating one of my friends from high school.
the second friend came about because she started talking to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dkga in "ICQ will stop working from June 26"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40471106</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40471106"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T22:35:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will forever treasure my ICQ memories.
The sounds it made. The moving image when it was connecting. Listening in Winamp to one of only a few dozen possible songs that I had carefully downloaded.
Being able to randomly connect to people you would filter. Yes, I want to talk to someone more or less my age but in Iceland. Or any other country.
But most of all, the feeling of being connected. As a teenager in the autism spectrum, that was one of the best feelings I had at that time.
Most people don’t get it when I say this, maybe someone here will, but to me it all started going downhill when people all of a sudden switched to a worse alternative, MSN. I see a direct line from there to the annoying easy-to-accept-while-hard-to-reject-but-always-there-anyway cookie pop-ups.
And no, this is isn’t some form of Ostalgie where we long for past days of hardship with tender feelings. ICQ just had a great user experience as far as I am concerned and to this day I prefer it to existing alternatives from WhatsApp to Webex chat (don’t mention Teams please, I’m having a poetic moment). It was rather a feeling that perhaps other Brazilians will share: a longing, saudade, for the simpler (yes) but better and more poetic 90s, when ICQ connected you to a world that watched Brazil win the fourth World Cup, Ayrton Senna was inspiring generations to be healthier and their better selves and Mamonas Assassinas could only make us laugh, not cry…
So long, ICQ. You will always be part of why I love the internet.
PS: I realize the timing of those events doesn’t necessarily align. But sentimentally they do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dkga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snewman in "Sharing details on a recent incident impacting one of our customers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40470453</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40470453"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the level of impact that this incident caused, I am surprised that the remediations did not go deeper. They ensured that the same problem could not happen again in the same way, but that's all. So some equivalent glitch somewhere down the road could lead to a similar result (or worse; not all customers might have the same "robust and resilient architectural approach to managing risk of outage or failure").
Examples of things they could have done to systematically guard against inappropriate service termination / deletion in the future:
1. When terminating a service, temporarily place it in a state where the service is unavailable but all data is retained and can be restored at the push of a button. Discard the data after a few days. This provides an opportunity for the customer to report the problem.
2. Audit all deletion workflows for all services (they only mention having reviewed GCVE). Ensure that customers are notified in advance whenever any service is terminated, even if "the deletion was triggered as a result of a parameter being left blank by Google operators using the internal tool".
3. Add manual review for any termination of a service that is in active use, above a certain size.
Absent these broader measures, I don't find this postmortem to be in the slightest bit reassuring. Given the are-you-f*ing-kidding-me nature of the incident, I would have expected any sensible provider who takes the slightest pride in their service, or even is merely interested in protecting their reputation, to visibly go over the top in ensuring nothing like this could happen again. Instead, they've done the bare minimum. That says something bad about the culture at Google Cloud.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snewman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by flourpower471 in "Financial Statement Analysis with Large Language Models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40468991</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40468991"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not to mention, as somebody who works in quant trading doing ml all day on this kind of data. That ann benchmark is nowhere near state of the art.
People didn't stop working on this in 1989 - they realised they can make lots of money doing it and do it privately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>flourpower471</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by antimatter15 in "Financial Statement Analysis with Large Language Models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40468878</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40468878"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:10:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figure 3 on p.40 of the paper seems to show that their LLM based model does not statistically significantly outperform a 3 layer neural network using 59 variables from 1989.
  This figure compares the prediction performance of GPT and quantitative models based on machine learning. Stepwise Logistic follows Ou and Penman (1989)’s structure with their 59 financial predictors. ANN is a three-layer artificial neural network model using the same set of variables as in Ou and Penman (1989). GPT (with CoT) provides the model with financial statement information and detailed chain-of-thought prompts. We report average accuracy (the percentage of correct predictions out of total predictions) for each method (left) and F1 score (right). We obtain bootstrapped standard errors by randomly sampling 1,000 observations 1,000 times and include 95% confidence intervals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>antimatter15</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/24/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272149</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics, the Bragg trial winds down. imperceptible skin sensors, Hokusai's  Great Wave ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hazeldine: &ldquo;Favoured Nation&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/favoured-nation</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/favoured-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T17:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate America’s Anglophilia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized for low-latency workloads, Mistral Small now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>e0a304814f47b02fee302f211161315a528a747f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/optimized-for-low-latency-workloads-mistral-small-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral Small, an efficient large language model, joins Amazon Bedrock's lineup, excelling in low-latency tasks, multilingual support, and coding prowess while maintaining cost-effectiveness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jedberg in "ICQ will stop working from June 26"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40467689</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40467689"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This makes me sad.  I mean, I haven't logged in in about 20 years now, and couldn't if I wanted to (don't have the password or access to the email address).
But I had a low five digit user number, and built a lot of relationships on ICQ (some of which continue today!).  It was my main method of electronic communication in college. I had romantic relationships live and die on ICQ.
Another reminder of how things change over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jedberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Egoless Convictions]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/egoless-convictions/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/egoless-convictions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:06:28.998Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Convictions are important in life. If you don't have strong convictions you will find yourself going wherever the next opinionated and charismatic person you meet points you.  But it is important to choose them wisely.
What if your conviction is that penguins can fly, they only need the right motivation? So you spend your life trying to give motivational speeches to penguins. Hoping one of them will fly. You will even meet people with similarly strong convictions. Form a strong community. Make derogatory memes about the 'others' who believe in things like the 'scientific method' and so on.
And your ego attaches itself tightly to your penguin motivator persona. So anyone trying to challenge you is attacking you and your community. So you viciously attack this person back. Congratulations. You are now in a toxic pointless echo chamber.
The only solution is selecting convictions using first principles. Employ the scientific method. Be open to being challenged as long as the challenge comes through solid first principles thinking as well. All the while keeping the ego in check.
So in essence develop an egoless conviction. Be open to being challenged. Don't end up in pointless toxic echo chambers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by HL33tibCe7 in "Don't microservice, do module"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40466243</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40466243"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:47:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I’ve grown older I have developed a heuristic, which is that people who talk/write like this, i.e. being completely convinced that one way of doing things is always wrong and one way of doing things is always right, and that people doing things the other way are just ignorant/stupid/wrong, usually have no idea what they are talking about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HL33tibCe7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/24/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our sporty daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SouthCom Commander Laura Richardson Just Described “Plan Colombia” As A Success, A Model for the Region]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272099</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/southcom-commander-laura-richardson-just-described-plan-colombia-as-roaring-success-a-model-for-region.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even the US House of Representatives Foreign Affairs Committee has admitted that Plan Colombia was a resounding failure from a counter-narcotics perspective while providing short-term benefits from a counter-insurgency perspective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Grid Wants to Heat More Homes With Converted Food Waste — and Make You Pay For It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272124</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/national-grid-wants-to-heat-more-homes-with-converted-food-waste-and-make-you-pay-for-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Grid's biogas plant is performing poorly, as shown by downtimes and methane flaring, yet it wants more consumer subsidies to expand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my favorite restaurant closed]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/my-favorite-restaurant-closed/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/my-favorite-restaurant-closed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T07:45:34.975Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm watching the bear and sydney said something along the lines of "it's hard to work in a restaurant and not lose your mind."
when you have a neighborhood place, somewhere that's been a cornerstone of your community, it is like heartbreak to see it close. The Press in Claremont, California is, and has, been my favorite restaurant for years. it's where my family would go to eat before I was born, where my teenage cousin revealed to them that she was pregnant with my cousins, where my parents would go on date nights before I came around. and now it's gone.
they closed it in 2020 with lockdown, and their website has said they were coming back soon for months, for years. I'm watching the bear
and sydney's risotto is a dish they would've had as a special and I'm thinking of them. I'm thinking …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cookiengineer in "Daylight Computer – New 60fps e-paper tablet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40463380</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40463380"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is really a nice product, but I won't order it unless SolOS and its firmware and drivers are open sourced.
I've probably spent far more than 8000 bucks over the years for devices like this, only to have to throw them away eventually because their software got abandoned and they've been so proprietary that they can only function as an expensive brick on the shelf.
If the software is closed source, I'd recommend everyone to stay away from any product like this. It is a deal breaker for me now, and it took a lot of cash and hype to realize it.
Products like this are not a mainstream product, which makes them high risk for their investors. And you have to minimize risk by demanding open source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cookiengineer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set the Killers Free: the Pardoning of Daniel Perry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323471</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/set-the-killers-free-the-pardoning-of-daniel-perry/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one of the most egregious uses of the pardon power since Bill Clinton freed billionaire tax cheat, Israeli agent and international fugitive Marc Rich as the clock struck midnight on his lamentable administration, last week Texas Gov. Greg Abbott freed an avowed racist who ran a red light, before plunging his car into a crowd of protesters and fatally shooting a man who was trying to protect people from being run over. Abbott granted the killer a pardon, even though the gunman had been obsessed for months with the idea of killing BLM activists. More
The post Set the Killers Free: the Pardoning of Daniel Perry appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s Mouthpiece for Israel: David Ignatius]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-washington-posts-mouthpiece-for-israel-david-ignatius/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s David Ignatius has always been an apologist for the Central Intelligence Agency; then he added the Pentagon to his list for institutional apologies.  But now Ignatius is going much further; he has become the mouthpiece for both the administrations of President Joe Biden and Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu.  His most recent editorial (“The U.S. is assembling the pieces of a Gaza war endgame”) foresees the “contours of a possible exit ramp” in Gaza that is constructed out of sheer fantasy. More
The post The Washington Post’s Mouthpiece for Israel: David Ignatius appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Tested Nukes on Its Own People. It’s Time to Apologize and Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323539</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-u-s-tested-nukes-on-its-own-people-its-time-to-apologize-and-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tina Cordova is intimately familiar with the legacy of the atomic bomb. Her hometown, Tularosa, New Mexico, is just thirty-four miles downwind from the Trinity Test Site, where Manhattan Project scientists first detonated what they called “the Gadget.” When both of her great-grandfathers, who were in Tularosa during the blast, succumbed to stomach cancer ten years later, it was just the beginning of her family’s troubles. More
The post The U.S. Tested Nukes on Its Own People. It’s Time to Apologize and Pay appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing University: How the California State University Became Complicit in Palestinian Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323614</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/boeing-university-how-the-california-state-university-became-complicit-in-palestinian-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Over the years, Boeing and its employees have played a vital role in the advancement of Cal State Long Beach.” Jane Close Conoley, President, California State University, Long Beach Pro-Palestinian student protests and encampments have bloomed this spring across U.S. universities. Unsurprisingly, campus administrators have responded with calls for civility and peace — that is,  More
The post Boeing University: How the California State University Became Complicit in Palestinian Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JAKE ALIMAHOMED-WILSON, SABRINA ALIMAHOMED-WILSON, ARACELI ESPARZA, STEVEN OSUNA, DENNIS LÓPEZ AND AZZA BASARUDIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Lahore, With Love: Musings of a Traveling Feminista, From Pakistan to Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323581</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/to-lahore-with-love-musings-of-a-traveling-feminista-from-pakistan-to-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So many trips back and forth from the US to Pakistan ever since I "left" Lahore on Sep 12th, 1979. My 21st birthday. I was off to conquer the world, become the free and independent woman I had always dreamt of being, away from the strictures of desi patriarchy- or so I imagined. So many tearful and joyful reunions, departures, and arrivals over four and a half decades that now appear to have passed in the blink of an eye. More
The post To Lahore, With Love: Musings of a Traveling Feminista, From Pakistan to Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fawzia Afzal-Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Three Penny Media Opera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323616</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/trumps-three-penny-media-opera/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has to be some irony that as Donald Trump sits in the dock in lower Manhattan, on charges of cooking his corporate books for $130,000 after paying off a porn star (only the flag-waving Supreme Court would let him walk), while slightly to the west, on Wall Street, the same grifter (here as the  More
The post Trump’s Three Penny Media Opera appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Indicted Congressman’s Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323491</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-indicted-congressmans-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-deserved indictments keep hitting Congress. The latest indicted legislator is Texas Democrat Henry Cuellar, the politician backed by former House speaker Nancy Pelosi in his last election, against a more progressive opponent, of course. On May 3, the justice department charged Cuellar with accepting roughly $600,000 from Azerbaijan’s state-owned oil company and a Mexican bank.  More
The post The Indicted Congressman’s Club appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Above the Law? Israel, Hamas and the ICC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323514</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/whos-above-the-law-israel-hamas-and-the-icc/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While statements that “No one is above the law,” are repeated in the U.S. over the trials of former President Donald Trump, can the same be said internationally? By analogy, Chief Prosecutor Karim Khan of the International Criminal Court (ICC) said yes when he announced he was seeking arrest warrants for Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on charges of war crimes and crimes against humanity. More
The post Who’s Above the Law? Israel, Hamas and the ICC appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constant Killing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323600</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/constant-killing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are constants in this world — occurrences you can count on. Sunrises and sunsets. The tides. That, day by day, people will be born and others will die. Some of them will die in peace, but others, of course, in violence and agony. For hundreds of years, the U.S. military has been killing people.  More
The post Constant Killing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Turse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Western Sahara: Visiting a Forgotten People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323637</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/at-western-sahara-visiting-a-forgotten-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South of the Algerian town of Tindouf on the border with Western Sahara are five refugee camps. The camps are home to the Sahrawi people of Western Sahara and are administered by their freedom movement Polisario, which is fighting to liberate their homeland from Morocco. Life in the desert camps leaves a deep impression and  More
The post At Western Sahara: Visiting a Forgotten People appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc B. Sanganee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nakba Resurrected – How the Gaza Resistance Ended Segmentation of Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323602</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/nakba-resurrected-how-the-gaza-resistance-ended-segmentation-of-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inadvertently, Israel has pressed the reset button on its war with the Palestinian people, taking back the so-called conflict to square one. Save for a few self-serving Palestinian officials affiliated with the Palestinian Authority (PA), most Palestinians do not seem consumed with the return to the peace process, or even engaged in discussions about two-state  More
The post Nakba Resurrected – How the Gaza Resistance Ended Segmentation of Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Rainforest Collapse?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323589</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/amazon-rainforest-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A major question is whether a large-scale collapse of the Amazon forest system could actually happen within the twenty-first century.” (Source: Bernardo M. Flores, et al, Critical Transitions in the Amazon Forest System, Nature, Feb. 14, 2024). It may seem absurd to consider collapse of the Amazon rainforest (65-million-years-old) which seems impossible, too far out,  More
The post Amazon Rainforest Collapse? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifting the Veil: Demystifying Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323631</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/lifting-the-veil-demystifying-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel has, for decades, created many versions of itself—Israel in politics, in history, in the United States, in books, in movies and on television.  The real Israel, however, has been shrouded behind a veil of deception.  After 7 October 2023, the undisguised coarse Israel has revealed itself.   For years, Israel has made sure that Palestine, with its  More
The post Lifting the Veil: Demystifying Israel  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Misplaced Purity: Democracies and Crimes Against International Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323639</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/a-misplaced-purity-democracies-and-crimes-against-international-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The application for arrest warrants by the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court, Karim A.A. Khan in the Israel-Hamas War gives us a chance to revisit a recurring theme in the commission of crimes in international humanitarian law.  Certain states, so this logic goes, either commit no crimes, or, if they do, have good reasons for doing so,  More
The post A Misplaced Purity: Democracies and Crimes Against International Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War Cuts the Heart Out of Humankind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323634</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/war-cuts-the-heart-out-of-humankind/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the apartment of my friends in Baghdad (Iraq), they tell me about how each of them had been impacted by the ugliness of the 2003 U.S.-imposed illegal war on their country. Yusuf and Anisa are both members of the Federation of Journalists of Iraq and both have experience as “stringers” for Western media companies  More
The post War Cuts the Heart Out of Humankind appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where, Now, the Big Dream? An Amen for Ambivalence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323642</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/where-now-the-big-dream-an-amen-for-ambivalence/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No symbolic system [i.e., basis for culture] in history has been able to rival religious faith, which forges a bond between the routine behavior… of individuals and ultimate, imperishable truths.  It’s the most enduring, deep-rooted universal form of popular culture that history has ever witnessed….            – Terry Eagleton, Where Does Culture Come from? London Monthly Review 4/25/24  More
The post Where, Now, the Big Dream? An Amen for Ambivalence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of an Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323488</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-future-of-an-illusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Eastern race well versed in Western culture and profoundly in sympathy with Western ideals will be established in the Orient. Furthermore, a Jewish state will inevitably fall under the control of American Jews who will work out, along Jewish lines, American ideals and American civilization. —William Yale, US State Department consultant, 1919 Unrelenting mass  More
The post The Future of an Illusion appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iain Boal, T.J. Clark, Joseph Matthews, and Michael Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memoriam: H. Bruce Franklin (1934-2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323586</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/in-memoriam-h-bruce-franklin-1934-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American cultural historian called the creation of the US Space Force an “open declaration of our national insanity.” This CounterPunch feature, in honor of Professor Franklin who passed away on May 19, 2024, is from a previous discussion with him in 2018 and found in Foreign Policy Journal. Bruce Franklin is a US academic who specializes in  More
The post In Memoriam: H. Bruce Franklin (1934-2024) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Myths Regarding the Genesis of Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/some-myths-regarding-the-genesis-of-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a colloquium on early entrepreneurs had been convened in the early 20th century, most participants would have viewed traders as operating on their own, bartering at prices that settled at a market equilibrium established spontaneously in response to fluctuating supply and demand. According to the Austrian economist Carl Menger, money emerged as individuals and  More
The post Some Myths Regarding the Genesis of Enterprise appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Labor Today and the Way Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323583</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/us-labor-today-and-the-way-forward/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The labor movement in the United States used to be respected and looked to for leadership; people cared about what positions labor took, watched when they mobilized, and noticed the causes they supported.  This was especially true among the left. Today, for most of the country, crickets.  Including much of the left.  And yet, labor  More
The post US Labor Today and the Way Forward appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Scipes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bach and the Beasts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323685</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/323685/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not until the last of the eight episodes of Ripley, which dropped in April on Netflix, that Bach’s music makes an appearance. I’d been expecting it, and not just any piece from among the one-thousand-plus numbers in the Baroque master’s catalog. It had to be the Goldberg Variations. One of Bach’s most celebrated  More
The post Bach and the Beasts appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ten Ways to Soften a Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323625</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/top-ten-ways-to-soften-a-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Gen·o·cide: the deliberate killing of a large number of people from a particular nation or ethnic group with the aim of destroying that nation or group.” -Oxford Dictionary “Now we all have one common goal— erasing the Gaza Strip from the face of the earth.” — Nissim Vaturi, Deputy Speaker of the Knesset [Israeli parliament].  More
The post Top Ten Ways to Soften a Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamus Cooke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of Violent Retribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323653</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/fear-of-violent-retribution/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bit of recent history seems worth recalling as the nation careens towards an election that seems somewhat likely to put a man Noam Chomsky once rightly called “the most dangerous criminal in human history” back in the world’s most powerful office. It’s quite possible that the fascist monster Donald “Take Down the Metal Detectors” Trump would  More
The post Fear of Violent Retribution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024: People Starve As The Rich Get Richer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323622</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/2024-people-starve-as-the-rich-get-richer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earning enough to pay the rent or mortgage, cover utility bills and travel costs, buy food and have the occasional coffee is impossible for many. But its not hard for everyone, is it; there are a small number of people living among us who don’t have to worry about the bills, are not troubled when  More
The post 2024: People Starve As The Rich Get Richer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Peebles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radical Feminism and the Failures of the Left]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323644</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/radical-feminism-and-the-failures-of-the-left/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was politicized and radicalized fairly late in life, beginning at the age of 30 at the end of the 1980s, when I embraced left politics and radical feminism at the same time. Despite tensions between the two philosophies, I remain committed to both. Back to the ‘80s: Until then, I had been a fairly  More
The post Radical Feminism and the Failures of the Left appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve Got a Bigger Problem Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323678</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/weve-got-a-bigger-problem-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Living through the 1970s was like walking through a never-ending storm.  The cavalcade of world-changing events never seemed to end.  Trying to make sense of the maelstrom was a constant game of catching up and keeping pace.  This was true in politics, international affairs, culture and community.  The contradictions of the post-World War Two world  More
The post We’ve Got a Bigger Problem Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of the Mini Navals]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:08:26.314Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed a proliferation of a new essayist archetype on the internet in recent years - the "Mini Navals." Modeled after angel investor, entrepreneur, and philosopher Naval Ravikant, these mini me's desperately want to become the next big thought leader by aping Naval's pithy, maxim-filled style. Naval has achieved success through decades of experience, and he reflects on it. In contrast, Mini Navals try to compress "wisdom" into a handful of tweets and blog posts.
Most Mini Navals tend to be in their early-to-mid 20s, still figuring things out but portraying themselves as gurus who have life all figured out. They boldly proclaim hot takes on everything from tech trends to philosophy to politics, with little credibility to back it up other than having read Naval's entire archive. With the Mini Navals, it's usually just word salad dressed up as profundity.
Sometimes, the best philosophy is just living intentionally without needing to proselytize your process. In a world that could use more wisdom, perhaps we don't need so many more mini-versions when the original is still strong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Karpenter Nodes with Multus on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>66b95967b06e8c62395ccb2841f747f47b41fe13</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/deploying-karpenter-nodes-with-multus-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T04:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container based Telco workloads use Multus CNI primarily for traffic or network segmentation. Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) supports Multus CNI enabling users to attach multiple network interfaces, apply advanced network configuration and segmentation to Kubernetes-based applications running on AWS. One of the many benefits of running applications on AWS is resource elasticity (scaling out and scaling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rolando Jr Hilvano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Gossip]]></title>
        <id>https://erickrueger.com/good-gossip/</id>
        <link href="https://erickrueger.com/good-gossip/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⏲ 3-minute read | last updated {{ post_last_modified }} ago
Difficult to control and spreads quickly - but unlike fires, not always dangerous.(photo credit: sippakorn yamkasikorn)

Humans are social creatures, and we receive a lot of information about the world when we gossip - it isn't (necessarily) a bad thing.
Evolution
Gossip is in our blood. Humans who shared information among social circles had an evolutionary advantage. They were able to find those among the group they could trust, and (more importantly) identify bad actors. At the most basic level, gossip was a tool for survival. It answered important questions that helped the group function:
Who wields the most power/influence in the group? (alliances to make)
Who has limited resources? (alliances to avoid)
Whose sleeping with who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alemanek in "Daylight Computer – New 60fps e-paper tablet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40461262</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40461262"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T23:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding an additional comment here for a little extra visibility.  I would absolutely love, like really love, a USB-C portrait monitor version of this.  If I could just plug this in to my existing laptop and use it for reading specs, technical docs, …etc that would be amazing.
Android tablet is a tough sell for my employer due to compliance, security, and such.  So buying one of those for work use would take like a year minimum gathering all the necessary approvals and likely would still get denied by someone.  But, a dumb monitor with no real OS I can expense that without approval.  just a heads up to my boss really to say I am buying this and here is why.
I know you are a small company so have to pick your battles.  But, maybe something to consider down the road.
EDIt: forgot to say, congrats on the launch.  Looks like a great product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alemanek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy is dead, long live democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://tinavanschelt.com/democracy-is-dead-long-live-democracy/</id>
        <link href="https://tinavanschelt.com/democracy-is-dead-long-live-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:45:01.661Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past Saturday, my little family and I went to Den Haag to vote in the 2024 South African National Election. An experience that has stayed with me all week, eventually morphing into this post.
We arrived at the embassy at 11:00, expecting to be there no more than two hours. Truthfully, we really weren’t prepared for what awaited us.
A common joke (read truthism) among expats is that it’s incredibly easy to identify a South African embassy as it’s generally the only embassy with burglar bars, uncut grass and a queue outside. Walking through the doors of a South African embassy is like walking through a portal linked directly to The Department of Home Affairs in Bellville. It's quite a surreal experience actually.
The queue on Saturday was something else. It wrapped around several blocks…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jimmysong in "Daylight Computer – New 60fps e-paper tablet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40460251</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40460251"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As one of the beta testers, let me just say that I really like this device. It's very different than a kindle, kobo or reMarkable in that the refresh rate really makes a big difference. When I show this device to people, I show them how quickly zooming in on a PDF is. It's way faster and more responsive than any e-ink screen and it's way less addicting than the typical laptop, phone or tablet.
I'm attempting to make this device my main driver over the next few months and while the ecosystem isn't exactly mature yet, most android apps just work out of the box and I've found myself doing a lot more reading, either through an e-reading app (Lithium), PDF reader or Instapaper. I have X, Primal, Telegram and many other apps installed, but I don't go to them nearly as much. The device really is a lot more human centered and it makes for a much more intentional device.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jimmysong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telstra redundancies, AI robots come in, the future is now]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/telstra-redundancies-ai-robots-future-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s largest telecommunications company, Telstra, announced this week it was making about three thousand employees, or ten percent, of its workforce redundant. About three hundred people were sent home straightaway — hopefully with some sort of pay-out — while the remainder will depart between now and the end of the year. This is terrible news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build bases on the Moon, instead of going for a week]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7671</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/build-bases-moon-instead-going-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA is dead set keen to return to the Moon. But their current plan, called Artemis, is dead set crazy, writes Polish-American entrepreneur and writer, Maciej Cegłowski: You don’t have to be a rocket scientist to wonder what’s going on here. If we can put a man on the moon, then why can’t we just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ibejoeb in "Act on Press"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40459428</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40459428"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:20:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm sure there are many contexts in which this is a good idea.
For many others, though, I like to be able to press, move whatever pointing device I'm using from the hot zone, and release to cancel the action. It's like holding the chess piece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ibejoeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by voidwtf in "We're ending our Samsung collaboration"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458832</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458832"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T19:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My partner has a Samsung phone with the curved/wrap around edge screen. The screen is cracked. She's been trying to get it replaced for months, but none of the "Samsung approved" repair shops around here can get a screen. Apparently they have screens meant for the same phone in different colors, but do not have the screen for her phone color. Samsung WILL NOT allow them to use a screen from a different color of the same phone, despite being a working part. Samsung has provided no ETA when the part will be available. This is the kind of problem that shouldn't exist. Would love it if our legislators would tell manufacturers to shove it, and if they want to be the exclusive source for parts that the parts must be sold at some limited/reasonable profit percentage and if they're not available they should not be able to limit the availability or function of 3rd party parts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>voidwtf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexandrB in "Spotify is going to break every Car Thing gadget it ever sold"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458470</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458470"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T18:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Thank you for being on this journey with us, safe travels.
I miss the era when I was a customer paying for a product. Now I'm apparently some kind of traveller that's on a journey with dozens of companies as they try to find local maxima of profit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexandrB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Cu3PO42 in "iTerm2 removes AI feature from core, creates separate plugin"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458335</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40458335"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T18:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel really sorry for the developer. I've only been a casual observer, but from my view point the community's reaction was... not great, to put it lightly.
I get that a lot of us are tired of 'AI' being shoved down our throat at every possible turn. I get that a lot of us have privacy concerns. I get that maybe you don't want it in your terminal emulator.
But iTerm is a free (both as in gratis and as in libre) open source project. The developer released a feature that they were probably happy and excited about. It was off by default and didn't siphon data or do anything malicious. And a ton of reactions were as if iTerm had just added the devil incarnate or attacked people personally.
Disliking the feature is fine. Voicing your concerns and feedback is fine. But it should always be gracious and in good faith. I think this is a good change, if only to pacify the masses, and I applaud the developer for taking these steps, but I don't like how we got here.
EDIT: gnachman, if you're reading this, thank you for your tireless work on iTerm. It serves me extremely well whenever I'm on macOS and holds a special place in my heart. I bought a MacBook in 2013 and it was the first *nix system that I daily drove as a desktop for a long time. I installed iTerm  2 in my first week and it was a constant companion for many years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cu3PO42</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by boochiboo12 in "Daylight Computer – New 60fps e-paper tablet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40457491</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40457491"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T17:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi yall, founder of Daylight here.
Happy to answer any questions you have. Long time lurker, so this is pretty cool to finally take part :)
I made this because I wanted the eye-strain free and minimalist qualities of my kindle/Eink applied to so much more of what I do on a computer.
Lack of speed and ghosting felt like it made traditional Eink impossible to do most computing tasks. So we focused on making the most Paperlike epaper display that has no ghosting and high refresh rate - 60 to 120fps. We started working on this in 2018.
We developed our own custom epaper display tech we call LivePaper. We focused on solving the tradeoffs RLCDs traditionally have - around reflectance %, metallic-look / not Paperlike enough, viewing angle, white state, rainbow mura, parallax, resolution, size, lack of quality backlight, etc.
First proof of concept in late 2021, and then it took us 2.5 years to get it into production.
And we built a whole android tablet around it.
It’s essentially our attempt at making a remarkable tablet on steroids / kindle on steroids. Definitely some trade offs, but on the whole we think it’s worth it. (& on twitter a bunch of early customers seem to think so too)
Note: it’s 60fps epaper, not off the shelf Eink. We spent years developing what we think is the best epaper display in the world and it’s exclusively manufactured by our display factory in Japan.
There’s still many cases where traditional Eink is going to be better (bistability, viewing angle, white state color, etc), but we feel for more general purpose computers you can code on and do google docs on and do fast multitouch amongst a thousand other things, the speed and lack of ghosting totally makes it worth it.
Think of it as a Godzilla sized pebble watch with a decade of improvement
Or think of it as a gameboy advanced, advanced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>boochiboo12</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by elvis70 in "The Space Quest II Master Disk Blunder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456792</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456792"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T16:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Double Dragon II: The Revenge for DOS from 1989 was distributed on two floppy disks, one of which contained the entire source code in a deleted archive file, invisible from the DIR command but easily recoverable: https://tcrf.net/Double_Dragon_II:_The_Revenge_(DOS)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elvis70</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cuSetanta in "First pictures from Euclid satellite reveal billions of orphan stars"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456474</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456474"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T16:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Always a bit special to see science come from a spacecraft I had the pleasure of working on. Honestly there were a lot of issues during the build of Euclid that I was very glad to not be a part of, but seeing the images coming out of it now is pretty damn impressive.
Hope all of the engineers that struggled to get this mission spacebourne can enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cuSetanta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by HarHarVeryFunny in "OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456256</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40456256"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clearly an SJ voice was the goal, given that Altman asked her to do it, asked her a second time just two days before the ChatGPT-4o release, and then tweeted "her" on the release day. The next day Karpathy, recently ex-OpenAI, then tweets "The killer app of LLMs is Scarlett Johansson".
Altman appears to be an habitual liar. Note his recent claim not to be aware of the non-disparagement and claw-back terms he had departing employees agree to. Are we supposed to believe that the company lawyer or head of HR did this without consulting (or more likely being instructed by) the co-founder and CEO?!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HarHarVeryFunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmull in "OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40455846</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40455846"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, here are some things that aren't really being disputed:
* OpenAI wanted an AI voice that sounds like SJ
* SJ declined
* OpenAI got an AI voice that sounds like SJ anyway
I guess they want us to believe this happened without shenanigans, but it's bit hard to.
The headline of the article is a little funny, because records can't really show they weren't looking for an SJ sound-alike. They can just show that those records didn't mention it. The key decision-makers could simply have agreed to keep that fact close-to-the-vest -- they may have well understood that knocking off a high-profile actress was legally perilous.
Also, I think we can readily assume OpenAI understood that one of their potential voices sounded a lot like SJ. Since they were pursuing her they must have had a pretty good idea of what they were going after, especially considering the likely price tag. So even if an SJ voice wasn't the original goal, it clearly became an important goal to them. They surely listened to demos for many voice actors, auditioned a number of them, and may even have recorded many of them, but somehow they selected one for release who seemed to sound a lot like SJ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G7: Whether or not to maintain the suspension of Ukrainian debt payments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the G7 discussing Ukraine's debt? 
English

/ 
G7 / G20, 
Debt in Northern countries, 
Ukraine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[沈阳 photo dump（mostly 老北市）]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:19:59.869Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some photographs from the Chinese city of 沈阳 (Shenyang).

I could spend all day browsing these five-story malls. This one boasted restaurants, cafes, daycares, basketball courts, go-karting, and live fish.

Fine dining in 沈阳. These are the food models in the lobby. Outside the frame, my mom is fighting with my aunt and uncle-in-law first to pay the bill, and when she loses that battle, to order fewer items. Lots of 客气 to go around. 

Although it may look the part, those flowers are not lavender. You can't see it here, but the whole time we were in Shenyang it looked as though it were snowing. I later learned that the "snow" was actually the seed hairs of the willow and the poplar trees. It looks cool until the fuzz gets in your eyes, on your clothes, everywhere. (source)
老北市
A popular night market in 沈阳 which runs every night. If you're there at the right time, you can catch the show with flying drone-powered phoenixes shooting fireworks from their wings. Sadly I don't have any good photos of that show — my senses were overwhelmed for most of the night (in a good way).










Night markets have been ruined for me forever. How can anything measure up to that? Not to mention we passed two markets en route to 老北市 that also looked better than anything I'd ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by notRobot in "DuckDuckGo was down"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40454004</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40454004"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T12:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interesting how they insist that they use "so much more" than just Bing for their results, but the moment Bing goes down their search functionality is down entirely, unable to show a single result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>notRobot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by npteljes in "DuckDuckGo was down"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40453897</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40453897"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T12:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the acknowledgement that DDG put on their page.
    We're currently experiencing an issue with DuckDuckGo Search. Thanks for your patience while we get our ducks in a row.

    In the meantime, you can use other search engines right here by using "bangs"

So fun and straightforward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>npteljes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michael9423 in "DuckDuckGo was down"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40453348</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40453348"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T11:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So much about DuckDuckGo's claim that Bing is only a part of their search results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michael9423</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skill Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:37:22.552Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term skill issue is thrown around Twitter a lot. It comes from gaming culture. If you can't beat a level. It is a skill issue. Just level up and win. If you think about it, it is a powerful term. It gives power to the player.
Applied to life everything is a skill issue. Can't do the perfect juggle? Skill issue. Can't write awesome distributed performant code? Skill issue. Can't convince a penguin to try your awesome new ice cream? You guessed it. Skill issue. It is a powerful mindset. Gives you extreme ownership.
But there is a catch. Do you take ownership of other people's shitty behavior? No. You can take ownership of the triggers and environment you perhaps created to lead to that shitty behavior. Especially if you are in positions of power to have a big impact(ie: manager/CEO). Otherwise, constant shitty behavior is their burden to bear. Avoid such people. People rarely change and you don't need the negativity in your life.
Here the skill issue is effectively able to isolate and weed out the negativity. This is purely in a professional context. In a more personal context, things are a lot more messy. I don't have an answer for that which works. A skill issue on my end. Need more life experience to resolve it.
Make everything a skill issue and just level up!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running clubs, the IndieWeb of the dating realm?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7657</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/running-clubs-indieweb-dating-realm/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Marshall, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Run South Yarra co-founder Tom Adair is wary of any suggestion that run clubs are the new Tinder, yet relationships are born here, and side-by-side chats while jogging, he notes, are definitely less pressurised than face-to-face interactions. (Plus, you can always pick up the pace and scoot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16644</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/balancing-old-tricks-with-new-feats-ai-powered-conversion-from-enzyme-to-react-testing-library-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of frontend development, one thing remains certain: change is the only constant. New frameworks emerge, and libraries can become obsolete without warning. Keeping up with the ever-changing ecosystem involves handling code conversions, both big and small. One significant shift for us was the transition from Enzyme to React Testing Library (RTL), prompting […]
The post Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergii Gorbachov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable data management at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21235</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/data-infrastructure/composable-data-management-at-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, Meta’s data management systems have evolved into a composable architecture that creates interoperability, promotes reusability, and improves engineering efficiency.  We’re sharing how we’ve achieved this, in part, by leveraging Velox, Meta’s open source execution engine, as well as work ahead as we continue to rethink our data management systems.  Data is at [...]
Read More...
The post Composable data management at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21222</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/security/post-quantum-readiness-tls-pqr-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the internet (like most digital infrastructure in general) relies heavily on the security offered by public-key cryptosystems such as RSA, Diffie-Hellman (DH), and elliptic curve cryptography (ECC). But the advent of quantum computers has raised real questions about the long-term privacy of data exchanged over the internet. In the future, significant advances in quantum [...]
Read More...
The post Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans in the Labor Market: 2024 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29773</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/veterans-are-doing-better-in-the-labor-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans constitute a significant segment of the male labor force, and understanding labor market disparities between veterans and non‑veterans is an important component of studying disparities in the economy as a whole. In a previous Liberty Street Economics post, we have shown that even relative to a group of comparable non-veterans, veterans have lower employment and labor force participation rates. One year later, we see that veterans continue to experience lower labor market attachment and the employment gap has widened, though the earnings gap has closed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Dan Garcia, and Maxim Pinkovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding Regional Services configuration flexibility for customers]]></title>
        <id>66448139abf9e2000aee8587</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/expanding-regional-services-configuration-flexibility-for-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're happy to announce expanded capabilities that will allow you to configure Regional Services for an increased set of defined regions to help you meet your specific requirements for being able to control where your traffic is handled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is generally available: a unified interface for managing and scaling your generative AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>664cf64607441c000a06e4ed</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-gateway-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is an AI ops platform that provides speed, reliability, and observability for your AI applications. With a single line of code, you can unlock powerful features including rate limiting, custom caching, real-time logs, and aggregated analytics across multiple providers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Liao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A genuine selfmade billionaire]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52714</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/22/a-genuine-selfmade-billionaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that no-one deserves to be a billionaire. In the public realm, defenders of wealth concentration often come up with an example of a person who has created all their wealth themselves – the selfmade billionaire. They didn’t get their money from inheritance or some other form of luck, but from entrepreneurial instincts and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wolfensohn switches on the charm (1995-2005)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[apartment hunting, and finding meaning in living alone]]></title>
        <id>https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/</id>
        <link href="https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:38:01.193Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fall, I'll be moving to a new city to pursue graduate studies. I thought it'd be a good idea to move in a few months early to get a feel for the area - and also avoid fighting over good areas around campus, especially if I wait too long.
Next week I'm flying out to visit some apartments. It dawned upon me that this would be the first time where I live truly alone - no housemates, roommates, parents, pets - it'll be just me, in a new city. I'm excited of course, but also quite scared. The thought of being free and landing into a new city is something amazing, but for the first time, I'm really on my own.
I moved back with my parents to save on rent a year ago. And while I do appreciate them for their generosity, I think it's time for me to leave; I've been paying rent with my mental health, something a lot of Asian kids can relate to. I also feel restricted when I came back to the city where I attended high school. It was like I'm in purgatory: suffering for some time before entering heaven (a place of my own).
It's a big step, despite something I'm excited for. Yet very scary. But if I'm scared to do it, it's exactly because I'm scared that I should do it.
I think I'm ready now. Ready to take that big leap, into a new home, nearly a thousand miles away from where I grew up.
The (paper) journal I've kept since 2020 is reaching the last few pages, appropriately. It's as if it knew that my journey here was coming to an end, and a new one will begin soon.
I'll be buying a new notebook once in Seattle. Only appropriate when closing a chapter, no?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental selling point of all productivity advice is getting more done in less time. It's a good hook. I have over the years consumed a lot of content around productivity. It took me a long time to realise I was making a fundamental mistake.
I assumed I would stumble upon some specific protocol that I can follow perfectly and my life is set. So I have tried it all. All kinds of wake-sleep times. Journaling. All kinds of productivity apps and timing techniques. Trying to get as much damn sunlight in my little eye holes within x minutes of waking up(yes, I had a Huberman era). Nothing worked.
The fundamental mistake in all of this is I thought of my mind as some unmotivated child that I could be strict with and discipline into getting stuff done. But if you have ever taught young children( I have) you will know that discipline and fear only get you so far. Getting them interested in the topic changes the game.
This realisation drastically changed my life. I can get my mind interested in doing things through self-programming. Everyone is different on how to do this. Many of these routines and techniques that we hear about are just outcomes of effective self-programming unique to that individual. Each of us needs to find our unique way.
How to program your mind? You can introspect and the documentation of your mind will reveal itself to you. Also, there are some ways you can make the mind more malleable to programming. I have given a framework I follow for this in my 'Hacking Hardwork' post.
There is no golden technique that will save you. Only you can save yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My 2001: A Space Odyssey remake joke post trained Google AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7631</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2001-a-space-odyssey-remake-joke-post-trained-google-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two and bit years ago, I spotted an entry on Fandom about a “remake” of the Stanley Kubrick sci-fi classic, 2001: A Space Odyssey. Being a 2001 fan, I naturally wrote about it. I’ve had a lot of fun with the post ever since. People stumble upon it every now and again, and link to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth wins NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of year 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7637</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/she-is-the-earth-wins-nsw-premiers-literary-awards-book-year-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth, a work of verse, written by Yankunytjatjara (South Australia) poet Ali Cobby Eckermann, was named the NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of the year, on Monday 20 May 2024. Award judges were unstinting in their praise of Eckermann’s writing: She is the Earth is a stunning verse novel that takes the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An indie guide to the IndieWeb, by Wing Pang]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7641</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-guide-indieweb-wing-pang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based product designer Wing Pang, whom I wrote about last week, has published a comprehensive guide to the IndieWeb. Coming from a design background, joining the IndieWeb was an incredibly exciting and rewarding, yet maze-like journey. To be honest, almost every step of the way was like a leap! But I’ve learnt so much […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring fair bandwidth allocation for Amazon EKS Workloads]]></title>
        <id>6094b32da7c2d5cacc202444ec0b024d73ee06c4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/ensuring-fair-bandwidth-allocation-for-amazon-eks-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Service Vendor (ISV) users often offer their end-user solutions hosted on a multi-tenant architecture to reduce cost and operational management. However, this approach can lead Kubernetes clusters to resource exhaustion or network starvation issues that impact neighboring workloads. By default, Kubernetes provides capabilities to enforce resource availability such as CPU and memory to prevent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, bringing back the blogosphere one blog at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7643</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/blog-of-the-day-bringing-back-blogosphere-one-blog-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, yes, styled as Blog of the .Day, a collaboration between James of James’ Coffee Blog, and Joe Crawford, will highlight a new blog every day. Aside from casting the spotlight daily on a blog, another goal of the project is to bring the term blogosphere back into popular usage. For those […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouth Dildos]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:41:59.234Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People that use mouth dildos annoy the shit out of me. Either commit and smoke a cigarette, or give it up.
I hate smoking. I think it's fucking disgusting and I don't understand why anyone would want to do it. I especially hate it when there's a gaggle of smokers huddled around the front door of a pub, tooting away on their fags. It's vile and I don't want my pink fluffy lungs affected by that shit.
But do you know what I hate more than smoking?
Mouth dildos.
What the fuck is a mouth dildo?
-- Everyone
This is a mouth dildo:

Not only do you look ridiculous putting that stupid fucking contraption in your mouth, but the plumes of flavoured vapour that bellow from these things make you look even more like an utter cunt.
I don't want to be subjected to the cherry ice cream vapour pouring from your mouth dildos, seemingly by the bucket load. At least smokers are committing, knowing they're gonna kill themselves, have decided to enjoy it while they're here.
But you mouth dildo fuckers are the worst. We don't want to smell your stupid fucking vape. So put it away because you look (and smell) like a dick head.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Changing Landscape of Corporate Credit]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29223</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/the-changing-landscape-of-corporate-credit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firms’ access to credit is a crucial determinant of their investment, employment, and overall growth decisions. While we usually think of their ability to borrow as determined by aggregate credit conditions, in reality firms have a number of markets where they can borrow, and conditions can vary across those markets. In this post, we investigate how the composition of debt instruments on U.S. firms’ balance sheets has evolved over the last twenty years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Boyarchenko and Leonardo Elias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Mr. Mitsotakis criminalizes, threatens and represses students who defend international legality!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If some people think they can repeat what they've seen in other countries and occupy universities, pitch tents and make a mess, they're deeply mistaken”. This - so eminently delicate - statement by the Greek Prime Minister, which followed the brutal “evacuation” of the law faculty on Tuesday May 14 (28 arrests), can only surprise the uninformed: the Greek state and its governments have always had a soft spot for anything to do with apartheid and apartheid regimes! Today Israel, formerly South (...)
English

/ 
Greece, 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Kharkow - The Advice Led to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ilya Kharkow
Title: The Advice Led to Hell
Date: May 16, 2024
Source: https://actionweek.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/16/rady-vedou-do-pekla-ilya-kharkow/#more-1104

 I wrote about how difficult it was to get from Kyiv to Lviv on the first day of a full-scale war in the novel THE MINING BOYS. But when I finally got there, it only got worse. 
 The people who sheltered me sincerely did not understand why I did not want to defend the country with weapons in my hands. My hope to go to Europe seemed like a betrayal to them. At the same time, I had to hide from them not only my fear, but also my culture and my orientation. 
 These same people advised me to voluntarily join the territorial defense. Their acquaintances, who also didn’t want to fight, deliberately signed up there so they wouldn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The health benefits of giving up drinking coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/health-benefits-giving-up-drinking-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with many things we consume, the science on coffee can be conflicted. One decade caffeine consumption is a no-no, the next it seems coffee is quite beneficial. Regular readers will know I’m a coffee drinker, but in — what I consider to be — moderation: two (large serve) cups per day. But some people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I'm blogging again]]></title>
        <id>https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/</id>
        <link href="https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:55:38.443Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the glory days of the internet, when social media was just becoming mainstream, I used to blog regularly. I would write and publish a post anywhere from 1 - 3 times a week.
I didn't monetize my blog and I had no dreams of my personal site becoming a business. It was simply a place for me to share things that were on my mind and lessons learned from books I was reading.
Fast forward many years and what we have is the current state of the internet.
Everything is an ad. Everyone is an influencer. And the algorithms determine what we see and dictate what we post. And for some reason they insist on the entire population becoming video producers.
It's an endless game that I lost my taste for long ago.
That's why I'm attempting to blog again. I need somewhere to get my thoughts and opinions out without distraction and without too much tech.
If the internet stresses you out as much as it does me, might I suggest starting your own blog?
Or heck, maybe just quit the social internet altogether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;A Reprieve for Assange&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism as ‘espionage’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Application Load Balancer IPv6, Amazon S3 pricing update, Amazon EC2 Flex instances, and more (May 20, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3ec4a6e752f974d277f95d9da7228e9f5bba4ba4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-application-load-balancer-ipv6-amazon-s3-pricing-update-amazon-ec2-flex-instances-and-more-may-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is in full swing around the world, with last week’s events in Bengaluru, Berlin, and  Seoul, where my blog colleague Channy delivered one of the keynotes. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon S3 will no longer charge for several HTTP error codes – A customer reported […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>