<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-19T02:20:23.511Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-19T02:20:23.511Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn, a professional network, or a blogging platform?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8044</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/linkedin-professional-network-blogging-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2008, I had a brief tweet exchange with another Twitter member, about the merits of LinkedIn*. At that point, I was a member, but really didn’t like the platform. I thought having a personal website, showcasing your abilities, was a better idea. #IndieWeb me was thinking — all of sixteen years ago — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on being unemployed at 26]]></title>
        <id>https://pj.bearblog.dev/on-being-unemployed-at-26/</id>
        <link href="https://pj.bearblog.dev/on-being-unemployed-at-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T18:06:17.766Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is the first time i'm revealing my age on bear, something i kept hidden for privacy's sake. 

i'm quitting my part-time job next week. 

is it okay to be unemployed at 26? 

i think it's mainly because i don't like where i am right now. 

when i was a kid i picked up on things very quickly. 

i know (i hope) i won't be stuck here forever. 

i'm still struggling, and even if i tell myself and others that there is no such thing as being behind, i can't help but feel dissatisfied with my current situation. 

i'm trying to have faith in myself but i'm not so good on my own, so please put your faith in me as well. 
and hope with me that this too shall pass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275213</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T18:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; A former Navy SEAL takes a view on Trump's assempted assassination;  the Republican National Convention  and  J.D. Vance; unelecting Biden: irresistible (albeit private) force, immovable (albeit ill) object; Marimekko patterns online. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinclair Thomson: &ldquo;Mutiny in Bolivia&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/mutiny-in-bolivia</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/mutiny-in-bolivia"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crisis of the MAS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hudson on Super Imperialism 1]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45483</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/18/hudson-on-super-imperialism-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog In this sequence of posts, I will present the contents of the video podcast entitled “Michael Hudson: Why the US has a unique place in the history of imperialism? ” For me, Hudson’s book Super Imperialism: The Economic Strategy of the American Empire was an amazing eye-opener, essential reading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[loose thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/loose-thoughts/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/loose-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[-Women are not allowed to be women. We're expected to look like teenagers for the rest of our lives, and it's exhausting.
-One of my favorite hobbies used to be reading books. Now, it feels impossible to read one page without having to backtrack and read that page again (and sometimes...again) because I have no idea what I just read. My mind is unable to keep focus. I buy a lot of books, but I don't read them. I'm a collector of nightstand-books.
-I started eating Kimchi for the first time ever this week and...I'm in love.
-A part of me wants to remove my blog archives page from the navigation, create a new page, and showcase only the posts I want to keep sharing. idk.
-Dating someone new is hard. Constantly making sure you're shaved, smelling wonderful, hair at its best, face presentable, worried about farting in front of them or taking a shit in your own bathroom, making sure you're wearing sexy underwear, not eating too much in front of them...honestly, it's like I'm afraid of being human. I just want to be a slob on my couch sometimes.
-Do you use Are.na? I want to, but it looks awful. I downloaded Cosmos, and I do like it so far. I wonder if there are any other apps similar to Are.na (not Pinterest).
-I sent out my weekly letter yesterday. Did you read it? I love writing these tiny missives through email. Are people reading it though? I don't know. But I shall keep writing and sharing, and hopefully, it will help someone out there feel a little less alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday 004 - Finding Nemo]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-finding-nemo/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-finding-nemo/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Throwback Thursday post brings us to the Philippines during that one time I finally found Nemo. He was just as surprised to see me as I was him -- although I think he was absolutely ready for his close up.
Taken while snorkeling on one of the islands (I think El Nido, Palawan).

August 2014, Philippines, GoPro Hero 3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Big Pharma Preys on Poor Countries – and Patients Pay the Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275208</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/how-big-pharma-preys-on-poor-countries-and-patients-pay-the-price.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New investigation reveals unequal access to life-saving meds across Europe thanks to Big Pharma system that favors the rich]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Caddy – Meta’s next-gen mixed reality CAD software]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21495</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/18/virtual-reality/caddy-cad-mixed-reality-mr-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when a team of mechanical engineers get tired of looking at flat images of 3D models over Zoom? Meet the team behind Caddy, a new CAD app for mixed reality. They join Pascal Hartig (@passy) on the Meta Tech Podcast to talk about teaching themselves to code, disrupting the CAD software space, how [...]
Read More...
The post Meet Caddy – Meta’s next-gen mixed reality CAD software appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! A Dev Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://binarydigit.dev/dev-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://binarydigit.dev/dev-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all started with a post on my main blog where I still have the urge to revisit the art of learning software and web tools. Even if they are small things, I want to learn basics again other than simply editing templates or static site generators. I'll keep my main blog for everything else I want to share, but I had to buy-yet-another-domain as a nudge to see if I can seperate this tech space online. I also hope to actually put it on a resume one day.
I want to focus on fun projects that I might use, such as learning how to create a discord bot, a Twitch bot or overlay, or other tools that I'll use for my current hobbies. I think a to do list of sorts that I come back to now and again is a good start.
 Send a message]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275178</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T10:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our cuddly daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden 2024 Run Back in Play as Democratic Pushback Escalates, Covid Case Offers Face-Saving Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275179</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/biden-2024-run-back-in-play-as-democratic-pushback-escalates-covid-case-offers-face-saving-out.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T10:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden political survival watch has resumed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wealthy Enclaves Belatedly Rebelling Against Supersized Houses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275176</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/wealthy-enclaves-belatedly-rebelling-against-supersized-houses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T08:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of the wealthy have  taken to recoiling against hypertrophied houses, although they don't 'splain why very well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exporting Extinction: The Global Political Economy of Biodiversity Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275153</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/exporting-extinction-the-global-political-economy-of-biodiversity-loss.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report, Exporting Extinction, delves into the economic and political drivers of species-destroying resource exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump and the Age of Victim-could]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328422</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/trump-and-the-age-of-victimcould/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First, it was a breaking-news headline. Loud bangs heard at Trump rally in Pennsylvania. Then, an explanatory update. Shots fired. Then, it was named. Assassination attempt. Sounds became actions, actions became intentions. Then, finally—but thanks to the internet, so quickly—the image: Trump being ushered off-stage by his security detail, a grimace across his face, a smack of red blood above his right ear, his fist raised in defiance. More
The post Trump and the Age of Victim-could appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathryn Claire Higgins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Seeks to Redraw the Laws of War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328318</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/israel-seeks-to-redraw-the-laws-of-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people probably don’t know this but Wikipedia has a page called “List of Israeli assassinations”. It begins in July 1956 and stretches over 68 years until today. The majority on the list are Palestinians; among them are famous Palestinian leaders PFLP’s Ghassan Kanafani, Fatah’s Khalil Ibrahim al-Wazir - also known as Abu Jihad, Hamas’s Sheikh Ahmed Yassin, and Islamic Jihad’s Fathi Shaqaqi. More
The post Israel Seeks to Redraw the Laws of War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neve Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Court; No Integrity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328451</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/high-court-no-integrity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 10, 2024, Articles of Impeachment were introduced in the U.S. House of Representatives against Justices Clarence Thomas and Samuel Alito, by Congresswoman Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez (NY-14), Vice Ranking Member of the Committee on Oversight and Accountability. Read the two Resolutions in the press release at this link:  https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/13/politics/amy-coney-barrett-supreme-court-not-partisan/index.html The two Resolutions were grounded in the two  More
The post High Court; No Integrity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James C. Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tragedy and Irony in America’s Presidential Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328452</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/tragedy-and-irony-in-americas-presidential-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekends are often points for transitions. The past one certainly is proving so. One man, close to being eased out of the White House, hasn’t appeared this presidential in months. Taking a superb opportunity to reunite the nation, his words are replete with authority and resolve. With his unlimited powers, he launches an intensive investigation.  More
The post Tragedy and Irony in America’s Presidential Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>B. Nimri Aziz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocco Schavone: Italy’s Red Hot Cop in Ice Cold Murders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328449</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/rocco-schavone-italys-red-hot-cop-in-ice-cold-murders/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Brits have them, the French have them and so do the Swedes and the Poles. All Europeans have cop dramas and police procedurals that reflect their national identities, many of them on Netflix, PBS and Amazon and available for binge watching. I’ve watched a dozen or so of these shows and have come to  More
The post Rocco Schavone: Italy’s Red Hot Cop in Ice Cold Murders  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Economy and the Fate of Minority Rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328315</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/the-us-economy-and-the-fate-of-minority-rule/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent polls show that the economy is still chosen by more voters than any other issue as the most important in this election. A recent Washington Post/Schar School survey shows this to be true also for the swing voters in the swing states — Arizona, Georgia, Michigan, Nevada, Pennsylvania, and Wisconsin — the people who  More
The post The US Economy and the Fate of Minority Rule appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Weisbrot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Small Town Union Leader on Building Vermont’s Labor Movement for a New Generation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328320</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/a-small-town-union-leader-on-building-vermonts-labor-movement-for-a-new-generation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The symbols of public-sector infrastructure are often associated with urban areas: major highways and subway systems, for instance; bridges and tunnels; large ports and airports; billions of gallons of fresh water to deliver and hundreds of tons of solid waste to cart away every day. Yet public works departments are no less important in rural  More
The post A Small Town Union Leader on Building Vermont’s Labor Movement for a New Generation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Early</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Goes Nuclear with ADVANCE Act]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328476</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/biden-goes-nuclear-with-advance-act/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden has signed the ADVANCE Act, a measure passed overwhelmingly by both houses of the U.S. Congress which promotes nuclear power. “I signed the ADVANCE Act, a bipartisan win for American energy security, innovation and achieving economy-wide, net-zero emissions by 2050. Clean nuclear power and good union jobs. That’s what the ADVANCE Act  More
The post Biden Goes Nuclear with ADVANCE Act appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Humingbirds are in Rapid Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328271</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/why-humingbirds-are-in-rapid-decline/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Native American lore, bees symbolize community; Celtic myths tell us bees are spirit messengers from the Otherworld. Around the world, butterflies evoke the promise of metamorphosis. And the sparkling, hovering hummingbirds, because they are impossibly tiny and fast and beautiful, are emblems of irrepressible life. The Aztecs believed hummingbirds, who are furious fighters, are  More
The post Why Humingbirds are in Rapid Decline appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sy Montgomery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surviving Trauma: Filipe Faria’s Journey to Recovery from PTSD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328479</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/18/surviving-trauma-filipe-farias-journey-to-recovery-from-ptsd/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filipe Faria, a humanitarian pilot, shares the traumatic event that led to his Post Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD): “being taken hostage by child soldiers.” We chat over Chinese food about his work flying humanitarian workers and goods around countries like the Democratic Republic of the Congo and Uganda. Filipe just got recertified for his pilot’s  More
The post Surviving Trauma: Filipe Faria’s Journey to Recovery from PTSD appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Out Loud About My Photos Overload]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/thinking-out-loud-about-my-photos-overload/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/thinking-out-loud-about-my-photos-overload/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things I’m trying to make a habit of is posting more frequently (or often) in my photoblog page. My posts have always been slightly sporadic, and definitely not consistent since I started that site (last year). Maybe it’s because I have a problem.
When I go on photowalks, or a full day of shooting, I accumulate a lot of photos from that day. I upload all my photos to my external SSD. My folder hierarchy for photos is typically:
Year > Photos > Camera > Month > Folder Name with date
So in some instances that would look something like:
2004 > Photos > X100V > 07 July > 071724 aWalkInSF
(Yes, I am a supporter of camelCase instead of snake_case)
Anyways… my photos are not tagged, and keep their original names. If a particular photo is edited, the original is DSCF3415, and the edited…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 14, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240717</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240717"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To find #IndieWeb, more people need to know it exists]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8032</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/to-find-indieweb-more-people-need-know-exists/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JTR, writing at The Art Of Not Asking Why: Indie blogs are like good spots in town. Sure, they’re on the map, but you need to ask the locals to point them out. In terms of indie blogs, this means other bloggers. Word of mouth is sure a great way to spread the news about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275154</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics; Crooks remains an enigma; unelecting Biden: irresistable force, immovable object; Republican National Convention and J.D. Vance; how to sing ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing Karpenter: Transitioning Kafka to Amazon EKS with AWS solutions]]></title>
        <id>910ef3a53d9d7fb2e0aa32c2b41b897b162560a8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/harnessing-karpenter-transitioning-kafka-to-amazon-eks-with-aws-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppsFlyer is a global leader in mobile attribution and marketing analytics. AppsFlyer helps businesses understand the impact and their marketing efforts across every channel and device, through a comprehensive measurement platform and privacy cloud that fosters ecosystem collaboration while preserving customers’ privacy. Within AppsFlyer, data is the core, it gives the ability to expose detailed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alicia Plotnikov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[goodbye to all that]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/goodbye-to-all-that/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/goodbye-to-all-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post I didn't finish writing everything I wanted to say before hitting Publish. My posts often get broken up like this in my desire to publish fast and often; when I find a nice place to stop, I put a bow on my draft and send it out, lest I dawdle too long and kill my momentum.
That said, this post will be a continuation of sorts. Here are the rest of the thoughts inspired by Misha's post.
it feels like people are moving forward with their lives, but i’m still stuck at the same place i was when i was when i was 18, choosing a college degree that will change the trajectory of my life.
i had bigger dreams as a teenager. i wanted to do things—get out more; live a little differently than how my 15 year old self did. instead, i became the type of person who waits for her paycheck twi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Thomson Reuters achieved 5X operational efficiency and 30% cost optimization with Plexus on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>cb24bb84b9abe4d08c13bcea2f3f6bb640f40ccf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-thomson-reuters-achieved-5x-operational-efficiency-and-30-cost-optimization-with-plexus-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In today’s dynamic business landscape, operational efficiency and cost optimization are two critical ingredients for a successful business outcome. This is especially true for companies navigating through digital transformation. In 2020, Thomson Reuters (TR), a leader at the intersection of content and technology with trusted data, committed to a cloud-first strategy with Amazon Web […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Yan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Election Risks and the Impact of Trump’s Re-Election Odds on Financial Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275145</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/us-election-risks-and-the-impact-of-trumps-re-election-odds-on-financial-markets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T13:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some prognostications on how Mr. Market will react to election maneuvering and possible outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: a life lived diligently]]></title>
        <id>https://therat.bearblog.dev/re-a-life-lived-diligently/</id>
        <link href="https://therat.bearblog.dev/re-a-life-lived-diligently/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:11:15.518Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Misha!
I've read your post a life lived diligently, and it made me want to write to you.
When I was younger, I dreamed every day of becoming a product designer. I had convinced myself I was going to go study abroad, become self-employed, and the riches and fame would be mine.
poor, depressed artist aesthetic, after which I would be discovered and prove everyone wrong about not chasing your dreams. My peers would see me on TV and gawk. Grand finale: let the curtain fall; everyone applauds.
I'm happy to say none of that came true.
The truth is, your 20s are a little bit of a bitch. These are the years someone can either be going steady with a child on each hip or they can be partying 'til the sun goes down. Comparison is hard to keep at bay since everyone is going at a different pace and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wage Insurance: A Potential Policy for Displaced Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30761</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/wage-insurance-a-potential-policy-for-displaced-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the existing safety net, worker displacement continues to have severe consequences that motivate the consideration of new social insurance programs. Wage insurance is a novel policy that temporarily provides additional income to workers who lose their job and become re-employed at a lower wage. In this post, we draw on evidence from our recent working paper analyzing the effects of a U.S. wage insurance program on worker earnings and employment outcomes. Among workers displaced by international trade, we find that eligibility for wage insurance increased the probability of employment in the first two years following job loss and led to higher long-term earnings. The program resulted in net savings to the government because workers collected fewer benefits and paid taxes on their increased earnings. Together, these findings suggest that wage insurance could support displaced workers more effectively than traditional social insurance programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Hyman, Brian Kovak, and Adam Leive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275002</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tawdry daily links: Neanderthal-human contacts, Cuba cancer vaccine, Covid v. exercise, CA power survives swelter, China EVs for EU still? German permanent econ losses, moar Gaza bombing, Lavrov, intel fail, Trump shooting post-mortems, JD Vance, Biden v. Supremes, Amazon enforcing worker attendance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates: Concept Anchoring in Biomedical Science and Its Resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275130</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/updates-concept-anchoring-in-biomedical-science-and-its-resolution.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How concept anchoring creates attachment to and supports funding for not-so-hot ideas, such as in Alzheimer's research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Towards an Especifista Feminism in North America]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/2022-towards-an-especifista-feminism-in-north-america?v=1721210769</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/2022-towards-an-especifista-feminism-in-north-america?v=1721210769"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Towards an Especifista Feminism in North America
Date: 2022
Source: Scanned from a zine.

Introduction
TO BEGIN...
 “We recognize that the feminist camp has made great efforts, by revealing the mechanisms that oppress women and dissidence, and by naming issues that used to be invisible. However, this does not mean that the concepts and categories, and therefore the theoretical frameworks, are all equally valid. As especifist anarchists we task ourselves with taking from these theoretical productions, the concepts and categories that are consistent with our own ideology. Referring to the guiding principles of other currents will not only lead us down a different ideological path but also have concrete effects on the militancy, on the political level as on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Tolstoy - Three Deaths]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-three-deaths-bain-translation?v=1721203105</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-three-deaths-bain-translation?v=1721203105"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Leo Tolstoy
Title: Three Deaths
Date: 1859
Notes: Translated by Robert Nisbet Bain and published in 1902.
Source: <revoltlib.com/anarchism/three-deaths-bain-translation-tolstoy-leo>

I.
 It was Autumn. A carriage and a calesche were proceeding at a sharp trot along the high-road. In the carriage sat two women. One of them was the mistress, thin and pale. The other was the maid, smug, florid, and buxom. Her short dry tresses peeped forth from under her faded bonnet, her pretty hand in her torn glove readjusted them from time to time; her swelling bosom, covered by a rug, was full of the breath of health; her quick black eyes glanced at one moment out of the window at the scurrying fields, at another stared boldly at her mistress, or glanced uneasily at the corners of the carriage. B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crisis in the West, Opportunity for the Rest?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328322</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/crisis-in-the-west-opportunity-for-the-rest/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T06:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thirty years ago, U.S. corporate capital, along with the Clinton administration, envisioned globalization, achieved through trade, investment, and financial liberalization, as the spearhead of its greater domination of the global economy. Wall Street and Washington were wrong. It was China that was the biggest beneficiary of globalization and the United States one of its main victims. More
The post Crisis in the West, Opportunity for the Rest? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resisting Israeli Scholasticide and Academic Apartheid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328358</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/resisting-israeli-scholasticide-and-academic-apartheid/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s genocidal war is both massacring Palestinians and destroying their physical and social infrastructure. In particular, Israel has targeted Palestinian educational institutions. In late April, UN experts concluded, “with more than 80% of schools in Gaza damaged or destroyed, it may be reasonable to ask if there is an intentional effort to comprehensively destroy the Palestinian education system, an action known as ‘scholasticide’.”1 The aim of this settler-colonial project is to eradicate the physical, intellectual, and political reproduction of the Palestinian people. As Maya Wind documents in her new book Towers of Ivory and Steel, the Israeli higher education system plays a key role in this agenda. Spectre’s Ashley Smith interviews Wind about the current war, the nature of Zionist higher educational institutions, and the case for a boycott of Israeli universities. More
The post Resisting Israeli Scholasticide and Academic Apartheid appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Knowledge Economy and Science Bolster Cuba’s Socialist Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328401</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/how-the-knowledge-economy-and-science-bolster-cubas-socialist-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cuba and Cuban science gained acclaim worldwide for producing their own very effective Covid-19 vaccines. The achievement stood out among nations of the Global South. The feat reflects Cuba’s development over decades of a formidable scientific establishment engaged in the development and marketing of biologic products oriented to healthcare mostly, and also to food production.  More
The post How the Knowledge Economy and Science Bolster Cuba’s Socialist Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Moves to Ban Forced Prison Labor, But There’s Still More to Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328404</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/california-moves-to-ban-forced-prison-labor-but-theres-still-more-to-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a rare bit of good news, look no further: California is finally taking steps to abolish slavery from its constitution by banning it in state prisons. On June 27, 2024, the state legislature passed the End Slavery in California Act, teeing up a statewide vote this fall on whether to end  More
The post California Moves to Ban Forced Prison Labor, But There’s Still More to Do appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giuliana Perrone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rapid Weight Loss Drugs Give Junk Food Sellers a Pass]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328407</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/rapid-weight-loss-drugs-give-junk-food-sellers-a-pass/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2019, a ban on junk food advertising across London’s entire public transport network–– foods and drinks high in fat, salt and ads for foods––resulted in prevention of 100,000 obesity cases according to some academics. Yet the U.S. love affair with the new semaglutide-based weight loss drugs like Ozempic gives junk food advertising and availability a huge  More
The post Rapid Weight Loss Drugs Give Junk Food Sellers a Pass appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martha Rosenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging]]></title>
        <id>https://emmasdilemmas.bearblog.dev/emerging/</id>
        <link href="https://emmasdilemmas.bearblog.dev/emerging/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what the name may suggest, this is not a blog dedicated solely to my problems. As I make my debut into the realm of Bear — thrilled at the thought of reaching other bloggers through the ever-inspiring discovery feed — I must make one thing clear: I love a good rhyme. Sometimes more than logic. And in this case, the tradeoff for choosing a name that rhymes is that the content in my blog won’t always align with the title, and I’m okay with that.
My purpose here isn’t to please or to delight; it’s to express — something we rarely get the space to do authentically online. Being here takes a degree of vulnerability for me, but it comes with the gentle comfort of some anonymity.
Here, I am still Emma as I am in everyday life, but I am also imperceptible behind the words you read. While I plan to share with an open heart and freely exhibit the more anomalous corners of my mind, I know that the stakes are lower than what they seem to be on other platforms, where it often feels like I'm being observed too closely, or slipping into an alter-ego that doesn't truly capture me. Here, it feels like I can say what I want to say without the recurring fear of being perceived or held to a fixed identity. And, no matter who happens to stumble upon the musings of these pages — no matter who thinks what of the words I write — I still intend to make this a space where I can comfortably express whatever may come to the surface of my being.
And so, with a nod of thanks to you, the equally imperceptible reader, and also one to the creator of this charming platform — who happens to be the man I gladly spend my days with — so begins my emergence. Let’s see what this Bear blogness is all about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assessing the Flames of Protest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328419</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/assessing-the-flames-of-protest/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It began with Aaron Bushnell and a visceral response of mine: Why would anyone do such a thing? Bushnell was the 25-year-old active-duty airman who set himself ablaze on February 25th in front of the Israeli embassy in Washington, D.C., to protest that country’s brutal war in Gaza. The first question was tough enough, but  More
The post Assessing the Flames of Protest appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nan Levinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Offshore Man and the Wages of Foresight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328226</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/letter-from-london-offshore-man-and-the-wages-of-foresight/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another four people died last week after their dinghy capsized in the Channel. ‘When you’re drowning, you don’t say ‘I would be incredibly pleased if someone would have the foresight to notice me drowning and come and help me,’ you just scream,’ once said former Beatle John Lennon. Attempting foresight, our new UK Home Secretary  More
The post Letter from London: Offshore Man and the Wages of Foresight appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Ear For An Ear Leaves The Whole World What?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328417</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/an-ear-for-an-ear-leaves-the-whole-world-what/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Friends, Romans, countrymen, lend me your ears; I come to bury Caesar, not to praise him.” —Shakespeare, from Julias Ceasar, spoken by Marc Antony “A proposition might fall kindly on your ear.” —Prop Joe, The Wire But do you condemn Thomas Matthew Crooks? With or without their ears, none of the ruling class hears the  More
The post An Ear For An Ear Leaves The Whole World What? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Pemberton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “ADVANCE Act”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328228</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/328228/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wednesday July 10th President Joe Biden signed the “ADVANCE Act,” which stands for “Accelerating Deployment of Versatile, Advanced Nuclear for Clean Energy.” The controversial bill aggressively promotes the narrow, short-term interests of the U.S. nuclear industry in ways that threaten the long-term national environmental, climate and national/international security interests. Further, it functionally rewrites the  More
The post The “ADVANCE Act” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Kraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do Voters Want?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328225</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/what-do-voters-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Right is resurgent! The Left is Back! The Center is on the march! It’s always tempting to declare, on the basis of a few elections, that a political tendency is on the ascendant. I should know: I’ve done it myself. But the only commonality in the most recent consequential elections—France, the UK, and Iran—is  More
The post What Do Voters Want? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tyrannicide: An American Value?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328334</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/tyrannicide-an-american-value/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US has a long, chequered relationship with assassination. On one hand, the myths of 1776 recount of a nation born through resistance to the tyranny that it holds at the core of its identity. Values legitimizing tyrannicide can be imputed from the second paragraph of the Declaration of Independence. On the other hand, the US  More
The post Tyrannicide: An American Value? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kary Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teamster President Sean O’Brien’s Pro-Worker Speech at RNC  Only Helped Trump and His Anti-Worker Agenda]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/teamster-president-sean-obriens-pro-worker-speech-at-rnc-only-helped-trump-and-his-anti-worker-agenda/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teamster President Sean O’Brien gave a rip-roaring speech to the Republican National Convention in which he denounced politicians, condemned the banks and corporations, and demanded justice for workers. It was a ringing, rousing, radical speech on behalf of the underdogs of America presented to a party that represents the very banks, corporations, and politicians that  More
The post Teamster President Sean O’Brien’s Pro-Worker Speech at RNC  Only Helped Trump and His Anti-Worker Agenda appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan La Botz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Democracy: When Wars Come Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328254</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/17/defending-democracy-when-wars-come-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The elected majorities of both political parties argue Israel’s genocide of Palestinians must be supported because Israel is the only democracy in the Middle East. $175 billion, in just 2 1/2 years, has been appropriated for war in Ukraine to defend democracy. The GOP and the Democrats have brought about a needless and reckless cold  More
The post Defending Democracy: When Wars Come Home appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Hoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Words and History Mean Things]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing?v=1721164918</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing?v=1721164918"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T21:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Words and History Mean Things
Subtitle: A Response to “Addicted to Losing”
Date: 2024-05-02
Source: Retrieved on 2024-07-16 from https://bbnews.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/02/words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing/

 Most of what comes out in the text “Addicted to Losing” is not new. Black anarchists and anti-authoritarians have been critiquing black non-profits, Black academics, Black activists and black authoritarians for years before the 2020 uprising. Black anarchists who have been active PRIOR to 2020 have been deeply aware of these critiques, mainly based on their experiences. We are unsure how connected the author is to Black anti-authoritarians but, best believe Black anarchists been having these conversations. There has been so much ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes my personal website looks like a bad photo of me]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8020</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/my-personal-website-looks-like-bad-photo-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T21:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Bohacek writing on his Mastodon page: The problem with redesigning your personal website is that it looks great for about a week, and then you start to hate it. This is a problem of the ages. In the late 1990’s I’d redesign my websites (I had several back then) every few weeks. Or what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anarchist Library]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/special/index?v=1721150856</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/special/index?v=1721150856"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T17:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you in and/or from South Asia and literate in a South Asian language? 
 Check out the Initiative for a South Asian Anarchist Library and contact us in our chatrooms. 
 Also check out our guide on how to add a new language library. 
 There are also initiatives for an Arabic, Farsi, and Hungarian anarchist libraries. 
 Please contact us to get in touch with these initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Shower Incident 🦗🦗🦗]]></title>
        <id>https://usamainsights.com/morning-shower-incident/</id>
        <link href="https://usamainsights.com/morning-shower-incident/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T17:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⏱️ Takes about 3 minutes to read 
 

___________

Yesterday, when I woke up to go for work. I always take a shower & change cloths.
I was half sleep ironing my pant & shirt while yawning . Then, I went to bathroom to put my cloth on the hooks.
The bathroom door look like this ( I kinda trying my hand at pixel art)

Then I remember, I forgot to bring my towel. I went to get my towel and as I was putting the towel on the hook. I saw Grasshopper sitting on that hook .
My half sleep state was gone. My brain got in a panic mood, I cant move a muscle or scream. I knew if I did that it will fly and I dont want it to sit on me or near me. I slowly move one step at a time. Then, I slowly put my cloth and swiftly run from the bathroom after opening my door.
My grandma saw me shooting like a meteoroid from a bathroom. She worriedly inquired: is everything ok?
I told her that I saw grasshopper sitting on the door hook. My brother over heard my story as he was ironing cloth from a different room. I asked should I let it flew away or kill it by hitting with besom. He said smash the grasshopper with the besom.
I cant even say to my bro do it for me. :( Then with a bit of courage, I take a besom in my hand and went to a fight a ferocious battle for a noble cause  of disturbing my morning bath (hahha).
I was successful in my first strike but he was alive. He start to move that scared the shit out of me. After some more awful hitting it besom he died.
I felt both awful for killing it but cant have it flying it over my head or in my cloth. I even shudder just thinking about this event.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Finn: &ldquo;Same Blade&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/same-blade</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/same-blade"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T16:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palestine and Labourism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Lab: The secrets to keeping machine learning engineers moving fast]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21470</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/16/developer-tools/ai-lab-secrets-machine-learning-engineers-moving-fast/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The key to developer velocity across AI lies in minimizing time to first batch (TTFB) for machine learning (ML) engineers. AI Lab is a pre-production framework used internally at Meta. It allows us to continuously A/B test common ML workflows – enabling proactive improvements and automatically preventing regressions on TTFB.  AI Lab prevents TTFB regressions [...]
Read More...
The post AI Lab: The secrets to keeping machine learning engineers moving fast appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unedited thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/unedited-thoughts/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/unedited-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had planned to write a post about which text editor I use and why. Another idea was to write about why my next phone might be a Pixel instead of an iPhone. But it feels so incredibly boring to write about.
I don't know what it is, but lately these things feel completely pointless to write about. I'm a tech geek, so it's natural for these ideas to come up, but writing serves a different purpose. At least for me.
Am I saying that writing about technology is "bad"? No, of course not. I read blogs like MacRumors and 9to5Google every day with great interest (I used to run similar blogs myself). But that's not what I want to write about, at least not right now.
Now I like writing mainly for the therapeutic, almost meditative effect it has on me. I write every day, and I find it very rewarding on a personal level.
These thoughts also lead me to a topic I've been writing about several times now: my ambivalence toward writing in English. I'm writing this text in Swedish because it's too hard and time-consuming to do it in English (I've tried many times) and then using DeepL to translate it.
Why bother with all of that? Well, that's what I'm asking myself.
If I'm writing mainly for personal gain, why not just in Swedish? The only thing I can think of is because of the increased attention, which honestly feels like an idiotic argument.
Ok, this was not a text I had planned. Maybe I shouldn't even post it, but that doesn't matter.
These are my thoughts here and now, unedited.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating hardware with Load Balancing and Cloudflare One]]></title>
        <id>6690757a58eb3b000a367f33</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/eliminating-hardware-with-load-balancing-and-cloudflare-one"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is adding support for end-to-end private traffic flows to our local traffic management (LTM) load balancing solution, and allowing for the replacement of hardware load balancers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Crouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q2 2024 Internet disruption summary]]></title>
        <id>6694b67558eb3b000a368051</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/q2-2024-internet-disruption-summary"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government directed shutdowns and cable cuts were both significant sources of Internet outages in Q2 2024. This post explores these disruptions, as well as others caused by power outages, maintenance, technical problems, military action, and unknown causes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was Up with Grocery Prices?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30757</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/what-was-up-with-grocery-prices/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The consumer price index for groceries has risen more than the overall price index since the start of the pandemic, with a particularly large jump in 2022. In looking for explanations, a starting place is the behavior of raw commodity prices, which surged from early 2021 to mid-2022. In addition, wages for low-paid grocery workers have gone up faster than wages for the workforce as a whole. Finally, even though profit margins for grocery stores have gone up, the increase appears to be only a small contributor to the rise in food prices relative to the increase in their operating costs. This analysis suggests that the significant moderation in food inflation since the start of 2023 is due to still-high wage inflation for grocery workers being offset by the retreat in commodity prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Klitgaard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[⭐️ i know love as a fading thing]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lost-dreams/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lost-dreams/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is inspired by Misha’s post a life lived diligently.
I started playing the piano when I was five. My first dream was to be a concert pianist like Lang Lang. I was drawn to the glitz and glamor of playing in cavernous concert halls to people in suits sitting on red velvet chairs. I let go of that dream a few years later when it became painfully apparent that I lacked both the talent and the dedication to fulfill it.
For a brief period after, I settled on a more realistic goal — playing the viola in a symphony orchestra. There were more orchestras than world-famous concert pianists, after all, and less violists than pianists to go around. I thought it a nice compromise between my childhood fantasies and reality.
Mom pulled the plug on my private lessons when I was seventeen, after …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a life lived diligently]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-life-lived-diligently/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-life-lived-diligently/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[two weeks ago, i had an existential crisis so bad, i had to take a leave from work. it was my first ever leave since joining the company in late february. i spent the evening rolling my thoughts around in the darkness of my room.
i started doing a lot of new things recently.
getting back into kpop
using actives in my skincare routine to curb my adult acne
mat pilates at home (i’ve been trying to do them daily, but it’s hard. some days just feel harder than others)
trying to lose weight healthily (a point proven difficult by my bulimia that’s graduated to restrictive eating (i barely have any full meals))
watching new kdrama to fill up my empty days
about the last point: i recently watched because this is my first life. in the show, we meet ji-ho, a 30 something who gave up on her dream to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Parker, Jane E Ferrie - Health and welfare]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tony-parker-jane-e-ferrie-health-and-welfare?v=1721112342</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tony-parker-jane-e-ferrie-health-and-welfare?v=1721112342"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Tony Parker, Jane E Ferrie
Title: Health and welfare
Subtitle: rejecting the state in the status quo — examples of an Anarchist approach
Date: December 2016
Source: International Journal of Epidemiology, Volume 45, Issue 6, December 2016, Pages 1754–1758, DOI: 10.1093/ije/dyx001

 For most of the 20th century, all mainstream political parties in Western Europe coalesced around the idea that, ultimately, the state should be the chief provider of social welfare and instrument of social reform. Although Feminist, Anti-Racist, Neo-Marxist, Green and other left-leaning critiques were put forward, particularly in the 1970s,[1] criticism of the welfare state has come predominantly from the free-market right. This has culminated in attacks on the direct provision of welfare by the state in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Stop Block Cop City!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Stop Block Cop City!
Date: 10/25/23
Source: https://berkmananarchy.noblogs.org/post/2023/10/26/stop-block-cop-city/

Tire fire barricade at the AirBnBs!
 Throw a molotov at the PowerPoint Presentations! Dump a smelly bucket of shrimp on the peaceful protest! We’re going to Stop Block Cop City!! 
 Why? 
 Because I’m mad that they wasted my time with their awful presentation/book-report/thinly-veiled-business-management-double-speak that tried to sell me and a bunch of other anarchists a program of non-violent civil disobedience to stop the police training facility from being constructed in the Old Prison Farm. 
I had to sit through:
 Being told about the history of the movement in a few awful slides 
 …know your fucking audience. 
 Being told not only about affinity…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cancer on the West Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328298</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/a-cancer-on-the-west-bank/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1979, I made the first of what would turn out to be decades of periodic visits to Israel and the West Bank. I traveled there for the New York alternative publication The Village Voice to investigate Israel’s growing settler movement, Gush Emunim (or the Bloc of the Faithful). The English-language Israeli newspaper, The Jerusalem Post, then reported that settlers from Kiryat Arba, a Jewish West Bank outpost, had murdered two Palestinian teenagers from the village of Halhoul. There, in one of the earliest West Bank settlements established by Gush Emunim, a distant cousin of my husband had two acquaintances. Under cover of being a Jew in search of enlightenment, I spent several days and nights with them. More
The post A Cancer on the West Bank appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Cantarow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Selective Outrage” Towards Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328176</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/selective-outrage-towards-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The near century of oppression and occupation, massive waves of media coverage and the unprecedented damage Israel has done in its war all play a role in people’s dissent. Even more so, frustration grows with the fact that the US could take immediate steps to stop this, but instead actively aids and abets a genocide.  More
The post “Selective Outrage” Towards Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CODEPINK’s Palestinian-American Staff Member Arrested on False Accusation of Assault by Member of Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328347</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/codepinks-palestinian-american-staff-member-arrested-on-false-accusation-of-assault-by-member-of-congress/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milwaukee, WI  In an incident of political thuggery and intimidation at the RNC, CODEPINK’s Palestinian campaign organizer, Nour Jaghama, has been unjustly arrested by police on accusation of assaulting a member of Congress. While peacefully waiting in line to enter the event, Nour, a visibly Palestinian woman, was intentionally bumped into by a bald, white  More
The post CODEPINK’s Palestinian-American Staff Member Arrested on False Accusation of Assault by Member of Congress appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nim Thorn - Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nim Thorn
Title: Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland
Subtitle: Tankies and Authoritarian Entryist Groups in Philadelphia
Date: July 10, 2024
Notes: From the original post: A general, group-by-group overview of some tankie and authoritarian entryist Left orgs in Philly (though partly relevant to other contexts; many are national groups), to help more autonomous, uncontrollable rebels better understand and defend against their manipulations. Includes some reflections and propositions at the end (‘Anti-Social Social War?’). pdf for reading pdf for printing
Source: Retrieved on July 15, 2024 from Reeking Thickets Press

Freedom from money, jobs, and education!
PSL (Party for Socialism and Liberation) and WWP (Workers World Party) and ANSWER Coalition (Act Now to Stop War and End …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Childcide in the Age of Fascist Theocracies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/childcide-in-the-age-of-fascist-theocracies/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of over five hundred shootings during the July 4th weekend, reports indicate that “a Texas-based company has developed vending machines that sell bullets and installed them at a handful of grocery stores in Texas, Oklahoma, and Alabama, with plans for expansion into other states.”1 Violence has become an organizing and governing principle  More
The post Childcide in the Age of Fascist Theocracies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump on Immigrants: “They’re Not Humans, They’re Animals”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328283</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/trump-on-immigrants-theyre-not-humans-theyre-animals/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The June 28th debate between Joe Biden and Donald Trump was a two-pronged disaster.  Much has been made of Biden’s “senior moments” as well as Trump’s 30-plus false claims.  There is a growing number of “liberal” national media outlets, led by The New York Times, calling for Biden to step aside for a younger and more coherent candidate. Sadly, less attention has been  More
The post Trump on Immigrants: “They’re Not Humans, They’re Animals” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing Pleads Guilty to Criminal Fraud: the Continuing 737 Max Saga]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328277</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/boeing-pleads-guilty-to-criminal-fraud-the-continuing-737-max-saga/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing has agreed to plead guilty to a criminal fraud charge regarding the two crashes of 737 Max airplanes that caused the death of 346 passengers on two flights: a Lion Air flight out of Indonesia in October 2018 and an Ethiopian Airlines flight in March 2019. Though Boeing had tried hard to convince the world that  More
The post Boeing Pleads Guilty to Criminal Fraud: the Continuing 737 Max Saga appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prabir Purkayastha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We Love you Joe, but…”: Hollywood’s Advice to President Biden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328275</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/we-love-you-joe-but-hollywoods-advice-to-president-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something to be said about ignoring actors.  They assume roles, quite literally, camouflage themselves in scripts where personalities are created, and behave accordingly.  Given that they are paid liars, their political promptings should be treated with caution.  It is no accident that much the same thing can be said about the members of Congress. Given that  More
The post “We Love you Joe, but…”: Hollywood’s Advice to President Biden appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating development feedback loops with AWS CDK hotswap deployments for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>ce26d458d598d4737adde02742504651c450ef09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/accelerating-development-feedback-loops-with-aws-cdk-hotswap-deployments-for-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T04:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Culture Amp is an employee experience platform that provides the insights into employee engagement, performance, and development that organizations need to build a category-defining culture. Culture Amp’s mission is to create a better world of work. Developer feedback loops An efficient developer feedback loop is a critical part of an effective development process – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoe Baker - What is the Proletariat?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T02:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zoe Baker
Title: What is the Proletariat?
Date: 2024/05/10
Source: Retrieved on 2024-07-16 from <anarchopac.com/2024/05/10/what-is-the-proletariat>

 In 1848 Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels published the Manifesto of the Communist Party. It famously ends by declaring, “let the ruling classes tremble at a communist revolution. Proletarians have nothing to lose in it but their chains. They have a world to win. Proletarians of all countries unite!” (Marx and Engels 1996, 30). The word proletariat continues to be used by socialists and communists today. This does not mean that the word is widely understood. Some people use it as a meaningless adjective whereby their ideas, attitudes, and activities are proletarian. Those of people they dislike are bourgeois. Others equate the proletaria…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On keeping a book past its due date]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-keeping-a-book-past-its-due-date/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-keeping-a-book-past-its-due-date/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I consider myself a pretty fast reader. I typically get through a book way before it needs to be returned back on Libby1. I get 21 days to finish a book (although my friends have reported 14 days), and that is usually plenty of time. With that said, I’ve never stressed about finishing a book in time.
Until now.
It’s taking me forever to finish A Court of Silver Flames by Sarah J. Maas. It’s not that it’s a terrible book but I haven’t been finding enough energy to read lately. I even switched to listening on Spotify Premium, and I’m still not done.
Anyways.
The return due date has come and gone, but I’m still not done with the book. For those who are familiar with the ACOTAR series, it’s pretty popular right now so the wait time is pretty long. I was on hold for several months for each book…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anonymous - Train To Nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anonymous
Title: Train To Nowhere
Subtitle: Call for a week of world wide action and solidarity against the North Bothnia Line, August 11th to 17th, 2024!
Date: 2024
Source: https://de.indymedia.org/node/377193

1. THE NORTH BOTHNIA LINE
Why aiming at this beast?
 This is a call to action against the North Bothnia Line, a railway just beginning to be built along the coast of Swedish-occupied Sápmi. This project is a continuation of several hundred years of brutal colonization of the peoples and lands in Sápmi. Extractive industries are thriving on the increased demand for raw materials following the so-called “green transition”. This makes them continually stress the importance and urgency of the train line. So do the Swedish State and the European Union. 
 The track will be used f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seventy-five of the best sci-fi books, but I only ever read one]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8011</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/seventy-five-best-sci-fi-books-but-only-ever-read-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might be a fan of science-fiction stories, 2001: A Space Odyssey, Star Trek, Star Wars, and the like, but of the seventy-five titles listed by Esquire magazine, on their best sci-fi books of all time, I’ve only read one. The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy, by Douglas Adams. That’s it. 1984, by George Orwell? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions, great for IndieWeb, and, unfortunately, spammers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8007</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/webmentions-great-indieweb-unfortunately-spammers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T20:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions allow you to notify the publisher of a website that you’ve mentioned, or linked to, one of their pages, from your website or blog. Webmentions are commonly used in the Indie and Small Web communities, and have existed as a W3C recommendation since 2017. But Webmentions have also come to the attention of spammers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Advanced capabilities in Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Q, and more (July 15, 2024).]]></title>
        <id>1fd3ff20bcccaf56da4bc38e70780bfd8ba588bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-advanced-capabilities-in-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-q-and-more-july-15-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T18:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 16, 2024: Updated link for “IDE workspace context awareness in Amazon Q Developer chat” As expected, there were lots of exciting launches and updates announced during the AWS Summit New York. You can quickly scan the highlights in Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2024. My colleagues and fellow AWS News […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Top 1% now have more wealth than the middle class]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45472</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/15/u-s-top-1-now-have-more-wealth-than-the-middle-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cruising]]></title>
        <id>https://passerine.bearblog.dev/cruising/</id>
        <link href="https://passerine.bearblog.dev/cruising/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it was hard to write anything at all on the cruise ship last may. i'd spend so much of the day walking that by night time my feet were fast asleep before i was. i also generally found that there was so little for me to say. i could only describe X, Y, and Z as “so cool” &  “so interesting” so many times before it got dull. so i’ll say it just once here! each stop was, in fact, so cool and so interesting. i do love good food, old architecture, and scenic views – europe has these aplenty. i just wish i spent more time birdwatching. (but i knew that that would be particularly difficult to do on such a tight schedule).
honestly, before my trip, i was 100% convinced i’d hate being on the ocean for such long stretches of time. and this is still partially true now that it's over. i’m prone to motion sickness and i’m afraid of a slow death. i ended up partially bedridden for three days, so i was right to worry about the former. i couldn’t eat anything but apples, and i threw up everytime i moved from my bed. it sucked, but at least i'm not dead.
when i recovered, i discovered that it was ironically grounding to stroll the topmost deck and see nothing but blue and horizon. and that it was especially beautiful at night, even if you couldn't really see the stars at all. instead, i’d watch the water long enough for it to look like a fingerprint. then, even longer to find the unicorns in the sea foam. i found myself returning to the same thought each time: in the grand scheme of all things, i am fortunately very small. i will never run out of earth to explore. nothing is never really just nothing, but nothing feels as good as finally being home too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019
Subtitle: A collection of news, updates letters, texts and communiques
Date: 2019
Notes: This pamphlet has been put together by Act for freedom now. Check actforfree.nostate.net for updates in English.
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/SCRIPTA-pdf-2019.pdf>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Operation ‘Scripta Manent’ is one repressive operation among the many that have already occurred, and continue to occur, against comrades who dare to oppose the Italian State. The pretext here was of trying to find those who have taken part in Informal Anarchist Federation attacks since 2005, but it is also an attempt to destroy all insurrectional conflict in Italy and to cut off any solidarit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Putting into practice]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Putting into practice
Subtitle: Adding to the conversation on anarchist activity in Montreal
Date: March 21, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=26705>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 We’d like to respond with our thoughts to a text “Mise en Commun” (Putting in Common) that has been circulated critiquing insurrectionary projects and perspectives in Montreal. We appreciate that the authors of Mise en Common want to elaborate similarities and clarify differences, and move past bad faith. We’re taking this as an occasion to respond and to clarify ideas that we’ve been reflecting on for a few years now. We’ll try to use points of difference with Mise en Commun as an opportunity to delve further into ideas and how they inform practices, rather than…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Rain & Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Rain & Fire
Subtitle: Statement from a UK FAI sector
Date: September 13, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=6304>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This text was written during the course of the growing European social war, and our attempts to situate ourselves in the context of that, whilst in the midst of rising fascism, complicity from most of the society and a fractured and divisive anti-capitalist ‘movement’. These scant few pages cannot express the complexity of the various situations being described in any great depth, but we write so that other rebels at the edges can know how it is for us here. As we were putting the final touches to the text, cities in the UK exploded and remain volatile. However this is not an analysis of the riots –…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Fischer - An Essay on Total Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Fischer
Title: An Essay on Total Liberation
Subtitle: Marcusean Insights for Catalyzing Transformation
Date: 2024
Source: Building Multispecies Resistance Against Exploitation: Stories from the Frontlines of Labor and Animal Rights, edited by Zane McNeill (New York: Peter Lang, 2024)

 A 2021 study found that 56% of young people across ten countries believed “humanity is doomed.” The researchers rightly warned against narratives of “individualizing ‘the problem’ of climate anxiety, with suggestions that the best response is for the individual to ‘take action.’” However, they followed with the equally misguided suggestion that “such action needs to be particularly taken by those in power.”[1] Those of us influenced by Frankfurt School theorist Herbert Marcuse’s analysis consider…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism
Subtitle: 'Federation or Death'
Date: 2022
Notes: Anarchist Studies 30.1
Source: https://archive.org/details/05-anarchist-studies-30.1-pastellopoulos

Abstract:
 The article presents a first overview of the emergence and early development of anarchism in the Republic of Cyprus, utilising archival material. It contextualises Cypriot anarchism within the broader wave of political ideas making their appearance after the island’s de-facto partition in 1974, tracing the formation of the first anarchist groups and the circulation of early Cypriot anarchist publications. It moves on to briefly discuss three key historical moments of anarchist political expression, followed by an examination of early Cypri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)
Subtitle: “Cyprus Belongs to its Mouflons”
Date: 2017
Source: Retrieved on 23rd March 2022 from www.grin.com

Abstract
 This dissertation examines the structure of Cypriot anarchist ideology and the way it challenges Greek Cypriot ethnic nationalism, as it developed in the first decade following the partition of the island of Cyprus. It aims to contribute to the understanding of grass root political activity in Cyprus, by examining the early expressions of anarchism in the island. Ideology has been argued to function around the use of key discursive signifiers, through which the mediation of a fixed meaning is structured and social reality is experienced. This research…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - The only possible administration]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: The only possible administration
Subtitle: The question of cities
Date: October 4, 2018
Notes: “L’unica amministrazione possibile. La questione delle città”, “Vetriolo” #1, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=31586>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 These are times when it seems there are big discussions about the issue of cities, urban areas, about the possibilities of revolt inside them (even of living), of their reformability. Big discussions frequently focused on various topics relating to struggles carried out by many opponents, antagonists, often reformists, sometimes even by enemies of every order and authority; among these issues there is gentrification, a word not so unusual anymore, a word we now want to express some thoughts about. 
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should right to disconnect laws be scrapped because of lazy workers?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7997</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/should-right-disconnect-laws-scrapped-because-lazy-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne based Workplace Relations lawyer Paul O’Halloran, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald, on Australian “right to disconnect” workplace laws that come into effect on Monday 26 August 2024: Well, laziness is an increasing trend in the cases I defend for employers. Putting aside pandemic lockdowns where all sorts of things other than work were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding peace in settling down more than traveling]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/finding-peace-in-settling-down-more-than-traveling/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/finding-peace-in-settling-down-more-than-traveling/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess most of us have been exposed to the promotion of traveling by someone around us at least once in our lives. Like, how traveling around the world, seeing new places, having adventures and visiting museums are important and how life would be so bad without those.
Alright, I know they are not bad activities at all and they might be one of the ways to enrich our inner selves. But traveling is neither holy nor sacred.
In my 20s, I loved exploring new places. I hitchhiked around Eastern Europe, rode my touring bicycle along the coast in western Türkiye and went on numerous camping trips. Back then, these activities gave me a sense of freedom and the joy of meeting interesting people. Nowadays, these activities no longer bring me the same enjoyment.
These days, I do not enjoy traveling an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell - Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: ‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell
Title: Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee
Subtitle: In solidarity with Monica Caballero and Francisco Solar
Date: November 20, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15603>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

We Are not Spectators but Enemies of all Forms of Dominion
 Today we wanted to give vent to a small anarchist impulse by brandishing the weapons of life and the ideas of rebellion. 
 As we are convinced that the status quo is being maintained not only by those who hold power but also by the servile attitude of those who tacitly support it, toady we decided to attack polling station 98a in the town of La Reina with an explosive/incendiary device. 
 The electoral committee is a piece of the democ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism
Subtitle: or: an imprecise definition of terms
Date: July 3, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 4th July 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 One time, maybe ten years back, I was on the DC metro with my family. My brother and I were happily talking about the feminist implications of GI Joe, because my brother is cool as hell, when a stranger looked over at my father (not knowing we were related) to complain about how I spoke. 
 “They really don’t teach people how to speak English anymore,” the stranger complained. 
 I’m not the world’s fighty-est person, but I’ve also never been the world’s least fighty person, so I confronted him immediately. “Oh?!” I asked. “What’s wrong with the way we’re talking?!” 
 He went on a tirade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Beniamino - Right you are… if you think you are]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anna Beniamino
Title: Right you are… if you think you are
Subtitle: Reflections and updates on a trial
Date: March 20, 2018
Source: actforfree.nostate.net>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 There’s not much to be said about an episode of repression, after all it’s the simple cyclical occurrence of action and reaction – or even on how repression plays dirty – another well-known fact. At most these are just a few notes on the development of techniques and strategies. 
 This I’ll try to do. More than a year after the arrests, with the trial already underway, a crack has opened in the censuring bell jar and the court papers been disclosed in all their misery after the short report on the last issue of Croce Nera and the latest developments on the closure of investigatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell - Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell
Title: Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)
Date: June 10, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?paged=174>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

PHOENIX PROJECT
Freedom for anarchists of praxis incarcerated in Italy
I ‘Return of the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire from the ashes’
 Only in those moments when our tension for freedom is rejoined with practice do we truly manage to live anarchy, here and now. Unfortunately the dream we carry in our hearts is too great to avoid the risk of finding ourselves up against the monstrous wall of authority raised in defense of the State and Capital. When we really put our life in play, inevitably we end up confronting the hardness t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity - Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity
Title: Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage
Date: January 27, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3553>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

The War Is on
 Today more than ever, the fortification of Power and it’s attack against the internal enemy becomes an urgent necessity. Under the fear of the oncoming rebellions and the dynamics that have been developed , mainly in the latest years, the Dominance has to protect it’s interests and will do it. 
 So, we ‘r leaving in an unprecedented upsurge of repression and control. Their mechanisms of chasing the enemy are being enforced and enriched in both human and technical level, while their legal arsenal expands and becomes more flexible. The new ‘anti-terror’ law that states thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial
Date: 2012
Source: <interarma.info/2012/02/02/dilwsi_xristou_tsakalou_synedriasi6/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 According to your court indictment, Conspiracy of Cells of Fire is a terrorist organization. But words were never, nor are or will ever be neutral. Words acquire the meaning given by the person who uses them. We do not speak the language of the judges and prosecutors. We speak the language of the hunted who have refused the victimʼs role, the wanted who have not handed themselves in to the authorities, the prisoners who have not caged their will for freedom, the anarchists who have never kneeled in front of Power. Solidarity, Dignity, Urban Guerrilla, Anarch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Letter about persecutory procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Letter about persecutory procedures
Date: May 10, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=4537>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

On the 27th of April, Christos Tsakalos, for the case of C.C.F. with the upgraded charge of the managerial executive, was transported to the prisons of Koridallos, after a call for appearance at the juridical council, where he denies to appear.
 Today therefore, Wednesday the 27th of April, I announce officially to the juridical authorities, to not “bother me again” with their repeated calls for my presence in the interrogative process, because they will receive my total refusal and my factual contempt. 
 There is not even a millimeter of dialogue to be shared with my judges. 
 As I have declared repeatedl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAFE Boulder - Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: SAFE Boulder
Title: Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside
Date: July 12th, 2024
Notes: We created this zine to hand out alongside ice packs and gatorade as a deadly heatwave swept accross our region. At time of posting, that heatwave is continuing east across North America, and more will certainly follow in the coming months and years as the climate crisis worsens. While this zine contains a couple sentences specific to so-called Boulder Colorado, it should still be broadly applicable, and we encourage people to print and distribute it anywhere that’s affected by extreme heat. We note that the advice contained within is not particularly useful without the supplies needed to follow it, and we recommend accompanying this zine with water, electrolyte powder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc - Against the Logic of the Guillotine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc
Title: Against the Logic of the Guillotine
Subtitle: Why the Paris Commune Burned the Guillotine—and We Should Too
Date: April 8, 2019
Source: Retrieved on June 11, 2019 from https://crimethinc.com/2019/04/08/against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine-why-the-paris-commune-burned-the-guillotine-and-we-should-too

 148 years ago this week, on April 6, 1871, armed participants in the revolutionary Paris Commune seized the guillotine that was stored near the prison in Paris. They brought it to the foot of the statue of Voltaire, where they smashed it into pieces and burned it in a bonfire, to the applause of an immense crowd.[1] This was a popular action arising from the grassroots, not a spectacle coordinated by politicians. At the time, the Commune controlled Paris, which was st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Dining with Vultures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Dining with Vultures
Subtitle: Bristol Anarchists & the UK Media
Date: 2015, February
Source: Retrieved on July 13, 2024 from https://darknights.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/13/dining-with-vultures-bristol-anarchists-the-uk-media/

 The purpose of this piece is to better understanding of mass media’s relationship to rebels (including anarchists of all stripes), in general as well as in the context of a repressive atmosphere in Bristol. As well as raising local specifics, it hopes to encourage stronger awareness around wider issues of representation and counter-insurgency. 
 It will speak critically, even harshly when deemed necessary, of some self-professed radicals’ interactions with the establishment – but not out of an impulse for character-assassination. Contrary t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: house martins]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52864</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sunday-photoblogging-house-martins/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my issue with online interactions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The longer I am off of any social media and not constantly bombarded with the language and digital mannerisms inherent to it, the more I notice how odd it feels to detect that kind of language in others outside of those timelines and feeds.
I am active in very few Discord servers and most of them are small, friends-only groups. However, in the few public ones I am in, I often see groups of people whose choices of words and how to express themselves, how to enter conversations, their tone and views make them feel eerily... unreal. I've thought about it, and the best way I could describe it is as if someone trained AI on the most active Twitter users. There is a specific flavor of overly cool, casually careless, sarcastic, flippant, at times vitriolic undertone to everything that is hard to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sex, lies and Videotape]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52862</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sex-lies-and-videotape/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T06:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What to do when we can’t trust our own eyes (or at least, the videos we are looking at. I spoke last weekend at a panel discussion on Navigating Lies, Deepfakes & Fake News, organised by McPherson Independent. This a group promoting the idea of an independent community candidate in the electorate of McPherson south of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm ditching spotify]]></title>
        <id>https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/im-ditching-spotify/</id>
        <link href="https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/im-ditching-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T11:17:37.602Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[spotify is legal piracy. you can listen to most of your music by just paying a small amount and most of that doesn't go to the artist. hell with the rise of AI, enshittification got to a level that it never has before. I just don't want to be a part of that anymore.
there is also another reason I'm doing this. having physical files of your collection feels great. you can take your music collection anywhere you want, convert it to any format you wish and use any music player you fancy. it is at times a bit time consuming but I enjoy growing my collection and not having to throw money at a faceless company just to keep listening to my music.

how I manage it
I download most of my music as flacs then convert it to opus at 160kbps. the ones I couldn't get as flacs stay as mp3s. I store them in an SD card and use poweramp as my music app. I am not really settled on it yet, so recommendations are welcome.
I use last.fm and regular old internet browsing for recommendations. I never really used spotifys recommendation algorithm to begin with, because i value a passionate music fans words more than an algorithm.
notes
you can also take a look at kit's post for an artists perspective on why spotify is shitty as a platform. kit puts it into words better than I ever could.
reply via email
liked this post? you can follow my rss feed for more. i'd also appreciate if you toasted this post below.  🍞]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T20:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In June, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: June 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serge Halimi: &ldquo;Victory Deferred&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/victory-deferred</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/victory-deferred"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s new Assembly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deaton on labour shortages and wages]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45469</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/12/deaton-on-labour-shortages-and-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T15:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll ZEIT: Today, the debate focuses on the labor shortages facing many industrialized countries. Angus Deaton: I am always cautious when people talk about a scarcity of labor but don’t talk about wages. The argument always is: Americans don’t want to do these jobs, Germans don’t want to do these jobs. So we have to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Barker: &ldquo;Washingtonology&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/washingtonology</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/washingtonology"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T14:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the debate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>