<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-05T12:46:25.115Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-05T12:46:25.115Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279823</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T10:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our thunderous daily links: Thai turtle rescue, viruses correlated with Alzheimers, Covid heart damage, Oz real estate as Ponzi, Cape of Good Horn crisis? Israel pounds Lebanon cities, Iran warns of oil destruction, US spying on political affiliations, Kamala courts Visa, Biden warns of election violence, censorship coalition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Year of Escalating Conflict in the Middle East Has Ushered in a New Era of Regional Displacement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279863</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/a-year-of-escalating-conflict-in-the-middle-east-has-ushered-in-a-new-era-of-regional-displacement.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T09:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A catalogue of the displacement all over the Middle East that has resulted from Israel's campaign in Gaza and Lebanon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OK, Forget it, False Alarm, Labor Market Is Fine, Bad Stuff Last Month Was Revised Away, Wages Jumped. No More Rate Cuts Needed?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279850</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/ok-forget-it-false-alarm-labor-market-is-fine-bad-stuff-last-month-was-revised-away-wages-jumped-no-more-rate-cuts-needed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T08:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New and revised labor market data suddenly says the US economy is just fine. Mr. Market's continued rate cuts look off the table for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to identify inactive users of Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>3c8053df1e60e8c4552906f954b9aabc2c5c8d81</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-to-identify-inactive-users-of-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T22:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is leading to many new features and capabilities. As a result, your employees may not know about all the new tools you are deploying. I was recently working with a customer that had deployed Amazon Q Developer for all their software developers. However, many developers didn’t know they had access to the productivity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand final day: when some introverts must leave the house]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8631</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/grand-final-day-some-introverts-must-leave-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No posts about sport, hardly ever, then two in a week. But the NRL football (rugby league) grand final (Penrith Panthers versus Melbourne Storm) is on this long weekend, and since I wrote about the AFL the other day, this seems right. More a personality/psychology post though: a profile of Nathan Cleary, the Panthers halfback, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All IndieWeb participants need to be vocal, not just developers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indieweb-participants-vocal-not-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evan Sheehan, writing at The Darth Mall: I think Jeremy Keith is right, that all that really matters is having your own website. However big or small, however you make it, whatever you choose to put on it. I just don’t think that this is what the IndieWeb is actually focused on. The IndieWeb feels […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the latest AWS innovations with the new AWS Cloud Control provider for Pulumi]]></title>
        <id>956d52eea644a70dfc8ebceae873bac6346bbd13</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-the-latest-aws-innovations-with-the-new-aws-cloud-control-provider-for-pulumi/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of the AWS Cloud Control provider for Pulumi, an modern infrastructure management platform, which allows our customers to adopt AWS innovations faster than ever before. AWS has consistently expanded its range of services to support any cloud workload, supporting over 200 fully featured services and introducing more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Novikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/4/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279816</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-4-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Poltiics, syndemics; New RCP chart (it's tied) and new Covid charts (not worsening); Kamala to throw Khan, Gensler under the bus (ka-ching); Boeing strike continues, Warren and Blumenthal call for criminal investigations of executives ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Jäger: &ldquo;National Lockstep?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/national-lockstep</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/national-lockstep"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Belgium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the jungle: Rethinking land ownership for a sustainable Future]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45613</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/04/escaping-the-jungle-rethinking-land-ownership-for-a-sustainable-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog Introduction: Beyond the Jungle For centuries, capitalism has told us that land is a commodity to be bought, sold, and exploited for profit. It has also sold us a dangerous myth: that humans are inherently competitive, isolated individuals, destined to fight for survival in a brutal world. According […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asad Zaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Always Quitting Your Hobbies]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/the-subtle-art-of-always-quitting-your-hobbies/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/the-subtle-art-of-always-quitting-your-hobbies/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, it's been a while. Where do I start?
Let’s start at the beginning.
I’ve been writing for most of my life. As a kid, I wrote stories, though they never went beyond a few pages. I even started a neighborhood newspaper, but that didn’t last long. I wrote about football matches during big tournaments like the World Cup, but once the tournament ended, so did my writing. Not that I felt really sad about that, by the way. Most of the time I was glad it was over, because I could finally stop the forced writing.
I also wrote for a fairly big gaming website for a couple of years, but I always dreaded writing long reviews. Enjoyment was far away.
Then, in June of this year, I rediscovered my love for writing — this time, on my personal blog. I found a community of fellow writers on Mastodon and r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel-Axis of Resistance Escalation and the Importance of the Minority Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279812</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/israel-axis-of-resistance-escalation-and-the-importance-of-the-minority-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T15:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking at some information limits and biases in the ever-intensifying Israel-Axis of Resistance conflict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Banfico built an Open Banking and Payment Services Directive (PSD2) compliance solution on AWS]]></title>
        <id>5aedbbd23e8bd759d82d3999de0db5fb2461fbaa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-banfico-built-an-open-banking-and-payment-services-directive-psd2-compliance-solution-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T14:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Paulo Barbosa, the COO of Banfico.  Introduction Banfico is a London-based FinTech company, providing market-leading Open Banking regulatory compliance solutions. Over 185 leading Financial Institutions and FinTech companies use Banfico to streamline their compliance process and deliver the future of banking. Under the EU’s revised PSD2, banks can use application […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otis Antoniou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/4/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279803</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-4-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our unvanquished daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Third Day of Claudia Sheinbaum’s Presidency, Mexico’s Supreme Court Plunges Country Into Constitutional Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279789</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/on-third-day-of-claudia-sheinbaums-presidency-mexicos-supreme-court-plunges-country-into-unprecedented-constitutional-crisis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T10:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people, including three of the Supreme Court judges, are calling it an attempted "coup". Unsurprisingly, Washington's fingerprints are all over this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When We Have Well-Funded Palliative and Social Care, We Can Discuss Assisted Dying, but We’re Not There Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279800</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/when-we-have-well-funded-palliative-and-social-care-we-can-discuss-assisted-dying-but-were-not-there-yet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T08:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of the shortcomings of end of life care in the US and UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing News Left and Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279796</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/sharing-news-left-and-right.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T06:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study finds that conservative news-consumers are more resistant to Twitter de-amplifcation measures that lefties.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu’s Dangerous Militarism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335707</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/netanyahus-dangerous-militarism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T06:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mainstream media has been largely critical of Russian President Vladimir Putin’s dangerous use of military power, and largely supportive of Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s equally dangerous use of military power.  The leading proponents of these contrasting views have been David Ignatius in the Washington Post and Bret Stephens in the New York Times.   More
The post Netanyahu’s Dangerous Militarism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, The Purge, Black Nazis and the Language of Apocalyptic Lies and Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335511</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/trump-the-purge-black-nazis-and-the-language-of-apocalyptic-lies-and-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T06:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a campaign rally in Erie, Pennsylvania, Trump invoked a chilling convergence of law, order, and violence—a cornerstone of what can only be described as his politics of disposability. By referencing The Purge, a dystopian film where the government legalizes all forms of violence, including murder, for 12 hours, Trump escalates his rhetoric to a dangerous metaphor. In his hands, “the purge” becomes more than just a narrative device; it embodies a vision in which state-sanctioned violence reaches its grotesque climax. More
The post Trump, The Purge, Black Nazis and the Language of Apocalyptic Lies and Violence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism and Journalism Don’t Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335814</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/capitalism-and-journalism-dont-mix/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please support our annual fund drive.
The post Capitalism and Journalism Don’t Mix appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes From a Phony Campaign: The Great Un-Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335619</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/notes-from-a-phony-campaign-the-great-un-debate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s vice-presidential debate, one of the most tedious and dull in US history, was praised by the punditocracy for its civility. Is civility in politics what we want when the current government is arming a genocide and the rival campaign wants to arrest 15 million people and deport them? More
The post Notes From a Phony Campaign: The Great Un-Debate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance: Mob Lawyer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335279</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/jd-vance-mob-lawyer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vance walked off the stage holding his wife’s hand, with the look of a man who had just learned that he is the legal heir to a vast, if dissipated political fortune, and that to cash it in all he has to do is to mouth clichés and deceptions about illegal immigrants streaming across the southern border or alternatives theories of January 6. More
The post JD Vance: Mob Lawyer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Other Animals Have Consciousness?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335567</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/do-other-animals-have-consciousness/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans have had relationships with their pets for thousands of years, talking to them, coddling them, and imbuing them with human attributes. But are these animals “thinking,” and do nonhuman animals have the same sorts of feelings that humans have? Most people with pets would say “yes.” What does the science say? In recent decades,  More
The post Do Other Animals Have Consciousness? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marjorie Hecht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Revolution Will Not Be Podcast: Pacifica Radio at 75]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335833</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/the-revolution-will-not-be-podcast-pacifica-radio-at-75/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At three o’clock on a spring afternoon in 1949, in a sixth floor studio above University Avenue in Berkeley, volunteer sound-proofers, “hammering down the carpet at the last moment”, paused in their work. Lewis Hill stepped to a microphone and in his distinctive baritone announced for the first time: “This is KPFA, listener-sponsored radio in Berkeley.” It  More
The post The Revolution Will Not Be Podcast: Pacifica Radio at 75 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iain Boal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More Bro Hugs: Time to Reset U.S./Israel Relations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335383</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/no-more-bro-hugs-time-to-reset-u-s-israel-relations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli ground troops enter Lebanon. Iran sends missiles into Israel and Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu promises to retaliate. Violence in the Middle East escalates, but this didn’t have to happen. In another example of the bizarre co-dependent nature of U.S./Israel relation, last week news sources reported that Israel was ready to agree to a U.S.  More
The post No More Bro Hugs: Time to Reset U.S./Israel Relations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elections, War and What They Mean for Labor (With or Without Presidential Endorsements)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335286</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/elections-war-and-what-they-mean-for-labor-with-or-without-presidential-endorsements/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time since Bill Clinton’s 1996 re-election campaign, the 1.3-million member Teamsters union declined to endorse a Democrat running for president. Buit while Teamsters chieftain Sean O’Brien, known to hobnob with Trump at Mar-A-Lago, is busy not endorsing anyone, unions have plenty to do that’s more mundane and more important: namely strikes and  More
The post Elections, War and What They Mean for Labor (With or Without Presidential Endorsements) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can You Afford Climate Change?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335557</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/can-you-afford-climate-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer pocketbooks are taking the heat. Climate change is no longer a theoretical issue that will happen at some distant point in the future, like 2050 or 2100. Already, unprecedented climate change is happening on a regular basis and clobbering the American capitalistic system via consumer pocketbooks. People can’t afford ordinary life. They’re priced out  More
The post Can You Afford Climate Change? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wealth, Income, Poverty, Homelessness, and Hunger: Biden’s Record]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335703</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/wealth-income-poverty-homelessness-and-hunger-bidens-record/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“…he [Biden] has been the most effective president in the modern history of our country…” Senator Bernie Sanders “We know that most people say that they think the economy has performed poorly under the Biden-Harris administration. However, we also know that by standard economic measures the administration has been an incredible success story.” Dean Baker  More
The post Wealth, Income, Poverty, Homelessness, and Hunger: Biden’s Record appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Baum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weaponizing Antisemitism 101: A Back-to-School Special]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335219</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/weaponizing-antisemitism-101-a-back-to-school-special/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is irony at its most bitter. Not so very long ago, hundreds of white supremacists marched in Charlottesville, Virginia. With tiki-torches held high, they chanted “Jews will not replace us!” And yet here we are, seven years later, and apparently these fanatical card-carrying antisemites have indeed been “replaced” in the minds of many Americans. Why? Because  More
The post Weaponizing Antisemitism 101: A Back-to-School Special appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roy Eidelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“What Should I Do With This Pain?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335561</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/what-should-i-do-with-this-pain/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the first anniversary of the October 7th Hamas attack on Israel approaching, the death toll in Gaza climbing to more than 41,500, and Israel inflicting ever more extreme violence on the West Bank and now on Lebanon as well, something very different happened recently in a poky classroom at Columbia University. Two young men, one Palestinian and one Israeli, both of whom  More
The post “What Should I Do With This Pain?” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HELEN BENEDICT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Target: Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335471</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/target-iran-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel has assassinated the leader of Hezbollah and killed many of its members by way of booby-trapped pagers and walky-talkies. After a blitzkrieg bombing campaign, Israel once again invaded Lebanon this week to escalate its campaign against the paramilitary-cum-political party. Meanwhile, it continues to wage war against Hamas in Gaza. It has bombed various locations  More
The post Target: Iran appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Vice-Presidential Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335690</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/the-first-vice-presidential-debate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday’s Vice Presidential debate between Republican J.D. Vance and Democrat Tim Walz might have been called the ‘First Presidential Debate of 2028’. Based on the reasonable debate performances by both, Vance and Walz are clearly now the front runners as presidential candidates for their parties in the next 2028 national election. Of course, the bar  More
The post The First Vice-Presidential Debate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Rasmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workin’ Out at the Misfitness Gym, or, Dreaming Big]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335671</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/workin-out-at-the-misfitness-gym-or-dreaming-big/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faced with a rapid disintegration of the class equilibrium due to the developing structural crisis of capital, key sectors of monopoly-finance capital—including fossil capital, the new tech-finance elite, and the military-industrial complex—turned to neoliberalism, and then when that began to fail, increasingly to neofascism.   – Gerald Home, writer for Monthly Review The present oneness of the totality  More
The post Workin’ Out at the Misfitness Gym, or, Dreaming Big appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marching Down to Armageddon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335661</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/marching-down-to-armageddon/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A person develops thick skin as a leftist in the US. It’s a given. But while reading the New York Times on September 26th, I began to shake: “Zelensky Says Western Allies Must Allow Strikes Deep Into Russia,” (September 23, 2024). Here was an end of the world appeal. I turned to the comments section for this  More
The post Marching Down to Armageddon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Families Suffer Tragedies, All Families Deserve Paid Family Leave]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335638</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/all-families-suffer-tragedies-all-families-deserve-paid-family-leave/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of working American families are facing a crisis: how to care for loved ones. We all need to give or get care at some point in our lives, but all too often this can be incredibly burdensome or even impossible. Too many Americans simply cannot afford their own care or are unable to take  More
The post All Families Suffer Tragedies, All Families Deserve Paid Family Leave appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony Iovieno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There Aren’t Enough Services to Prevent Homelessness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335636</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/there-arent-enough-services-to-prevent-homelessness/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know who experiences homelessness in the United States? Often, it’s hard-working parents who give back to their communities — maybe people just like you. I worked with people experiencing homelessness and helped women who were survivors of domestic violence. Then I experienced domestic violence myself and lost my own home. After that, I  More
The post There Aren’t Enough Services to Prevent Homelessness appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Annabelle Ortiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Public Transit is Essential, We Need to Fund it Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335646</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/public-transit-is-essential-we-need-to-fund-it-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transit is a lifeline for communities across this country. It connects people to people, businesses, and opportunities. It drives economic growth and is a powerful tool in the fight against climate change. Buses, trains, walking paths, and bike lanes provide a clean, healthy, and affordable way to get around. Yet policymakers have put transit funding  More
The post Public Transit is Essential, We Need to Fund it Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Dauphin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Party of Carter Wouldn’t Get Carter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335632</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/the-party-of-carter-wouldnt-get-carter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter is garnering more attention for becoming a centenarian on October 1 than he did when he was the first former president of the USA to celebrate a 96th birthday. Yet what thin hope I held in 2020 that the Democratic candidate might “follow Carter’s deregulatory path” seems even more distant from a party that will  More
The post The Party of Carter Wouldn’t Get Carter appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Schlosberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Annihilation of Honeybees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335734</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/the-annihilation-of-honeybees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue Hesiod, the Greek epic poet of the 8th century BCE, considered honeybees a reward that the gods bestowed on just farmers — their sheep being weighted down with wool, the top of their oak trees teeming with acorns and the middle with honeybees.[1] Honeybees continue to bring prosperity, creating honey and pollinating fruits and  More
The post The Annihilation of Honeybees appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tommy Orange’s Oakland, California Indians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335668</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/tommy-oranges-oakland-california-indians/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t call them “resilient.” The word implies a quick recovery from trauma or a crisis. Tommy Orange’s fictional Indians don’t make quick recoveries from the trauma of colonization, urbanization, gentrification and commercialization. And don’t call them “vanishing,” either. They and their ancestors haven’t vanished in the long long war that has been fought against them.  More
The post Tommy Orange’s Oakland, California Indians  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highway Robbery: How Bad Trade Policies Make Life Unacceptable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335654</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/highway-robbery-how-bad-trade-policies-make-life-unacceptable/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of us know the pain of paying steep tolls, especially when a turnpike is taken over by a private company. Now imagine you live in one of our hemisphere’s most impoverished countries. Do that and you’ll get a glimpse into how unfair trade deals help make life unlivable in many countries — and force  More
The post Highway Robbery: How Bad Trade Policies Make Life Unacceptable appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Moore and Karen Spring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centuries Ago, the Maya Storm God Huracán Taught That When We Damage Nature, We Damage Ourselves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335565</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/centuries-ago-the-maya-storm-god-huracan-taught-that-when-we-damage-nature-we-damage-ourselves/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An illustration of K’awiil, the Maya god of storm, on pottery. K2970 from the Justin Kerr Maya archive, Dumbarton Oaks, Trustees for Harvard University, Washington, D.C., CC BY-SA The ancient Maya believed that everything in the universe, from the natural world to everyday experiences, was part of a single, powerful spiritual force. They were not  More
The post Centuries Ago, the Maya Storm God Huracán Taught That When We Damage Nature, We Damage Ourselves appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James L. Fitzsimmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frederic Jameson, Sui Generis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335864</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/frederic-jameson-sui-generis/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have known Fred Jameson for 38 years, and was his colleague for 31 of those years. Many would say 90 is a ripe old age, but the loss of Fred is devastating nonetheless. The following is a long read, but it details in outline how I came to know Fred and become his colleague.  More
The post Frederic Jameson, Sui Generis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth Surin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agriculture and Ecosystem Destruction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335563</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/agriculture-and-ecosystem-destruction/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sign to celebrate local farmers and ranchers at the Bozeman Coop. Photo George Wuerthner The other day I had a meal at the Coop in Bozeman. Outside was a huge banner that proclaimed “Support Farmers and Ranchers.” Such proclamations demonstrate the disconnect or mindless acceptance of myths by the largely well-educated urban dwellers who shop  More
The post Agriculture and Ecosystem Destruction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life for Gaza from Naples, Italy to the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335692</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/life-for-gaza-from-naples-italy-to-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Against the backdrop of an intensifying atmosphere of tension and repression across Italy and leading up to a preannounced confrontation with the state authorities that have banned a national mobilization for a demonstration of Palestinian solidarity set for Rome on October 5th, the second edition of Life for Gaza was held at the Ex-NATO base  More
The post Life for Gaza from Naples, Italy to the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Leonardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture of Cities: Traveling for It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/architecture-of-cities-traveling-for-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Illicit dreams beamed brightly: Port of Jackson sharks smiled gently: Some feared their smiles: A child imagined an auto’s bonnet, a glistening grill: The conical teeth ground and grinned: Brutality graced beauty, brutality it became: The real and unfamiliar lived in fresh flesh: Port of call came to mind: The voyage reminded me of Coleridge:  More
The post Architecture of Cities: Traveling for It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Schulman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Handel Organ Banquet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=335791</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/04/handel-organ-banquet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T05:34:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join me in a tankard-raising toast to today’s release of my colorful new album, Handel’s Organ Banquet! Hailed along with his contemporary J. S. Bach as the greatest organist of his age, Handel left behind almost no solo works for the King of Instruments. Undaunted, I fire up the famed Cornell Baroque Organ to cook  More
The post Handel Organ Banquet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[turning a bearblog into a microblog]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/microblog/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/microblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T03:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since Robert Birming released his Timeline design, I've been playing around with it and including it in some of my pages.
But I was also curious on how I could include it to make a microblog out of a typical Bearblog. Not that you can't make short posts on here in a default look, but most of the design of Bearblog and its themes is decidedly for longform content. I wanted something that looks more like a microblogging/short post platform.
==Some goals I had in mind for my own microblog:==
I didn't want these low effort posts to be in the Discovery section; make_discoverable has to be false in the Post preset.
The posts need to mention when they were made; I need to include {{ post_published_date }} in the h4 of the Timeline code.
I want the main page you land on to display the most recent …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art You Cannot See]]></title>
        <id>https://austinmwav.com/the-art-you-cannot-see/</id>
        <link href="https://austinmwav.com/the-art-you-cannot-see/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T02:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a child, I grew up in a hoarder home. My mother had me at 16. We lived with my grandmother and her then wife, who kept everything she ever received. I have vivid memories of two things in that house.
The first is the kitchen table. There were no chairs around the table, it was never used to eat meals. Instead it was filled to the edges with things left unused.
 

The second was the piano. It was old, out of tune. The wood was peeling and no one in the home knew how to play the instrument. It sat in the front of the house and I was the only one to ever touch it. Like the table, the top of the piano was a menagerie of unwanted items and dust. I would toy around on it, pressing the keys down and creating out of tune melodies that have been lost to time.
 

When I was 11, my mother …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independent bookshops, independent web, a tale of two cities]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8621</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/independent-bookshops-independent-web-tale-two-cities/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T21:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Menand, writing for The New Yorker. How familiar does this sound: Between 1998 and 2020, more than half of the independent bookstores in the United States went out of business. It was a similar story for personal websites and blogs, though definitely across different timeframes. Maybe from 2010 — later even — as social […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/3/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279766</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-3-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Trump and the Jack Smith brief; Boeing and Longshoremen strikes; UCLA tools up ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code September 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_94</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_94"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code September 2024 Release (1.94)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How open source AI can improve population estimates, sustainable energy, and the delivery of climate change interventions]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21793</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/03/ml-applications/open-source-ai-population-maps-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data for Good at Meta is open-sourcing the data used to train our AI-powered population maps.  We’re hoping that researchers and other organizations around the world will be able to leverage these tools to assist with a wide range of projects including those on climate adaptation, public health and disaster response. The dataset and code [...]
Read More...
The post How open source AI can improve population estimates, sustainable energy, and the delivery of climate change interventions appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AWS Neuron Helm Chart]]></title>
        <id>95dfc4f3cbdd61e24d37d2443925fb6f15ae679e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-aws-neuron-helm-chart/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction We are pleased to announce the launch of the Neuron Helm Chart, which streamlines the deployment of AWS Neuron components on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). With this new Helm Chart, you can now seamlessly install the necessary Kubernetes artifacts needed to run training and inference workloads on AWS Trainium and AWS Inferentia instances. Until now, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geeta Gharpure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate application upgrades with Amazon Q Developer agent for code transformation]]></title>
        <id>127ceb55ec20227577714c7d0c5af63df6e6cc7b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-application-upgrades-with-amazon-q-developer-agent-for-code-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:43:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, we will explore how Amazon Q Developer Agent for code transformation accelerates Java application upgrades. We will examine the benefits of this Generative AI-powered agent and outline strategies to achieve maximal acceleration, drawing from real-world success stories and best practices. Benefits of using Amazon Q Developer to upgrade your applications Amazon Q […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Vogel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[holy cow]]></title>
        <id>https://kelsey.bearblog.dev/holy-cow/</id>
        <link href="https://kelsey.bearblog.dev/holy-cow/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T04:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I momentarily forgot I had a blog, which means there is no monthly recap for September. I think I’m going to stop writing monthly recaps. It was fun for a little while, but I’m running out of contrived bullshit to write for “themes.”
Recently I bought a Tamagotchi and a Hello Kitty shaped compact mirror and a Bad Badtz-Maru purse and 2 notebooks and 3 pens (gave one pen to a friend) and a tshirt and a small case for an A5 sized notebook and a notebook cover and tacos and makeup remover wipes and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 29, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241002</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241002"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Homeowners Association Saga]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/our-homeowners-association-saga/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/our-homeowners-association-saga/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T21:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've lived in neighborhoods with a Homeowners Association1 all my life. There were times I found having one to be advantageous, but these days it's just plain annoying.
The house I grew up in had an HOA. You could tell that the neighborhood had an HOA because our neighborhood was the typical-ish middle class cul-des-sac neighborhood. It was surrounded by a huge man-made pond that was well kept, with a park that got upgraded throughout the years. It used to be an orchard that became what it is today. As far as I knew, there were no strict rules enforced by our HOA. I'm assuming the money went to the upkeep of that pond and park, and little things around the neighborhood.
When I bought my first house in 2012, that house also had an HOA. The fees were super minimal, and I paid once a year. Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Independent websites: vital for the survival of the hyperlink]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8611</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/independent-websites-vital-survival-hyperlinks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This Halifax Examiner article, by Philip Moscovitch, which features a number of quotes by Matt Pearce, a Los Angeles Times journalist, recorded on a recent episode of the Tech Won’t Save Us podcast, has been doing the rounds. The upshot being hyperlinks, links from one webpage to another, are in danger of becoming obsolete. Extinct. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the 2024 Steering Committee Election Results]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/10/02/steering-committee-results-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/10/02/steering-committee-results-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Steering Committee Election is now complete. The Kubernetes Steering Committee consists of 7 seats, 3 of which were up for election in 2024. Incoming committee members serve a term of 2 years, and all members are elected by the Kubernetes Community.
This community body is significant since it oversees the governance of the entire Kubernetes project. With that great power comes great responsibility. You can learn more about the steering committee’s role in their charter.
Thank you to everyone who voted in the election; your participation helps support the community’s continued health and success.
Results
Congratulations to the elected committee members whose two year terms begin immediately (listed in alphabetical order by GitHub handle):
Antonio Ojea (@aojea), Google
Benjamin Elde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React at Meta Connect 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21703</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/02/android/react-at-meta-connect-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, React and React Native are more than just tools; they are integral to our product development and innovation. With over five thousand people at Meta building products and experiences with React every month, these technologies are fundamental to our engineering culture and our ability to quickly build and ship high quality products. In [...]
Read More...
The post React at Meta Connect 2024 appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding multilingual token compression in GPT-o family models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.njkumar.com/gpt-o-multilingual-token-compression/</id>
        <link href="https://www.njkumar.com/gpt-o-multilingual-token-compression/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: I wrote this article before OpenAI released o1, which now hides its "reasoning" tokens making them inaccessible through the tiktoken library. I think o1 uses the same base tokenizer as GPT-o, but unfortunately we can no longer observe this directly.
GPT-o introduces a new tokenizer o200k_base, which both doubles the model's vocabulary size to 200k (previously 100k with GPT-4) and significantly improves token compression, especially for non-English tokens.

Source: GPT-o release
Compression
For non-Latin scripts, o200k_base achieves significantly higher token compression compared to GPT-4's c100k_base, demonstrating more efficient word tokenization.
For example, looking at the Tamil sentence நீ எப்படி இருக்கிறாய்? நான் நல்லா இருக்கேன். (translation: How are you? I am fine.), c10…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on Sufic Rewilding]]></title>
        <id>https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-sufic-rewilding/</id>
        <link href="https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-sufic-rewilding/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dawah Inc is dying. Tumblr e-girl intrigue, the notoriety of public celebrity, the psy-slop of attention hacking economics and industrial scale mediocrity is tearing down the aura, prestige and myth of Islamicate civilization in cyber. The latent iconoclastic potential of Islamicate art has been squandered and instead we have meatspace media empires, fools who have tried to make gold off the back of other fools. In the process we have a contagion of functional illiteracy, cultural apocalypse and no real vibrancy. The Muhammadan spirit is missing from Dawah Inc. There is no real transgression, when Dawah Inc positions itself as a menu item that also includes Ben Shapiro and Jordan Peterson.
There must be consideration for what comes next. Part of what must come next, must grasp the iconocla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Day in Carmel-by-the-Sea, CA]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/a-day-in-carmel-by-the-sea-ca/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/a-day-in-carmel-by-the-sea-ca/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:11:47.091Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carmel by the Sea is such a cute little town—super quaint and dog-friendly! We spent the day here for my birthday back in August.
Already trying to figure out when we can go again to continue exploring since we didn't get a chance to do the Fairy Tale Houses tour.
Thankfully walking around town was a fairy tale in itself.



There were a ton of cute alleyways like this.

One of the libraries we visited so I could sign up for a library card to add to my collection.

Here's another library. Unfortunately we didn't go inside to get a library card here.

Plenty of artwork gems to discover like this.

and this.

We event found a nice little dog shop where we almost bought a bag for Cocoa.

🎂 Related (Birthday Weekend Series):
San Francisco in a Frame
Incoming Fog Down the PCH
An August Morning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Web NFC for authentication on Android mobile devices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/eaf62b27fbc1</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/using-web-nfc-for-authentication-on-android-mobile-devices-eaf62b27fbc1?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how Capital One uses Web NFC to authenticate customers on Android mobile devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposure to Generative AI and Expectations About Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30970</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/exposure-to-generative-ai-and-expectations-about-inequality/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of generative AI (genAI) tools such as ChatGPT, many worry about the tools’ potential displacement effects in the labor market and the implications for income inequality. In supplemental questions to the February 2024 Survey of Consumer Expectations (SCE), we asked a representative sample of U.S. residents about their experience with genAI tools. We find that relatively few people have used genAI, but that those who have used it have a bleaker outlook on its impacts on jobs and future inequality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalia Emanuel and Emma Harrington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare auto-mitigated world record 3.8 Tbps DDoS attack]]></title>
        <id>4j6QWqeVFn6qzs0Md0LK7h</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-auto-mitigated-world-record-3-8-tbps-ddos-attack"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past couple of weeks, Cloudflare's DDoS protection systems have automatically and successfully mitigated multiple hyper-volumetric L3/4 DDoS attacks exceeding 3 billion packets per second (Bpps). Our systems also automatically mitigated multiple attacks exceeding 3 terabits per second (Tbps), with the largest ones exceeding 3.65 Tbps. The scale of these attacks is unprecedented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Arora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Robert Owen and the History of Experiments in Living]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53250</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/02/on-robert-owen-and-the-history-of-experiments-in-living/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T08:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 1991 my co-blogger here at Crooked Timber, Elizabeth S. Anderson, reminded every one of the significance of John Stuart Mill and Experiments in Living (Ethics, 102(1): 4-26). She situated Mill’s views on the matter in the context of a debate with Bentham (and Parfit) over the nature of the good in which Mill wanted […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Calm Before the Storm]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/the-calm-before-the-storm/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/the-calm-before-the-storm/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T04:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the time of writing this post, Typhoon Krathon will hit the populated west side of Taiwan in four hours.
I was feeling rather cooped up earlier so I went out for a walk. Smack in the pouring rain. Thankfully, my sneakers were worn and in need of replacing so getting them soaked wasn't the biggest deal; still, one is forced to ask oneself if they're capable of making good life decisions when the wind starts howling against your umbrella. By the time I got to the halfway point of my walk, lightning was flashing furiously. Like I said, not a good life decision.
Almost every store was closed today. The only things left running were big corporate: convenience stores and chain cafes. I stopped by a Louisa (Taiwan's Starbucks equivalent) and saw that there was only the barista inside.
I asked …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juice: the new cli-fi novel by Australian author Tim Winton]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8607</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/juice-new-cli-fi-novel-australian-author-tim-winton/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T21:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juice is the latest novel by Australian author Tim Winton, which was published yesterday. From this synopsis, Juice sounds like it blends elements of the Max Mad saga, with Winton’s own environmental and climate change concerns: Two fugitives, a man and a child, drive all night across a stony desert. As dawn breaks, they roll […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PRC 75 today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/PRC-75-today</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/PRC-75-today"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is the 75th anniversary of the founding of the People's Republic of China (PRC). The survival of the PRC is now longer than the Soviet Union, which lasted 74 years. China has nearly one-fifth of the world's population and on some measures is the largest economy in the world, although per person national income is only 30% of that of the US. 
English

/ 
China, 
Capitalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NICE DCV is now Amazon DCV with 2024.0 release]]></title>
        <id>ced116e7e17d31fc151eb05653942b5f0b206031</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/nice-desktop-cloud-visualization-dcv-is-now-amazon-dcv/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T19:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how this high-performance remote protocol securely streams graphics-intensive apps from cloud to device, with QUIC, client enhancements, and extended OS support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inktober #01 : Peas in a Pod]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/inktober-01-peas-in-a-pod/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/inktober-01-peas-in-a-pod/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T18:24:09.452Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know there is a prompt sheet available for the challenge, but I'm going rogue as I kind of tend to scribble stuff that pops into my head at any given time. And, so ... here's my first offering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from AWS App Mesh to Amazon VPC Lattice]]></title>
        <id>cd545d279ab991a3ed8f657b7adc59e9b1f42900</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/migrating-from-aws-app-mesh-to-amazon-vpc-lattice/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T17:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After careful consideration, we have made the decision to discontinue AWS App Mesh, effective September 30th, 2026. Until this date, existing AWS App Mesh customers will be able to use the service as normal, including creating new resources and onboarding new accounts via the AWS CLI and AWS CloudFormation. Additionally, AWS will continue to provide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shukla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hal Foster: &ldquo;Asperity and Delight&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/asperity-and-delight</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/asperity-and-delight"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T15:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Serra (1938-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘The Blessing' for genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Blessing-for-genocide</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Blessing-for-genocide"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T12:14:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden-Harris genocide-facilitation team is celebrating about wanting a conflict-free world and post-Western geopolitical arrangements, including a two-state solution for Israel and Palestine. So this public recognition by Netanyahu of their usefulness should be humiliating enough. (At the United Nations, among BRICS+ members only Ethiopia typically joins Axis-of-Genocide powers by abstaining on resolutions criticising Israel, including a September 18 enforcement of the International (...)
English

/ 
South Africa, 
WTO, 
Israel, 
BRICS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Nonbank Financial Institutions Systemic?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31733</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/are-nonbank-financial-institutions-systemic/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T11:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent events have heightened awareness of systemic risk stemming from nonbank financial sectors. For example, during the COVID-19 pandemic, liquidity demand from nonbank financial entities caused a “dash for cash” in financial markets that required government support. In this post, we provide a quantitative assessment of systemic risk in the nonbank sectors. Even though these sectors have heterogeneous business models, ranging from insurance to trading and asset management, we find that their systemic risk has common variation, and this commonality has increased over time. Moreover, nonbank sectors tend to become more systemic when banking sector systemic risk increases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andres Aradillas Fernandez, Martin Hiti, and Asani Sarkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shambles, But Make It Digital]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53225</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/01/shambles-but-make-it-digital/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T08:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work at a very large University. I am the parent of a child who has just started secondary school, and of one in the middle of their primary school journey. I am currently taking what in the UK is called a Level 2 Adult Education course. In all four of those domains – and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Ronzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impact of Verizon’s September 30 outage on Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>2dMuW3phhA9ClF8ROOAYPH</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/impact-of-verizons-september-30-outage-on-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T00:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, September 30, customers on Verizon’s mobile network in multiple cities across the United States reported experiencing a loss of connectivity. HTTP request traffic data from Verizon’s mobile ASN (AS6167) showed nominal declines across impacted cities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye, Cohost]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/goodbye-cohost/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/goodbye-cohost/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T00:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alright, I'm a little sick, and I have something of a headache, and I'm emotional for more reasons than just Cohost, but here goes.
I've been writing on the internet for most of the time that I've been alive. I've done it on blogs, I've done it on social media. I've done it for money and I've done it for free. I've done it on Tumblr and on more than one defunct media vertical and in interactive fiction.
Cohost was the first place where it felt like, consistently, someone was always reading. Something about the site's design and user culture created a magical space where people approached things with openness and curiosity and willingness to give their time and attention.
This felt like a place where you could write about anything and people would care. I've talked about the Put your Helmet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do mullets make for great Australian Football League teams?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8602</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mullets-great-australian-football-league-teams/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not very sporty as regular readers will have gathered. Of the approximate sixteen-hundred posts here at present, less than half a dozen are sport related. Of these, the majority relate to the Matildas, the Australian women’s football/soccer team, which I wrote during last year’s World Cup tournament. To think it’s been over a year […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Telemetry Events in Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>997dd18c527aa0428e12fdb6d20bc3309fd39e11</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/exploring-telemetry-events-in-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As organizations increasingly adopt Amazon Q Developer, understanding how developers use it is essential. Diving into specific telemetry events and user-level data clarifies how users interact with Amazon Q Developer, offering insights into feature usage and developer behaviors. This granular view, accessible through logs, is vital for identifying trends, optimizing performance, and enhancing the overall […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Ernst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and Kubecost Collaborate to Deliver Kubecost 2.0 for Amazon EKS Users]]></title>
        <id>533837ea15587ac1d6c7f1df3cb349aa1fad90ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/aws-and-kubecost-collaborate-to-deliver-kubecost-2-0-for-amazon-eks-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T19:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In August 2022, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) announced the availability of an Amazon EKS-optimized bundle of Kubecost for cluster cost visibility. The bundle is available to Amazon EKS users free of charge and enables users to gain deeper cost insights into Kubernetes resources, such as namespace, cluster, pod, and organizational concepts (for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Janiak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[been thinking about tangible reality]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/been-thinking-about-tangible-reality/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/been-thinking-about-tangible-reality/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T17:16:00.547Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this post was originally written for the final couple days of cohost, a long-form social media site that as of october 1st will be sunsetting.
it really is precious, sometimes. to look at something and be able to experience it with your senses. it's novel, most days. you just do it without thinking.
but then there's times when you experience an intangible unreality so strong that it becomes a force in your life that can't be measured. we don't have scales for that, or weights that add up the unreal intangible space that exists between little lights in a grid & your brain.
there is a space, somewhere within the imagination, that fills in bit by bit over time. like reading a book, making the world come to life, hearing voices, making up the parts that the author never tells you. internet spa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Jamba 1.5 family, Llama 3.2, Amazon EC2 C8g and M8g instances and more (Sep 30, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>d2c501e1f24b7e9eca5982d22f0f3c5ae24c59b0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-jamba-1-5-family-llama-3-2-amazon-ec2-c8g-and-m8g-instances-and-more-sep-30-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, there’s a new Amazon Web Services (AWS) community event where you can network, learn something new, and immerse yourself in the community. When you’re in a community, everyone grows together, and no one is left behind. Last week was no exception. I can highlight the Dach AWS Community Day where Viktoria Semaan closed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/timeline/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/timeline/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T16:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Timeline
Atomic Age
Alexandra was born at a very young age, in Germany, to English speaking parents, which confused the hell out of her.
Three Years Later
At aged 3, Alexandra took a very long boat journey with her parents half way around the world, from England to Hong Kong, via South Africa, and never once got sea sick.
Three Years Later
Having survived an earthquake, a 1000 year historic tsunami that lifted a ship out of the harbour, and a mega typhoon that sucked all the windows out of their third story apartment, Alexandra and her family flew back to England for tea and marmalade sandwiches.
Three Years Later
After the heat and humidity of SE Asia, Alexandra and her family spent 3 years shivering in the cold frozen north of Scotland eating a lot of fish and chips. She did, however, get to sit in an English Electric Lightning fighter jet, and has the photographic evidence to prove it.
Three Years Later
What seemed like months but was, in fact, only days, Alexandra and her family arrived, by plane, in Singapore. Having hopped, skipped, and seemingly, jumped, through various countries. Singapore was very similar to Hong Kong minus the earthquake. It did, however, have a lot of tropical fish which Alexandra enjoyed collecting.
Three Years Later
Arriving back in England, on a fancy jet, Alexandra and her family settled back into a boring English life where, secretly, they all longed to be back in SE Asia, anywhere, but the north of England. Whereupon, Alexandra quietly waited for adulthood to arrive.
Six Years Later
Having waited patiently for adulthood to arrive, Alexandra packed a marmite sandwich, her toothbrush, favourite teddy bear, and a lucky button wrapped in a ten shilling note and, like Nelly the elephant, ran away to join the circus. Also known as, at this time, the Women's Royal Air Force. Where she became an air traffic controller, as it is also known, air is notoriously difficult to control at any given time of the day or night.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accenture Expedites Infrastructure Deployment with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>3551fd691e991805cf5b17a5d031b3ad3b6bbc0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accenture-expedites-infrastructure-deployment-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T14:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Priya Mallya, Managing Director – Accenture, Sandeep Singh Bhatia, Sr Manager – Accenture      Vikas Purohit – Sr. Solutions Architect – AWS Being able to internally setup and manage flexible, efficient infrastructure can be painful. Manually authoring your Infrastructure as Code (IaC) templates is error prone and time consuming. However, adoption of generative […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikas Purohit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wrapping up another Birthday Week celebration]]></title>
        <id>65JnLP0MYKVzwTyOsItRJk</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/birthday-week-2024-wrap-up"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recapping all the big announcements made during 2024’s Birthday Week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly May Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline for Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/timeline-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/timeline-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T11:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline for Bear Blog

Do you want to present your blogging timeline in a stylish way? Or perhaps have a unique style for your micro thoughts? Or keep a changelog for documenting your blog’s development?
Say hello to the latest cub in the Bearming theme family: Timeline.
Here’s an example with the time-focused timeless song In the Year 2525 (further down the page, you’ll find instructions on how to implement it on your blog):
Year 3535
In the year 3535, ain't gonna need to tell the truth, tell no lie, everything you think, do and say, is in the pill you took today.
Year 5555
In the year 5555, your arms hangin' limp at your sides, your legs got nothin' to do, some machine's doin' that for you.
Year 9595
In the year 9595, I'm kinda wonderin' if man is gonna be alive, he's taken everything t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Central Banking Beauty Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31665</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/the-central-banking-beauty-contest/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expectations can play a significant role in driving economic outcomes, with central banks factoring market sentiment into policy decisions and market participants forming their own assumptions about monetary policy. But how well do central banks understand the expectations of market participants—and vice versa? Our model, developed in a recent paper, features a dynamic game between (i) a monetary authority that cannot commit to an inflation target and (ii) a set of market participants that understand the incentives created by that credibility problem. In this post, we describe the game, a type of Keynesian beauty contest: its main novelty is that each side attempts, with varying degrees of accuracy, to forecast the other’s beliefs, resulting in new findings regarding the levels and trajectories of inflation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gonzalo Cisternas and Aaron Kolb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on CNCF Deaf and Hard-of-hearing Working Group (DHHWG)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/30/cncf-deaf-and-hard-of-hearing-working-group-spotlight/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/30/cncf-deaf-and-hard-of-hearing-working-group-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recognition of Deaf Awareness Month and the importance of inclusivity in the tech community, we are spotlighting Catherine Paganini, facilitator and one of the founding members of CNCF Deaf and Hard-of-Hearing Working Group (DHHWG). In this interview, Sandeep Kanabar, a deaf member of the DHHWG and part of the Kubernetes SIG ContribEx Communications team, sits down with Catherine to explore the impact of the DHHWG on cloud native projects like Kubernetes.
Sandeep’s journey is a testament to the power of inclusion. Through his involvement in the DHHWG, he connected with members of the Kubernetes community who encouraged him to join SIG ContribEx - the group responsible for sustaining the Kubernetes contributor experience. In an ecosystem where open-source projects are actively seeking co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a ranking of iMac G3 colors]]></title>
        <id>https://platinumtulip.bearblog.dev/a-ranking-of-imac-g3-colors/</id>
        <link href="https://platinumtulip.bearblog.dev/a-ranking-of-imac-g3-colors/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T22:09:11.448Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bondi blue

a classic. delicious Y2K Teal. iconic. gotta love her. 4.5/5.
blueberry

barely distinguishable from the original Bondi Blue, but from what i can tell in photos online and in real life, it's a slightly lighter color compared to bondi blue. but because of that, i think it's missing some contrast. i don't like it as much. 3/5
grape

underappreciated one! this color combination makes me think of the Teenz Zone at my library circa 2000. 4/5
tangerine

truthfully, my fondness for this one is 99% because of The Cheat's computer. but it's a fun, retrofuturistic color choice, especially with the form factor. on its own i give it a 4.5/5, but it gets elevated to 5/5 because it makes me think of Homestar.
lime

it's very Nickelodeon Slime Green. i wasn't fond of this one when i first wro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vale British actor Maggie Smith, Harry Potter, A Room with a View, star]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8589</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/vale-british-actor-maggie-smith/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure the 1984 film, A Room with a View, made by James Ivory and Ismail Merchant, was my introduction to the work of British stage and screen actor Maggie Smith, who died last week, aged 89. I’d been trying to read the 1908 novel of the same name, by E.M. Forster, but was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comrade President? Change and Continuity in Sri Lanka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Comrade-President-Change-and-Continuity-in-Sri-Lanka</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Comrade-President-Change-and-Continuity-in-Sri-Lanka"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T15:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anura Kumara Dissanayake's (AKD) victory on 21 September as the candidate of the centre-left National People's Power (NPP) coalition is highly significant for symbolic and substantive reasons. His predecessors have been from the social and political elite that has mis-ruled Sri Lanka since independence from Britain in 1948. Some were born into that elite, while a couple (Ranasinghe Premadasa, Maithripala Sirisena) made their way into it through the business of politics before they occupied (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nihil: Embracing Digital Minimalism]]></title>
        <id>https://andout.bearblog.dev/nihil-embracing-digital-minimalism/</id>
        <link href="https://andout.bearblog.dev/nihil-embracing-digital-minimalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of endless notifications, feature-bloated apps, and constant digital noise, I found myself yearning for simplicity. That's why I created Nihil - a suite of minimalist tools designed to help you focus on what truly matters.
The Vision Behind Nihil
Nihil was born out of a personal need. As a developer and a user, I was frustrated with the complexity of many digital tools. I wanted something that would strip away the unnecessary and leave only the essential. Something that would help me think clearer and live more intentionally.
That's the core of Nihil's philosophy: less is more. Each tool in the Nihil suite serves a single, specific purpose. No bloat, no distractions - just pure functionality.

What Makes Nihil Different?
Purposeful Design
Every feature in Nihil is there because …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM welcomes the sovereign stance of the new Government of Mexico of not inviting King Felipe VI of Spain to attend the inauguration ceremony]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-welcomes-the-sovereign-attitude-of-the-new-Government-of-Mexico-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-welcomes-the-sovereign-attitude-of-the-new-Government-of-Mexico-of"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T13:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the ceremony of the transfer of power from the President of Mexico, Andrés Manuel López Obrador, to the new President, Dr. Claudia Sheimbaum Pardo, next Tuesday, October 1, there will be a notable absence, that of King Felipe VI de Borbón of the Kingdom of Spain. 
English

/ 
Mexico, 
Neocolonialism, 
Colonialism, 
Human Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;Consequences of Nasrallah&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/consequences-of-nasrallah</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/consequences-of-nasrallah"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T11:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel and the Resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Salisbury Cathedral]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53241</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/29/sunday-photoblogging-salisbury-cathedral-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T06:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citizens’ Assemblies in Michigan and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52701</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/29/citizens-assemblies-in-michigan-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T01:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citizens’ assemblies are a hot topic these days in democratic theory. Hélène Landemore gave her Tanner Lecture at University of Michigan last semester, describing her experience on the governance committee of the French Citizens’ Convention on the End of Life. Her account of how ordinary citizens could not only deliberate seriously about a contentious issue, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>