<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-12T01:17:26.109Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-12T01:17:26.109Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics on AWS: Optimizing wind turbine performance using OpenFAST in a digital twin]]></title>
        <id>15b43805eef7a9a28f3253f162528f28d1cfd790</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/physics-on-aws-optimizing-wind-turbine-performance-using-openfast-in-a-digital-twin/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T22:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wind energy plays a crucial role in global decarbonization efforts by generating emission-free power from an abundant resource. In 2022, wind energy produced 2100 terawatt-hours (TWh) globally, or over 7% of global electricity, with expectations to reach 7400 TWh by 2030. Despite its potential, several challenges must be addressed to help meet grid decarbonization targets. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Masciola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs become more covertly racist with human intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089683</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/11/1089683/llms-become-more-covertly-racist-with-human-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T18:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since their inception, it’s been clear that large language models like ChatGPT absorb racist views from the millions of pages of the internet they are trained on. Developers have responded by trying to make them less toxic. But new research suggests that those efforts, especially as models get larger, are only curbing racist views that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 3/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268201</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/200pm-water-cooler-3-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Enduring Predictability of the Mostly Apolitical Oscars]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/oscars-academy-awards-2024-politics-gaza/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/oscars-academy-awards-2024-politics-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T17:08:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What can you say about the Academy Awards ceremony this year that you don’t say every year, if you happen to keep watching? It’s one of the few American events that still reliably draws a mass audience — the Super Bowl is another, far more popular event — and as such, it can be widely [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VR headsets can be hacked with an Inception-style attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089686</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/11/1089686/hack-vr-headsets-inception/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Christoper Nolan movie Inception, Leonardo DiCaprio’s character uses technology to enter his targets’ dreams to steal information and insert false details into their subconscious.  A new “inception attack” in virtual reality works in a similar way. Researchers at the University of Chicago exploited a security vulnerability in Meta’s Quest VR system that allows…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Heikkilä</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sped up AWS CloudFormation deployments with optimistic stabilization]]></title>
        <id>aca9fd3bf0ae74d5710c89512f26c242d6e97df7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-we-sped-up-aws-cloudformation-deployments-with-optimistic-stabilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction AWS CloudFormation customers often inquire about the behind-the-scenes process of provisioning resources and why certain resources or stacks take longer to provision compared to the AWS Management Console or AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI). In this post, we will delve into the various factors affecting resource provisioning in CloudFormation, specifically focusing on resource stabilization, which allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavani Kanneganti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Claude 3 Sonnet support in Bedrock, new instances, and more — March 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>1ac173b1e82d4b67e6ec4044be26f6b60a2f29dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-sonnet-support-in-bedrock-new-instances-and-more-march-11-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday was International Women’s Day (IWD), and I want to take a moment to appreciate the amazing ladies in the cloud computing space that are breaking the glass ceiling by reaching technical leadership positions and inspiring others to go and build, as our CTO Werner Vogels says. Last week’s launches Here are some launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is “greedflation” over?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45202</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/11/is-greedflation-over/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker Peter Coy used his column yesterday to beg President Biden not to use the term “greedflation” to explain the runup in inflation since the pandemic. I am sympathetic to much of his argument, most importantly, the idea that corporations suddenly turned greedy is a bit far out. As Coy notes, corporations are always greedy. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamaal Bowman Deserves the Left’s Support]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/jamaal-bowman-cease-fire-gaza-reelection/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/jamaal-bowman-cease-fire-gaza-reelection/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We often hear from the Left on how important it is to use our power — as voters, union members, protesters — to reject politicians who have not called for a cease-fire in Israel’s war on Gaza, which has claimed upward of thirty thousand lives. But it’s equally urgent to defend those elected officials who [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Week 2024 wrap up]]></title>
        <id>65eea293a5fcdf000a08b807</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/security-week-2024-wrap-up"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A summary of the blog posts and product announcements released during Security Week 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniele Molteni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hayden and Jane Fonda, Capitol Hill Antiwar Lobbyists]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/hayden-fonda-vietnam-antiwar-lobbyists/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/hayden-fonda-vietnam-antiwar-lobbyists/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T13:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fifty years ago, New Leftist Tom Hayden and actress and activist Jane Fonda infiltrated the Capitol. Congressman Clair Burgener (R-UT) was enraged: “A course in ‘American imperialism’ taught by Miss Fonda and Mr Hayden for employees of this Congress is more than I can accept.” Burgener delivered this statement on the House floor on March [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: rise of the multimodal robots, and the SEC’s new climate rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089669</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/11/1089669/the-download-rise-of-the-multimodal-robots-and-the-secs-new-climate-rules/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. An OpenAI spinoff has built an AI model that helps robots learn tasks like humans The news: In the summer of 2021, OpenAI quietly shuttered its mulrobotics team, announcing that progress was being…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An OpenAI spinoff has built an AI model that helps robots learn tasks like humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089653</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/11/1089653/an-openai-spinoff-has-built-an-ai-model-that-helps-robots-learn-tasks-like-humans/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the summer of 2021, OpenAI quietly shuttered its robotics team, announcing that progress was being stifled by a lack of data necessary to train robots in how to move and reason using artificial intelligence.  Now three of OpenAI’s early research scientists say the startup they spun off in 2017, called Covariant, has solved that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James O'Donnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aligning With Washington Is Bad News for Argentina]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/argentina-economy-debt-us-hegemony/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/argentina-economy-debt-us-hegemony/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T11:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Argentina’s president Javier Milei is a throwback. He sports muttonchops and a leather jacket. His favorite band is the Rolling Stones. He is a Cold Warrior, spouting anachronistic anti-communist rhetoric that doesn’t correspond to the geopolitical dynamics of the twenty-first century. But the realities of Argentine and global economics have not deterred Milei from pursuing [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 3/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268162</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/links-3-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our sizzling hot daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Crises and Tax Havens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268184</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/financial-crises-and-tax-havens.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tax havens not only facilitate tax evasion and corruption in ‘normal times’, they also harbour funds during economic crises, slowing down recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Egalitarian Radicalism of Thomas Müntzer]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/thomas-muntzer-peasants-war-egalitarian-radicalism/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/thomas-muntzer-peasants-war-egalitarian-radicalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When the princes finally captured Thomas Müntzer, they put the thumbscrews on him. Shortly before he was beheaded on May 27, 1525, he confessed under torture to starting the Peasants’ War “in order that Christianity should make all men equal.” Any noble who refused to share his goods “amongst everyone according to their need” was [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Isolation to Containment: Washington’s Economic War Against Russia Gets a Rebrand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268099</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/from-isolation-to-containment-washingtons-economic-war-against-russia-gets-a-rebrand.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T10:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foreign Affiars recycles a 75-year-old strategy from George Kennan that no longer fits the geopolitical realities of the world in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Left Fell in and Out of Love With Free Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/left-free-trade-british-empire-wto/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/left-free-trade-british-empire-wto/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T09:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In November and December of 1999, at least forty thousand protestors descended on downtown Seattle to protest the World Trade Organization (WTO) conference. Some dressed as or brandished images of sea turtles, which symbolized the WTO’s overturning of environmental regulations against trawling. Alongside them marched representatives of the steelworkers’ unions, who protested the dumping of [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Market  Gives Vote of No Confidence in Latest Israel Genocide, Um, War-Financing Bonds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268160</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/market-gives-vote-of-no-confidence-in-latest-israel-genocide-um-war-financing-bonds.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T08:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[High interest rates for Israeli bond offerings, plus mumble-shuffle by manager Goldman and the SEC, confirm investor doubts about its prospects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debt Forgiveness in the Bronze Age]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315751</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/debt-forgiveness-in-the-bronze-age/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T06:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Civilization’s earliest written records, from Sumer in the third millennium BC, provide the best evidence for civilization’s monetized debt relations “in the beginning.” Two categories of debt existed, each associated with its own designated monetary commodity. Business obligations owed by traders and entrepreneurial managers were denominated in silver, above all those associated with foreign trade. The agrarian economy operated on credit denominated in barley units, assigned a value equal to the silver shekel in order to strike a common measure. More
The post Debt Forgiveness in the Bronze Age appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gilded Age Then, the Gilded Age Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315779</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/the-gilded-age-then-the-gilded-age-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How many people in India are going hungry? Researchers working on the Global Hunger Index are currently tracking 125 nations across the world. Exactly 110 of those nations, those researchers reported last fall, are suffering less hunger than India. But India, by contrast, is doing quite well on the gluttony front. Few nations today can  More
The post The Gilded Age Then, the Gilded Age Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State-Sponsored Kidnapping and Extraordinary Rendition Threatens Yellowstone Buffalo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315766</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/state-sponsored-kidnapping-and-extraordinary-rendition-threatens-yellowstone-buffalo/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yellowstone’s wild, free-roaming buffalo are wildlife. The biggest threat to wild buffalo today is settler-colonialism, domestication, and plantation farming for trophy hunters. Unfortunately, 21st-Century American colonial adventures persist in the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem. In February 2024, 141 wild Yellowstone buffalo were kidnapped, loaded into trucks, and relocated to the Fort Peck Indian Reservation, some 500  More
The post State-Sponsored Kidnapping and Extraordinary Rendition Threatens Yellowstone Buffalo appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montanans Oppose Catbox Cleanups of Superfund Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315857</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/montanans-oppose-catbox-cleanups-of-superfund-sites/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montanan’s 1972 Constitution is very direct about what it means when it comes to pollution. All Montanans are guaranteed the “inalienable right” to “clean and healthful environment.”  Equally unambiguous is the mandate that “all lands disturbed by the taking of natural resources shall be reclaimed.”  And finally, “the state and each person shall maintain and improve a clean and  More
The post Montanans Oppose Catbox Cleanups of Superfund Sites appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stones Cry Out Delegation: From the Ground in Palestine to the US Government and Churches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315859</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/the-stones-cry-out-delegation-from-the-ground-in-palestine-to-the-us-government-and-churches/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Nothing has changed, and everything has changed.”  These are the words of Sam Bahour, a Palestinian-American businessman and activist who spoke to our delegation. Nothing has changed because the deadly oppression of the Palestinian people has been ongoing for 76 years. Everything has changed since October 7, the day Hamas fighters pierced the walls of the concentration camp called Gaza.  As followers of Jesus,  More
The post The Stones Cry Out Delegation: From the Ground in Palestine to the US Government and Churches appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wendell Griffen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Life for Mexico’s Oldest Union]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315861</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/a-new-life-for-mexicos-oldest-union/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humberto Montes de Oca is the Secretary for Internal Relations of the Mexican Union of Electrical Workers (SME). He was originally a working-class art student who became active in the left-wing political movements of the period of Mexico’s Dirty War (1970s to early 1980s). He joined the SME as a political act to become part  More
The post A New Life for Mexico’s Oldest Union appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Bacon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Play for Our Time: Ionesco’s “Rhinoceros”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315763</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/a-play-for-our-time-ionescos-rhinoceros/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When theatergoers in Dusseldorf, Germany sat down one October evening in 1959 to watch the world premiere of Eugene Ionesco’s latest work, they witnessed a strange, new kind of play: rhinoceroses charging through a provincial European town, townspeople themselves turning into rhinoceroses, a whole society transforming rapidly from human to beast, and, at the end,  More
The post A Play for Our Time: Ionesco’s “Rhinoceros” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Campaign to Free Assange: Reflections on Night Falls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315805</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/the-campaign-to-free-assange-reflections-on-night-falls/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The town hall meeting is the last throbbing reminder of the authentic demos.  People gather; debates held.  Views converge; others diverge.  Speakers are invited to stir the invitees, provoke the grey cells.  Till artificial intelligence banishes such gatherings, and the digital cosmos swallows us whole, cherish these events. And there was much to cherish about  More
The post The Campaign to Free Assange: Reflections on Night Falls appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief History of The Spark: A Journal of Contemporary Anarchist Thought]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315760</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/a-brief-history-of-the-spark-a-journal-of-contemporary-anarchist-thought/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first issue of The Spark: A Journal of Contemporary Anarchist Thought was published in July, 1983, and the final issue in June 1984. A total of five issues were published. A list of the writers includes: Steve O’Keefe, editor & publisher Patrick Michael, staff Rosemary Fury, staff Bob Black Karl Hess Kerry Wendell Thornley  More
The post A Brief History of The Spark: A Journal of Contemporary Anarchist Thought appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve O’Keefe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Marxism, Economic Parasites, and Debt Cancellation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268083</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/michael-hudson-marxism-economic-parasites-and-debt-cancellation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson in a bracing talk, including history of crises, the role of debt, and how ancient Greek and Roman law promoted inequality]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economy Created 275,000 Jobs in February, Unemployment Edged Up to 3.9 Percent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315807</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/economy-created-275000-jobs-in-february-unemployment-edged-up-to-3-9-percent/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T04:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economy continued to create jobs at a rapid pace last month, with payroll employment up by 275,000. However, any concerns about an excessive pace of job growth are alleviated by the fact that the prior two months’ total was revised down by 167,000. This puts the three-month average at 265,000. The household survey showed  More
The post Economy Created 275,000 Jobs in February, Unemployment Edged Up to 3.9 Percent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Last Chance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/11/bidens-last-chance/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T04:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue I watched President Joe Biden delivering his March 7, 2024 State of the Union speech. “My lifetime,” he said, “has taught me to embrace freedom and democracy. A future based on the core values that have defined America: honesty, decency, dignity, equality. To respect everyone. To give everyone a fair shot. To give hate  More
The post Biden’s Last Chance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the State of the Union Speech: What Biden Left Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268129</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/on-the-state-of-the-union-speech-what-biden-left-out.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T20:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a post about nothing; or rather the nothing that is where one would expect a something to appear]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing 2024 Water Cooler Fundraiser!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268102</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/announcing-2024-water-cooler-fundraiser.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T16:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My goal is 🌡️ 400 donors, an increase of 25 over last year. If you can give a lot, give a lot. If you can only give a little, give a little. (You can also pay it forward by donating on behalf of those whose circumstances do not permit them to do so, this year.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Middlemen Are Profiting off the Broken US Pharma System]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/pharmacy-benefit-managers-drug-prices-congress/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/pharmacy-benefit-managers-drug-prices-congress/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T16:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Lawmakers from both parties and thirty-nine state attorneys general joined forces to stop the shadowy corporate middlemen behind rising drug prices and the death of independent pharmacies. Now these reform efforts are in peril, following nearly $50 million in industry lobbying — including tens of thousands to congressmembers who sponsored reform legislation. These largely unregulated [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unions Can’t Be Rebuilt Piecemeal. We Need to Go Big.]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/cio-sit-down-strikes-roosevelt-communists/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/cio-sit-down-strikes-roosevelt-communists/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T14:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Erik Loomis is a professor of history at the University of Rhode Island and the author of A History of America in Ten Strikes (New Press, 2018) and Empire of Timber: Labor Unions and the Pacific Northwest Forests (Cambridge University Press, 2016). Loomis presents here a strong case in favor of the idea that the [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Todd Prophesies the Defeat of the West]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/emmanuel-todd-demography-religion-putin-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/emmanuel-todd-demography-religion-putin-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T11:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Western admirers of Vladimir Putin’s Russia are a strangely assorted bunch, with each finding quite different things to like about it. Tucker Carlson raves about the living standards. He returned from a recent journey to Moscow enthusing over the spotless Metro system and the cheap supermarkets. The Putin-understanders of the German far right see [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 3/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268085</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/links-3-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T10:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our world-class daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Archaeological Discovery of Our Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=268097</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/03/the-great-archaeological-discovery-of-our-time.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T10:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with renowned archaeologist Gary M. Feinman on the emergence of a global data set from our past that humanity can use to prosper—and avoid the biggest mistakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debating Class Dealignment]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/debating-class-dealignment-democrats-republicans/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/debating-class-dealignment-democrats-republicans/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T09:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A specter is haunting socialist politics — the specter of the “Brahmin left.” The renowned political economist Thomas Piketty, with Amory Gethin and Clara Martínez-Toledano, discussed this group in an influential 2022 research paper on political cleavages in Western democracies since the mid-twentieth century. This group is referring to highly educated voters, typically employed in [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gary Convention Elided Black America’s Internal Disunity]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/gary-convention-civil-rights-black-power-class/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/gary-convention-civil-rights-black-power-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T08:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Between March 10th and 12th of 1972, the West Side High School auditorium was buzzing with excitement and hope. The room was filled with a tour de force of black political activists, politicians, and cultural figures. Comedian Dick Gregory delivered his usual mix of jokes and political commentary, while Muhammad Ali served as sergeant at [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times’ Bret Stephens, Hasbarist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315693</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/10/bret-stephens-hasbarist/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T07:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bret Stephens speaking at the 92nd Street Y, Youtube screenshot.
On October 15, 2023, a week after Hamas’s attack on Israel and in the early days of an indiscriminate Israeli response, New York Times editorialist Bret Stephens wrote a column titled “Hamas Bears the Blame for Every Death in This War.”
After allowing that “[r]easonable people can criticize Israel for not allowing enough time for civilians to get out of harm’s way,” Stephens, having rhetorically covered himself, endorses the impending ground invasion and arrives at the conclusion inscribed in the column’s title. “The central cause of Gaza’s misery is Hamas,” he writes. “It alone bears the blame for the suffering it has inflicted on Israel and knowingly invited against Palestinians.”
After five months of war, at least 30,000 Palestinians dead (12,000 children, certainly an undercount), innumerable documented atrocities, a partial indictment for genocide, and the prospect of a spiraling Middle East conflagration, you might think his tune would have shifted, even a little. After all, even Tom Friedman has managed to squeeze out some criticism of Israel.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The New York Times’ Bret Stephens, Hasbarist appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Biden and the Democrats Can Appear to Do About Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315743</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/10/what-biden-and-the-democrats-can-appear-to-do-about-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T06:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Adam Schultz, White House.
When it comes to the genocide that the United States is helping Israel inflict on Gaza, Joe Biden is never more repugnant than when he pretends to care.
I actually prefer his one-sided regional empathy: tedious reminiscences of chats with Golda Meir and odious references to Israel’s psychopathic Prime Minister as “Bibi”. { A  term of endearment which for me has long since become the moral equivalent of musing about Reichsführer Himmler as “Heiny”. }
Yet while Biden’s casual enabling of wanton carnage has wrought a humanitarian nightmare, there is a public relations solution to Gaza so simple I’m surprised the hierarchy of the Democratic Party hasn’t stapled it atop Joe’s binder and marked it “FOR IMMEDIATE PRATTLE”. 		
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What Biden and the Democrats Can Appear to Do About Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ding Dong, Former Canadian PM Brian Mulroney Is Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/brian-mulroney-canada-neoliberalism-privatization/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/brian-mulroney-canada-neoliberalism-privatization/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T16:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Whether they like it or not, Canadians are still living in the Canada that Brian Mulroney shaped, even if it isn’t exactly what he envisioned. Superficially progressive, fundamentally conservative, Mulroney sold out Canadian economic and political sovereignty to assume something of a privileged role as a vassal state to the United States. He cultivated Canada’s [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evelyn Trent Was One of America’s Great Revolutionaries]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/evelyn-trent-india-mexico-revolution/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/evelyn-trent-india-mexico-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T14:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In the history of the US left, Evelyn Trent (1892–1970) is a shamefully neglected figure. If known at all, she is merely remembered as the American wife of the dashing, globe-trotting Indian anti-colonial revolutionary M. N. Roy. Active at a critical conjuncture in the 1920s, Trent helped found the communist parties of Mexico and India. [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starvation Games]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315689</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/09/starvation-games/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T13:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lethal air drops of aid over Gaza.
With more than a half-million Gazans already facing starvation and more and more children dying of hunger, Biden’s solution, a floating port, will take 30-60 days to build and even then Israeli forces will still be in charge of inspecting the trucks of supplies, the main reason trucks are backed up for miles at the entry points into Gaza. Even the trickle of humanitarian supplies and food Biden has pledged to provide to Palestinians in Gaza won’t do much, if any, good, if there’s no one there to distribute it and Israel just moved to deny visas to the aid workers who have the experience and means to get the aid where it needs to go, a clear strategy to double down on its warfare by starvation. 		
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Starvation Games appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kohei Saito’s “Start From Scratch” Degrowth Communism]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/kohei-saito-degrowth-communism-environment-marxism/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/kohei-saito-degrowth-communism-environment-marxism/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T12:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Almost every day, it seems as though the headlines deliver some fresh grim episode of the unaffordability of everyday life for millions of ordinary people, from greedflation to the housing crisis, from the soaring cost of education and health care to how roughly 60 percent of Americans live paycheck to paycheck. Across the advanced capitalist [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<cite>Union</cite> Gives a Close Look at the Historic Amazon Labor Union Win]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/amazon-labor-union-documentary-christian-smalls/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/amazon-labor-union-documentary-christian-smalls/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T10:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In 2022, a group of Amazon workers stunned the world by winning a union election at the huge JFK8 warehouse in Staten Island, New York. Many had wondered if Amazon workers in the United States could ever win a union election at the corporate giant, which transformed from a small online bookseller in the 1990s [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<cite>Perfect Days</cite> Celebrates Spare, Mindful Escapism]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/perfect-days-wim-wenders-japan-escapism/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/perfect-days-wim-wenders-japan-escapism/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T09:44:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I can see why people love Perfect Days, the new Wim Wenders film about a Japanese toilet cleaner named Hirayama (Kōji Yakusho) who lives a quiet, solitary life of aesthetic appreciation expressed through his love of music, photography, and gardening. It’s a prevalent fantasy of our times, that we could somehow escape through ascetic choices [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Portugal’s Election, the Center Left Struggles to Hold On]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/portugal-election-socialist-party-santos/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/portugal-election-socialist-party-santos/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This Sunday, Portugal votes in a snap general election that will mark the end of Socialist Party prime minister António Costa’s eight years in power. Despite three election victories, Costa had to step down in November after prosecutors suggested that he may be involved in a major corruption scheme. Costa’s rule has been through different [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC’s new climate rules were a missed opportunity to accelerate corporate action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089648</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/08/1089648/the-secs-new-climate-rules-were-a-missed-opportunity-to-accelerate-corporate-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T19:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the US Securities and Exchange Commission enacted a set of long-awaited climate rules, requiring most publicly traded companies to disclose their greenhouse-gas emissions and the climate risks building up on their balance sheets.  Unfortunately, the federal agency watered down the regulations amid intense lobbying from business interests, undermining their ultimate effectiveness—and missing the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dara O'Rourke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaires Hate This One Weird Trick: Taxing Them]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/billionaire-global-wealth-tax-proposal-brazil/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/billionaire-global-wealth-tax-proposal-brazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In 2023, the world’s billionaires were worth a collective $12.7 trillion dollars. For a sense of scale, that’s a value roughly half of the 2023 US GDP, which was $23.4 trillion. As Oxfam reports, from 2020 to 2022, the planet’s top 1 percenters took in nearly twice as much wealth as the rest of the [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s State of the Union Showcased a President in Denial]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/biden-state-of-the-union/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/biden-state-of-the-union/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last night’s State of the Union (SOTU) address made official what we’ve heard now from countless pieces of reporting: despite every warning sign about his handling of both the economy and Israel’s genocide in Gaza, President Joe Biden will continue stubbornly doubling down on his approach to both — despite the majority of both official [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log Explorer: monitor security events without third-party storage]]></title>
        <id>65e9e84ca5fcdf000a08aaa8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/log-explorer"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the combined power of Security Analytics + Log Explorer, security teams can analyze, investigate, and monitor for security attacks natively within Cloudflare, reducing time to resolution and overall cost of ownership for customers by eliminating the need to forward logs to third-party SIEMs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Sells</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launching email security insights on Cloudflare Radar]]></title>
        <id>65e9e88ca5fcdf000a08aabc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/email-security-insights-on-cloudflare-radar"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Email Security section on Cloudflare Radar provides insights into the latest trends around threats found in malicious email, sources of spam and malicious email, and the adoption of technologies designed to prevent abuse of email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol detection with Cloudflare Gateway]]></title>
        <id>65e9e87aa5fcdf000a08aab4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/gatway-protocol-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Gateway, our secure web gateway (SWG), now supports the detection, logging, and filtering of network protocols using packet payloads without the need for inspection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Aggarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network performance update: Security Week 2024]]></title>
        <id>65e9e852a5fcdf000a08aaac</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-performance-update-security-week-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is the fastest provider in 44% of networks around the world for 95th percentile connection time. Let’s dig into the data and talk about how we do it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Tuber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing chaos in Cloudflare offices]]></title>
        <id>65e9e891a5fcdf000a08aac0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/harnessing-office-chaos"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post will cover the new sources of “chaos” that have been added to LavaRand and how you can make use of that harnessed chaos in your next application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cefan Daniel Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Requests for Information (RFIs) and Priority Intelligence Requirements (PIRs) for threat intelligence teams]]></title>
        <id>65e7cdc8a5fcdf000a089ddc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/threat-intel-rfi-pir"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Security Center now houses Requests for Information (RFIs) and Priority Intelligence Requirements (PIRs). These features are available via API as well and Cloudforce One customers can start leveraging them today for enhanced security analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Javier Castro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s URL Scanner, new features, and the story of how we built it]]></title>
        <id>65e9e85aa5fcdf000a08aab0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-urlscanner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the enhanced URL Scanner API: Now with direct access from the Security Center Investigate Portal, enjoy unlisted scans, multi-device screenshots, and seamless integration within the Cloudflare ecosystem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sofia Cardita</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: organoid uses, and open source voting machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089630</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/08/1089630/the-download-organoid-uses-and-open-source-voting-machines/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. The many uses of mini-organs This week, we reported on a team of researchers who managed to grow lung, kidney, and intestinal organoids from fetal cells. Because these tiny 3D cell clusters mimic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Legislatures Are Waging War on Public Schools]]></title>
        <id>https://jacobin.com/2024/03/public-charter-schools-lgbtq-policy/</id>
        <link href="https://jacobin.com/2024/03/public-charter-schools-lgbtq-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:06:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On February 8, sixteen-year-old nonbinary sophomore Nex Benedict died of causes that have yet to be explained to the public. The day before, Nex had told a police officer they were beaten by three schoolmates in a bathroom at their Oklahoma high school. Sue Benedict, Nex’s grandmother and adoptive parent, told the Independent that Nex [&hellip;]</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacobin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins and Crypto Shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28471</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/stablecoins-and-crypto-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, we described the rapid growth of the stablecoin market over the past few years and then discussed the TerraUSD stablecoin run of May 2022. The TerraUSD run, however, is not the only episode of instability experienced by a stablecoin. Other noteworthy incidents include the June 2021 run on IRON and, more recently, the de-pegging of USD Coin’s secondary market price from $1.00 to $0.88 upon the failure of Silicon Valley Bank in March 2023. In this post, based on our recent staff report, we consider the following questions: Do stablecoin investors react to broad-based shocks in the crypto asset industry? Do the investors run from the entire stablecoin industry, or do they engage in a flight to safer stablecoins? We conclude with some high-level discussion points on potential regulations of stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenechukwu Anadu, Pablo D. Azar, Marco Cipriani, Thomas Eisenbach, Catherine Huang, Mattia Landoni, Gabriele La Spada, Marco Macchiavelli, Antoine Malfroy-Camine, and J. Christina Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A plan to bring down drug prices could threaten America’s technology boom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089592</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/08/1089592/a-plan-to-bring-down-drug-prices-could-threaten-americas-technology-boom/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty years ago, Kendall Square in Cambridge, Massachusetts, was full of deserted warehouses and dying low-tech factories. Today, it is arguably the center of the global biotech industry.  During my 30 years in MIT’s Technology Licensing Office, I witnessed this transformation firsthand, and I know it was no accident. Much of it was the direct…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lita Nelsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The many uses of mini-organs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089612</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/08/1089612/the-many-uses-of-mini-organs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article first appeared in The Checkup, MIT Technology Review’s weekly biotech newsletter. To receive it in your inbox every Thursday, and read articles like this first, sign up here. This week I wrote about a team of researchers who managed to grow lung, kidney, and intestinal organoids from fetal cells floating around in the amniotic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cassandra Willyard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Madeleine Albright Got the War the U.S. Wanted]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315221</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/how-madeleine-albright-got-the-war-the-u-s-wanted/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T07:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-five years have passed since the U.S.-orchestrated NATO attack on Yugoslavia. As the United States readied its forces for war in 1999, it organized a peace conference that was ostensibly intended to resolve differences between the Yugoslav government and secessionist ethnic Albanians in Kosovo on the future status of the province. A different scenario was being played out behind the scenes, however. U.S. officials wanted war and deliberately set up the process to fail, which they planned to use as a pretext for war. More
The post How Madeleine Albright Got the War the U.S. Wanted appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gregory Elich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empire Decline and Costly Delusions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315480</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/empire-decline-and-costly-delusions/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T07:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Napoleon engaged Russia in a European land war, the Russians mounted a determined defense, and the French lost. When Hitler tried the same, the Soviet Union responded similarly, and the Germans lost. In World War 1 and its post-revolutionary civil war (1914-1922), first Russia and then the USSR defended with far greater effect against two invasions than the invaders had calculated. That history ought to have cautioned U.S. and European leaders to minimize the risks of confronting Russia, especially when Russia felt threatened and determined to defend itself. More
The post Empire Decline and Costly Delusions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Atheism at 20: How an Intellectual Movement Exploited Rationalism to Promote War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315339</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/the-new-atheism-at-20-how-an-intellectual-movement-exploited-rationalism-to-promote-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T07:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by the attacks of September 11th, the New Atheism appeared on the scene shortly after the invasion of Iraq in 2003. It became immediately clear that the Four Horsemen were exploiting Enlightenment principles to justify the bombing of women and children in third world nations.  Muslim terrorists are not aggrieved by Western foreign policy, the authors claim, but rather by their fanatical devotion to their faith. The decimation of Iraq was not motivated by elite US strategies to control oil markets, but because “god” told Bush to invade. The state does not exploit religious differences for cynical realpolitik; but rather, hateful mobs randomly attack each other because of their different belief systems. More
The post The New Atheism at 20: How an Intellectual Movement Exploited Rationalism to Promote War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>T.J. Coles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Too Obvious to be Real]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315418</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/roaming-charges-112/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human kind Cannot bear very much reality. – T.S. Eliot. “Burnt Norton” + An AP poll from this week found that 6 in 10 US adults doubt the mental capability of Biden and Trump. + What it looks like when the Void stares into you… What is WRONG with Biden? pic.twitter.com/pL5UyQ9WSK — suzy (@Suzy_1776) March  More
The post Roaming Charges: Too Obvious to be Real appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coastal Cities at High Noon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315547</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/coastal-cities-at-high-noon/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antarctica, the massive continent of ice, the size of the continental US and Mexico combined, is breaking apart more and more as a recent scientific expedition discovered unambiguous signals of considerably more danger than previously realized. “The changes to the sea-ice indicate that in the coming decades coastal cities will need to be reconfigured because  More
The post Coastal Cities at High Noon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Right to Your Life Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315584</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/the-right-to-your-life-movement/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personhood for Embryos, no isolation requirements for active respiratory infections, advancement of genocide—it's a recipe for early-onset dementia to try and unravel the current “pro-life” atmosphere hanging over the United States and to grapple with the logical fallacies being advanced as principled stands. More
The post The Right to Your Life Movement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is Joe Biden: Repolarization Anyone?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315641</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/this-is-joe-biden-repolarization-anyone/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genociden, Ecociden and Otherwise Sliden With Biden Whatever one makes of the widespread belief that Joe Biden is cognitively decrepit, nobody who knows his past should be surprised by the moral decrepitude of his corporate imperial presidency, which has included: + signing on to escalated oil and gas drilling to crank up US carbon emissions amidst  More
The post This is Joe Biden: Repolarization Anyone? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extraordinary Political Delusions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315647</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/315647/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wanting to make sense of how Republicans in 14 out of 15 primaries on Super Tuesday could vote for Donald Trump as if he were running unopposed or in the guise of an Iron Curtain strongman who is used to receiving 98% of the votes cast, I reached out to a political insider—someone I like  More
The post Extraordinary Political Delusions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cut From the Same Cloth: The United States and Israel in Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315551</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/cut-from-the-same-cloth-the-united-states-and-israel-in-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionaries in Iran in the 1970s referred to the United States as the “Great Satan” and to its ally, Israel, as the “little Satan.” The truth of their rallying cry resounds today as Israel executes, unimpeded, its scorched earth policy in Gaza. The Israeli war on Gaza has been oiled by the military, financial and  More
The post Cut From the Same Cloth: The United States and Israel in Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bad Idea Whose Time, Evidently, Has Come: Stealing Russian Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315255</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/a-bad-idea-whose-time-evidently-has-come-stealing-russian-assets/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stealing other countries’ money is not Washington’s best look. It erodes confidence in the entire American financial architecture – the dollar, USD as reserve currency, U.S. banks, U.S. Treasuries – when that confidence already is at an all-time low. Yet it is exactly what Congress is poised to do. On February 15, GOP senator Rand  More
The post A Bad Idea Whose Time, Evidently, Has Come: Stealing Russian Assets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sisters Are Doing It For Themselves]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315590</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/sisters-are-doing-it-for-themselves/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three of the leading Oscar nominees for best picture for 2024 — Barbie, Oppenheimer, and Poor Things — include women in controlling situations that make one wonder if post-postmodern feminism isn’t upon us, and, if so, how did men get so chickenchoked. Not that there’s anything wrong with that. I’m not trying to say anything  More
The post Sisters Are Doing It For Themselves appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There a Journalism That Doesn’t Love a War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315595</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/is-there-a-journalism-that-doesnt-love-a-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War, what is it good for? Well, the media for starters. Shortly after the Biden administration responded to the killing of three American soldiers in a drone attack on a base in Jordan by bombing 85 Iran-connected targets in Iraq and Syria, the Columbia Journalism Review (CJR) asked in a headline: “Is the press dragging America to  More
The post Is There a Journalism That Doesn’t Love a War? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nan Levinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discarding Old Theories on the Path to Finding the First Humans Outside Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315580</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/discarding-old-theories-on-the-path-to-finding-the-first-humans-outside-africa/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I began studying human prehistory in the mid-1990s, little did I know that I would witness a paradigm shift in our understanding of when the first humans settled in Western Eurasia firsthand. At the time, I was preparing my master’s thesis about the stone tools from the Caune de l’Arago cave, an Acheulian site situated in the picturesque  More
The post Discarding Old Theories on the Path to Finding the First Humans Outside Africa appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Barsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Solidarity and Kushner’s Shame: How Gaza Defeated US Stratagem, Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315608</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/on-solidarity-and-kushners-shame-how-gaza-defeated-us-stratagem-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jared Kushner, a former US official whose relationship to power is that he married the wealthy daughter of a man who was later to become the US president, once attempted to teach Palestinians how to handle their own struggle for freedom. In 2020, he advised Palestinians to stop ‘doing terrorism’, summing up the Palestinian problem  More
The post On Solidarity and Kushner’s Shame: How Gaza Defeated US Stratagem, Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Informal Settlements on the Front Lines of Wildfire Risk in Bogotá]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315604</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/informal-settlements-on-the-front-lines-of-wildfire-risk-in-bogota/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Don’t worry I will build a better house for you, a house made out of bricks,” said the owner of the house to her son while hugging him, almost in tears, as they looked out at a pile of debris and ashes. Their house in an informal settlement of Ciudad Bolívar, on the outskirts of  More
The post Informal Settlements on the Front Lines of Wildfire Risk in Bogotá appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalia Torres Garzón</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop the Worsening UNDERCOUNT of Palestinian Casualties in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=315613</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/08/stop-the-worsening-undercount-of-palestinian-casualties-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the Hamas raid penetrated the multi-tiered Israeli border security on October 7, 2023 (an unexplained collapse of Israel’s defensive capabilities), 2.3 million utterly defenseless Palestinians in the tiny crowded Gaza enclave have been on the receiving end of over 65,000 bombs/missiles plus non-stop tank shelling and snipers. The extreme right-wing Netanyahu regime has enforced  More
The post Stop the Worsening UNDERCOUNT of Palestinian Casualties in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale your Amazon ECS using different AWS native services!]]></title>
        <id>70b136257100414015f3edd9d302efd1f3639888</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/scale-your-amazon-ecs-using-different-aws-native-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers accelerate application development and enhance deployment consistency across environments, thus enabling organizations to improve productivity and agility. AWS container services such as Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) make it easier to manage your application so you can focus on innovation and your business needs. Customer experience is the most important yardstick by which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Chandapillai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how economics must change]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45195</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/08/why-and-how-economics-must-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T01:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Jayati Ghosh Economics needs greater humility, a better sense of history, and more diversity The need for drastic change in the economics discipline has never been so urgent. Humanity faces existential crises, with planetary health and environmental challenges becoming major concerns. The global economy was already limping and fragile before the pandemic; the subsequent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Diverse ML Systems at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d2e6b6d205d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/supporting-diverse-ml-systems-at-netflix-2d2e6b6d205d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While AI revolutionizes software development, it still relies on developers to pilot its use. In this blog, we’ll cover the skills that developers need to have for navigating this new AI-powered coding frontier. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/">Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Moderation in Wage Growth Continue?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28480</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/will-the-moderation-in-wage-growth-continue/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wage growth has moderated notably following its post-pandemic surge, but it remains strong compared to the wage growth prevailing during the low-inflation pre-COVID years. Will the moderation continue, or will it stall? And what does it say about the current state of the labor market? In this post, we use our own measure of wage growth persistence – called Trend Wage Inflation (TWIn in short) – to look at these questions. Our main finding is that, after a rapid decline from 7 percent at its peak in late 2021 to around 5 percent in early 2023, TWin has changed little in recent months, indicating that the moderation in nominal wage growth may have stalled. We also show that our measure of trend wage inflation and labor market tightness comove very closely. Hence, the recent behavior of TWIn is consistent with a still-tight labor market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Almuzara, Richard Audoly, Augustin Belin, and Davide Melcangi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How open source voting machines could boost trust in US elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089524</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/07/1089524/open-source-voting-machines-us-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T16:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the vendors pitched their latest voting machines in Concord, New Hampshire, this past August, the election officials in the room g­­asped. They whispered, “No way.” They nodded their heads and filled out the scorecards in their laps. Interrupting if they had to, they asked every kind of question: How much does the new scanner…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spenser Mestel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare protects global democracy against threats from emerging technology during the 2024 voting season]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab25a5fcdf000a08a3f2</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protecting-global-democracy-against-threats-from-emerging-technology"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, more than 80 national elections are slated to occur, directly impacting approximately 4.2 billion individuals. At Cloudflare, we’re ready to support a range of players in the election space by providing security, performance, and reliability tools to help facilitate the democratic process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building secure websites: a guide to Cloudflare Pages and Turnstile Plugin]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab42a5fcdf000a08a402</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/guide-to-cloudflare-pages-and-turnstile-plugin"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use Cloudflare Pages and Turnstile to deploy your website quickly and easily while protecting it from bots, without compromising user experience. Follow our tutorial here for a seamless integration]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free network flow monitoring for all enterprise customers]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab34a5fcdf000a08a3fa</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/free-network-monitoring-for-enterprise"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce that a free version of Cloudflare’s network flow monitoring product, Magic Network Monitoring, is now available to all Enterprise Customers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Draper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced DNS Protection: mitigating sophisticated DNS DDoS attacks]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab3ba5fcdf000a08a3fe</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/advanced-dns-protection"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're proud to introduce the Advanced DNS Protection system, a robust defense mechanism designed to protect against the most sophisticated DNS-based DDoS attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Yoachimik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General availability for WAF Content Scanning for file malware protection]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab47a5fcdf000a08a406</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-content-scanning-for-malware-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the General Availability of WAF Content Scanning, protecting your web applications and APIs from malware by scanning files in-transit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Radwa Radwan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collect all your cookies in one jar with Page Shield Cookie Monitor]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab2ca5fcdf000a08a3f6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/collect-all-your-cookies-in-one-jar"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting online privacy starts with knowing what cookies are used by your websites. Page Shield extends transparent monitoring to HTTP cookies, empowering security and compliance teams with an easy overview without the need for an external scanner, nor changing existing web applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zhiyuan Zheng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Download: hydropower’s rocky path ahead, and how to reverse falling birth rates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.technologyreview.com/?p=1089593</id>
        <link href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2024/03/07/1089593/the-download-hydropowers-rocky-path-ahead-and-how-to-reverse-falling-birth-rates/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is today’s edition of The Download, our weekday newsletter that provides a daily dose of what’s going on in the world of technology. Emissions hit a record high in 2023. Blame hydropower. Hydropower is one of the world’s largest sources of renewable electricity. But last year, weather conditions caused hydropower to fall short in a major…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rhiannon Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It&#8217;s all demand side]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203144/0/themoneyillusion~Its-all-demand-side/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203144/0/themoneyillusion~Its-all-demand-side/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s The Economist: The economists who had warned that excessive stimulus and overheating demand, rather than production snarls, would make inflation a more serious problem seemed prescient. In the shorthand of the day, it looked as if &#8220;Team Persistent&#8221; had defeated &#8220;Team Transitory&#8221;. Fast-forward to the present, and something strange has happened. The Fed, along [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203144/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787746">>5% N-gDp. Powell should have and could have stopped the ...</a> <i>by spencer</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787542">Prof. Sumner,   This is a golden opportunity to disagree with ...</a> <i>by TravisV</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787218">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6786788">What's the practical difference between average inflation ...</a> <i>by Robert Simmons</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6786754">Robert, Yes, but average inflation targeting should produce a ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It&#8217;s all demand side]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203144/0/themoneyillusion~Its-all-demand-side/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203144/0/themoneyillusion~Its-all-demand-side/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here&#8217;s The Economist: The economists who had warned that excessive stimulus and overheating demand, rather than production snarls, would make inflation a more serious problem seemed prescient. In the shorthand of the day, it looked as if &#8220;Team Persistent&#8221; had defeated &#8220;Team Transitory&#8221;. Fast-forward to the present, and something strange has happened. The Fed, along [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203144/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203144/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787746">>5% N-gDp. Powell should have and could have stopped the ...</a> <i>by spencer</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787542">Prof. Sumner,   This is a golden opportunity to disagree with ...</a> <i>by TravisV</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6787218">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6786788">What's the practical difference between average inflation ...</a> <i>by Robert Simmons</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comment-6786754">Robert, Yes, but average inflation targeting should produce a ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/its-all-demand-side/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How dare I disagree with the public!]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203147/0/themoneyillusion~How-dare-I-disagree-with-the-public/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203147/0/themoneyillusion~How-dare-I-disagree-with-the-public/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the populists that infest my comment section have challenged my claim that the economy is doing well, despite 51% of the public rating it as &#8220;poor&#8221;. They suggest that I am arrogant to disagree with the general public. After all, doesn&#8217;t the average American understand his or her economic situation better than a [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203147/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788788">Scott,   “…I notice that Trump supporters wish to ignore ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788621">Scott, that's interesting.   Both in 1989 and 2006 voters had ...</a> <i>by Bobster</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788567">Bobster, We didn't have an economy like this in the 1970s. A ...</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788472">@Scott,   and yes, fiscal policy under trump was a disaster, it ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788439">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How dare I disagree with the public!]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203147/0/themoneyillusion~How-dare-I-disagree-with-the-public/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203147/0/themoneyillusion~How-dare-I-disagree-with-the-public/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of the populists that infest my comment section have challenged my claim that the economy is doing well, despite 51% of the public rating it as &#8220;poor&#8221;. They suggest that I am arrogant to disagree with the general public. After all, doesn&#8217;t the average American understand his or her economic situation better than a [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203147/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203147/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788788">Scott,   “…I notice that Trump supporters wish to ignore ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788621">Scott, that's interesting.   Both in 1989 and 2006 voters had ...</a> <i>by Bobster</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788567">Bobster, We didn't have an economy like this in the 1970s. A ...</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788472">@Scott,   and yes, fiscal policy under trump was a disaster, it ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comment-6788439">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/how-dare-i-disagree-with-the-public/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loud, salty, and stupid (give em what they want)]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203150/0/themoneyillusion~Loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203150/0/themoneyillusion~Loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I saw Dune 2 in a huge theater (with only one other patron.) Before the feature presentation, I was subjected to 35 minutes of torture. First a series of ads, then one preview after another full of loud explosions and ridiculous CGI monsters. (Remakes of Planet of the Apes, King Kong and Mad Max, [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203150/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6788950">Ssumner,   Maybe I'm not familiar with your specific life ...</a> <i>by Acebojangles</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6788393">I think we are turning the corner on culture.   Whatever one ...</a> <i>by Bobster</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6787841">We now have evidence that Cheney, Sumner's hero, supressed ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6787562">Acebogangles, If you think wokism is a trivial problem, then ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6786976">Do people have much of a choice?   Lot of food is canned or ...</a> <i>by Paul</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loud, salty, and stupid (give em what they want)]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203150/0/themoneyillusion~Loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873203150/0/themoneyillusion~Loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I saw Dune 2 in a huge theater (with only one other patron.) Before the feature presentation, I was subjected to 35 minutes of torture. First a series of ads, then one preview after another full of loud explosions and ridiculous CGI monsters. (Remakes of Planet of the Apes, King Kong and Mad Max, [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873203150/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873203150/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6788950">Ssumner,   Maybe I'm not familiar with your specific life ...</a> <i>by Acebojangles</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6788393">I think we are turning the corner on culture.   Whatever one ...</a> <i>by Bobster</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6787841">We now have evidence that Cheney, Sumner's hero, supressed ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6787562">Acebogangles, If you think wokism is a trivial problem, then ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comment-6786976">Do people have much of a choice?   Lot of food is canned or ...</a> <i>by Paul</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/loud-salty-and-stupid-give-em-what-they-want/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The Political Economy of COVID-19”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45176</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/06/the-political-economy-of-covid-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New book from WEA Books At the beginning of 2020, the outbreak of Covid-19 and the lockdown practices imposed worldwide generated a global economic crisis that challenges the traditional explanations of economic downturns .  Like the economic crisis of 2008, the Covid-19 pandemic crisis was systemic and global, and this collection of essays examines it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS now supports io2 Block Express volumes for mission-critical database workloads]]></title>
        <id>e1f154044ec7ddbc580e087aadbcf76d2131d2a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-now-supports-io2-block-express-volumes-for-mission-critical-database-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 7, 2024: Post updated to change GB to GiB. March 8, 2024: Post updated to reflect correct region availability. Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS) io2 Block Express storage volumes for all database engines in Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS). Amazon RDS provides you the flexibility to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest Heroes of the year – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>1c28a1aa7d172c4f3ef6f586d0d873794d1f054c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-heroes-of-the-year-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are inspirational thought leaders who go above and beyond to knowledge share in a variety of ways. You can find them speaking at local meetups, AWS Community Days, or even at re:Invent. And these technical experts are never done learning—they’re passionate about solving problems and creating content to enable the community to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CRaC to reduce Java startup times on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>26b1f9ab0d42d8e039ae489d79cbced9ed8430e2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-crac-to-reduce-java-startup-times-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application modernization is a focus area for organizations of different sizes and across industries to achieve business objectives such as reduced time to market, improved cost efficiency, and better customer experience. Containers and container orchestration platforms have been one of the key enablers for these modernization initiatives. Many customers standardize on Kubernetes as a containers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Islam Mahgoub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Cloud Networking simplifies security, connectivity, and management of public clouds]]></title>
        <id>65e75835a5fcdf000a089d22</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-magic-cloud-networking"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Magic Cloud Networking, a new set of capabilities to visualize and automate cloud networks to give our customers secure, easy, and seamless connection to public cloud environments]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Welham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux kernel security tunables everyone should consider adopting]]></title>
        <id>65e86cb7a5fcdf000a08a125</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/linux-kernel-hardening"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post illustrates some of the Linux Kernel features, which are helping us to keep our production systems more secure. We will deep dive into how they work and why you may consider enabling them as well]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ignat Korchagin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare treats SASE anxiety for VeloCloud customers]]></title>
        <id>65e7d2dba5fcdf000a089e5b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/treating-sase-anxiety"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The turbulence in the SASE market is driving many customers to seek help. We’re doing our part to help VeloCloud customers who are caught in the crosshairs of shifting strategies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Tokuyoshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminate VPN vulnerabilities with Cloudflare One]]></title>
        <id>65e7d659a5fcdf000a089e88</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/eliminate-vpn-vulnerabilities-with-cloudflare-one"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cybersecurity & Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) recently issued an Emergency Directive due to the Ivanti Connect Secure and Policy Secure vulnerabilities. In this blog, we discuss the threat actor tactics exploiting these vulnerabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying how enterprises connect to Cloudflare with Express Cloudflare Network Interconnect]]></title>
        <id>65e7cac3a5fcdf000a089da0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/announcing-express-cni"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Express Cloudflare Network Interconnect makes it fast and easy to connect your network to Cloudflare. Customers can now order Express CNIs directly from the Cloudflare dashboard, and they will be ready to use in 3 minutes. Express CNI also simplifies setting up Magic Transit and Magic WAN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Ritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Trust WARP: tunneling with a MASQUE]]></title>
        <id>65e7d0a8a5fcdf000a089e1b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/zero-trust-warp-with-a-masque"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog discusses the introduction of MASQUE to Zero Trust WARP and how Cloudflare One customers will benefit from this modern protocol]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bending pause times to your will with Generational ZGC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/256629c9386b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bending-pause-times-to-your-will-with-generational-zgc-256629c9386b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Utility theory — explaining everything and nothing]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45173</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/05/utility-theory-explaining-everything-and-nothing/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T21:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Despite the rise of behavioral economics, many economists still believe that utility maximization is a good explanation of human behavior. Although evidence from experimental economics and elsewhere has rolled back the assumption that human agents are entirely self-interested, and shown that altruism and cooperation are important, a prominent response has been to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows authentication with gMSA on Linux containers on Amazon ECS with AWS Fargate]]></title>
        <id>4ec2c9e4d9ddbea5e7b461fc9fa5c45c03eaa037</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/windows-authentication-with-gmsa-on-linux-containers-on-amazon-ecs-with-aws-fargate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T21:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today, we are announcing the availability of Credentials Fetcher integration with AWS Fargate on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS). With this launch, you have the option of running Linux containers that depend on Windows authentication on Amazon ECS using both the Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) launch type, as well as with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cristobal Espinosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risk-Aware Product Decisions in A/B Tests with Multiple Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7002</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/03/risk-aware-product-decisions-in-a-b-tests-with-multiple-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR We summarize the findings in our recent paper, Schultzberg, Ankargren, and Frånberg (2024), where we explain how Spotify’s decision-making [...]
The post Risk-Aware Product Decisions in A/B Tests with Multiple Metrics appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community matters: Four open source trends in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6f1d879983d6</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/community-matters-four-open-source-trends-in-2024-6f1d879983d6?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking ahead at open source trends and technology in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free data transfer out to internet when moving out of AWS]]></title>
        <id>75d716af79fb6ef0c02f33b4b7ca18cfd5dd4743</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/free-data-transfer-out-to-internet-when-moving-out-of-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You told us one of the primary reasons to adopt Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the broad choice of services we offer, enabling you to innovate, build, deploy, and monitor your workloads. AWS has continuously expanded its services to support virtually any cloud workload. It now offers over 200 fully featured services for compute, storage, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your unprotected assets with Security Center: quick view for CISOs]]></title>
        <id>65e6029aa5fcdf000a089799</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/security-insights-quick-ciso-view"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are excited to introduce a new set of capabilities within the Security Center to directly address a common challenge: ensuring comprehensive deployment across your infrastructure. Gain precise insights into where and how to optimize your security posture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Moraru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Cloudflare with Cloudflare: a Zero Trust journey]]></title>
        <id>65e602caa5fcdf000a0897a9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/securing-cloudflare-with-cloudflare-zero-trust"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A deep dive into how we have deployed Zero Trust at Cloudflare while maintaining user privacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Pitts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simpler migration from Netskope and Zscaler to Cloudflare: introducing Deskope and a Descaler partner update]]></title>
        <id>65e602a6a5fcdf000a0897a1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/deskope-program-and-asdp-for-descaler"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Cloudflare is excited to expand the Descaler program to Authorized Service Delivery Partners (ASDPs) who will now have exclusive access to the Descaler toolkit. Cloudflare is also launching Deskope, a new set of tooling to also help migrate existing Netskope customers to Cloudflare One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Mahan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting APIs with JWT Validation]]></title>
        <id>65e602bfa5fcdf000a0897a5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protecting-apis-with-jwt-validation"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare customers can now protect their APIs from broken authentication attacks by validating incoming JSON Web Tokens (JWTs) with API Gateway]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Cosgrove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing two highly requested DLP enhancements: Optical Character Recognition (OCR) and Source Code Detections]]></title>
        <id>65e602a1a5fcdf000a08979d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/dlp-ocr-sourcecode"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare One now supports Optical Character Recognition and detects source code as part of its Data Loss Prevention (DLP) service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Kagan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expectations and the Final Mile of Disinflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28517</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/expectations-and-the-final-mile-of-disinflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, the U.S. economy experienced a swift recovery accompanied by a sharp rise in inflation. Inflation has been gradually declining since 2022 without a notable slowdown in the labor market. Nonetheless, inflation remains above the Federal Reserve's 2 percent target and the path of the so-called final mile remains uncertain, as emphasized by Chair Powell during his press conference in January. In this post, we examine the unemployment-inflation trade-off over the past few years through the lens of a New Keynesian Phillips curve, based on our recent paper. We also provide model-based forecasts for 2024 and 2025 under various labor market scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard K. Crump, Stefano Eusepi, and Ayşegül Şahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radar Trends to Watch: March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/?p=15488</id>
        <link href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/radar-trends-to-watch-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T11:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[January was a dull month, at least in my opinion. Maybe everyone was recovering from their holidays. February was a short month, but it was far from dull. And I’m not even counting the first shipments of Apple Vision. OpenAI has demoed an impressive text-to-vision model called Sora; Google has two very impressive small language […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Loukides</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About that 2017 Tesla bubble]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016943/0/themoneyillusion~About-that-Tesla-bubble/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016943/0/themoneyillusion~About-that-Tesla-bubble/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when the claims of bubble proponents becomes so far-fetched that you wonder if it&#8217;s all just a spoof. Bloomberg provides a recent example: Nvidia Corp.&#8217;s&#160;rise&#160;is captivating the stock market and driving the S&#38;P 500 Index to new highs. But it also raises cautionary reminders of another investor darling that soared on dreams [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016943/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-04-at-12.49.06-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785079">Jeff, It's a big mistake not to take markets seriously. I'd ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785032">@Tacitus   I think that the market for collectibles serves as a ...</a> <i>by Lizard Man</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785018">Lizard Man, we could call it a hot potato…   But, I don't ...</a> <i>by Tacticus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6784952">@ Agrippa   I continue to maintain that a word should exist ...</a> <i>by Lizard Man</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6784919">Solon,   > I do wonder about certain collectible items that ...</a> <i>by Jeff</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About that 2017 Tesla bubble]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016943/0/themoneyillusion~About-that-Tesla-bubble/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016943/0/themoneyillusion~About-that-Tesla-bubble/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are times when the claims of bubble proponents becomes so far-fetched that you wonder if it&#8217;s all just a spoof. Bloomberg provides a recent example: Nvidia Corp.&#8217;s&#160;rise&#160;is captivating the stock market and driving the S&#38;P 500 Index to new highs. But it also raises cautionary reminders of another investor darling that soared on dreams [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016943/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-04-at-12.49.06-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016943/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785079">Jeff, It's a big mistake not to take markets seriously. I'd ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785032">@Tacitus   I think that the market for collectibles serves as a ...</a> <i>by Lizard Man</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6785018">Lizard Man, we could call it a hot potato…   But, I don't ...</a> <i>by Tacticus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6784952">@ Agrippa   I continue to maintain that a word should exist ...</a> <i>by Lizard Man</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comment-6784919">Solon,   > I do wonder about certain collectible items that ...</a> <i>by Jeff</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/about-that-2017-tesla-bubble/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful (horrible) economy (economic policy)]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016946/0/themoneyillusion~The-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016946/0/themoneyillusion~The-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This made me laugh out loud: Biden can&#8217;t catch a break. For the past year, Dems have been scheming to run against Trump, arguably the weakest candidate in US history. Now they are finally getting their wish, and Biden&#8217;s going to lose. (They don&#8217;t read my blog.) Here are some truths about the current US [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016946/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-03-at-11.28.23-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785752">ssumner,   I think we generally agree and I'm not trying to ...</a> <i>by acebojangles</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785085">Michael, The global angle is a valid point.   Viennacapitalist, ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785050">Edward… liberty and decentralization? Is that why we replaced ...</a> <i>by Student</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6784950">The “trumpian” part of the GOP is the GOP.   The GOP has ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6784650">Scott,   it is not that simple:   Yes (nominal) incomes have ...</a> <i>by Viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The wonderful (horrible) economy (economic policy)]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016946/0/themoneyillusion~The-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016946/0/themoneyillusion~The-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This made me laugh out loud: Biden can&#8217;t catch a break. For the past year, Dems have been scheming to run against Trump, arguably the weakest candidate in US history. Now they are finally getting their wish, and Biden&#8217;s going to lose. (They don&#8217;t read my blog.) Here are some truths about the current US [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016946/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-03-at-11.28.23-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016946/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785752">ssumner,   I think we generally agree and I'm not trying to ...</a> <i>by acebojangles</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785085">Michael, The global angle is a valid point.   Viennacapitalist, ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6785050">Edward… liberty and decentralization? Is that why we replaced ...</a> <i>by Student</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6784950">The “trumpian” part of the GOP is the GOP.   The GOP has ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comment-6784650">Scott,   it is not that simple:   Yes (nominal) incomes have ...</a> <i>by Viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-wonderful-horrible-economy-economic-policy/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am the captain now]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016949/0/themoneyillusion~I-am-the-captain-now/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016949/0/themoneyillusion~I-am-the-captain-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after the 2020 election, I suggested that the results were bad news, as now we&#8217;d have 12 years of Trump instead of 8 years of Trump. I immediately realized that the closeness of the race meant that Trump would be back&#8212;more fascist than ever and seeking revenge against those who oppose him. Flash [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016949/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f01%2fScreen-Shot-2024-01-25-at-8.46.29-PM-1024x656.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6785089">Sean, You said:   “Seems dishonest to say the economy is ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784924">Seems dishonest to say the economy is doing well. Its doing wel ...</a> <i>by Sean</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784295">BTW, Sumner, I think your claims “He won’t enact the tax ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784279">I don't think Sumner's a fascist, but I do wonder why he so ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784136">BC, “It’s surprising that even pro-Ukraine Trump critics ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am the captain now]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016949/0/themoneyillusion~I-am-the-captain-now/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873016949/0/themoneyillusion~I-am-the-captain-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after the 2020 election, I suggested that the results were bad news, as now we&#8217;d have 12 years of Trump instead of 8 years of Trump. I immediately realized that the closeness of the race meant that Trump would be back&#8212;more fascist than ever and seeking revenge against those who oppose him. Flash [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873016949/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f01%2fScreen-Shot-2024-01-25-at-8.46.29-PM-1024x656.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873016949/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6785089">Sean, You said:   “Seems dishonest to say the economy is ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784924">Seems dishonest to say the economy is doing well. Its doing wel ...</a> <i>by Sean</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784295">BTW, Sumner, I think your claims “He won’t enact the tax ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784279">I don't think Sumner's a fascist, but I do wonder why he so ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comment-6784136">BC, “It’s surprising that even pro-Ukraine Trump critics ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-am-the-captain-now/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving from Rule-based Classifier: Machine Learning Powered Auto Remediation in Netflix Data…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/039d5efd115b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/evolving-from-rule-based-classifier-machine-learning-powered-auto-remediation-in-netflix-data-039d5efd115b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T18:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — New models for Amazon Bedrock, CloudFront embedded POPs, and more — March 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>f440c1bc8007c2c450a5b97f3269e968ed59221b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-models-for-amazon-bedrock-cloudfront-embedded-pops-and-more-march-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been a busy week – we introduced a new kind of Amazon CloudFront infrastructure, more efficient ways to analyze data stored on Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), and new generative AI capabilities. Last week’s launches Here’s what got my attention: Amazon Bedrock – Mistral AI’s Mixtral 8x7B and Mistral 7B foundation models […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Sonnet foundation model is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>afa44e98fb3dea486d0fe36887411e429dd8794c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-sonnet-foundation-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T16:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September 2023, we announced a strategic collaboration with Anthropic that brought together their respective technology and expertise in safer generative artificial intelligence (AI), to accelerate the development of Anthropic’s Claude foundation models (FMs) and make them widely accessible to AWS customers. You can get early access to unique features of Anthropic’s Claude model in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Supply Chains and U.S. Import Price Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28408</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/global-supply-chains-and-u-s-import-price-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation around the world increased dramatically with the reopening of economies following COVID-19. After reaching a peak of 11 percent in the second quarter of 2021, world trade prices dropped by more than five percentage points by the middle of 2023. U.S. import prices followed a similar pattern, albeit with a lower peak and a deeper trough. In a new study, we investigate what drove these price movements by using information on the prices charged for products shipped from fifty-two exporters to fifty-two importers, comprising more than twenty-five million trade flows. We uncover several patterns in the data: (i) From 2021:Q1 to 2022:Q2, almost all of the growth in U.S. import prices can be attributed to global factors, that is, trends present in most countries; (ii) at the end of 2022, U.S. import price inflation started to be driven by U.S. demand factors; (iii) in 2023, foreign suppliers to the U.S. market caught up with demand and account for the decline in import price inflation, with a significant role played by China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Amiti, Oleg Itskhoki, and David E. Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Income inequality in the USA increased with each expansion]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45164</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/03/income-inequality-in-the-usa-increased-with-each-expansion/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T18:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pavlina R.Tchemevra is the source of the data for this chart which appeared in September 2014 in the New York Times in an article by Neil Irwin “The Benefits of Economic Expansions Are Increasingly Going to the Richest Americans”.  Can anyone source or provide an updated version of this chart?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Commons of Ameland: An Uncommon History.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45153</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/03/45153/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-03T15:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no ‘tragedy of the Commons.’ But a tragedy of the absence of Commons-as organizations, let’s call it ‘the tragedy of uncommons’, does exist. Below, I will provide the example of the island of Ameland in the Northern Netherlands, in line with the historical examples of successful Commons mentioned by Elinor Ostrom (especially those […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lucas critique cuts both ways]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906273/0/themoneyillusion~The-Lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906273/0/themoneyillusion~The-Lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I&#8217;m occasionaly asked how NGDP level targeting would have performed in a specific historical case, such as 1981 or 2023. The usual worry is that when NGDP is well above trend, a policy of level targeting might require a highly contractionary monetary policy, triggering a recession. Here it&#8217;s worth recalling the Lucas critique (from Wikipedia): [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906273/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6784139">dtoh, Maybe, but given the gridlock in DC, how long will that ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6784057">Scott, you said “I think the Fed has to do this [create a ...</a> <i>by stoneybatter</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783418">Scott,   Just like there is monetary offset to fiscal policy, ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783296">People seem to have short memories, as I've gone over the NRH ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783284">dtoh,   1. A lack of evidence for particular departures from ...</a> <i>by William Peden</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lucas critique cuts both ways]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906273/0/themoneyillusion~The-Lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906273/0/themoneyillusion~The-Lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I&#8217;m occasionaly asked how NGDP level targeting would have performed in a specific historical case, such as 1981 or 2023. The usual worry is that when NGDP is well above trend, a policy of level targeting might require a highly contractionary monetary policy, triggering a recession. Here it&#8217;s worth recalling the Lucas critique (from Wikipedia): [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906273/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906273/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6784139">dtoh, Maybe, but given the gridlock in DC, how long will that ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6784057">Scott, you said “I think the Fed has to do this [create a ...</a> <i>by stoneybatter</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783418">Scott,   Just like there is monetary offset to fiscal policy, ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783296">People seem to have short memories, as I've gone over the NRH ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comment-6783284">dtoh,   1. A lack of evidence for particular departures from ...</a> <i>by William Peden</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-lucas-critique-cuts-both-ways/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In praise of mispronunciation]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906276/0/themoneyillusion~In-praise-of-mispronunciation/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906276/0/themoneyillusion~In-praise-of-mispronunciation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently saw a Wall Street commentator talk about how uniformed uninformed investors are piling into Nvidia stock. He mocked some people he overheard at the gym referring to it as &#8220;nah-vidia&#8221;, instead of the correct &#8220;en-vidia&#8221;. But I don&#8217;t think we should mock people who mispronounce words, as it&#8217;s often a sign of intelligence. [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906276/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783628">Where'd sds Ricardo come from?   All your ideas are contrarian ...</a> <i>by Bob Loblaw</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783298">Chris, I notice that too.</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783278">The Supreme Court overruled the radical left wing in Colorado. ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783113">I always enjoy the irony of people proudly proclaiming that ...</a> <i>by Chris</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6782758">Scott,   I downloaded The Midas Paradox. I'll let you know your ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In praise of mispronunciation]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906276/0/themoneyillusion~In-praise-of-mispronunciation/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906276/0/themoneyillusion~In-praise-of-mispronunciation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently saw a Wall Street commentator talk about how uniformed uninformed investors are piling into Nvidia stock. He mocked some people he overheard at the gym referring to it as &#8220;nah-vidia&#8221;, instead of the correct &#8220;en-vidia&#8221;. But I don&#8217;t think we should mock people who mispronounce words, as it&#8217;s often a sign of intelligence. [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906276/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906276/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783628">Where'd sds Ricardo come from?   All your ideas are contrarian ...</a> <i>by Bob Loblaw</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783298">Chris, I notice that too.</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783278">The Supreme Court overruled the radical left wing in Colorado. ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6783113">I always enjoy the irony of people proudly proclaiming that ...</a> <i>by Chris</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comment-6782758">Scott,   I downloaded The Midas Paradox. I'll let you know your ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/in-praise-of-mispronunciation/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent articles/tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906279/0/themoneyillusion~Recent-articlestweets/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906279/0/themoneyillusion~Recent-articlestweets/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. I agree with 95% of the views in this Zvi Mowshowitz post, but not this one: Andrew Biggs makes the case for eliminating the tax preference for retirement accounts. This mostly benefits the rich, does not obviously increase net savings values, causes lots of hoops to be jumped through, and we can use the [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906279/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2023-08-07-at-1.24.40-AM-1024x666.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783302">anon/portly, I also think a lot about all this wasted effort in ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783142">I think one of the problems is that economists have very little ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783131">“At this point, the difference between a good and bad ...</a> <i>by Iskander</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6782656">“Most economics papers and other academic work is useless, ...</a> <i>by anon/portly</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6782640">Jim, Isn't it obvious that most of these pundits oppose the ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent articles/tweets]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906279/0/themoneyillusion~Recent-articlestweets/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/872906279/0/themoneyillusion~Recent-articlestweets/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T16:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. I agree with 95% of the views in this Zvi Mowshowitz post, but not this one: Andrew Biggs makes the case for eliminating the tax preference for retirement accounts. This mostly benefits the rich, does not obviously increase net savings values, causes lots of hoops to be jumped through, and we can use the [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/872906279/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2023-08-07-at-1.24.40-AM-1024x666.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/872906279/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783302">anon/portly, I also think a lot about all this wasted effort in ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783142">I think one of the problems is that economists have very little ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6783131">“At this point, the difference between a good and bad ...</a> <i>by Iskander</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6782656">“Most economics papers and other academic work is useless, ...</a> <i>by anon/portly</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comment-6782640">Jim, Isn't it obvious that most of these pundits oppose the ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/recent-articles-tweets/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>89d81f50ad915d63aec01b16bf9f82dd3a8cf534</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T21:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we announced that Mistral AI models are coming to Amazon Bedrock. In that post, we elaborated on a few reasons why Mistral AI models may be a good fit for you. Mistral AI offers a balance of cost and performance, fast inference speed, transparency and trust, and is accessible to a wide range […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from the NeurIPS applied research conference]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/854061d6ceff</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/highlights-from-the-neurips-applied-research-conference-854061d6ceff?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s AI research team recaps NeurIPS conference, including neural networks and explainable AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complexity and Econ 100]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45148</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/02/29/complexity-and-econ-100/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T20:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Maria Alejandra Madi and RWER issue 106 Complexity is characteristic of a system that preserves the differentiation among its constituent elements while also preserving their identity. Complexity also implies dynamic systems, that is to say, open totalities of interrelated parts constantly changing in spacetime. The complexity of a system is related to the coexistence of intertwined parts in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wax and the Wane of the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://alistapart.com/article/the-wax-and-the-wane-of-the-web/</id>
        <link href="https://alistapart.com/article/the-wax-and-the-wane-of-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I offer a single bit of advice to friends and family when they become new parents: When you start to think that you’ve got everything figured out, everything will change. Just as you start to get the hang of feedings, diapers, and regular naps, it’s time for solid food, potty training, and overnight sleeping. When you figure those out, it’s time for preschool and rare naps. The cycle goes on and on.
The same applies for those of us working in design and development these days. Having worked on the web for almost three decades at this point, I’ve seen the regular wax and wane of ideas, techniques, and technologies. Each time that we as developers and designers get into a regular rhythm, some new idea or technology comes along to shake things up and remake our world.
How we got here
I built …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>by</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Architecture Blog Posts of 2023]]></title>
        <id>fc3e2465c18d9acd40d28e1e91cc60659e703e06</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/top-architecture-blog-posts-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was a rollercoaster year in tech, and we at the AWS Architecture Blog feel so fortunate to have shared in the excitement. As we move into 2024 and all of the new technologies we could see, we want to take a moment to highlight the brightest stars from 2023. As always, thanks to our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Courtright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Electric Cars Power China’s Growth?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28371</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/02/can-electric-cars-power-chinas-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China’s aggressive policies to develop its battery-powered electric vehicle (BEV) industry have been successful in making the country the dominant producer of these vehicles worldwide. Going forward, BEVs will likely claim a growing share of global motor vehicle sales, helped along by subsides and mandates implemented in the United States, Europe, and elsewhere. Nevertheless, China’s success in selling BEVs may not contribute much to its GDP growth, owing both to the maturity of its motor vehicle sector and the strong tendency for countries to protect this high-profile industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Klitgaard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One joins the Partnership on AI (PAI)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9202b814c170</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-one-joins-the-partnership-on-ai-pai-9202b814c170?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T21:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One is working alongside industry leaders to advance the future of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with economics — too much maths, too little history]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45142</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/02/27/the-problem-with-economics-too-much-maths-too-little-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T21:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Mainstream economists have always wanted to use their hammer, and so have decided to pretend that the world looks like a nail. Pretending that uncertainty can be reduced to risk and that all activities, relations, processes, and events can be adequately converted to pure numbers, have only contributed to making economics irrelevant […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Universal API Access from Postgres and SQLite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/?p=15473</id>
        <link href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/universal-api-access-from-postgres-and-sqlite/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T13:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In “SQL: The Universal Solvent for REST APIs” we saw how Steampipe’s suite of open source plug-ins that translate REST API calls directly into SQL tables. These plug-ins were, until recently, tightly bound to the open source engine and to the instance of Postgres that it launches and controls. That led members of the Steampipe community to ask: “Can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Udell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three principal strategies for theorizing a “new economics of ecological limits”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45145</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/02/26/three-principal-strategies-for-theorizing-a-new-economics-of-ecological-limits/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T20:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Richard Parker and RWER issue 106 Back in the late 1960s, a tiny band of unconventional economists encountered an environmentalism in the midst of radical rethinking. Prompted by Carson’s Silent Spring, capitalism and its science were being accused of major crimes—against nature, our fellow species and humankind itself.  Hiroshima had shattered confidence in the benignity of Progress, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — .Net Runtime for AWS Lambda, PartyRock Hackathon, and more — February 26, 2024]]></title>
        <id>557c364821cd44b128215dafdb19f284275de1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-net-runtime-for-aws-lambda-partyrock-hackathon-and-more-february-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Community AWS re:invent 2023 re:caps continue! Recently, I was invited to participate in one of these events hosted by the AWS User Group Kenya, and was able to learn and spend time with this amazing community. AWS User Group Kenya Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention during the previous […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing bpftop: Streamlining eBPF performance optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6a727c1ae2e5</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/announcing-bpftop-streamlining-ebpf-performance-optimization-6a727c1ae2e5?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T16:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Region in Mexico is in the works]]></title>
        <id>1c1efeb64d8a5864b3db0f67a64b46b33d53cb69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-region-in-mexico-is-in-the-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T14:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I am happy to announce that we are working on an AWS Region in Mexico. This AWS Mexico (Central) Region will be the second Region in Latin America joining the AWS South America (São Paulo) Region and will give AWS customers the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in-country. Mexico […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI models coming soon to Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>308fb7192ffb87eae22e5e1a861fa7efc2aa36a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/mistral-ai-models-coming-soon-to-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral AI, an AI company based in France, is on a mission to elevate publicly available models to state-of-the-art performance. They specialize in creating fast and secure large language models (LLMs) that can be used for various tasks, from chatbots to code generation. We’re pleased to announce that two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data security strategies to safeguard sensitive data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/a509c5afd490</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/data-security-strategies-to-safeguard-sensitive-data-a509c5afd490?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive approach to data security for real-time applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distributed machine learning with Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>4fa4e5af0a5c9a8249cf68d532af93826772df16</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/distributed-machine-learning-with-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T14:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running distributed machine learning (ML) workloads on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) allows ML teams to focus on creating, training and deploying models, rather than spending time managing the container orchestration engine. With a simple architecture, control plane transparent upgrades, and native AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) authentication, Amazon ECS provides a great environment […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Santiago Flores Kanter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Grover saves costs with 80% Spot in production using Karpenter with Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>281da0e0f7b10d2b2dc67ad5c9969cb9228b0126</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-grover-saves-costs-with-80-spot-in-production-using-karpenter-with-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T13:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-written with Suraj Nair, Sr. DevOps Engineer at Grover. Introduction Grover is a Berlin based global leader in technology rentals, enabling people and empowering businesses to subscribe to tech products monthly instead of buying them. As a pioneer in the circular economy, Grover’s business model of renting out and refurbishing tech products results […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mehdi Yosofie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World democracy map]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45133</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/02/23/world-democracy-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atheists are the new Christians]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871992323/0/themoneyillusion~Atheists-are-the-new-Christians/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871992323/0/themoneyillusion~Atheists-are-the-new-Christians/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T03:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don&#8217;t mean that literally. Atheists have not started believing in God. But in one respect they have replaced Christians&#8212;they are now the group that views all humans as having equal worth. In contrast, universalist Christianity has largely been replaced with Christian nationalism (which of course is a sort of oxymoron.) Here&#8217;s Matt Yglesias: George [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/871992323/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6779968">All true scott. At the same time, we see people who claim to be ...</a> <i>by Bob</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6777381">Another Atheist attacked a Christian yesterday.   According to ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6777003">PEPFAR may have done net good (such programs often fail a ...</a> <i>by Philo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6776746">I just read Matt's article.   Matt laments that one cannot ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6776707">I have a rule for social media: Anyone who uses the phrase ...</a> <i>by Steve</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atheists are the new Christians]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871992323/0/themoneyillusion~Atheists-are-the-new-Christians/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/871992323/0/themoneyillusion~Atheists-are-the-new-Christians/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T03:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don&#8217;t mean that literally. Atheists have not started believing in God. But in one respect they have replaced Christians&#8212;they are now the group that views all humans as having equal worth. In contrast, universalist Christianity has largely been replaced with Christian nationalism (which of course is a sort of oxymoron.) Here&#8217;s Matt Yglesias: George [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/871992323/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/871992323/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6779968">All true scott. At the same time, we see people who claim to be ...</a> <i>by Bob</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6777381">Another Atheist attacked a Christian yesterday.   According to ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6777003">PEPFAR may have done net good (such programs often fail a ...</a> <i>by Philo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6776746">I just read Matt's article.   Matt laments that one cannot ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comment-6776707">I have a rule for social media: Anyone who uses the phrase ...</a> <i>by Steve</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/atheists-are-the-new-christians/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI code generation works]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the capabilities and benefits of AI code generation, and how it can improve the developer experience for your enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/">How AI code generation works</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a singular software delivery pipeline in the open]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4255e8dce825</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/building-a-singular-software-delivery-pipeline-in-the-open-4255e8dce825?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Businesses See Inflationary Pressures Moderating]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28273</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/02/businesses-see-inflationary-pressures-moderating/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after the recovery from the pandemic recession began, the U.S. economy entered a period of high inflation as surging demand, severe supply disruptions, and worker shortages combined to create large imbalances and inflationary pressures in the economy. More recently, however, inflationary pressures have been moderating. Indeed, the inflation rate as measured by the consumer price index (CPI) has come down from its recent peak of 9.1 percent in the summer of 2022 to 3.1 percent at the start of 2024. Have inflationary pressures also moderated for local businesses in the New York–Northern New Jersey region? The New York Fed’s February business surveys asked firms about increases in their costs and prices. Results indicate that the pace of increase in costs, wages, and prices have all slowed considerably over the past year. Moreover, firms in the region expect cost and price increases, as well as the overall inflation rate, to moderate further in the year ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel and Richard Deitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate Responsibility in the Age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/?p=15409</id>
        <link href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/corporate-responsibility-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T17:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its release in November 2022, almost everyone involved with technology has experimented with ChatGPT: students, faculty, and professionals in almost every discipline. Almost every company has undertaken AI projects, including companies that, at least on the face of it, have “no AI” policies. Last August, OpenAI stated that 80% of Fortune 500 companies have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Baldwin and Mike Loukides</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for managing Terraform State files in AWS CI/CD Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>ff0f4251002e39256c4600a1ae7afd903c1179d2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-for-managing-terraform-state-files-in-aws-ci-cd-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T19:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today customers want to reduce manual operations for deploying and maintaining their infrastructure. The recommended method to deploy and manage infrastructure on AWS is to follow Infrastructure-As-Code (IaC) model using tools like AWS CloudFormation, AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) or Terraform. One of the critical components in terraform is managing the state file which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar Selvaraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Control Tower new API, TLS 1.3 with API Gateway, Private Marketplace Catalogs, and more — February 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>b59bdf9a07666673edfdba0242f35b6312ab73cb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-control-tower-new-api-tls-1-3-with-api-gateway-private-marketplace-catalogs-and-more-february-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, our service teams have continued to innovate on your behalf, and a lot has happened in the Amazon Web Services (AWS) universe that I want to tell you about. I’ll also share about all the AWS Community events and initiatives that are happening around the world. Let’s dive in! Last week’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irshad Buchh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring Windows pods with Prometheus and Grafana]]></title>
        <id>d2f4562e222d6cf4b5aa06ce9307ae6be035ea05</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/monitoring-windows-pods-with-prometheus-and-grafana/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T14:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-authored by Cezar Guimarães, Sr. Software Engineer, VTEX Introduction Customers across the globe are increasingly adopting Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) to run their Windows workloads. This is a result of customers figuring out that refactoring existing Windows-based applications into an open-source environment, while ideal, is a very complex task. It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcio Morales</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The past, present & future of cloud computing for businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/946d67d17186</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/the-past-present-future-of-cloud-computing-for-businesses-946d67d17186?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T18:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing has impacted business across many sectors. Dive into cloud computing and its future potential.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How VMware Tanzu CloudHealth modernized container workloads from self-managed Kubernetes to Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>6a954892a233855c06e22a7ce532eba8919eb7a6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-vmware-tanzu-cloudhealth-modernized-container-workloads-from-self-managed-kubernetes-to-amazon-elastic-kubernetes-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T08:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-written with Rivlin Pereira, Staff DevOps Engineer at VMware Introduction VMware Tanzu CloudHealth is the cloud cost management platform of choice for more than 20,000 organizations worldwide that rely on it to optimize and govern the largest and most complex multi-cloud environments. In this post, we will talk about how VMware Tanzu […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Thomson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T20:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In January, we experienced three incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A peek under the hood of GitHub Advanced Security code scanning autofix.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/">Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How and Why Do Consumers Use “Buy Now, Pay Later”?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28119</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/02/how-and-why-do-consumers-use-buy-now-pay-later/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, we highlighted that financially fragile households are disproportionately likely to use “buy now, pay later” (BNPL) payment plans. In this post, we shed further light on BNPL’s place in its users’ household finances, with a particular focus on how use varies by a household’s level of financial fragility. Our results reveal substantially different use patterns, as more-fragile households tend to use the service to make frequent, relatively small, purchases that they might have trouble affording otherwise. In contrast, financially stable households tend to not use BNPL as frequently and are more likely to emphasize that BNPL allows them to avoid paying interest on credit-finance purchases. We explore below what drives these differences and consider the implications for future BNPL use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Aidala, Daniel Mangrum, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequential A/B Testing Keeps the World Streaming Netflix
Part 1: Continuous Data]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cba6c7ed49df</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/sequential-a-b-testing-keeps-the-world-streaming-netflix-part-1-continuous-data-cba6c7ed49df?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lindon, Chris Sanden, Vache Shirikian, Yanjun Liu, Minal Mishra, Martin Tingley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The npm engineering team recently transitioned to using GitHub Codespaces for local development for npm registry services. This shift to Codespaces has substantially reduced the friction of our inner development loop and boosted developer productivity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/">Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SafeTest: A Novel Approach to Front End Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/37f9f88c152d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-safetest-a-novel-approach-to-front-end-testing-37f9f88c152d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Moshe Kolodny]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenAI Endgame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.oreilly.com/radar/?p=15401</id>
        <link href="https://www.oreilly.com/radar/the-openai-endgame/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T11:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the New York Times sued OpenAI for infringing its copyrights by using Times content for training, everyone involved with AI has been wondering about the consequences. How will this lawsuit play out? And, more importantly, how will the outcome affect the way we train and use large language models? There are two components to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Loukides</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Cohere embedding models]]></title>
        <id>88d3cbd7b505e228dadab86f0501d5938c543301</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-cohere-embedding-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T21:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During AWS re:Invent 2023, we announced the general availability of Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). In my previous post, I described how Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock manages the end-to-end RAG workflow […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Happy Lunar New Year, IaC generator, NFL’s digital athlete, AWS Cloud Clubs, and more — February 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>568484dcfa30bc001b0bf56c13972382e5ce2537</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-happy-lunar-new-year-iac-generator-nfls-digital-athlete-aws-cloud-clubs-and-more-february-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T20:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Lunar New Year! Wishing you a year filled with joy, success, and endless opportunities! May the Year of the Dragon bring uninterrupted connections and limitless growth 🐉 ☁️ In case you missed it, here’s outstanding news you need to know as you plan your year in early 2024. AWS was named as a Leader […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring Treasury Market Depth]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28161</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/02/measuring-treasury-market-depth/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A commonly used measure of market liquidity is market depth, which refers to the quantity of securities market participants are willing to buy or sell at particular prices. The market depth of U.S. Treasury securities, in particular, is assessed in many analyses of market functioning, including this Liberty Street Economics post on liquidity in 2023, this article on market functioning in March 2020, and this paper on liquidity after the Global Financial Crisis. In this post, we review the many measurement decisions that go into depth calculations and show that inferences about the evolution of Treasury market depth, and hence liquidity, are largely invariant with respect to these decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Fleming, Isabel Krogh, and Claire Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>