<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-12T06:30:35.215Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-12T06:30:35.215Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Forgotten Faces on the Uranium Trail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325137</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/the-forgotten-faces-on-the-uranium-trail/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T06:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite piece of fictional writing of all time is the play for voices, Under Milk Wood by the Welsh writer, Dylan Thomas. It opens like this: “To begin at the beginning”. If you want to put human faces to the story of nuclear power, you have to begin at the beginning. That’s why those  More
The post The Forgotten Faces on the Uranium Trail appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Pentz Gunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year of Immanuel Kant and Black Enlightenment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325085</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/the-year-of-immanuel-kant-and-black-enlightenment/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T06:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just recently, Shoshana Liessmann and Antje Herzog wrote about Immanuel Kant in honor of his 300th birthday and explained how the celebrated “revolutionary thinker and one of the most prominent philosophers of the Enlightenment” could also be placed under “critical scrutiny.” They write, with “His overt racism, anti-Judaism, and disparaging remarks about women …. How  More
The post The Year of Immanuel Kant and Black Enlightenment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sana’ and Milad Daqqah: Reproductive Heroism Defies Israel’s Prisons and Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325134</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/sana-and-milad-daqqah-reproductive-heroism-defies-israels-prisons-and-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milad was conceived through the smuggling of sperm by Walid Daqqah from inside an Israeli prison. She was born to Sana’ in February 2020 during the 34th year of Walid’s imprisonment.  Walid and Sana’ met in a prison visiting room in 1996 when Sana’ came to report on prisoner conditions. In 1999 they won the difficult fight to get married inside Ashkelon prison with the presence of their comrades and members of their family. However, they were unable to win their struggle for conjugal visits. More
The post Sana’ and Milad Daqqah: Reproductive Heroism Defies Israel’s Prisons and Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Buttu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Absence — and Presence — of Daniel Ellsberg]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325126</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/the-absence-and-presence-of-daniel-ellsberg/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a warm evening almost a decade ago, I sat under the stars with Daniel Ellsberg while he talked about nuclear war with alarming intensity. He was most of the way through writing his last and most important book, The Doomsday Machine: Confessions of a Nuclear War Planner. Somehow, he had set aside the denial so  More
The post The Absence — and Presence — of Daniel Ellsberg appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the Energy Transition: Renewables Abound, but Grid Challenges Loom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325264</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/navigating-the-energy-transition-renewables-abound-but-grid-challenges-loom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 stands out as a year in which climate records were set. It also showed us that we have put the cart before the horse regarding renewable energy. Firstly, the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) reported in January 2024 that in the year prior, the planet experienced its highest temperatures ever recorded since global temperature records  More
The post Navigating the Energy Transition: Renewables Abound, but Grid Challenges Loom appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erick Shelby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intruder at Large: The United States in the Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325090</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/intruder-at-large-the-united-states-in-the-middle-east/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Iranian prime minister, Mohammad Mossadegh (1951-53), was overthrown in a U.S.-British coup, he stated: “I am aware that my fate must serve as an example in the future throughout the Middle East in breaking the chains of slavery and servitude to colonial interests.” Right now, his words have special meaning and importance. Mossadegh understood  More
The post Intruder at Large: The United States in the Middle East appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: A Barrage of Farage in the Garage of Hellthat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325088</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/letter-from-london-a-barrage-of-farage-in-the-garage-of-hellthat/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bad news over here last week was that former City of London metals trader Nigel Farage chose our very own South East London as his General Election launchpad last week. It was right by the river that he flip-flopped like a frogman into the giant garage-like Glaziers Hall, not just to announce he was  More
The post Letter from London: A Barrage of Farage in the Garage of Hellthat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lesser Evil Gambit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325087</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/12/the-lesser-evil-gambit/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The election paradox looms. Do I calm myself down, steady my hand, pull the lever for Joe, even though it feels like voting for Netanyahu? Even though it feels like I’m loosing another bomb on Gaza? I’ve had a number of intense conversations with friends about this recently, the essence of the pro-Biden argument being: We  More
The post The Lesser Evil Gambit appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>8da48ee2807e1e4e56d1d5e36b5355877d24b331</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-region-in-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T03:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing that a new AWS Region will be coming to Taiwan by early 2025. The new AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region will consist of three Availability Zones at launch, and will give AWS customers in Taiwan the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in Taiwan. Each of the Availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini - International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini
Title: International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/01/05/ccf_int_net>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 “Solidarity is a constant attack against the system and society, an act where the words fabrication, innocent, guilty, do not fit. Because as revolutionaries it is our duty to always be guilty for this system, always dangerous and always proud of our choices. We are not persecuted for our ideas, but because it seemed poor to us to not transubstantiate them into actions.” 
 (Gerasimos Tsakalos member of the prisoners cell of C.C.F.). 
 Real solidarity between revolutionary consciences and groups of comrades is what the dominators fear most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - 2008’s communiques]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: 2008’s communiques
Date: December 1, 2010
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3269>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Communique on the arson against the French press agency (Athens, 3/12/2008)
 While the peaceful citizens where enjoying the coffee break of their inexistance in the paved street of Kolonaki, we set ourselves for once again under the “services” of destruction and prepared a new gift out of idyllic ashes. With these, we send our revolutionary greetings to the French comrades that selected to attack the network of the high speed trains, sabotaging the routes of everyday hurry and anxiety, of a determined pre-set life imposed by the bio-authority to its subjects. 
 Striking at the ordinary flaw of the system, using aggres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 9, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well-built furniture should last centuries, not a couple of years]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7793</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/well-built-furniture-should-last-centuries-not-couple-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Bray: When Lauren was pregnant with a child who’s now turning 25, we purchased a comfy dark-brown leather sofa which fits our living room nicely. What with kids and relatives and employees and cats and Standards Comittees and friends and book clubs and socials, the butt-support cushions had, a quarter century later, worn out. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by polairscience in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40650281</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40650281"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T19:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those of you who are inclined to say "HackerNews doesn't deal with politics", I hope that Lynn's story reminds you that any work you do is intertwined with politics. While I appreciate that it's a difficult line to walk, to have productive and relevant political discussion in a forum like this, politics and social acceptance are a part of every aspect of our lives. Brilliant, kind, impactful people are kept from leading the life they want to lead every day because of societal intolerance for who they are. Incredible people like Lynn who have overcome that intolerance to lead a remarkable life should remind everyone of the suffering that others go through. There are uncountable other people who are not allowed to be themselves and who are suffocated in our society, with the lives of transgender people often ending in ostracisation or murder. One of the remarkable things about technology is that it enables trodden people to escape this tyranny to an extent once impossible. It enables marginalized people to be themselves in our world.  Let us continue to enable that.
Such "political" discussions and the impact technology has on them are an important part of the discourse here. I'm sad she is gone but I'm glad to see that this post is high up the front page. If you're inclined to denigrate transgender people, I encourage you to consider that they are trying to lead an honest life. I encourage you to consider what you're taking away from them and from the world by dehumanizing them. No matter why they are who they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>polairscience</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[os poetas foram estudar Freud]]></title>
        <id>https://adrianamassocato.bearblog.dev/os-poetas-foram-estudar-freud/</id>
        <link href="https://adrianamassocato.bearblog.dev/os-poetas-foram-estudar-freud/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[os poetas foram estudar Freud
os poetas querem escrever o que o inconsciente diz
e eu, bem, ora, veja só
tento
ser uma pessoa que se pareça com uma pessoa
uma poeta que se pareça com uma poeta
e que todas as vezes que, neste poema, escreveu a palavra
inconsciente
errou]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273164</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Hunter Biden -- dear Hunter! -- convicted on gun charges; Luntz focus group on Trump conviction; Library card catalogs ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by spencerchubb in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649334</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible
"The fact that I started a new career all over again, at the bottom of the ladder, after being fired by IBM and rejected by family and friends . . . may also give hope to others trapped in similar situations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>spencerchubb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mlsu in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649244"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recommend reading Lynn's story, written in her own words:
https://ai.eecs.umich.edu/people/conway/RetrospectiveT.html
It is amazing, tragic, and triumphant in so many ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mlsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DonHopkins in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649014</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649014"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lynn Conway co-wrote "the book" on VLSI design, "Introduction to VLSI Systems", created and taught this historic VLSI Design Course in 1978, which was the first time students designed and fabricated their own integrated circuits, including James Clark (SGI) who made the Geometry Engine, and Guy L Steel (MIT) who made the Scheme Microprocessor.
She invented superscalar architecture at IBM, just to be fired in 1968 after she revealed her intention to transition, then 52 years later IBM formally apologized to her in 2020. She successfully rebooted her life, invented and taught VLSI design to industry pioneers who founded many successful companies based on the design methodology she invented, wrote the book on, and personally taught to them, and then she became a trans activist who helped many people transition, find each other, and avoid suicide, fight abuse and bigotry, and find acceptance, by telling her story and building an online community.
Lynn Conway receives 2009 IEEE Computer Society Computer Pioneer Award:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i4Txvjia3p0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DonHopkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we improved push processing on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Pushing code to GitHub is one of the most fundamental interactions that developers have with GitHub every day. Read how we have significantly improved the ability of our monolith to correctly and fully process pushes from our users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/">How we improved push processing on GitHub</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticker Anxiety and the Idea of Permanence]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to LOVE collecting stickers, and in some ways, I still do. Every time I traveled or visited some place, if they had stickers, I would get at least one. They were my souvenirs from all the places I visited, each sticker told some kind of story or memory.
Over the years, I started facing a dilemma that I never truly faced when I was collecting other things like magnets or keychains: where do I put them? The idea of permanence gave me some unneeded anxiety. On one hand, I loved the idea of decorating my laptop with the stickers, but the thought of losing those stickers when my laptop died (because they all inevitable do), made me super sad. This hesitation led to a growing collection of stickers sitting unused, each waiting for that perfect place that never seemed to come.
The crazy th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21299</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/11/core-infra/mobileconfig-meta-mixed-reality-mr/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MobileConfig enables developers to centrally manage a mobile app’s configuration parameters in our data centers. Once a parameter value is changed on our central server, billions of app devices automatically fetch and apply the new value without app updates. These remotely managed configuration parameters serve various purposes such as A/B testing, feature rollout, and app [...]
Read More...
The post Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jedberg in "All three game console makers have now abandoned X integration"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40647128</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40647128"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amusingly this was posted on reddit, and the top comments were all "What's X?" "Oh they mean Twitter why doesn't the headline say that?" "I thought this was some Xbox integration, didn't realize it was Twitter".
Talk about the worst rebrand ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jedberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sofixa in "Norway discovers Europe's largest deposit of rare earth metals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646825</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646825"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On one hand, it's unfair that a country already very rich with natural resources discovers more of them.
On the other hand, if there is a country which can be trusted to exploit natural resources in a way that benefits the whole country and its population, and not fall down the resource curse[1], it's Norway.
1 - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Resource_curse]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sofixa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by duxup in "A new term, ‘slop’, has emerged to describe dubious A.I.-generated material"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646473</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646473"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slop seems like a good term for unwanted AI generated content.
But I wonder how much this is AI and how much we've sort of curated a slop pattern even before AI:
- Video game tips web pages with massive chunks of text / ads before you get to the inevitable answer of "hit A when X happens".
- The horrendous mess that Quora became with technically correct in some ways but also misleading answers to historical content.
- Medium articles about coding that are filled with irrelevant pics and blocks of text that are "not wrong" but also "not right" followed by weirdly specific code...
We had all that before AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>duxup</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Audit Manager extends generative AI best practices framework to Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>f0f3c70728357d6ed187ea0df993809736f41c25</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-audit-manager-extends-generative-ai-best-practices-framework-to-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain comprehensive visibility with the AWS Audit Manager generative AI best practices framework v2, which now includes Amazon SageMaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify AWS CloudTrail log analysis with natural language query generation in CloudTrail Lake (preview)]]></title>
        <id>24bdb2fd2e9ad8e57868d4acc1da126f35a18e52</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-aws-cloudtrail-log-analysis-with-natural-language-query-generation-in-cloudtrail-lake-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline compliance and security analysis using natural language query generation. Ask questions like "What errors occurred last month?" and get ready-to-run SQL queries tailored to your needs – no technical expertise required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon GuardDuty Malware Protection for Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>dd44be812e425caecd4fb1915afa474d215f2431</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-guardduty-malware-protection-for-amazon-s3/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty expands malware scanning to secure S3 uploads, enabling continuous monitoring and isolation of malicious files without infrastructure overhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM Access Analyzer Update: Extending custom policy checks & guided revocation]]></title>
        <id>940b08797e1a3df84f46252ee98dfbdd72457eea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/iam-access-analyzer-update-extending-custom-policy-checks-guided-revocation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New custom policy checks for critical resources, public access detection, and guided revocation to remove unused permissions - proactively securing AWS environments with tailored analysis and actionable insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS adds passkey multi-factor authentication (MFA) for root and IAM users]]></title>
        <id>21e15c1e7596eeb37b7d4390f7e9925a4b0eb8aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-adds-passkey-multi-factor-authentication-mfa-for-root-and-iam-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortify your AWS account security with new passkey MFA and mandatory root user MFA. Experience seamless authentication while bolstering protection against unauthorized access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hate reading]]></title>
        <id>https://ree.bearblog.dev/hate-reading/</id>
        <link href="https://ree.bearblog.dev/hate-reading/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:58:59.423Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever watched a show because of how annoying it is, or maybe it makes you feel angry but you just can’t stop consuming it, perhaps akin to watching a train wreck?
That’s how it feels reading my RSS feed these days.
Perhaps the biggest mistake I made was adding some aggregator feeds, one that features posts from various uncurated blogs. Which is weird because it didn’t feel that way before, but now.. I’m not quite sure what happened.
When I get lucky, I get to read and discover some nice things happening to a stranger, or perhaps read about their current struggles and dilemma. When I’m not so lucky (which is half the time), I get to read how AI is the next big inevitable shining future, and make a million dollars in a few months with a written ad every three paragraphs.
I guess it’s time to clean up my morning newspaper and manually curate it if I want to read quality human posts from now on. I feel sad for all the new, worthy blogs I won’t get to randomly discover because of this change, but I know I will eventually find my way to it if I’m meant to encounter it.
Life has always been that way, and I know it always will.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273026</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastercard Launches Its Biometric Retail Payment System in Europe, Using Poland As a Testing Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273048</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/mastercards-biometric-retail-payment-system-finally-arrives-in-europe-following-pilot-tests-in-global-south.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Buy with your eyes, pay with your glance."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buzzer Beater – Russian General Staff Aims at Ending the Ukraine by Electric War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273127</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/buzzer-beater-russian-general-staff-aims-at-ending-the-ukraine-by-electric-war.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:11:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Western press is largely ignoring Russia's destruction of Ukraine's electric system, which will bring Ukraine to its knees]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU “Center” Embraces the Right Kind of “Right”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273109</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/the-eu-center-embraces-the-right-kind-of-right.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at Europe’s elections and a comparison of the neoliberal, pro-war center with a right that abandons its EU and NATO skepticism begs the question, what’s the difference between the two?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Student protests and academic freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52754</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/11/on-student-protests-and-academic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier post (here), prompted by some writings by Jacob T. Levy, I defended the idea that student protests can fall under academic freedom. My argument for this starts from the fact that while many universities can have mission specific interpretations of the latitude and constraints on how they interpret academic freedom (non-trivially constrained […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carbon Capture Will Extend Oil Production by 84 Years, Industry Study Finds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273071</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/carbon-capture-will-extend-oil-production-by-84-years-industry-study-finds.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T09:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Canadian oil field that should have shut down in 2016 can now keep producing oil until 2100.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ABS in "POV-Ray – The Persistence of Vision Raytracer (2021)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40644023</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40644023"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I still remember when I used to leave my 386 sx 25Mhz running all night to render very simple scenes with POV-Ray (somehow sleeping through the loud fan noise!).
And the extreme excitement the day I upgraded to a 486 dx 33/66 Mhz which, thanks to the math co-processor, rendered those same scenes in (10s of) minutes instead!!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ABS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perinomics: a yet to exist discipline]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45410</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/11/perinomics-a-yet-to-exist-discipline/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Edward Fullbrook Humankind urgently needs a new discipline.  Our very survival may depend on it.  Natural science tells us that the economy now threatens humanity with calamity and potentially with extinction; and the daily news tells us that the economy’s forty-year upward redistribution of wealth, income and power threatens democracy and social order.  But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Fullbrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lz400 in "Noam Chomsky 'no longer able to talk' after 'medical event'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40643491</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40643491"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T07:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chomsky was doing so many podcasts up to the moment he disappeared from the radar presumably due to medical issues. I've seen him going for 2 hours with some nobody with 5K followers, being asked juvenile and stupid questions and answering with the patient of a Saint. He looked quite diminished physically, elderly and frail but mentally he's always sharp and his recall and memory is scary.
I feel that in his later years he made a conscious effort to talk to young people and made them aware of the history and depth of the problems the world is facing, and he used very modern avenues to do so, like podcast interviews. I will always have the highest degree of respect for this man and an admiration for his integrity, sensitivity and scholarship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lz400</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden: Pushing America Deeper into the Russian/Ukrainian War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325048</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/joe-biden-pushing-america-deeper-into-the-russian-ukrainian-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T06:07:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Joe Biden increasingly slipping America into the quagmire of the Russian/Ukrainian war? Something like the U.S. did in Vietnam? When Russia invaded Ukraine on February 24, 2022, Biden announced that the U.S. government would help Ukraine for “as long as it takes.” Despite being someone who taught classes on the “separation of powers,” he  More
The post Joe Biden: Pushing America Deeper into the Russian/Ukrainian War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Conviction Papers Over Much Bigger Crimes that He (and Every Other Recent US President) Have Committed While in Office]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324994</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/trumps-conviction-papers-over-much-bigger-crimes-that-he-and-every-other-recent-us-president-have-committed-while-in-office/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As practically everyone on planet Earth must now know, Donald Trump has become the first former US president to be convicted of felonies after leaving office. The response to the outcome of the trial from Democrats and Republicans has been predictably binary. Democrats have been reveling in the outcome and seem to think that the  More
The post Trump’s Conviction Papers Over Much Bigger Crimes that He (and Every Other Recent US President) Have Committed While in Office appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bolton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Moment of Truth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325188</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/our-moment-of-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear friends of the planet, Today is World Environment Day. It is also the day that the European Commission’s Copernicus Climate Change Service officially reports May 2024 as the hottest May in recorded history. This marks twelve straight months of the hottest months ever. For the past year, every turn of the calendar has turned  More
The post Our Moment of Truth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antonio Guterres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Socialism: the Great Anti-Theft Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324995</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/324995/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his 1869 essay Yours Or Mine, the radical American writer and publisher Ezra Heywood argued that capitalists had made stealing a fine art. Heywood had no problem in principle with a competitive market economy. But he saw state power as serving the interests of the capitalists, and he called the state “one great embodiment  More
The post Socialism: the Great Anti-Theft Movement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David S. D’Amato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering the Transnational History of the Sandinista Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324996</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/recovering-the-transnational-history-of-the-sandinista-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I submitted my dissertation in 2019, my supervisor gave me the mug that had been on her desk for years. Printed on it were the red and black silhouettes of people waving rifles, flags, and signs in the air. And in white cursive letters, it read: “Nicaragua Must Survive.” This was one of the  More
The post Recovering the Transnational History of the Sandinista Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eline van Ommen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning from the Venetian Republic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325082</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/learning-from-the-venetian-republic/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For some time I have been reading about Venice. Initially I studied what most immediately concerns me, books about the old master visual art. But then I turned my concerns to the fascinating political history, which isn’t usually much discussed by the art historians. For almost a millennium, from 826 until 1797, when it was  More
The post Learning from the Venetian Republic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hindipendence: Is the Philippines Really Free from the U.S. War Machine?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325184</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/hindipendence-is-the-philippines-really-free-from-the-u-s-war-machine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year on June 12th, many Filipinos worldwide celebrate Philippine Independence Day and the freedom wrested from Spanish colonizers in 1898. Other Filipinos like us, however, claim instead that we have “Hindipendence” (“hindi” means “no” in Tagalog) – challenging the idea that the Philippines is really free. As we reflect on the upcoming Philippine Independence  More
The post Hindipendence: Is the Philippines Really Free from the U.S. War Machine? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malaya Movement Seattle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand Tall in Your Child’s Eyes: Speak Out For Peace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325079</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/11/stand-tall-in-your-childs-eyes-speak-out-for-peace/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A father stands tall in their child’s eyes. Mine towered. He was a 6’6”, red-headed giant of a man, a farmer who loved rock ‘n roll and corny jokes. He taught me to stand up for the underdogs, fight the good fight, and stick it to the Man. He also taught me to speak out  More
The post Stand Tall in Your Child’s Eyes: Speak Out For Peace appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rivera Sun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by userbinator in "Ship Something Every Day"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641762"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMHO "every day" is far too frequent, and this ADHD-ish attitude is one of the reasons why the quality of average software has gone down the drain. Developers need to step back, think more deeply, and not worry about being pressured into "shipping code" that barely works.
The dopamine rush of your code being shipped
This frequent overstimulation leads to less ability for long-term attention. When I taught programming, I saw plenty of beginners do this, especially with an IDE, and the addictive nature of being able to edit and run to see the changes immediately lead to many of them falling into an unproductive rapid iteration loop where they were barely even thinking about what they were doing, just making random changes until something seemed to work.
Your team (and manager) sees you're working
Tough problems need time to solve, and you won't see much meanwhile. If needing to put on a show for others is more important than actually working, something is very wrong.
Your git commit streak looks good
Yes, people say this doesn't matter. But I'm sure people like recruiters look at GitHub profiles, and an empty page isn't a great look.
Optimising for metrics never works for those who can see through the illusion, and that's an increasing number of people over time. If I was a recruiter and saw that sort of activity, I wouldn't think of it as more than someone just putting on a show --- especially if the majority of those commits are effectively "thrashing" or "churning".
The satisfaction (and mental benefits) of getting something done
I can personally say that the satisfaction is far bigger the longer you've persevered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>userbinator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BenFranklin100 in "Private Cloud Compute: A new frontier for AI privacy in the cloud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641446</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641446"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If he really wanted no one to be reading his tweets he’d be using BluSky or Masto…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BenFranklin100</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rishabhjain1198 in "Apple's On-Device and Server Foundation Models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641415</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641415"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For people interested in AI research, there's nothing new here.
IMO they should do a better job of referencing existing papers and techniques. The way they wrote about "adaptors" can make it seem like it's something novel, but it's actually just re-iterating vanilla LoRA. It was enough to convince one of the top-voted HackerNews comments that this was a "huge development".
Benchmarks are nice though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rishabhjain1198</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crooked-v in "Deterioration of local community a major driver of loss of play-based childhood"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641341</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641341"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My particular bugbear here is the absolutely insanity of truck and SUV heights, to the point that even full-grown adults are no longer clearly visible from inside new vehicles (https://i.imgur.com/1dHWVxn.png).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crooked-v</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call to support Australia’s most at-risk entities]]></title>
        <id>6650a29807441c000a06ea10</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/heeding-the-call-to-support-australias-most-at-risk-entities"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call for industry to step up support of Australia's most at-risk entities, Cloudflare and CI-ISAC are teaming up to help protect Australia’s General Practitioner clinics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Ramsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by loteck in "Private Cloud Compute: A new frontier for AI privacy in the cloud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640713</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640713"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T23:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some good comments on this from cryptographer Matt Green here: https://x.com/matthew_d_green/status/1800291897245835616?t=C...
(I wonder if Matt realizes nobody can read his tweets without a X account? Use BlueSky or Masto man)
Edit: here's his thread combined
https://threadreaderapp.com/thread/1800291897245835616.html?...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loteck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bedobi in "Deterioration of local community a major driver of loss of play-based childhood"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640212</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640212"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The design of the physical environment is in no small part responsible for this. Don't believe me go to Europe and Japan where kids are still allowed to walk and bike to school, to friends places and just in general play and exist outside unattended to a much higher degree than in the US. Because in the US they would be roadkill, and even if they somehow survived outside of a car, car centric design means there's nowhere for them to go on foot or by bike anyway. Everything is too far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bedobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just enough social media]]></title>
        <id>https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:50:21.615Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve had this paragraph on the home page of my personal website for a while now:
Disconnected from social media, but will always answer an email.
My retreat from social media was gradual and uneventful. I left Facebook so long ago that I barely remember what I used it for. I left Instagram well before it became the weird jumble of videos, shorts and occasionally photos it is today. People trying to be brands, brands posing as people. Twitter broke my heart - it connected me to many cool people, helped me find an audience as a musician, and led to lifelong friendships. And then it all went to shit - though honestly, it had been going to shit for a while.
It was a clean break. For the most part, I haven’t missed social media. I’ve kept in touch with friends in other ways, from the ubiquitous…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Nition in "Apple Intelligence for iPhone, iPad, and Mac"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40639568</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40639568"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aside from the search and Siri improvements, I'm really not sure about the usefulness of all the generative stuff Apple is suggesting we might use here.
If you spend an hour drawing a picture for someone for their birthday and send it to them, a great deal of the value to them is not in the quality of the picture but in the fact that you went to the effort, and that it's something unique only you could produce for them by giving your time. The work is more satisfying to the creator as well - if you've ever used something you built yourself that you're proud of vs. something you bought you must have felt this. The AI image that Tania generated in a few seconds might be fun the first time, but quickly becomes just spam filling most of a page of conversation, adding nothing.
If you make up a bedtime story for your child, starring them, with the things they're interested in, a great deal of the value to them is not in the quality of the story but... same thing as above. I don't think Apple's idea of reading an AI story off your phone instead is going to have the same impact.
In a world where you can have anything the value of everything is nothing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nition</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Linux, farewell to toxic Windows operating systems]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7787</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/hello-linux-farewell-toxic-windows-operating-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve read a stack of articles recently about Windows 11 (11), the successor operating system (OS) to Windows 10 (10), and am not liking a single thing I’ve seen. Microsoft (MS) will soon begin forcing users to install Windows 11, whether they like it or not. If that’s not toxic behaviour on Microsoft’s part, what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by basisword in "Apple unveils 'Passwords' manager app at WWDC 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638702</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638702"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>> People don't want everything tied to one identity, one service, one login.
I think this is exactly what _most_ people want.
With password management specifically, Apple has had a Chrome extension available for a while now which has allowed me to use it on other browsers/platforms. Not ideal, but good enough for most.
On top of that, they don't lock you in with passwords. You can easily import and export your passwords, just like you can with 1Password.
Apple Music has had a web client for a long time. iTunes has been on Windows for 20+ years and Apple Music was supported via that until recently when they built an Apple Music specific app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>basisword</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ninth Circuit Supports Jacobson Public Health Doctrine, But Accepts “Non-Traditional” Covid Vaccines May In Fact Be Treatments (and Hence Should Not Have Been Mandated)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273024</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/ninth-circuit-supports-jacobson-public-health-doctrine-but-accepts-non-traditional-covid-vaccines-may-in-fact-be-treatments-and-hence-should-not-have-been-mandated.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key question for consequentialists: If "non-traditional" vaccines are in fact treatments as under the Ninth Circuit's opinion, what happens to the liability of Pfizer et al. for vaccine injury?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cletus in "Apple unveils 'Passwords' manager app at WWDC 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638134</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638134"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Apple's big problem: it's not a replacement for so many alternatives because it isn't supported on all platforms.
Safari? Not on Windows.
Apple Music? This actually has a Windows client. I'm not sure how good it is. But Spotify supports Windows and even Linux.
Apple Password Manager? Will this be tied to iCloud? Will I be able to use it on Android? If I no longer have an iPhone will it be a pain to maintain and use?
A dog cannot serve two masters. A company like Apple doesn't see any of these things as a product. They're a means to an end: to push the iPhone platform (and hardware sales). That priority will always trump the interests of a product like this.
It's also why I refuse to buy more into Google products: it's too much of a risk to lose access to everything if Google wakes up one day and decides to suspend your account with no recourse other than making enough of a stink on social media such that an employee will actually look into it.
People don't want everything tied to one identity, one service, one login.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cletus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "Apple Intelligence for iPhone, iPad, and Mac"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637674</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637674"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I always saw this level of personal intelligence to come about at some point, but I didn’t expect Apple to hit it out of the park so strongly. Benefit of drawing people into their ecosystem.
It's the benefit of how Apple does product ownership. In contrast to Google and Microsoft.
I hadn't considered it, but AI convergence is going to lay bare organizational deficiencies in a way previous revolutions didn't.
Nobody wants a GenAI feature that works in Gmail, a different one that works in Messages, etc. -- they want a platform capability that works anywhere they use text.
I'm not sure either Google or Microsoft are organizationally-capable of delivering that, at this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by blueelephanttea in "OpenAI and Apple Announce Partnership"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637620</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637620"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMO this really feels like the Facebook / Twitter integration from early iOS. That only lasted a few years.
Apple clearly thinks it needs a dedicated LLM service atm. But still thinks it is only supplemental as they handle a bunch of the core stuff without it. And require explicit user consent to use OpenAI. And Apple clearly views it as a partial commodity since they even said they plan to add others.
Tough to bet against OpenAI right now...but this deal does not feel like a 10 year deal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blueelephanttea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TechnicolorByte in "Apple Intelligence for iPhone, iPad, and Mac"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637094</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637094"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have to say, I was thoroughly  impressed by what Apple showed today with all this Personal AI stuff. And it proves that the real power of consumer AI will be in the hands of the platform owners where you have most of your digital life in already (Apple or Google for messaging, mail, photos, apps; Microsoft for work and/or life).
The way Siri can now perform actions based on context from emails and messages like setting calendar and reservations or asking about someone’s flight is so useful (can’t tell you how many times my brother didn’t bother to check the flight code I sent him via message when he asks me when I’m landing for pickup!).
I always saw this level of personal intelligence to come about at some point, but I didn’t expect Apple to hit it out of the park so strongly. Benefit of drawing people into their ecosystem.
Nevermind all the thought put into private cloud, integration with ChatGPT, the image generation playground, and Genmoji.  I can genuinely see all this being useful for “the rest of us,” to quote Craig. As someone who’s taken a pessimistic view of Apple software innovation the last several years, I’m amazed.
One caveat: the image generation of real people was super uncanny and made me uncomfortable. I would not be happy to receive one of those cold and impersonal, low-effort images as a birthday wish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TechnicolorByte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wwalexander in "macOS Sequoia Preview"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637054</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637054"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never thought I’d see the day macOS would get tiling window management. Wonder how it will interact with Stage Manager if at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wwalexander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelthuzad in "Apple blocks PC emulator in iOS App Store and third-party app stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40636485</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40636485"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Apple can block what's on "independent" third-party app stores, then the letter of the DMA may be violated or not, but its spirit is most certainly violated. Hope the EU cracks down on such malicious compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelthuzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273058</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[missives from a dream]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/missives-from-a-dream/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/missives-from-a-dream/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sunday morning, june 9th, 2024
i woke up and cried.
i had a dream of my grandfather for the first time in a long, long time.
he died in 2011 after a painful battle with pneumonia and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease. by the end of it all, he told my mom he was tired and that he wanted to rest.
in my dream, i was seated at the breakfast nook, looking through my laptop. i had a messaging app open and i was texting my grandfather. he was dead in the dream and i was talking to him in the afterlife.
i told him about how i was birdwatching now—how his little granddaughter who hated the sun and the soil now goes to forests and rivers and hikes mountains, despite her fear of bugs.
i sent him an aerial view of a plane ride. my college graduation. my friends, who i’ve all met after his passing. i told him my cousins were in college now. i said i missed him over and over again.
i can’t remember his responses. all i remember was him saying he missed me too.
it was the first time i wasn’t a child in my dream. i was myself, all 23 and some of me.
it was the first time he was dead in my dream—that he wasn’t wearing his trademark red polo and tan slacks.
there’s something bittersweet about that. i think i prefer the dreams where he’s still alive and i am still a child, clinging to the hem of his pants and telling him where to find the parking lot in my favourite mall (he knows the way so much better than i do, but he still follows my lead).
it’s been 13 years since his death. i’ve moved on, mostly. but there is a hole in my heart in the shape of our secret dates to fast food restaurants; a hole in the shape of a grandfather who adored me enough to take a drive over an hour across the city just because i missed him. it’s a hole only a grandfather can fill.
it will stay empty for the rest of my life.
ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚ੈ✩‧₊˚༺☆༻ੈ✩‧₊˚
i have two songs today. this one and this one.
i miss my grandparents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In praise of pluralism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45407</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/10/in-praise-of-pluralism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Recognition of the speculative value of counterfactualizing provides the grounding for a defense of theoretical pluralism in economics. The existence of multiple contending theories in economics is inconvenient, of course. It casts doubt on the truth content of the counterfactual scenarios generated by the predominant approach and challenges the predominant causal claims […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Jupyter Notebooks at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21209</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/10/data-infrastructure/serverless-jupyter-notebooks-bento-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, Bento, our internal Jupyter notebooks platform, is a popular tool that allows our engineers to mix code, text, and multimedia in a single document. Use cases run the entire spectrum from what we call “lite” workloads that involve simple prototyping to heavier and more complex machine learning workflows. However, even though the lite [...]
Read More...
The post Serverless Jupyter Notebooks at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New AWS Heroes, Amazon API Gateway, Amazon Q and more (June 10, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>9cfd65284251edc6dd58c8e354d0d331f26c8185</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-aws-heroes-amazon-api-gateway-amazon-q-and-more-june-10-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last AWS Weekly Roundup, Channy reminded us on how life has ups and downs. It’s just how life is. But, that doesn’t mean that we should do it alone. Farouq Mousa, AWS Community Builder, is fighting brain cancer and Allen Helton, AWS Serverless Hero, his daughter is fighting leukemia. If you have a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the 2024 EU Election: Internet traffic trends and cybersecurity insights]]></title>
        <id>666716c4e955c4000a8b4cf1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exploring-the-2024-eu-election-internet-traffic-trends-and-cybersecurity-insights"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 EU Parliament election caused declines in Internet traffic during voting and spikes during results announcements, with persistent cyber threats targeting government sites]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by toddmorey in "Understanding the neuroscience behind burnout (2022)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40633255</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40633255"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T13:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I parent a child with autism. The care needs are intense; the burnout is real. But I can't employ usual burnout mitigation techniques like taking time off or making career / lifestyle changes. The world relentlessly marches forward. However, I've learned human resilience is AMAZING. You'll be surprised at what you are capable of when life asks for it.
Here are a few big insights that have really helped me:
- You never have to feel like doing something to start doing it. This insight is so strangely freeing. It really got me out of my head and the loop that I was in berating myself about motivation.
- The act of doing something is usually what creates motivation to continue. Tell yourself you'll spend 30 minutes on whatever it is. No matter what it is, I always know I can survive 30 minutes of it. However, 90% of the time, the timer goes off, but I don't feel like stopping. I've found my grove and I keep going.
- Procrastination isn't poor time management; it's poor emotional management. Be gentle with yourself. Know that you can be scared, frustrated, or angry but don't have to let those emotions define you. CBT works really well here. Don't define emotions as "good" or "bad". Define them as "useful". If the emotion you feel isn't useful, acknowledge it, but realize it's fleeting and let it pass on. Some people like to visualize emotions as clouds drifting by.
"And whatever your labors and aspirations, in the noisy confusion of life, keep peace in your soul. With all its sham, drudgery and broken dreams, it is still a beautiful world. Be cheerful. Strive to be happy."
(My grandmother, who survived the Great Depression on a farm, had the Desiderata posted on her wall. https://www.desiderata.com/desiderata.html)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>toddmorey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian Endgame in Ukraine and European Resistance to “Right Wing” Advances: A Thought Experiment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273036</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/the-russian-endgame-in-ukraine-and-european-resistance-to-right-wing-advances-a-thought-experiment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T12:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How the unexpected success of right wing parties in France, Germany, and Austria might be focusing a few minds about Russia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273016</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T10:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hcrean in "Elsevier embeds a hash in the PDF metadata that is unique for each download (2022)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40631834</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40631834"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine working this hard to track down people sharing ideas, that you didn't work to produce or fund in the first place, in order to punish them for not giving you a financial cut... Companies like this are just holding humanity back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hcrean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The importance of record keeping and choosing your platform]]></title>
        <id>https://isejael.com/record-keeping/</id>
        <link href="https://isejael.com/record-keeping/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you certainly will not know, I have been writing blogs for almost ten years. Do I have any proof of this? I do not. For I have deleted them all. Why?, I hear you not ask, well I never felt comfortable with the name, the platform, you name it. All I wanted to do was write but I found myself instead worrying about being judged, rejected, subscriber numbers, aesthetics, and the time it took to load a page on Wordpress.
shudders
I began, like most of us, on Wordpress. After growing disillusioned with it and the years it took to rectify margins, I transitioned to Medium. Medium promised me the world, money and followers. It encouraged me to write often and with hooks. It spat out posts by writers claiming they made their first million on Medium.
It was the worst writing of my life.
To this d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complicity in Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324992</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/complicity-in-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T06:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With likely findings of war crimes and genocide by the International Court of Justice (ICJ) against Israel; and arrest warrants against two members of the Israeli war cabinet by the International Criminal Court (ICC), it may be time to consider the possible liabilities of the state and individual parties that have aided and abetted Israel in its war on Gaza. What are the governing laws?  How have the international legal institutions addressed complicity in other cases of genocide?  Could the complicity provisions apply to the United States and its leaders  for assisting Israel in a war on Gaza that has cost so many thousands of civilian lives? More
The post Complicity in Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Should End the Fossil Fuel Industry’s Secret Weapon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324981</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/biden-should-end-the-fossil-fuel-industrys-secret-weapon/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an obscure mechanism by which fossil fuel companies maintain their global domination even as their products are destroying our futures. Most rank-and-file climate activists haven’t heard of it and most news media rarely discuss it in great detail. It is a tool that has its origins in colonialism and advantages corporate power over democracy. The technical term for such a tool is “Investor-state dispute settlement” or ISDS. And while it sounds boring and technical, it is crucial that we familiarize ourselves with it in order to dismantle it. More
The post Biden Should End the Fossil Fuel Industry’s Secret Weapon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu and Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324977</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/netanyahu-and-germany/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For people in southern Germany, there was not much to be happy about this springtime; many were hit by the worst flooding in living history. Not a few lost the results of a life’s work. Some were aware that the major perpetrators had known – decades ago – what cardinal sins they were committing but  More
The post Netanyahu and Germany appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Censorship, Free Speech, Carol Christ & Mario Savio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325117</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/censorship-free-speech-carol-christ-mario-savio/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Cal has the go-ahead from the State Supreme Court to build student housing in People’s Park I thought of Mario Savio, one of the leaders of the ’64 Free Speech Movement who was also for several decades a colleague of mine at Sonoma State University (SSU), an hour north of Berkeley. I wondered  More
The post Censorship, Free Speech, Carol Christ & Mario Savio appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Supreme Court’s Clean Water Act Decision Threatens the Nation’s Rivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325115</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/the-supreme-courts-clean-water-act-decision-threatens-the-nations-rivers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s impossible to underscore the importance of healthy rivers: 60 percent of the drinking water supply in the United States comes from rivers. And while your tap water may be clean, unfortunately, tens of millions of Americans don’t have the same assurance, and this problem is only escalating, particularly with so-called “forever chemicals” like PFAS contaminating the national water  More
The post The Supreme Court’s Clean Water Act Decision Threatens the Nation’s Rivers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Belan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radioactive Tritium from Monticello Reactor Leaked to the Mississippi River]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325043</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/radioactive-tritium-from-monticello-reactor-leaked-to-the-mississippi-river/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US Nuclear Regulatory Commission (NRC) has formally apologized for multiple false assurances from its staff that a major leak of radioactive tritium from Xcel Energy’s Monticello nuclear reactor had not reached the Mississippi River — the drinking water source for 20 million people, including, 3.7 million in the Minneapolis/St. Paul metro area. In opening  More
The post Radioactive Tritium from Monticello Reactor Leaked to the Mississippi River appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For the Rich, One Nation Isn’t Rolling Out the Red Carpet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324976</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/for-the-rich-one-nation-isnt-rolling-out-the-red-carpet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you think the rich have life easy, do you? Just try telling that to the deep pockets who’ve spent tens of millions buying condos at 432 Park Avenue, the 11-year-old Manhattan luxury tower that once rated as our hemisphere’s tallest residence. Condo owners in the tower have had to put up with “faulty elevators,  More
The post For the Rich, One Nation Isn’t Rolling Out the Red Carpet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Abolishing War Possibile?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325041</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/is-abolishing-war-possibile/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we can end, let us say . . . slavery — the legal “ownership” of other human beings — can’t we also end other great social wrongs? Can’t we also end war? As I ask this question, I am suddenly bludgeoned by an unexpected irony, since the United States ended slavery through a brutal  More
The post Is Abolishing War Possibile? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Defense of Brazil’s Public Universities (Again)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325146</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/in-defense-of-brazils-public-universities-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Approaching 60 days, the strike by the faculty of public federal universities (UFs) and federal high school institutes (IFs) in Brazil merits attention for its resilience and scope. In Congress, far-right deputies attempt to capitalize on workers’ discontent, betting on the current government’s deterioration. On the left, especially among PSOL (Socialism and  Liberty Party) members,  More
The post In Defense of Brazil’s Public Universities (Again) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carlos Zacarias de Sena Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republican Hubris in Courting Black Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325046</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/republican-hubris-in-courting-black-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a breathtaking hubris at work when a political party seeks to suppress the votes of an entire people, then claims its leaders are the champions of that same people. You don’t have to look far to find such hubris in the Republican Party today. When Donald Trump travels the country, telling African Americans that  More
The post Republican Hubris in Courting Black Voters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forest Service Must Follow the Law Like Everyone Else]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324998</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/10/forest-service-must-follow-the-law-like-everyone-else/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent column by the Anaconda Sportsmen Club disparaged the Alliance for the Wild Rockies for challenging the illegal Pintler Face logging project in southwest Montana in federal court. What they failed to disclose to you is that federal courts have already established as illegal the same type of actions the Forest Service has taken  More
The post Forest Service Must Follow the Law Like Everyone Else appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Garrity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "A ChatGPT mistake cost us $10k"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40628059</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40628059"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No, a lack of monitoring cost you $10K. Your app was throwing a database exception and nobody was alerted that this was not only happening, but happening continuously and in large volumes. Such an alert would have made this a 5-minute investigation rather than 5 days.
If you haven't fixed that alerting deficiency, then you haven't really fixed anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Pombo Da Silva - On detention]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-on-detention?v=1717970489</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-on-detention?v=1717970489"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gabriel Pombo Da Silva
Title: On detention
Date: December 17, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15779>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 JANUARY – OCTOBER – THE STRUGGLE CONTINUES 
 To my friends, brothers and sisters, comrades
I remember that last day as if it were yesterday, when !finally! I left (was expelled from) the cold,narrow aseptic cell of the maximum security prison of Aachen, Germany… On January 16 (2013) I was escorted to the airport of Barajas, Madrid, by Interpol, and from there I was taken to the tribunal of Plaza Castilla, not before being photographed (they were particularly interested in my chest as they looked in vain to find a tattoo of the acronym FAI/FRI), ‘playing the piano’ (had my fingerprints taken) in order to ascertain that it was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Tucker - Jurnal Anarki Interview with Anarchist Author Kevin Tucker]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker?v=1717970217</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker?v=1717970217"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T21:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kevin Tucker
Title: Jurnal Anarki Interview with Anarchist Author Kevin Tucker
Date: Feb 18, 2020
Source: <web.archive.org/.../anarchistsworldwide.noblogs.org/post/2020/02/18/indonesia-usa-jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker>

The following interview with self-described primal anarchist advocate, writer, editor, independent researcher, publisher, musician and rewilding human, Kevin Tucker, originally appeared in the first issue of the new Indonesian anarchist journal, Jurnal Anarki. Jurnal Anarki is written entirely in Bahasa Indonesian, and this is the first time content from it has been republished in English. We’d like to thank comrade Eat for making this possible!
1. Looking at the Anarcho-Primitivist Primer by John Moore, he explains that Anarcho-Primiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Tolstoy - A Calendar of Wisdom]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-a-calendar-of-wisdom?v=1717970042</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-a-calendar-of-wisdom?v=1717970042"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T21:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Leo Tolstoy
Title: A Calendar of Wisdom
Subtitle: Daily Thoughts to Nourish the Soul, Written and Selected From the World’s Sacred Texts
Date: 1906
Notes: Translated From the Russian by Peter Sekirin.
Source: <archive.org/details/calendarofwisdom0000tols>

This translation is dedicated to MELISSA TEMERTY
Translator’s Acknowledgments
 I would like to express my deepest and most sincere acknowledgments to the following people: 
 professors who introduced me to Russian literature: K. Lantz, R. Bogert, Ch. Barnes, H. Marshall, R. Lindheim, O. Bakitsh, C. Bedford, M. Valdez, L. Hutcheon; and other professors and students of the Slavic Department and the Department of Comparitive Literature of the University of Toronto; my literary agent, Ivy Fischer Stone, of the Fifi Oscard Agency; my …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aurornis in "A ChatGPT mistake cost us $10k"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40627837</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40627837"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T21:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On one hand, thanks for being honest about a story of how this bug came to be.
On the other hand, I don’t think advertising the fact that the company introduced a major bug from copy and pasting ChatGPT code around and that they spent a week being unable to even debug why it was failing.
I don’t know much about this startup, but this blog post had the opposite effect of all of the other high quality post-mortem posts I’ve read lately. Normally the goal of these posts is to demonstrate your team’s rigor and engineering skills, not reveal that ChatGPT is writing your code and your engineers can’t/won’t debug it for a very long time despite knowing that it’s costing them signups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurornis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Pombo Da Silva - A Letter]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-a-letter?v=1717966612</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-a-letter?v=1717966612"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gabriel Pombo Da Silva
Title: A Letter
Date: December 30, 2015
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=22046>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 ‘..while there is a lower class, I am in it, and while there is a criminal element I am of it, and while there is a soul in prison, I am not free.’ — Eugene Debs 
 Comrades!
Today I’m in high spirits (you know our life is not a straight line, nor constant, or static…), and those who know me personally know that I have a pretty black a sense of humour (what ‘scandalizes’ others makes me smile, etc.) almost cynically (especially when it comes to talking about/describing facts to do with the ‘Law’, ‘Rights’, the ‘Authorities’, etc.); because these are ‘things’ that I can’t take seriously (even though my life is wrapped up in all tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Francisco Solar - Nothing is over]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/francisco-solar-nothing-is-over?v=1717966072</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/francisco-solar-nothing-is-over?v=1717966072"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Francisco Solar
Title: Nothing is over
Subtitle: On the need to accept the fullness of our choices
Date: June 5, 2016
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=23856>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 ‘Anarchist prisoners are not alone’ and ‘if they touch one, they touch all’ are slogans that lived once again in the everyday anarchist action before, during and after the trial against us. The screams of disgust for authority that pierced the police control and the walls around those on trial clearly enraged the judge and magistrates, as was evident on their faces and which put smiles on ours. The presence in court of dear ones known and unknown filled us with pride and joy, preventing the prosecutors’ accusations and demands from having any possibility of intimidating us. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Theofilos Mavropoulos - Chaos just around the corner]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-chaos-just-around-the-corner?v=1717964569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-chaos-just-around-the-corner?v=1717964569"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Chaos just around the corner
Date: July 9, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=10293>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

(Italy, Mexico, Greece)
 On Wednesday, June 13th, the international anti-anarchist campaign under the name ‘operation boldness’ was set up. The Italian antiterrorism forces of ROS and carabiniers were put under the command of the Inquisitor-prosecutor of Perugia Manuela Comodi, and proceeded to arrest eight anarchist comrades. In parallel, investigations are conducted against other comrades as well (among them are the comrades of Edizioni Cerbero). 
 We neither know the details of the case, nor are we lawyers to speak the language of documentary evidence or not. All we know is that the wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos - Bullets of words for the bullets of FAI/FRI]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-bullets-of-words-for-the-bullets-of-fai-fri?v=1717964491</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-bullets-of-words-for-the-bullets-of-fai-fri?v=1717964491"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Bullets of words for the bullets of FAI/FRI
Date: May 14, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=9380>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It is a wonderful moment, the moment that the enemy kneels and falls from the determination of your brothers and sisters. A few days ago Roberto Adinolfi, CEO-magister of the nuclear energy company Ansaldo Nucleare, was shot by our brothers and sisters of the Olga Cell of the Informal Anarchist Federation (FAI)–International Revolutionary Front (FRI). 
 Roberto Adinolfi is a high priest of the new totalitarianism of science and technology imperatives. Science has become the modern religion of our time, promising an apathetic society the lethargy of a stuffed belly and arti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos - Breaking down the myths of prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-breaking-down-the-myths-of-prison?v=1717964334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-breaking-down-the-myths-of-prison?v=1717964334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Breaking down the myths of prison
Date: May 13, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=9359>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 SOLIDARITY TO OLGA ECONOMIDOU 
 “Turn off the main switch in this dump. Here the beautiful becomes ugly, the choice becomes a habit and the meaningless important. Prison dirties creases and swallows pieces of dreams, desires, thoughts and feelings. Its most permanent residents, the majority of the prisoners are now a part of the appliances of the prison. Bars, yard, cameras, locks, prisoners mix all together and re-enact the world of captivity. Nothing is worthy in here. Come let’s go and don’t look back… Only fire will cleanse this place… ” 
 Prison and its numbered residents. Pris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Unless We Die for Each Other, We Are Already Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-unless-we-die-for-each-other-we-are-already-dead?v=1717964258</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-unless-we-die-for-each-other-we-are-already-dead?v=1717964258"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Unless We Die for Each Other, We Are Already Dead
Subtitle: Communique by the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire About the Hunger Strike
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/11/ellada-keimeno-spf-gia-apergia-peinas>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 On March 3rd, “justice” decided on the pre-trial detention of the mother of the comrades Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos and the second one’s girlfriend, with the charge of accession and participation in a terrorist organization.
 Behind the obvious ridiculousness of the charge, it is the morbid vindictiveness of the counter-terrorism and the judicial authority hiding, which wishes to blackmail emotionally both the two comrades and all of us. It is not ju…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Two Statements of Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-two-statements-of-solidarity?v=1717964154</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-two-statements-of-solidarity?v=1717964154"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Two Statements of Solidarity
Source: <actforfreedomnow.wordpress.com/2011/11/16/a-flame-of-solidarity-from-the-ccf-for-the-brothers-and-sisters-in-chile> & <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=8188>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

A flame of solidarity from the CCF for the brothers and sisters in Chile (2011)
When the prison bars stop our hands from throwing the fire of anarchy into the world of power, our words become the sharp rasp of escape.
 Armed with thoughts, desires, secret plans, new conspiracies, we give a warmest embrace in our imaginary meeting with the comrades of action across the world. 
 Now we want our voice to reach our brothers and sister in distant Chile to Luciano (Tortuga) prosecuted on November 22 and to Monica, to Fe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-statement?v=1717963961</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-statement?v=1717963961"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Statement
Date: 31 March 2010
Source: <sysiphus-angrynewsfromaroundtheworld.blogspot.com/2010/03/athens-statement-from-conspiracy-of.html>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 The past 24 hours find us in an extreme emotional antithesis… 
 On the one hand, great sorrow for the death of the 15-year old Afghani and the injury of his sister and on the other hand, maximum rage for the reportages of the media which totally arbitrarily and purposefully try to involve our organisation in this event. We are not usually “bothered” by the panic-ridden scenaria of the media, yet the importance of the event forces us to take a public position directly, without a connection to any attack of ours. 
 For this reason we CLEARLY STATE THAT THE CONSPIR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Political Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-political-statement?v=1717960334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-political-statement?v=1717960334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T19:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Political Statement
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/12/02/politiki_dilwsi>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This statement is made to clarify and publicly state our position in relation to our recent attempted escape from prison. 
 The fact that we are captives in the prison cells of democracy does not mean that we accept for a moment our position either as prisoners or as defendants before the civil court-martial that you have set up against us. There will never be either a prison guard to lock up our soul or a judge to rule on our values. We are eternal enemies of law and order and eternal prison breakers. 
 Obviously these few following words cannot describe the miserable conditions inside penitentiaries that are experi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Memory is our Weapon]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-memory-is-our-weapon?v=1717958906</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-memory-is-our-weapon?v=1717958906"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Memory is our Weapon
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/05/19/ellada-i-mnimi-einai-to-oplo-mas-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It was the dawn of May 22, 2009, when an explosion in Santiago, Chile caused fragments which crossed endless kilometers and borders until they brought us the news that were nailed in our hearts. 
 It was the dawn of May 22, 2009 when our brother and comrade Mauricio Morales, consistent fighter of the anarchist insurrection, put his conspiratorial plan in place, heading to the school of prison guards in Santiago in order to blow it up. But fate played an ugly game that day. The bomb our brother was carrying exploded prematurely resulting in him falling dead, just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Letter regarding the new investigations by prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-letter-regarding-the-new-investigations-by-prosecutors?v=1717958712</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-letter-regarding-the-new-investigations-by-prosecutors?v=1717958712"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Letter regarding the new investigations by prosecutors
Date: March 29, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=8558>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I The choice of claiming responsibility and not capitulation
 We as Conspiracy of Cells of Fire-imprisoned members, chose and claimed responsibility from inside the prison for our participation in our project. The responsibility claim is the least way to defend and honour the most beautiful acts that we share. Not as a memory that fades away after our arrests but as a living reality and prospect of carrying on our actions in the continuous present, the here and now. 
 We believe that the responsibility claim and the words we express through this contribute decisively to the intensific…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - In Cold Blood]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-in-cold-blood?v=1717958555</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-in-cold-blood?v=1717958555"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: In Cold Blood
Subtitle: Concerning Gatherings, the Referendum and Complicit Democracy
Date: August 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma
Source: <interarma.info/2015/08/02/ellada-en-psixro-peri-sygkentoseon-dimopsifismatos-kai-sinenoxis-dimokratias-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

It is sometimes useful to keep a distance from events before you talk about them. Anticipation and the frozen time of captivity in prison accelerate, nevertheless, the cool-headed distance from events. A self-possessed distance gives you the opportunity to observe details which are usually ignored and bulldozed by the warm blood conditions’ momentum of intensity. So, as they often say, “the devil is hidden in the details”…
I. The rise before the fall …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Fire and Gunpowder]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-fire-and-gunpowder?v=1717958445</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-fire-and-gunpowder?v=1717958445"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Fire and Gunpowder
Subtitle: From Indonesia to Chile… A proposition for FAI/IRF
Date: December 4, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 We hear the song of fire that comes from far away. The words smell of gunpowder. From the other side of the world rebellious comrades burn the nights and liberate places and moments. we can hear them… They conspire, plan, attack… We do not have to say anything else, we leave our brothers and sisters to speak for us. 
“We are all Conspiracy Cells of Fire. C.C.F. is not an organization or just a group. On the contrary it is a antagonistic expression of rage and contempt towards authority and its structures. To spread the C.C.F. all you need is gasoline, matches and t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Either with Anarchy or with Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-either-with-anarchy-or-with-authority?v=1717958374</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-either-with-anarchy-or-with-authority?v=1717958374"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Either with Anarchy or with Authority
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/27/ellada-i-me-tin-anarxia-i-me-tin-eksousia-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It’s been already 25 days that the mother of Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos and the girlfriend of the second one are locked up in the cells of democracy. 
 We have already been for 25 days on hunger strike until death, demanding their immediate release. 
 It’s been 25 days and already eight of us are in hospitals with their health condition on the limits. 
 25 days are not just a number on a calendar, it is the experiment of evolution of repression, with new methods of emotional blackmail against imprisoned anarchist urban guerrillas.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Communization]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communization?v=1717958232</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communization?v=1717958232"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Communization
Subtitle: The Senile Decay of Anarchy (or Re-Inventing Anarchy)
Date: 2015
Notes: Fragment of the unpublished pamphlet “FAI Reloaded” by the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire. Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/06/01/ellada-kommounistikopoiisi-i-gerontiki-ania-tis-anarxias-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. Frozen Marxism
 Today’s era smells like engine oil, cheap labor sweat and naphthalene of the morality of voluntary obedience… We do not want to be defined by the culture of techno-industrial fascism, the white uniforms of scientists, the neckties of technocrats, the eager silences of ordinary people, the stupid smiles of consumers… We do not match with the aesthetics of the glass world of flat t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Communique for the Arrested Comrades]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communique-for-the-arrested-comrades?v=1717958118</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communique-for-the-arrested-comrades?v=1717958118"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Communique for the Arrested Comrades
Date: 25/11/2010
Source: <guerrillanews.wordpress.com/2010/12/25/communique-for-the-arrested-comrades-by-conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Declaration for the 1st November letter-bombing against European State targets by Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
 Currently our three brothers, three members of our group are incarcerated in the prisons of Greek democracy. Their absence from our side is not rectified through the text of a proclamation. The words seem hopelessly small and insignificant against the intensity of situations and emotions that we share with them. But even during these moments, when the walls and bars of the prison rise among us, nothing has changed… Gerasim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Better to Be a Demon of Vengeance, Than an Angel of Forgiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-better-to-be-a-demon-of-vengeance-than-an-angel-of-forgiveness?v=1717957988</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-better-to-be-a-demon-of-vengeance-than-an-angel-of-forgiveness?v=1717957988"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Better to Be a Demon of Vengeance, Than an Angel of Forgiveness
Date: 2015
Notes: A signal of complicity from the Greek prisons, for the international call of solidarity made from Publicacion Refractario, Colectivo Lucha Revolucionaria (Revolutionary Struggle Collective) and Sin Banderas Ni Fronteras, to our brothers and sister Nataly Casanova, Juan Flores, Guillermo Durán and Enrique Guzmán, who are imprisoned in Chile, accused for attacks made by the International Conspiracy of Revenge and the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Chile. 
 Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: interarma.info/2015/05/05/ellada-kalytera-daimonas-ths-ekdikhshs-para-aggelos-ths-sygxwreshs-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Nothing is uglier than ugliness repe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - And death will no longer have any power]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-and-death-will-no-longer-have-any-power?v=1717957804</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-and-death-will-no-longer-have-any-power?v=1717957804"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: And death will no longer have any power
Subtitle: Concerning the fire in the Marfin Bank
Date: July 10, 2010
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=2188>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 In the incidents of the 5th May concerning the fire in the Marfin Bank there were three dead bank employees and thousands of “charred” truths. The suffocating atmosphere of the heartbreaking hypocrisy of propaganda and the worn moralistic humanism of the radical movement’s Cassandras, force us to take a public stand concerning these events. This does not mean that we are talking as “specialists” of violence, or that we are “self-appointed” prosecutors or defenders of the people who attacked the bank building. But we find it necessary that some things …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Amongst Two Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-amongst-two-worlds?v=1717957605</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-amongst-two-worlds?v=1717957605"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Amongst Two Worlds
Subtitle: International Call of Action for the Hunger Strike of the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire Until Death
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/29/ellada-anamesa-se-2-kosmous-diethnes-kalesma-drasis-apo-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 The moment the following words were written, we’re on the 25th day of hunger strike, for the liberation of Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos’ mother, as well as the second one’s girlfriend. 
 The pre-trial detention of our two comrades’ relatives was an act of revenge by the judicial power against us, in retaliation for the escape we had prepared, with the bombing of the prison. 
 Now, reaching a tipping point between life and death, we wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - About the attacks against State and Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-about-the-attacks-against-state-and-capital?v=1717957404</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-about-the-attacks-against-state-and-capital?v=1717957404"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: About the attacks against State and Capital
Date: 9 November 2009
Source: <sysiphus-angrynewsfromaroundtheworld.blogspot.com/2009/11/about-attacks-against-state-and-capital.html>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 A huge storm of revolt raged through the streets of Greece in December 2008. After the young Andreas Grigoropoulos was murdered by a cop, riots spread throughout the whole country for several weeks. Hundreds of banks, shops, car dealers, offices,… were attacked, plundered and put on fire. Although it were anarchists and anti-authoritarians who took the lead in this storm during the first week after the murder, it spread itself fast and many people got involved in this revolt against miserable living conditions, against the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - A small contribution about Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-a-small-contribution-about-solidarity?v=1717957177</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-a-small-contribution-about-solidarity?v=1717957177"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: A small contribution about Solidarity
Date: May 4, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=4500>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Until the day comes we will remain with the head held high....
1. Solidarity is our weapon
 Many things have been written and said about solidarity. Usually when there have been so many discussions and so many texts have circulated on a matter, it ends up trite, predictable and without any particular interest. It seems as if its content has run out and it’s constantly being repeated. 
 We believe there are no trite practices, but trite ways of thinking. Particularly today, in the suspicious days we are living in, with the dozens of imprisoned urban guerrillas and anarchists, we should sharpen the blade o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini - Claim of responsibility for the bomb attack against the Administrative Court]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-claim-of-responsibility-for-the-bomb-attack?v=1717956838</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-claim-of-responsibility-for-the-bomb-attack?v=1717956838"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini
Title: Claim of responsibility for the bomb attack against the Administrative Court
Date: January 6, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3457>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. “The days are coming when they try…”
 “Whoever passed by the front of a courthouse or prison and his look didn’t darken in the thought that he could be there as the culprit, then he did not live his time with integrity and dignity” 
 The attack on the Administrative Court is dedicated with all our fire to our brothers (G.Tsakalos, P.Argirou, H.Hajimihelakis) of the prisoner’s cell of the members of Conspiracy Cells of Fire. Our comrades and the honest minority of dignified revolutionary Persons political and civil, are not just a piec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Economic Termites: Monopolies not noticeable enough for most of us"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40626041</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40626041"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T17:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four.
That's the magic number. There have to be four competitors of significant size before prices go down. There are both EU and US studies substantiating this.
It's been seen in cellular phone networks, ISPs, drugstores, and banks. Drop below the threshold of four, and the magic happens. Prices go up, margins go up, and consumers lose.
Four should be the basis of antitrust policy. Less than four, and there are two options - break up, or become a regulated public utility.
Two or three isn't enough. Collusion happens. Explicitly or implicitly, price competition doesn't happen with only two or three players.
Four seems to be enough that cartels usually break up on their own. Somebody won't play ball.
Four.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by woodruffw in "With congestion pricing stop, New York City enters new era of economic gridlock"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40625630</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40625630"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T16:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the more ridiculous things about the chaos Hochul has wrought over the last 72 hours is that it isn't remotely clear that she can even order the suspension of congestion pricing like this: it's the law of the land in New York, one she already signed, passed by our legislative branch, funded by taxes, and administrated solely by an independent public corporation (the MTA) that she has only minority authority over. It's the equivalent of a president signing a bill and then attempting to post-facto veto it.
It's been very frustrating to see so little news (both local and national) pick up on this basic reality: Hochul is acting far beyond her constitutional powers as the governor, and the legislative branch has so far responded only tepidly (by refusing to pass her last-minute tax alternative).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>woodruffw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[looking back over a lifetime, you see that love was the answer to everything]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/love-bradbury/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/love-bradbury/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes before I left home on Thursday one of my mom's coworkers pulled up on the driveway and handed me a plastic bag of zongzi as a going away gift. "Good luck with the move!" he said. "Go do what you love."
That last remark has been echoing in my head. It runs directly contrary to the advice I received from my parents and their friends growing up. Hearing my aunts now telling me to follow my dreams and not to worry about money makes me wonder how my mom's framed this new career shift of mine.
A large part of me is suspicious. Mom always told me growing up that being an adult was learning to do things you didn't want to do and that nobody would pay me to do a job I found fun. Why's she switching it up on me now? Did it take me crashing and burning in an actual job for her to realize I'm not cut out for a life in STEM? I try not to look back with regret, but how much further along would I be had I chased something I liked earlier?
In Zen in the Art of Writing Bradbury reflects and decides that "looking back over a lifetime, you see that love was the answer to everything." I've been thinking about that as I prepare mentally for a week (and month) of writing and teaching writing for fifty hours a week, things my parents have been telling everyone are things I like to do. At the risk of speaking too soon (knocks on wood), this is the first Sunday I'm not actually dreading the coming week, if not ever then at least for a very long time. I'm nervous and well aware that my schedule will test me, but a strong undercurrent of appreciation for what I'm doing (and not doing) buoys me now and that is nothing short of a revelation for me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ianbicking in "The Weird Nerd comes with trade-offs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40625190</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40625190"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T15:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's definitely been a move to demand individuals be good at everything... old stereotypes of the nerd brought a lot of negatives, but they were also apologetic, acknowledging the trade off, that paying attention deeply to one thing does lead to being worse at other things.
The exact stereotype differed by domain... the performer who is a diva, the self destructive author, the manic artist... each with a hint of nobility but also quite off-putting.
The author wanting to combine Weird Nerd with autistic is very incorrect IMHO... I've known a lot of weird nerds, am one myself, and there's lots of different flavors, most of them not autistic.
So much of talent is just really caring about something specific. Caring about it above other things. Specifically above external motivation and incentives. Do that and the weirdness grows naturally, neurodivergence isn't even necessary (though it might help)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ianbicking</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just keep doing the bit (Karma Yoga Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been preparing for job interviews (looking to get into genai+backend roles you know). I like building projects and learning new stuff but job search is something that scares me. Partly because of the various uncertainties involved like places to apply, strenous interview processes, where I would work next, what kind of work I will get. It’s not the first time I am going through this process but it sucks (a lot in the beginning atleast). The other aspect is the grind.
Translation: I am not afraid of slap sir, I am afraid of job search
I could be solving some leetcode problems right now, I could be applying right now… I have many things to do even outside job search - oh no - fuck fuck fuck. That’s sort of the state of my mind - atleast in the background. Till I don’t build some momen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Rose Anarchist Federation - Turning the Tide]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-rose-anarchist-federation-turning-the-tide?v=1717936810</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-rose-anarchist-federation-turning-the-tide?v=1717936810"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T12:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Black Rose Anarchist Federation
Title: Turning the Tide
Subtitle: An Anarchist Program for Popular Power
Date: May 1, 2023
Notes: Written and approved by the membership of Black Rose / Rosa Negra. First edition released May 1, 2023, available at blackrosefed.org. Cover illustration by Dinelli: dinelliarte.com.
Source: Retrieved on 2023-05-23 from blackrosefed.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/brrn-program-2023.pdf

General Introduction
 This is the political program of our organization, Black Rose Anarchist Federation / Federación Anarquista Rosa Negra (BRRN). The writings it contains are the result of nearly two years of collective analysis, discussion, and debate. The content of the program is divided into three parts: sections that detail our understanding of the social, political,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: wisteria at Iford]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52751</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/09/sunday-photoblogging-wisteria-at-iford/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T09:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism Can’t Overcome the Laws of Physics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324208</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/09/capitalism-cant-overcome-the-laws-of-physics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T06:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Dan Cristian Pădureț.
You can’t have infinite growth on a finite planet. That should be a commonplace idea. And that inevitably means facing up to the necessity of putting an end to capitalism in favor of an economic system of rationality, sustainability and equity for all the world’s peoples.
It can’t be said too many times that the concept of “green capitalism” is a chimera. Unfortunately, belief in that chimera is not limited to the world’s center-left political parties; it extends to the world’s Green parties. Various “Green New Deal” programs have been floated in recent years, generally revolving around a massive buildout of renewable-energy infrastructure and strengthening the social safety net. On their own, there is no rational argument that such programs, should they materialize, would not provide some benefits. But how transformative are such programs?
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Capitalism Can’t Overcome the Laws of Physics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Dolack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Need for Studying Zionism, Critically]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324863</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/09/the-need-for-studying-zionism-critically/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmaia Gelman.
Since 1897, Zionism has been the religious and political impetus behind what is now the nation-state of Israel, which, like the United States, is settled on the lives, land, and cultures of millions of Indigenous peoples. Although today’s Israel began as a refuge for European Jews fleeing the Holocaust, Zionism long ago broke out of its moral constraints to become a formidable geopolitical force that demands study. Which is why, in late 2023 America, the Institute for the Critical Study of Zionism was created. And why, because the Institute is fundamentally antizionist, it’s under attack for antisemitism.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Need for Studying Zionism, Critically appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susie Day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekends: A Different Kind of Busy]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/weekends-a-different-kind-of-busy/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/weekends-a-different-kind-of-busy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T18:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekends are an interesting concept for me. By the time Sunday night rolls around, I’m already counting down to Friday afternoon, which marks the start of of my weekend. I spend the whole week wishing for the weekend, but why exactly?
Weekdays are exhausting. I’ve mentioned that I'm not a morning person, despite having to be bright, fresh and ready for stand-up at 7am. After work, I crash and crawl into bed for my (much needed) afternoon nap. When I wake up, I am FAMISHED, so we either prep dinner or pick something up. After dinner, I decompress (reading or tv) or work out. Then the next day, it starts all over again. All of the errands, housekeeping, and life things that need to get done take a backseat during the weekdays because... work really just takes up a majority of my brain power.
By the time the weekend rolls around, personal and household to-do lists are endless. We spend the entire weekend being productive in other areas of our life that we neglected during the week. Because of this, there are times when there's just little room for excursions or “fun”. There are things that need to get done, so we get them done during the weekend.
It's an odd thing to look forward to doing other work outside of actual work. Perhaps it's not the work that I look forward to, but the shift in productivity. Although it’s nice to be productive, sometimes I wish we had more time for the fun things we actually want to do. Weekends are another kind of busy, but they could be so much more than just catching up on life’s to-dos.
Where is that petition for the 4-day work week?
This weekend’s task: Prep for the over-the-range microwave delivery, by attempting to figure out how to remove the backsplash.
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one day at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/one-day-at-a-time/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/one-day-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T15:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's up?
You made it through the day. I'm proud of you. Seriously, I'm so proud of you.
If nobody told you today, I love you. I mean that with all my heart.
You made it through today, and you should be proud of yourself too.
Sometimes, it's hard to look forward to anything when you're feeling down. But when you reach the end of the day and look back at what you went through, you'll see you have more to look forward to because every day it gets a bit better.
I always tell myself, "Someday I'll feel better. Someday I'll be alright." Remember, that "someday" comes one day at a time, and you'll get there. You will.
I'm proud of you. I'm very proud of you.
Make sure you come back.
Listen on YouTube or Spotify


Links: 
Email me if you want |
Website | Blog | 

Podcast: 
Spotify | Youtube | 

Share on: 
WhatsApp |  X/Twitter |  Facebook |  Linkedin | Reddit |]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whoops, They Did It Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324934</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/08/whoops-they-did-it-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T05:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whoops, they did it again. Only this time it was no “tragic mistake.” There were no apologies. Indeed, the IDF claimed the bombing was a “precision strike.” The target? An UNRWA school in the Nuseirat Refugee Camp in central Gaza, which was being used as a shelter for thousands of displaced Palestinian families. The victims: at least 40 killed, 14 of them children and 9 women. Another 75 were wounded, including 23 children and 18 women. The weapon? A US-made GBU 39, the same bombs used to kill 45 people at the Tel al-Sultan tent encampment outside Rafah last week.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Whoops, They Did It Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet insights on 2024 elections in the Netherlands, South Africa, Iceland, India, and Mexico]]></title>
        <id>66636b01e955c4000a8b4c6c</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/internet-insights-on-2024-elections-in-the-netherlands-south-africa-iceland-india-and-mexico"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T20:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 brings a global increase in election activity. Here, we highlight traffic and cyberattack trends witnessed in countries like the Netherlands, South Africa, Iceland, India, and Mexico. Additionally, we provide an up-to-date 2024 Election Insights report on Cloudflare Radar]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ETERNAL Norita!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-ETERNAL-Norita</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-ETERNAL-Norita"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T16:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 6:41 p. m. on Thursday, May 30, at the age of 94, our beloved Nora Cortiñas left us; we will miss her so much. Barely a few seconds after this sad news, which we didn't want to hear, was announced, someone had already shouted “ETERNAL Norita!” at this iconic Plaza de Mayo location. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Argentina, 
Human Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International, Eric Toussaint, Maria Elena Saludas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awesome aging]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/awesome-aging/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/awesome-aging/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was listening to an interview with the Swedish artist Peter Jöback. They were talking about aging and he said:
I feel like my life started after I turned 50. It's so much fun getting older! Now I can face the world with ease.
He says that after 50 he feels he has become more playful and that life feels "less serious".
I turned 50 myself a couple of years ago and I can relate 100 percent. Aside from a few minor “bugs”, like always having to keep a pair of reading glasses handy, there are only positive changes.
I don't worry so much about what people think of me. It's not that I don't care about things - on the contrary, humility and compassion are more prominent than ever - but I've come to truly realize that you can never control what others think and say about you.
You can't please them all – and that's fine!
In many ways, I think aging is a bit like the story of Benjamin Button. Not in terms of appearance, of course. Aging is noticeable in the form of gray hairs here and there, and other hairs have completely given up, never to return, etc…
But that doesn’t feel very important.
The lightness, though, really does feel like it makes the mind younger and younger. Like magic! It's more fun and interesting to live.
No matter your age, stay curious and enjoy life. Aging is pretty awesome, trust me.
Want more “proof”? Check out Alyssa’s post Thoughts on Being in My 30s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["AI-powered" has become a red flag]]></title>
        <id>https://iml.bearblog.dev/ai-powered-has-become-a-red-flag/</id>
        <link href="https://iml.bearblog.dev/ai-powered-has-become-a-red-flag/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the launch of ChatGPT back in 2022 AI has explod — just kidding. Those lead-ins are getting tiring, right?
But what has become even more irritating is how everything is "AI-powered" all of a sudden.
Let me make it clear up-front that I am not opposed to using AI, whatever that means anymore, for a product. I've done it myself and it's a good way to add value to the product, if it really needs it.
But what truly irks me are the common-day apps which have been just fine without such AI plug-ins and, all of a sudden, they become "AI-powered". Here are a few things that go through my head when "AI-powered" is advertised up-front:
How reliable are the outputs / are hallucinations present?
Where does my data go? (Probably OpenAI, but not 100% sure)
Is the AI-powered going to be a mark-up?
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JoAnn Wypijewski: &ldquo;Rule of Law?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/rule-of-law</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/rule-of-law"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T14:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump and the courts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the new South Africa of the betrayed expectations, also betrays its hero Dimitri Tsafendas!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/When-the-new-South-Africa-of-the-betrayed-expectations-also-betrays-its-hero</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/When-the-new-South-Africa-of-the-betrayed-expectations-also-betrays-its-hero"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T12:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“You are guilty not only when you commit a crime, but also when you do nothing to prevent it when you have the chance”. (Dimitri Tsafendas) 
English

/ 
South Africa, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five troubleshooting examples with Amazon Q]]></title>
        <id>e266f15f4c44e10267e7203bc95772d1893f4740</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-troubleshooting-examples-with-amazon-q/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators, administrators, developers, and many other personas leveraging AWS come across multiple common issues when it comes to troubleshooting in the AWS Console. To help alleviate this burden, AWS released Amazon Q. Amazon Q is AWS’s generative AI-powered assistant that helps make your organizational data more accessible, write code, answer questions, generate content, solve problems, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trevor Clarke: &ldquo;All or Nothing&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/all-or-nothing</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/all-or-nothing"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T10:56:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jiajun ‘Oscar’ Zhang’s first feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeBuild Managed Self-Hosted GitHub Action Runners]]></title>
        <id>164df924bc95becc32ff082f3115d9fb5a422c33</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/aws-codebuild-managed-self-hosted-github-action-runners/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T10:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeBuild now supports managed self-hosted GitHub Action runners, allowing you to build powerful CI/CD capabilities right beside your code and quickly implement a build, test and deploy pipeline. Last year AWS announced that customers can define their GitHub Actions steps within any phase of a CodeBuild buildspec file but with a self-hosted runner, jobs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6th International Eco-socialist Meeting and the 1st Latin American and Caribbean Eco-socialist Meeting concluded successfully]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-6th-International-Eco-socialist-Meeting-and-the-1st-Latin-American-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-6th-International-Eco-socialist-Meeting-and-the-1st-Latin-American-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over three days (9-11 May), the city of Buenos Aires received over 250 activists from 30 nations. After more than a year of planning, we were able to assemble in the auditorium of the ATE (Association of State Workers) to discuss and attempt to create strategies for developing resistance to the capitalist system. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Argentina, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Elena Saludas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VS Code Extensions and WebAssembly - Part Two]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/07/wasm-part2</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/07/wasm-part2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Settling into my new (notes) home]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/settling-into-my-new-notes-home/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/settling-into-my-new-notes-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, hello there.
I went back and forth on whether or not I wanted to make the move from my former (Notes) blogging platform to Bear blog. I listed out some pros and cons in one of my previous posts1, and I really thought I was going to stay put for a little bit. After all, I wanted to look away from the new and shiny temptation and really think about what it would mean to switch. Moving sucks, and I hate having to pack, and unpack.
Well, I spent the past few days packing, and then unpacking (aka migrating my blog). I figured this was a good way to test out Bear to see if writing in all markdown would bother me. It didn’t. I’m already primarily writing in Markdown on Bear (Notes App) before posting, so there wasn’t much overheard. I found myself enjoying this lightweight yet customizable platform.
So, here I am. Things are a little bit scattered. Still have no idea where to put some of my things. I think it will take some time, but I’m already cozying up in my new home.
If you’re new here, welcome! If you’ve been following me from the beginning, I’m so glad to have you on here. Grab a seat, and enjoy my Notes about anything and everything.
Until then, go read some posts from some awesome bloggers I have listed here for JUnited. They're all pretty great!
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS
originally posted on the other platform, and imported here.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alien: Romulus, the Alien story continues. Great poster though]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7778</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/alien-romulus-alien-story-continues-great-poster/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best I keep this brief, especially after complaining about film franchises continually rebooting and retelling the same story. Alien: Romulus (isn’t Romulus a planet in the Star Trek universe? Yeah, I thought so), is a story about some people on a spaceship, whose lives are threatened by a sinister alien stowaway. Reminds me a lot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wake Up Dead Man, by Rian Johnson, with Daniel Craig: Benoit Blanc returns]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7775</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wake-up-dead-man-rian-johnson-daniel-craig-benoit-blanc-returns/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T20:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great news for fans of 2019 thriller/comedy/whodunit, Knives Out… a follow up is on the way. Daniel Craig will reprise his role as private detective Benoit Blanc, in Wake Up Dead Man, due for cinematic release sometime in 2025. Check out the teaser/trailer, though it’s more teaser than trailer. Good to hear CSI KFC’s voice […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Round 2: A Survey of Causal Inference Applications at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fd78328ee0bb</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/round-2-a-survey-of-causal-inference-applications-at-netflix-fd78328ee0bb?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T20:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Netflix, we want to ensure that every current and future member finds content that thrills them today and excites them to come back for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch political websites hit by cyber attacks as EU voting starts]]></title>
        <id>66620b31e955c4000a8b4b51</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/dutch-political-websites-hit-by-cyber-attacks-as-eu-voting-starts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T19:23:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 European Parliament election began in the Netherlands on June 6. Cloudflare mitigated several multi-hour DDoS attacks on Dutch political websites on June 5 and 6]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify risk and compliance assessments with the new common control library in AWS Audit Manager]]></title>
        <id>601196434e43e79993b9d6b3fc9bcffdf6c5b9af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-risk-and-compliance-assessments-with-the-new-common-control-library-in-aws-audit-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T18:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Map enterprise controls to AWS data sources effortlessly with predefined, pre-mapped controls based on auditor reviews. Automatically inherit improvements as Audit Manager updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Drums of War are Banging in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Drums-of-War-are-Banging-in-Europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Drums-of-War-are-Banging-in-Europe"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These weeks see the end of the term for an ineffectual European legislature which served during the worst pandemic of this century, during Vladimir Putin's invasion of Ukraine, and with it, the outbreak of a war on European soil that evokes the worst memories of the world wars of the last century. And as we witness the televised genocide of the Palestinian people, it appears that the international system of liberal governance seems to be collapsing like a house of cards. 
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Europe, 
Ukraine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Miguel Urbán Crespo, Paul Murphy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Engaging Erik Olin Wright: Between Class Analysis and Real Utopias]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52745</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/06/engaging-erik-olin-wright-between-class-analysis-and-real-utopias/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T14:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s more than 5 years since Erik died which, for those who knew him, is quite hard to believe, as he is still a strong voice in many of our heads. Because I know many of our readers knew and admired him or his work (or both!) I thought I’d let you know that a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;Wartime Lithuania&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/wartime-lithuania</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/wartime-lithuania"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T12:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jingoism and discontent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting vulnerable communities for 10 years with Project Galileo]]></title>
        <id>66609308e955c4000a8b49da</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/galileo10anniversaryradardashboard"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In celebration of Project Galileo's 10th anniversary, we want to give you a snapshot of what organizations that work in the public interest experience on an everyday basis when it comes to keeping their websites online]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Years of Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/06/10-years-of-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/06/10-years-of-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten (10) years ago, on June 6th, 2014, the
first commit
of Kubernetes was pushed to GitHub. That first commit with 250 files and 47,501 lines of go, bash
and markdown kicked off the project we have today. Who could have predicted that 10 years later,
Kubernetes would grow to become one of the largest Open Source projects to date with over
88,000 contributors from
more than 8,000 companies, across
44 countries.
This milestone isn't just for Kubernetes but for the Cloud Native ecosystem that blossomed from
it. There are close to 200 projects
within the CNCF itself, with contributions from
240,000+ individual contributors and
thousands more in the greater ecosystem. Kubernetes would not be where it is today without them, the
7M+ Developers,
and the even larger user community that have all hel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attracting Similar People]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/attracting-similar-people/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/attracting-similar-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The point of this blog was to put myself out there. Why? I stopped filling my mind with content and the resulting silence led to an outpour of content in my head. I needed an outlet to express the thoughts in my head. Something I cover in my essay on writing here. Also who wants to miss out on being part of the future AGI training set?
Yet I never thought of one huge perk. Attracting like-minded people. The internet is amazing. You put out slivers of your consciousness and watch as like-minded people gather around. I have got DMS asking such specific things. Relating to my essays, to my impact page. People I looked up to on x. People who inspired me. It feels nice to interact with your tribe.
I have already got many people writing and sharing on Twitter. Especially through bearblog. I would urge more people to do the same. Be you. Even if you don't get many views. Just share your thoughts. You will attract similar-minded people. Find friends, business partners, and
maybe life partners. That is the hidden perk no one tells you about.
So if you are on the fence, start writing and sharing. Best of luck!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four-day workweeks are nigh, followed by zero-day workweeks]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7769</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/four-day-workweeks-nigh-zero-day-workweeks/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been talk of the four-day workweek for as long as I can remember. We were told about it when I started school. Yet it’s to fully, properly, officially, arrive. The work week is still, for the most part, in many places, five days: Monday to Friday. We don’t live in an age where […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[en] rabbit r1 it's a SCAM]]></title>
        <id>https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/en-rabbit-r1-its-a-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/en-rabbit-r1-its-a-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:55:10.692Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not new that the promise of artificial intelligence capable of helping us and solving a series of problems we don't have has emerged. However, it is only from 2022 onwards that large models (LLM, LAM, and others) are gaining traction and attention worldwide. It started with OpenAI and ChatGPT, followed by Humana's AI Pin and Rabbit R1 from Rabbit Inc. Neither delivered on their promises, but the Rabbit R1 has an extra touch.
While Humane's brooch is just an overpriced product that doesn’t work properly, the Rabbit R1 is a mishmash of poorly executed features and a good dose of scams, especially coming from a company previously involved with NFTs and "pay-to-win" games (which use NFTs). Most of the instructions are hardcoded into the device, meaning that most actions are predefined acc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nothing nonnegotiable]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/nothing-nonnegotiable/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/nothing-nonnegotiable/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vegetating aside, the last few days before big moves usually also brings lots of appointments. This week I get my teeth cleaned and eyes checked before I leave, scheduling follow-ups in a year and making plans to be back for them.
Going to these appointments is one of the few activities I actually prefer my parents come along. Not because I enjoy their company (it's hit or miss), but because I'm no good at doing the things they usually do. (And by 'they' I mean my mom.)
Today before I leave for the optometrist Mom tells me I shouldn't agree to pay more than $110 for my visit, the same amount we paid last year. Upon arrival, the receptionist informs me that the fee for checkups is $250 now. $250? I thought it was supposed to be $110, I say. She shows me a packet with the price printed in bo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>