<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-07T18:30:41.202Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-07T18:30:41.202Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Corbishley: Naked Capitalism – Uncomfortable Truths and Dissenting Views in an Age of Rising Censorship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=257605</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/naked-capitalism-telling-uncomfortable-truths-in-a-new-age-of-censorship.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T15:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support Naked Capitalism generously so it can continue  its reporting and analysis  in an increasingly hostile information environment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullets to the Head]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332926</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/07/bullets-to-the-head/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T14:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ On Friday, Aysenur Eygi, a 26-year-old American peace activist, was shot in the head and killed by an Israeli sniper during a demonstration against illegal settlements and land seizures in the West Bank village of Beita, near the city of Nablus. Eygi was taken to Rafida Hospital, where she was pronounced dead on arrival.  […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Bullets to the Head appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278027</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T10:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our yodeling daily links: Fungus controlled robots, Long Covid deaths, European heat, China economy induced obesity? Germany cancels AfD official's accounts, Israel destruction of West Bank, Ukraine loan stymied, imperial collapse watch, AI systemic fail, private equity debt worries, port union strike?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Wolff: The Decline of the U.S. Empire – Where Is It Taking Us All?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278090</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/richard-wolff-the-decline-of-the-u-s-empire-where-is-it-taking-us-all.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T10:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking stock of the trajectory of the US running into the limits of its empire, and what the history of imperial declines suggests is in store]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel: 11 Months of War Have Battered the Country’s Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278085</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/israel-11-months-of-war-have-battered-the-countrys-economy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T10:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel's economy continues to suffer as its war in Gaza drags on and unless the conflict ends soon, the damage will be lasting and deep.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278055</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T18:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ang_cire in "Effects of Gen AI on High Skilled Work: Experiments with Software Developers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41468219</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41468219"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T17:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I sometimes wonder about whether the decline in IT worker quality is down to companies trying to force more and more roles onto each worker to reduce headcount.
Developers, Operations, and Security used to be dedicated roles.
Then we made DevOps and some businesses took that to mean they only needed 2/3 of the headcount, rather than integrating those teams.
Then we made DevSecOps, and some businesses took that to mean they only needed 1/3 the original roles, and that devs could just also be their operations and appsec team.
That's not a knock on shift-left and integrated operations models; those are often good ideas. It's just the logical outcome of those models when execs think they can get a bigger bonus by cutting costs by cutting headcounts.
Now you have new devs coming into insanely complex n-microservice environments, being asked to learn the existing codebase, being asked to learn their 5-tool CI/CD pipelines (and that ain't being taught in school), being asked to learn to be DBAs, and also to keep up a steady code release cycle.
Is anyone really surprised they are using ChatGPT to keep up?
This is going to keep happening until IT companies stop cutting headcounts to make line go up (instead of good business strategy).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ang_cire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i don’t wanna live in a ring world]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/ring-world/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/ring-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ring cameras freak me out. Whenever I am unfortunate enough to see their ads, they seem dystopian to me. What I am fortunate in is not being in a country that is seemingly dominated by them, at least not yet.
It was already enough that entering people’s home increasingly meant being comfortable with Alexa and others, or that being in public meant you could either be in the background or the unkowing main topic of some TikTok video. I guess we are now increasingly entering an era where being outside means being filmed by a private person’s camera somewhere, or that you’ll even be recorded while visiting someone inside their home.
Now, I will say, I feel sympathy for the people using these in genuinely rough areas, or having survived some horrible break-ins. It hasn’t ever happened to me, bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's Something You Regularly Fail At?]]></title>
        <id>https://darrenhester.com/what-is-something-you-regularly-fail-at/</id>
        <link href="https://darrenhester.com/what-is-something-you-regularly-fail-at/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T16:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ironically, my answer is blogging.
I’ve abandoned four blogs this year, none lasting more than 60 days. My problem hasn’t been building the sites; it’s with my comfort level writing in public.
Things have improved recently. I’ve posted 11 days in a row. I’m determined to push past this awkward stage and find my voice.
The more you practice, the easier it gets.
I stopped trying to be perfect. I don't have to write an essay. If it's a short post, that's fine. There's no word count requirement. As long as I publish something, it's a win!
Show up each day and give it your best shot. How else could you expect to improve?
If you're a new blogger who can relate to this struggle, I hope this post encourages you. Don’t stress over clicking publish. Just share your honest thoughts. We want to hear your story.
Sidenotes
This post was based on a writing prompt from blogprompts.fyi, a simple site that helps you choose a topic to blog about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[coming up for air]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/coming-up-for-air/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/coming-up-for-air/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Junior year. Whew.
I've been slammed with work for the past few weeks (no time to really sit down and go through Bearblog or my mail; my most recent posts were all written on the fly using my phone, or done beforehand and posted on a schedule). Most of it has to do with extracurriculars instead of actual school, and I don't really know how I feel about that. Maybe a little annoyed, but I signed up for this, so it's up to me to work through it.
We've had really bad weather recently, so I spent most of this week holed up in my apartment, existing. I still haven't learned much. I think it's partly because I'm still in some mental fog and partly because I've been taking care of so much org work.
There are so many freshman events to organize. Okay, maybe not that many, but it's all I've been doing these past few weeks. I don't even remember attending most of these back then, but they've always existed, apparently. I guess I was kind of friendless and out of the loop as a freshman...
Anyway. I ended up with more responsibilities than I thought I'd have, so it's been a bit of a mad scramble to get it all done. I've been given the writing task I've done my best to avoid these past few years: post captions. I'm forever in awe of people who actually like writing captions, because I just can't do it without hyping myself up first. I've gotten used to doing it and I can fall into a rhythm now when I do, but sometimes it's still like, ugh, this again...
(I'm real proud whenever I see them posted though, so really, it's a love-hate relationship.)
D-day for this particular event is tomorrow, after which I'll have some time to let things settle a bit before the work starts up again. I only have a few things left to do for it, which is why I'm back here again, writing. Hope you guys are staying hydrated!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emojis are cool]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/emojis-are-cool/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/emojis-are-cool/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use a lot of emojis when I write (especially chat), and it has always struck me as interesting that most people around me don’t. “Don’t they want to convey how they feel about this?” I ask myself. So much so that, for a long time, I thought my overuse of emojis came from a needy, co-dependent part of me that wanted to be pleasant to others and avoid any misunderstandings by being extra clear that I wasn’t angry or displeased with them through the use of the smiley face.
It wasn’t until quite recently that I realized my use of emojis was not “a weak front” (as is usually viewed by the professional and academic worlds), though it is neither a strength. What is it then? Well, it’s just an extra set of punctuation marks.
Emojis have drastically evolved since their first (genius) inception an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie: When Markets Crash and Wars Rage, Naked Capitalism is Here to Inform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276919</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/rob-urie-when-markets-crash-and-wars-rage-naked-capitalism-is-here-to-inform.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Naked Capitalism keeps your back in ever more turbulent times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das: New Asian Cinematic Obsessions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278048</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/satyajit-das-new-asian-cinematic-obsessions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of recent Japanese and Korean films, and the origins of this cinematic vogue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alternatex in "Effects of Gen AI on High Skilled Work: Experiments with Software Developers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41465648</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41465648"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T12:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder if the study includes the technical debt that more experienced developers had to tackle after the less experienced devs have contributed their AI-driven efforts. Because my personal experience has involved a lot of that in one of the companies listed in the study.
Also, I've personally seen more interest in AI in devs that have little interest in technology, but a big interest in delivering. PMs love them though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alternatex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Toxic Masculinity]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/non-toxic-masculinity/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/non-toxic-masculinity/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My wife and I knew within a week of seeing each other that we would eventually get married. I had an adjustment to make though. In all my previous relationships, I'd been the biggest breadwinner in the family. This time that wouldn't be the case. I was a public-school employee, and she was a partner in the most prestigious accounting firm in the area, earning about triple my salary. As life struggles go, making that mental adjustment wasn't remarkably hard, but it did require me to reexamine myself, never a bad thing. I let go of the ego boost that earning a bigger wage gave me in the past and haven't really thought about it much since then. We've never had an argument over money, even if she, with her accountant's attention to detail, knows and often mentions the bank transactions I creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Barnay: &ldquo;Regional Interests&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/regional-interests</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/regional-interests"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:20:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Sahel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278037</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our joyful daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Sweden, Now Brazil: Digital Crime is Exploding in Two of the World’s Most Cashless Economies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277927</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/first-sweden-now-brazil-digital-crime-is-exploding-in-the-worlds-most-cashless-economies.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Criminal groups are migrating from physical to virtual crimes because it is a better, more lucrative and less risky business."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by defrost in "Did Sandia use a thermonuclear secondary in a product logo?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41464695</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41464695"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> What is it that the author thinks is particularly unusual about this image?
In two decades of crawling through most of the declassified public nuclear material from the US nuclear weapons program, some exposure to classified material, and numerous hours of interviews with working and retired nuclear scientists he believes it's the single most detailed schematic of an actual specific type of warhead he's seen so far.
https://blog.nuclearsecrecy.com/about-me/
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alex_Wellerstein
As he's blogging about this it's almost certain he has had real current working nuclear weapons experts from his contact list read the advances and not disagree.
Correct or not, it's not a casual random thought from someone with no exposure to such diagrams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>defrost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xrd in "2M users but no money in the bank"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41464593</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41464593"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T10:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is one of the saddest posts I've read in a long time.
I love exercism. It's beautiful, works in the browser and from CLI. The lessons are really well designed. It's the perfect coding school environment.
So, I'm sad it isn't viable.
But, I think I am really saddened by the comments here, second guessing all the decisions they made. If I were to second guess the people behind most of the comments, I would assume no one has ever run a business with payroll, or built something with this much reach. The comments ring really hollow for the most part and seem really callous given this person has sunk his life into making the world, and my life, a better place. I'm scared for the moment he is in life and sad there are not more positive comments, and even better, comments from people where they would actually help by making a donation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xrd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Action list to protect universities from budget cuts]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53158</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/06/action-list-to-protect-universities-from-budget-cuts/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T09:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to my previous post on the imminent threat to Dutch universities to have their budgets cut with up to 1 billion euros a year, I received a few emails from (mainly younger) staff to ask how they could contribute to the protests. I will respond specifically for the current Dutch case, but I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Rare Earth Restrictions Shake Up Global Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278029</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/chinas-rare-earth-restrictions-shake-up-global-markets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US ceding its once-dominant position in rare earths comes back to bite, as China uses rare earths to retaliate against US sanctions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Kamala Harris Erasing Palestinians?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332653</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/why-is-kamala-erasing-palestinians/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not that the Democrats did not show any concern about Palestinians at the Democratic National Convention. They showed extraordinary concern given the lengths they went to erase them from Kamala’s coronation.
Afterwards the Democrats seemed ecstatic that a little genocide didn’t disrupt their joy. But there were still plenty of protests and signs of divisions that could pose problems with Harris’s path to election especially as student protesters look to reinvigorate the movement. More
The post Why is Kamala Harris Erasing Palestinians? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Disappearance of International Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332845</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-disappearance-of-international-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The horrors of the Second World War sparked the creation of international organizations and international laws to ensure that such horrors would never occur again.  The center piece of these international bodies was the United Nations and its regional and functional agencies that were designed to provide international guardrails to limit the use of force.  The National Security Act of 1947 was designed in part to make sure that U.S. administrations played an active role in managing and even transforming the international community. More
The post The Disappearance of International Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Ain’t That America, Something to See, Baby?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332780</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/roaming-charges-116/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A country that tolerates the routine shootings of its own school children as the cost of doing business in our weird notion of a "free society" is unlikely to feel any empathy for Palestinian children killed by the weapons we sell Israel. Violence is our chief export; indifference to the bloodshed is our national characteristic. More
The post Roaming Charges: Ain’t That America, Something to See, Baby? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Would Six Israelis Receive More Attention Than Tens of Thousands of Murdered Palestinians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332759</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/why-would-six-israelis-receive-more-attention-than-tens-of-thousands-of-murdered-palestinians/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September 1, 2024, twenty-seven Palestinian families woke up to mourn their loved ones, including at least 11 who were killed at a “safe” shelter, Safad School in Zaitune neighborhood east of Gaza city. On the same day, the Israeli occupying army recovered the bodies of six Israeli captives, who died as a direct or indirect result of an Israeli incursion into a tunnel in Rafah. More
The post Why Would Six Israelis Receive More Attention Than Tens of Thousands of Murdered Palestinians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workers Need Protection From Record-Breaking Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/workers-need-protection-from-record-breaking-heat/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer is on track to being the hottest on record, with 2024 very likely to be the hottest year. Fueled by global warming, extreme heat is the leading weather-related cause of death in the United States. It claims the lives of around 2,000 workers and injures another 170,000 in heat stress-related incidents each year,  More
The post Workers Need Protection From Record-Breaking Heat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Craven Tokenism: The UK Suspension of Arms Export Licenses to Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332800</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/craven-tokenism-the-uk-suspension-of-arms-export-licenses-to-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The government of Sir Keir Starmer, despite remaining glued to a foreign policy friendly and accommodating to Israel, has found the strain a bit much of late.  While galloping to victory in the July elections, leaving the British Labour Party a heaving majority, a certain ill-temper could be found among the ranks on his attitudes regarding  More
The post Craven Tokenism: The UK Suspension of Arms Export Licenses to Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The Palestine Wave” at Socialism 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332890</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-palestine-wave-at-socialism-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent Socialism 2024 conference in Chicago was by all measures a great success. The three-day conference was sponsored by Haymarket Books, and it was the largest Socialism conference in its history with over 2,300 people attending from across the country, along with a small contingent of international visitors and speakers. There were ninety co-sponsoring organizations, including the  More
The post “The Palestine Wave” at Socialism 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humans Rescue Doomsday Glacier?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332740</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/humans-rescue-doomsday-glacier/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was only 3 years ago when a group of distinguished climate scientists led by Erin C. Pettit (Oregon State University) said Thwaites Eastern Ice Shelf of the Thwaites Glacier/Antarctica, aka: Doomsday Glacier, could collapse “within as little as 5 years.” (Source: C34A-07 Collapse of Thwaites Eastern Ice Shelf by intersecting fractures, American Geophysical Union,  More
The post Humans Rescue Doomsday Glacier? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Roulette: The U.S. Nuclear Employment Guideline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332685</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/nuclear-roulette-the-u-s-nuclear-employment-guideline/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Nuclear Employment Guideline Report, according to Department of Defense websites, appears to be a detailed target menu in the event the president orders a nuclear attack. It is required of the executive by Congress, Section 491, when the president alters the nuclear weapons strategy of the U.S. As alluded to by top-ranking administration  More
The post Nuclear Roulette: The U.S. Nuclear Employment Guideline appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Muhich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Conversation With a Columbia University Undergraduate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332783</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/a-conversation-with-a-columbia-university-undergraduate/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the subway riders boarded the 1 train at 116th Street on Manhattan’s West Side, it was apparent that many riders on this Labor Day were students. The subway car wasn’t particularly crowded and one of the people I guessed was a student sat down next to me. We began talking about the difference in  More
The post A Conversation With a Columbia University Undergraduate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paradox of Progress for Black Americans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332794</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-paradox-of-progress-for-black-americans/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the country moves rapidly toward the 2024 elections, Black Americans are experiencing the best economic conditions they’ve had in generations. Record low unemployment rates, record low poverty rates, and record high levels of income and wealth paint a picture of Black prosperity. Yet African Americans remain mired in great economic insecurity, reflected in their  More
The post The Paradox of Progress for Black Americans appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin and Dedrick Asante-Muhammad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nation of Debtors: USA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332883</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/a-nation-of-debtors-usa/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans are up to their eyeballs in debt. At a time when the national debt exceeds $35 trillion, U.S. citizens are awash in red ink. They’ve got medical debt, credit card debt, mortgage debt, educational debt and more. Contrary to the popular bromide that we are a nation of homeowners, we aren’t. Only 25 percent  More
The post A Nation of Debtors: USA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kind of Blue: Still on the Job at 65]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332885</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/332885/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miles Davis’s Kind of Blue turned sixty-five last month, the same age at which the trumpeter would die thirty-two years after recording the album. The record shows no signs of infirmity. It has no plans to retire, isn’t tempted to ease into the rocking chair heard to sigh and squeak in Davis’s elegiac rendition of  More
The post Kind of Blue: Still on the Job at 65 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why US Workers are Far Better Off Than Four Years Ago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332888</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/why-us-workers-are-far-better-off-than-four-years-ago/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:53:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not a tough one. First and foremost, workers are better off today because they overwhelmingly have jobs if they want them. They also are getting higher pay, even after adjusting for inflation. And they tell us they are much more satisfied at their jobs. When President Biden took office, the unemployment rate was  More
The post Why US Workers are Far Better Off Than Four Years Ago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Act]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332704</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/final-act/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:53:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who thinks my story is anywhere near over is sadly mistaken. ― Donald Trump Caught as we are at a deeply polarized moment, so intensely consuming, that it’s hard to recognize that, to quote Ecclesiastes, time and chance happens to us all. In other words, things will move on. Or just move. The curtain  More
The post Final Act appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris vs Trump and the Time Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332627</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/harris-vs-trump-and-the-time-competition/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most underestimated differences in the Kamala Harris vs Donald Trump presidential competition is the question of time. Yes Donald Trump was born in 1946 and Kamala Harris in 1964, so there is an obvious generation gap between them. But beyond the obvious question of age and generations is the larger question of  More
The post Harris vs Trump and the Time Competition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low Wage Work Isn’t Just Bad for Employees — It Hurts Customers, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332788</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/low-wage-work-isnt-just-bad-for-employees-it-hurts-customers-too/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always felt that working in customer-facing jobs is my calling. I’m passionate about making people feel comfortable when they enter a business, be it a retail store or a restaurant. But it was hard to keep that passion when I worked at Dollar General. Like workers at many other big retailers, we were so  More
The post Low Wage Work Isn’t Just Bad for Employees — It Hurts Customers, Too  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Guerra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two and a Half Hours Alone with Nixon, the Anti-Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332900</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/two-and-a-half-hours-alone-with-nixon-the-anti-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one would be more repelled by let-it-rip Trump than anal Nixon. Nixon, shrewd and sweaty, imploded behind closed doors. Trump, crude and swaggering, is an open faucet. “He left,” Trump says of Nixon. “I don’t leave.” I remember Nixon’s exit. Fifty years ago, Marine Onenixon l swooped down from a cloudless sky and slid  More
The post Two and a Half Hours Alone with Nixon, the Anti-Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerelle Kraus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trumptopia and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332756</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/trumptopia-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, long ago, I dreamt of being a novelist. Two ancient manuscripts packed away in a distant corner of my closet attest to that (ir)reality, as does one novel focused on the world of publishing (in which I’d been an editor) that made it into print, even if it was barely noticed. Still, from time to  More
The post Trumptopia and Beyond appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holding the Press and White House Accountable: Solomon’s Afterword on the Gaza War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332644</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/holding-the-press-and-white-house-accountable-solomons-afterword-on-the-gaza-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Norman Solomon’s new Afterword in the paperback edition of his book War Made Invisible: How America Hides the Human Toll of Its Military Machine, the author excoriates the White House for arming a genocide with assistance from a negligent press. Solomon tracks events following Hamas’ killings and kidnappings of Israelis on October 7th, a  More
The post Holding the Press and White House Accountable: Solomon’s Afterword on the Gaza War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcy Winograd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy’s Damndest Defamation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332631</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/democracys-damndest-defamation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a democracy, people automatically become liable for whatever the government inflicts upon them. Many of the most deadly errors of contemporary political thinking stem from the notion that in a democracy the government is the people and vice versa, so there is scant reason to distinguish between the two—or to worry about protecting citizens  More
The post Democracy’s Damndest Defamation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Children’s Rights Are Critical for Climate Policy and Environmental Activism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332777</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/why-childrens-rights-are-critical-for-climate-policy-and-environmental-activism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The actual cause of the climate crisis is the anthropogenic emission of greenhouse gases into the atmosphere since the start of the industrial revolution. But the proximate cause—the underlying activity that sparked the climate crisis and the intertwined environmental crises—is how we have built society, starting from when humans are born. Despite the threat of the sixth extinction, ecosystem collapse, air and water  More
The post Why Children’s Rights Are Critical for Climate Policy and Environmental Activism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Afolaranmi and Carter Dillard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hour of Miracles: Aimé Césaire’s And the Dogs Were Silent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332775</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-red-hour-of-miracles-aime-cesaires-and-the-dogs-were-silent/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Haitian revolution was the first victorious anti-colonial war in the so-called New World led by those enslaved by the colonizers. The battle engaged against the slavers and their empires was long and bloody. European kings and European republics fought and lost. In doing so, the latter revealed their colonialist and white supremacist similarities to  More
The post The Red Hour of Miracles: Aimé Césaire’s And the Dogs Were Silent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are We Better Off Accepting There’s No Free Will?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332779</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/are-we-better-off-accepting-theres-no-free-will/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:48:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Determined, a new book by renowned Stanford professor of primate behavior and neuroscience Robert M. Sapolsky, has catapulted him into the middle of an ancient debate: whether humans have free will and agency over their actions. Determined isn’t just a bio-philosophical treatise: It covers the potential benefits that a society that accepts Sapolsky’s thesis of  More
The post Are We Better Off Accepting There’s No Free Will? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jan Ritch-Frel and Marjorie Hecht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Hiroshima to Genocide in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332738</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/from-hiroshima-to-genocide-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I mourn the six dead Israeli hostages recently murdered by Hamas before Israeli Defense Forces could claim them as military victories because I strive to be a human being. But it has been revolting to hear and see so much detail in the dominant media about the beauty and humanity of one group of people  More
The post From Hiroshima to Genocide in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Intervention and Neoliberalism Aggravate Political Upheaval in Bangladesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332897</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/us-intervention-and-neoliberalism-aggravate-political-upheaval-in-bangladesh/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weeks of student-led and often violent protests forced the resignation and exile on August 5 of Bangladesh’s prime minister Sheikh Hasina. Demonstrators were reacting to inflation, unemployment, governmental and banking corruption and a quota system that preferentially opens up government jobs to descendants of people participating in the national liberation struggle. Brutal police repression and  More
The post US Intervention and Neoliberalism Aggravate Political Upheaval in Bangladesh appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HIV/AIDS Got Its Name: Science, Stigma and Religious Language]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332634</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/how-hiv-aids-got-its-name-science-stigma-and-religious-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention first used the term “AIDS” on Sept. 24, 1982, more than a year after the first cases appeared in medical records. Those early years of the crisis were marked by a great deal of confusion over what caused the disease, who it affected and how it spread. But  More
The post How HIV/AIDS Got Its Name: Science, Stigma and Religious Language appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Petro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Made the Dutch an Offer They Couldn’t Refuse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332797</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-us-made-the-dutch-an-offer-they-couldnt-refuse/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASML, a Dutch firm that currently is the world’s only manufacturer of the extreme ultraviolet lithography machines that produce the most advanced chips, is repeatedly getting stiff-armed by the US – intimidated into breaking deals and told not to sell a widening range of goods to China. Back at the start of the year, after a  More
The post The US Made the Dutch an Offer They Couldn’t Refuse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Venetian Birth of Modernism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332637</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/06/the-venetian-birth-of-modernism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider a short list of the defining qualities, the necessary and sufficient conditions of European modernism, in contrast or opposition to old master sacred tradition. Modernism involves secular rather than sacred subjects. Compare Impressionist landscapes with High Renaissance altarpieces. Modernism requires a system in which art is made to be sold in the marketplace rather  More
The post The Venetian Birth of Modernism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM : what to do with the Financial sector and the Banks and, with the Sovereign Debt arbitration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-what-to-do-with-the-Financial-sector-and-the-Banks</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-what-to-do-with-the-Financial-sector-and-the-Banks"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extract from “Social Movements and the Politics of Debt: Transnational Resistance against Debt on Three Continents” 
English

/ 
Arbitration, 
Bank of the South, 
Banks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM, Christoph Sorg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BadHumans in "Why Don't Tech Companies Pay Their Engineers to Stay?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41462100</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41462100"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T01:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This entire piece starts from the conclusion that engineers leave because they aren't paid enough then works backwards from there. This is wrong from my experience. Anecdotally, I have never left a job because of money. Sure, I left jobs and got ones that ended up paying more money but the reason I started looking in the first place wasn't money. It was for other reasons that usually included frustrations with management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BadHumans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Baeocystin in "Tell HN: Burnout is bad to your brain, take care"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41461945</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41461945"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T01:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You do it during work hours. Period.
Your brain only has so many truly 'on' hours in a day, and it's already less than 8.  Trying to burn even more in the pursuit of complex knowledge isn't just robbing Peter to pay Paul, it's eating the seed corn and wondering why your harvest failed.
It's a scary thing to realize, and can be hard to stick with.  But limits are real, and respecting them gets more work done in the long run than not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baeocystin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by burningChrome in "Tell HN: Burnout is bad to your brain, take care"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41461808</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41461808"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T00:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early on in my career (I was a late bloomer and already in early 30's) as a developer, I got burnt out pretty bad twice. After the second time and teetering on a third, I knew I had to do something to change what I was doing and how I managed my work load.
I just focused on getting MY stuff done and that was it. I stopped taking on other's people work. I stopped taking on more work once I got my stuff done. I would do exactly what a Sprint called for. Nothing more, nothing less. If I finished early with my tasks, I would stretch out the time and just tell the scrum master I was close, but not done yet, but always finished on time. I basically just did what was required of me. I wasn't out to impress anybody, I just became "Mr. Dependable" on any of the teams I worked on.
This was the approach that changed everything.
Now, some ten years later? I'm never too high or too low. I still do the same thing, I still just do what is asked of me and that's it. 5pm every night? Laptop gets turned off. Friday at 6pm? Laptop is off for the entire weekend. I turn it back on right before my meetings on Monday. Separating my personal life from my work life with a hard delimiter was paramount.
I found out that if you don't protect your sanity and your own well being, people will take advantage of you and your time and it will never end. Once you break the cycle and get that time back for yourself? You'll make sure you never willingly give it to someone else ever again.
Protect yourself. Protect your sanity. Once you lose it, like OP said, it's very, very hard to get back.
I hope this helps someone else struggling to break this cycle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>burningChrome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Post Using Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://darrenhester.com/my-first-post-using-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://darrenhester.com/my-first-post-using-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T21:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone who provided feedback on their experience with Bear. I appreciate it! All the comments were positive, so I'm jumping on board.
New Blog: 
darrenhester.com
New RSS: 
darrenhester.com/feed/
I also want to thank Robert for making his Bearming Theme available. I love the design, and it's easy to customize.
All my posts from Scribbles have been copied over, but I still have several pages to build out. I'll be working on that this weekend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add new Australian volcanic activity to the list of worries…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8419</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/add-new-australian-volcanic-activity-list-worries/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As if climate change, and the increasingly unstable weather it will bring, isn’t enough to worry about, parts of Australia may see an increase in volcanic activity. Not in the immediate future, thankfully, but at some point nonetheless: It is much less likely that a volcano that has already erupted will start again. It is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are You a Dalia? How We Created Data Science Personas for Spotify’s Analytics Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7199</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/09/are-you-a-dalia-how-we-created-data-science-personas-for-spotifys-analytics-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T19:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Spotify’s Analytics Platform, we’re dedicated to building products that empower data practitioners to discover, analyze, and share insights — [...]
The post Are You a Dalia? How We Created Data Science Personas for Spotify’s Analytics Platform appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[september sun]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/september-sun/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/september-sun/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T18:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just got back from getting my hair lopped at Mastercuts. $30. And let me tell you, this lady got it right, and I didn't have to spend a small fortune.
I stopped and got a cream cheese and lox bagel with a blood orange Pelligrino around the corner from the salon. I sat by the window, and people watched, hurrying to and from their office jobs high in the sky.
The bagel was alright, although I think I got spoiled living at Bathurst and Lawrence, a predominantly Jewish community, with their spectacular bagels, that now, every other bagel shop, pales in comparison. My people know how to make a mean cream cheese and lox.
I've been up to my neck in job search.
There's one in particular I'm hoping will call back. Not because I like the job, but because it's close to home, and i can do the job with my eyes closed.

I'm still spending most of my writing efforts on my email blog.
I wrote two letters: end of august diary, and deep affection. Hope you liked them <3
If you're a regular reader of my blog (hi ilu 🦄), consider signing up!
This past week, I've been trying out Substack. I know, I know, a lot of you don't like the platform for various reasons. I'm with you on quite a few of them.
But. BUT. What a pleasure it is to write in their editor. Things WORK! Can you even imagine?
There are no weird formatting issues. I can easily upload a picture and write a caption easy peasy. Bullet lists don't go all wonky when i hit publish.
But on the flip side, it doesn't feel like my writing home. The writers use the same writerly language, discussing Important Things in highly sophisticated, educated, long-form essays.
I feel like the outcast in the cafeteria sitting by myself eating a wet sandwich my mom made me.
on another note...

the most magical time of the year is finally upon us 🍂]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code August 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_93</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_93"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code August 2024 Release (1.93)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[will you miss me when i’m gone?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/going-home/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/going-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By this time next week I will be back at home. Although I love my life
here more than even I anticipated, I'm very much looking forward to
being home. In a moment which I recognize as an incredibly rare
occurrence in my life, I want to be both places.
Like most people in the States after I turned eighteen I started
splitting time between home and school, or work, or wherever I
happened to be at the time. At first I didn't go home very often
because I felt stagnant there, lost, and my parents' presence
exhausted me. I found ways to leave school days later than everyone
else and ways to return early from break. Most years I think I wanted
to be only in one place, if that — where I was — and in lower points
of my life I wanted to be neither where I was nor at home. So it is
with great gratitu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240905</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240905"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer Code Challenge]]></title>
        <id>3dabf76f52f09592f27882dc6288dd0f2a88080e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-code-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T11:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is a generative artificial intelligence (AI) powered conversational assistant that can help you understand, build, extend, and operate AWS applications. You can ask questions about AWS architecture, your AWS resources, best practices, documentation, support, and more. With Amazon Q Developer in your IDE, you can write a comment in natural language that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Sempf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Books and More Books, Never Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/books-and-more-books/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/books-and-more-books/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am genetically blessed with a good memory. I was born with it and I've done absolutely nothing special to cultivate it, other than to stuff it full of facts that I can pull out during games of Trivial Pursuit or at random times to surprise Wonder Woman. My mother saved a book she bought for me as a toddler that was a directory of horse breeds: Percheron, Clydesdale, Morgan - I memorized them all and family legend says I would "read" the book to visiting adults as a party trick.
Books were important to my parents. I've been surrounded by books my whole life. My mother still has the set of encyclopedias that she and my dad bought in 1970, along with a collection of classics like Gulliver's Travels and Pilgrim's Progress, books I challenged during elementary school. I was allowed to read an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loren Balhorn: &ldquo;Darker Turn&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/darker-turn</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/darker-turn"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in Thuringia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jwr in "A SpamAssassin Surprise"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41455281</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41455281"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T10:29:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please do not let a story like that discourage you from running your own mail server. I am really worried about the future where 2-3 adtech corporations control what we receive and read, and we are not far away from that future.
As a counterpoint, I have been running my own E-mail server for the last 25 years or so, and haven't found it to be terribly problematic. Yes, there is an occasional issue, but I'd rather control my mail, than hand it off to someone else.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jwr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dannyobrien in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41454990</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41454990"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I disagree with this assessment on  many levels, but I think the most important challenge I can make is to the idea that Brewster Kahle is a rogue actor, who in some sense mis-interpreted the mission and strategy of the Internet Archive.
For those of you who are just learning that name from this lawsuit, here's his wikipedia page:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brewster_Kahle
Kahle founded the Archive in the nineties, in the midst of the fairly determined attempts at that time to either delay or even re-engineer the early Internet to be more respectful of existing intellectual property and decency laws.
We inherit a searchable, saveable web, because of the work done then to establish the norm that the Internet itself should exist, and that open digital archives can exist, legally. Many many…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dannyobrien</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Am I The Immoral Person]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53149</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/05/am-i-the-immoral-person/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plain People of Crooked Timber: can’t see why you’re drafting us in here so often after leaving us out in the cold for five years or whatever, we are busy people with our own lives and so on. Me: but I love you and you’re the best! Plain People of Crooked Timber: well if you’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A global assessment of third-party connection tampering]]></title>
        <id>2PQ5yUYNh250JZfC8YuElJ</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/connection-tampering"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare brings visibility to the practice of connection tampering as observed from our global network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Sundara Raman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing insights into TCP resets and timeouts to Cloudflare Radar]]></title>
        <id>3SsAGFwmMK2KDYd7THI6Dn</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/tcp-resets-timeouts"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New TCP resets and timeouts dataset on Cloudflare Radar surfaces connection tampering, scanning, DoS attacks, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Valenta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Graeber - The Wisdom of Kandiaronk]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-wisdom-of-kandiaronk?v=1725518188</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-wisdom-of-kandiaronk?v=1725518188"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T06:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Graeber
Title: The Wisdom of Kandiaronk
Subtitle: The Indigenous Critique, the Myth of Progress and the Birth of the Left
Date: 2019
Notes: Article publié le 28 septembre 2019 Pour citer cet article : David Graeber , « La sagesse de Kandiaronk : la critique indigène, le mythe du progrès et la naissance de la Gauche », Revue du MAUSS permanente, 28 septembre 2019 [en ligne].
Source: Original: journaldumauss.net/?La-sagesse-de-Kandiaronk-la-critique-indigene-le-mythe-du-progres-et-la Translated at: nevermoremedia.substack.com/i/140700070/the-wisdom-of-kandiaronk-the-indigenous-critique-the-myth-of-progress-and-the-birth-of-the-left

 
 
Anthropologist David Graeber has been working for seven years, with archaeologist David Wengrow, on a work devoted to a history of inequality. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41452097</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41452097"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T00:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree with you about copyright, but the fact is that the IA never had a chance and we knew it years ago.
The top comment on HN a week after their launch of the EL is critical [0], right at the moment when HN would be most expected to rally to their defense. By the time the lawsuit was actually starting to take shape most commenters had become very concerned for the fate of the IA [1]. This is on a forum that reliably champions freedom of information, but most of us knew even at the time that what they'd done was extremely unlikely to pass muster.
The IA was never going to be hailed as a cultural hero because they stood no chance, and they are too valuable for other, unrelated reasons to make themselves a martyr. This never should have happened under the same legal entity as the web archive.
[0] https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=22731472
[1] https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=23485182]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weird winter weather points to yet more unstable weather]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8414</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/weird-winter-weather-points-more-unstable-weather/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T21:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mick Tsikas, writing for The Conversation: The severe weather rounds out a weird winter across Australia. The nation’s hottest ever winter temperature was recorded when Yampi Sound in Western Australia reached 41.6C on Tuesday. Elsewhere across Australia, winter temperatures have been way above average. 41.6°C? It doesn’t even get that hot in summer, at least […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41450224</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41450224"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T20:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The further you take a federal case the more precedent you create. The infinitesimal odds IA seemed to have at winning this case have to be weighed against the precedent they have created that may bind on future controlled digital lending cases with better facts. What IA did here wasn't costless.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by teruakohatu in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41450153</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41450153"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T20:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> In his many interviews with U.S. media, he portrays the court cases and legal judgements as a crusade against the Internet Archive and all librarians. It's not. It's the logical outcome of one man's seemingly fanatical conviction against the law and the people who work very hard to bring new books into being.
If IA had won, IA would be hailed as a cultural hero. They hit and they missed. Claiming Brewster Kahle is against "the people who work very hard to bring new books into being" is unfair. The copyright goalposts have moved so far past where they were originally, the people who work very hard can be dead for decades and their works still in copyright, and by the time they are dead for 70 years, the copyright will probably be extended again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teruakohatu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ilamont in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449965</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449965"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T19:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This has been playing out for many years. And it's all because Brewster Kahle decided that an overly broad interpretation of the Internet Archive's mission trumped the rights of authors and publishers, and the laws of the United States.
When IA was asked to stop CDL - many times - he continued. The National Writers Union tried to open a dialogue as early as 2010 but was ignored:
The Internet Archive says it would rather talk with writers individually than talk to the NWU or other writers’ organizations. But requests by NWU members to talk to or meet with the Internet Archive have been ignored or rebuffed.
https://nwu.org/nwu-denounces-cdl/
When the requests to abandon CDL turned into demands, Kahle dug in his heels. When the inevitable lawsuits followed, and IA lost, he insisted that he was still in the right and plowed ahead with appeals.
He also opened a new front in the court of public opinion. In his blog posts and interviews with U.S. media, Kahle portrays the court cases and legal judgements as a crusade against the Internet Archive and all librarians (see https://blog.archive.org/2023/12/15/brewster-kahle-appeal-st...). It's not. It's the logical outcome of one man's seemingly fanatical conviction against the law and the people who work very hard to bring new books into being.
In addition, there has been real collateral damage to the many noble aspects of the Internet Archive. Legal fees and judgements have diverted resources away from the Wayback Machine, the library of public domain works, and other IA programs that provide real value to society. I truly hope the organization can survive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ilamont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jandrese in "The Internet Archive has lost its appeal in Hachette vs. Internet Archive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449806</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449806"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T19:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Very much not a surprise.  I think the Internet Archive is providing an invaluable service to humanity in preserving works that would otherwise be lost to time.  it is one of the crown jewels of the Internet, doing a job that nobody else is willing to do.  But at the same time I know the courts side with publishers pretty much every time and copyright law being such as it is they're totally screwed. The only real question is how many trillions dollars will the judgment be.  Preserving history is at odds with the profit motive, and lawmakers care a lot more about the latter than the former.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jandrese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmward01 in "Amazon bans its drivers from moving their own lips too much at work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449761</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449761"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T19:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had a discussion with someone recently about how tech is enabling enforcement of laws/policies/etc at a scale never before possible and how that is a bad thing. The problem is that people can't conform perfectly and the tighter we force people to conform the more likely they are to 'break' and disconnect from society. Basically, if 'acceptable' is so narrowly defined that you can't achieve it 100% of the time, why try even a little to conform? In companies there is somewhat of an off-ramp, quit (which isn't always a realistic option obviously), but these enforcement abilities are invading areas that we can't avoid and that is a real problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmward01</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cube2222 in "Kagi Assistant"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449694</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41449694"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T19:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To repeat myself from a recent HN thread:
I've been using Kagi for a while (almost two years now!) and it's been nothing but excellent!
Lenses are very useful (Reddit lens is on every second search), and I personally really like the AI features they are working on.
The new more advanced assistant which is able to do searches, which can also be constrained to lenses, and lets you pick an arbitrary model, is excellent, and basically means I don't need a chatgpt/claude subscription, as Kagi covers it very well.
All in all, great product which I'm happy to pay for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cube2222</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AnotherGoodName in "Intel Honesty"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41448341</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41448341"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel is trapped. Its debt repayments alone are massive. The poor performance in stock has encouraged 20years of wage stagnation to the point where you can literally earn over 50% more at amd or nvidia or even an startup for equivalent roles so they aren’t hiring the best. Their pay in the Bay Area is double tsmc in taiwan for equivalent roles in raw dollar terms but the ppp differences means your better off working for tsmc in Taiwan than intel in the Bay Area. That’s not a joke. Intel are literally incapable of attracting talent from Taiwan right now.
They don’t have the talent they need and the debt trap and poor performance means a lot of push back to the needed doubling of wages to attract that talent. It’s a very hard sell for any exec trying to correct this problem. They sidelined lip bu tan who was one of the advocates for even more layoffs and wage freezes but he’s one of many backwards thinkers they need to remove. It’s going to be difficult to fix their board.
Without talent intel has no hope of winning and they can’t get that talent due to poor stock performance for the past 20years leading to executives and shareholders wishing to implement the opposite of what they need right now. In fact they have ongoing layoffs right now. A true downward spiral and the only real hope is for a newcomer to step up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnotherGoodName</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Read Meta’s 2024 Sustainability Report]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21669</id>
        <link href="https://sustainability.atmeta.com/2024-sustainability-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]
Read More...
The post Read Meta’s 2024 Sustainability Report appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stability AI’s best image generating models now in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>86d9ddca83c600aa88d09a9cd01d58ac64149314</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/stability-ais-best-image-generating-models-now-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T17:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generate photorealistic images with exceptional detail. Enhance visuals effortlessly across industries with improved multi-subject prompts, stunning image quality, and impeccable typography.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest AWS Heroes have arrived – September 2024]]></title>
        <id>31662511be8cd6f35550c899cca6ff0926eba21e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/the-latest-aws-heroes-have-arrived-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T16:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS Heroes program recognizes outstanding individuals who are making meaningful contributions within the AWS community. These technical experts generously share their insights, best practices, and innovative solutions to help others create efficiencies and build faster on AWS. Heroes are thought leaders who have demonstrated a commitment to empowering the broader AWS community through their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by semiquaver in "The Insecurity of Debian"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446964</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446964"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FWIW, I’ve worked at many RedHat shops over the years and I’ve never seen one where disabling SELinux wasn’t a normal part of provisioning a server. I haven’t seen the same thing with AppArmor (although I admit I have less visibility into debian systems administration). YMMV but it seems to me that a component which is so inconvenient that it’s normally disabled doesn’t provide much security in the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>semiquaver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Being Alone Doesn’t Have to be Lonely]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/when-being-alone-doesnt-have-to-be-lonely/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/when-being-alone-doesnt-have-to-be-lonely/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I consider myself an extroverted introvert. Or is it introverted extrovert? More on that later.
I feel like often times, us introverts are misunderstood. A lot of people mistake introverts to be anti-social, or shy… but that’s not always the case. Being an introvert means that our batteries are recharged by spending time alone, away from social interactions. This past weekend, I fully embraced my recharge by spending 3 days in solitude.
I mean… I mostly stayed away from human interaction. At least, I didn’t interact with any humans physically, and only through text with my other half, LC. This is also not because I don’t enjoy the company of others, especially LC’s, but there’s just something rejuvenating about spending time alone. You know… just existing in my own space, without the need to formulate words out loud, because sometimes there are just too many words. Of course, my dog got an earful from me every time I decided I needed to speak out loud.
There was a lot of silence, and little words, this weekend. It was nice not having any obligations outside of my own personal to-do list. I did a lot of reading, and a lot of binge watching (Dexter), which typically take a backseat in all of the life admin stuff I have to do. It was a great opportunity for me to recharge my mental and emotional batteries, and to force myself to find comfort in the quiet and the familiar.
I missed having my other half here, a lot, but it also felt good to take a step back from the world to focus on myself.
So here’s to the long weekend spent solo, the comfort in the quiet, and the understanding that being alone doesn’t have to be lonely.
Side note: I never really felt alone (even when I was) since I have a Velcro dog who literally needs to be attached to me at all times. That kind of balances things out, right?
53/100
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Ilya Sutskever's SSI Inc raises $1B"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446120</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446120"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T14:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Closest thing we have to a Manhattan Project in the modern era?
Minus the urgency, scientific process, well-defined goals, target dates, public ownership, accountability...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Ilya Sutskever's SSI Inc raises $1B"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446027</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41446027"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T14:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$1B raise, $5B valuation. For a company that is a couple months old and doesn't have a product or even a single line of code in production. Wild.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by laserbeam in "ReMarkable Paper Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41445458</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41445458"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love my remarkable 2. Bought it before "Connect" was a thing, so I don't have a subscription. But I cannot recommend it to anyone. There are better alternatives out there and MyDeepGuide (youtube) has reviewed them all better than I ever could.
The software is moving too slowly and often in a wrong direction. Especially since they released the keyboard folio most updates were around typing (which is supar on any eink device)... and they generally made my experience as a pen user worse.
I don't care if the new hardware is awesome, whenever mine breaks I will switch to a competitor.
EDIT: the reviewer I mention is excited about the device https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZkEg8WLeW4Q]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>laserbeam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI and the Labor Market: Will Firms Hire, Fire, or Retrain?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31531</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/ai-and-the-labor-market-will-firms-hire-fire-or-retrain/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid rise in Artificial Intelligence (AI) has the potential to dramatically change the labor market, and indeed possibly even the nature of work itself. However, how firms are adjusting their workforces to accommodate this emerging technology is not yet clear. Our August regional business surveys asked manufacturing and service firms special topical questions about their use of AI, and how it is changing their workforces. Most firms that report expected AI use in the next six months plan to retrain their workforces, with far fewer reporting adjustments to planned headcounts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel, Richard Deitz, Natalia Emanuel, and Benjamin Hyman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Professional Forecasters Predict Uncertain Times?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31494</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/can-professional-forecasters-predict-uncertain-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economic surveys are very popular these days and for a good reason. They tell us how the folks being surveyed—professional forecasters, households, firm managers—feel about the economy. So, for instance, the New York Fed’s Survey of Consumer Expectations (SCE) website displays an inflation uncertainty measure that tells us households are more uncertain about inflation than they were pre-COVID, but a bit less than they were a few months ago. The Philadelphia Fed’s Survey of Professional Forecasters (SPF) tells us that forecasters believed last May that there was a lower risk of negative 2024 real GDP growth than there was last February. The question addressed in this post is: Does this information actually have any predictive content? Specifically, I will focus on the SPF and ask: When professional forecasters indicate that their uncertainty about future output or inflation is higher, does that mean that output or inflation is actually becoming more uncertain, in the sense that the SPF will have a harder time predicting these variables?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecuador: From Rafael Correa to Guillermo Lasso via Lenin Moreno]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-From-Rafael-Correa-to-Guillermo-Lasso-via-Lenin-Moreno</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-From-Rafael-Correa-to-Guillermo-Lasso-via-Lenin-Moreno"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
Ecuador, 
South, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark clouds over Dutch Universities]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53130</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/04/dark-clouds-over-dutch-universities/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T06:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, the first day of our academic year, I went to a demonstration. The reason for the demonstration are the announced budget cuts for higher education, which our new right/extreme-right government wants to implement. The figures aren’t set in stone yet, but the financial appendix that was presented when the new government took office […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by teractiveodular in "We built the city of Colombo in Cities:Skylines"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41442168</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41442168"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T05:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modified traffic behavior using TM:PE mod to reflect Sri Lankan driving habits:
- Buses may ignore lane arrows
- Vehicles may enter blocked junctions
- Vehicles may do U-turns at junctions
- 10% of drivers are reckless
- Vehicles may park on the sides of streets
- Three wheelers and scooters
Brilliant!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teractiveodular</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JimDabell in "Llms.txt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41441178</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41441178"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T02:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not how these kinds of things should be designed for the web.
Instead of putting resources in the root of the web, this is what /.well-known/ was designed for. See RFC 5785:
https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/html/rfc5785
Instead of munging URLs to get alternate formats, this is what content negotiation or rel=alternate were designed for.
I’m not sure making it easier to consume content is something that is needed. I think it might be more useful to define script type=llm that would expose function calling to LLMs embedded in browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JimDabell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nadine El-Enany: &ldquo;Something Monstrous&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/something-monstrous</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/something-monstrous"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T00:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Britain’s colonial pathologies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to optimize log management for Amazon EKS with Amazon FSx for NetApp ONTAP]]></title>
        <id>ee6078e423b3fd64703d6132396bdc3f58b8887c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/optimize-log-management-for-amazon-eks-with-amazon-fsx-for-netapp-ontap/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T23:01:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud native technologies empower organizations to build and run scalable applications in modern, dynamic environments. Among Cloud Native patterns, Containers, and Kubernetes are mainstream across multiple businesses. According to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation Annual Survey of 2022, 44% of respondents are already using containers for nearly all applications and business segments, and another 35% say containers are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tsahi Duek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[coffee chats and donut dates]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/coffee-chats/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/coffee-chats/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T22:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The office I work out of runs an opt-in coffee chat program which
matches you with someone each week to have a short chat over coffee. I
don't know anyone in the office, so at the behest of my director I
signed up.
I had my first coffee chat today. The guy I was supposed to meet with
showed up fifteen minutes late, which might have irked me if (i) I
hadn't rescheduled our chat something like three times and (ii) if I
actually enjoyed networking. Even though our conversation wasn't bad,
all things considered, I still found myself rather grateful when we
had to run to our 4 PM meetings. I always feel phony networking with
other people in the office, especially when they're a married
fortysomething busy salesman high up on the org chart who has better
things to do than talk to a lowly peasant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS named as a Leader in the first Gartner Magic Quadrant for AI Code Assistants]]></title>
        <id>148be78c8c914b1e3dc764e8933faaf4e4bf8aad</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-in-the-first-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-ai-code-assistants/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T21:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Web Services (AWS) AI code assistant Amazon Q Developer named a Leader in Gartner's first Magic Quadrant for its Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision, driving innovation across the software development lifecycle with enterprise-grade controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie Web, small web, social web, whatever web, my web]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8399</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-web-small-web-social-web-whatever-web-my-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a bit of a surge in discussion recently about Indie Web, and seemingly what it means to be a true adherent. This time the focus appears to be about what I’m going to call technical proficiency. From what I can gather, having your own website, with your own domain name, and your own […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by panarky in "EUCLEAK Side-Channel Attack on the YubiKey 5 Series"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41438346</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41438346"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not just YubiKey.
NinjaLab: "All Infineon security microcontrollers (including TPMs) that run the Infineon cryptographic library (as far as we know, any existing version) are vulnerable to the attack."
- Chips in e-passports from the US, China, India, Brazil and numerous European and Asian nations
- Secure enclaves in Samsung and OnePlus phones
- Cryptocurrency hardware wallets like Ledger and Trezor
- SIM cards
- TPMs in laptops from Lenovo, Dell, and HP
- EMV chips in credit and debit cards]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>panarky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BearBoost Shortcut for Bear Bloggers]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bearboost-shortcut-bloggers/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bearboost-shortcut-bloggers/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T19:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BearBoost

BearBoost is an Apple shortcut designed to help you boost your blogging.
It's for all bloggers, but especially those who use the Bear blogging platform. The idea is to give you a quick and easy tool to help you get writing when you're feeling stuck.
It's like having your personal muse whisper, "No more writer's block! Let's turn this blank page into a blog masterpiece!" Okay, maybe not exactly that, but kind of.
The shortcut currently offers nine menu options:
Trending Posts (Bear discovery feed)
Recent Posts (Bear discovery feed)
Ten Topics (pick one and start writing)
Daily Prompt (via Kevin McDonald)
Random Prompt (from Blog Prompts)
Random Quote (from Random Quotations)
Today’s Word (via Merriam-Webster)
Blog Inspiration (a page of mine)
Discover Blogs (the blog directory)
I'll likely add more features over time. If you have any requests, please let me know.
Get the BearBoost shortcut]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by edent in "EUCLEAK Side-Channel Attack on the YubiKey 5 Series"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41437728</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41437728"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T18:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As per https://arstechnica.com/security/2024/09/yubikeys-are-vulner...
An attacker not only needs your username and password, they also need physical access to your key. They then have to disassemble the device. If they want to give it back to you, they'll need to reassemble it.
So not exactly trivial!
A blob of nail-varnish over a plastic seam might be a useful canary.
But this does highlight one weakness of these FIDO tokens - you have to manually maintain a list of where you've registered them. And if your token is lost or stolen, you have to manually revoke every single one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bko in "The Engineering of Landfills"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41436904</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41436904"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T17:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found this interesting:
> Another option is to put it to beneficial use to create heat or even electricity. The Puente Hills landfill I showed earlier has a gas-to-energy facility that’s been running since 1987, and even though the landfill is now closed, it currently provides enough electricity to power around 70,000 homes.
And towards the end
> Landfills seem like an environmental blight, but really, properly designed ones play a huge role in making sure waste products don’t end up in our soil or air or water. It’s not possible to landfill waste everywhere... But my point is: landfills are a surprisingly low-impact way to manage solid waste in a lot of cases. I hope the future is a utopia where all the stuff we make maintains its beneficial value forever, but for now, I am thankful for the sanitary engineers and the other professions involved in safely and economically dealing with our trash so we don’t have to.
I love reading about landfills. I wish more environmentalists would be excited about engineering solving environmental ills and relied less on knee-jerk reactions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diverting class warfare into generational warfare]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45582</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/03/diverting-class-warfare-into-generational-warfare/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T15:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker In the last-half century, productivity has outpaced the growth of real compensation for the median worker by more than 40 percent. This means that if workers’ pay had kept pace with productivity, as it did in the three decades after World War II, it would be roughly 40 percent higher than it is today. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yjftsjthsd-h in "Why bother with argv[0]?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41435515</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41435515"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T14:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So obviously claiming that there's no good reason for process to read argv[0] is either demonstrating the author's ignorance or needs a much stronger defense; I'd be fascinated to hear how they think busybox should work on an OpenWrt box with a 16MB root filesystem.
However, I am willing to consider the discussion about whether there could be merit to restricting the ability to write that value; I could imagine a system that populated it only from the actual file name and did not allow it to be written by the parent process or the child process at runtime. The obvious place this still falls apart is that an attacker could just
    ln /bin/curl ./some\ other\ name

but there are sometimes security measures that we use even though they're less than 100% effective so it at least conceivable that this might be a trade off worth making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yjftsjthsd-h</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sevensor in "The Art of Finishing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41434290</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41434290"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T12:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or, you could stop beating yourself up about it and reframe the whole activity as a creative release. Nobody else cares if you finish it, why should you? My neighbor died with a project car parked in his driveway. It had been there for years. Every so often he got out there and worked on it with his grandson. Who among us would call that time wasted? Why not dust off Project Foo on a Saturday afternoon, and just tinker with the fun parts?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sevensor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Partner]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/my-partner/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/my-partner/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am deeply and hopelessly in love and there's not much I can do about it. Luckily, the object of my affection is my wife of eleven years. Whenever we are separated, regardless for how long, I unconsciously begin a countdown in my mind until I see her again, even it it's just from the beginning of the work day until lunch. I've never known anyone as well as I know her. I can tell her mood from the sound of her footsteps as she descends the stairs from our bedroom into the living room. Neither of us ever attempt to hide an emotion from the other, so intune we are with each other's feelings.
My wife is a classic introvert. Our home is her haven, the place where she recharges her batteries. I long ago accepted the responsibility for answering every knock at the door and being the one to deal …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Professional Forecasters Overconfident?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31528</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/are-professional-forecasters-overconfident/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post-COVID years have not been kind to professional forecasters, whether from the private sector or policy institutions: their forecast errors for both output growth and inflation have increased dramatically relative to pre-COVID (see Figure 1 in this paper). In this two-post series we ask: First, are forecasters aware of their own fallibility? That is, when they provide measures of the uncertainty around their forecasts, are such measures on average in line with the size of the prediction errors they make? Second, can forecasters predict uncertain times? That is, does their own assessment of uncertainty change on par with changes in their forecasting ability? As we will see, the answer to both questions sheds light of whether forecasters are rational. And the answer to both questions is “no” for horizons longer than one year but is perhaps surprisingly “yes” for shorter-run forecasts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by laserbeam in "Greppability is an underrated code metric"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41432569</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41432569"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T08:21:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scenarios where an IDE with full syntactic understanding is better:
- It's your day to day project and you expect to be working in it for a long time.
Scenarios where grepping is more useful:
- Your language has #ifdef or equivalent syntax which does conditional compilation making syntactic tools incomplete.
- You just opened the project for the first time.
- It's in a language you don't daily drive (you write backend but have to delve in frontend code, it's a 3rd party library, it's configuration files, random json/xml files or data)
- You're editing or searching through documentation.
- You haven't even downloaded the project and are checking things out in github (or some similar site for your project).
- You're providing remote assistance to someone and you are not at your main development machine.
- You're remoting via SSH and have access to code there (say it's a python server).
Yes, an IDE will save you time daily driving. But there's no reason to sabotage all the other usecases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>laserbeam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lucumo in "Greppability is an underrated code metric"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41431701</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41431701"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T05:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grepping for symbols like function names and class names feels so anemic compared to using a tool that has a syntactic understanding of the code. Just "go to definition" and "find usages" alone reduce the need for text search enormously.
For the past decade-plus I have mostly only searched for user facing strings. Those have the advantage of being longer, so are more easily searched.
Honestly, posts like this sound like the author needs to invest some time in learning about better tools for his language. A good IDE  alone will save you so much time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lucumo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[getting a life]]></title>
        <id>https://aco.bearblog.dev/getting-a-life/</id>
        <link href="https://aco.bearblog.dev/getting-a-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T01:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i dont like getting asked "what have you been up to?". i don't know. i could have had the most interesting past few days, or the most uneventful, and i would simply not remember. my memory is slim these days, and comes to me in fleeting moments when i can form links with events in the present. sitting here in the sun the sun sends me back to the beach i was on this summer. the embrace from a friend brings the scent of the perfume my grandmother used to wear. the unassumed path we bike on takes me to my mom's hometown. i wonder at times if i only remember things by association.

i've been doing a lot of things recently, which has been nice. i've been seeing friends and getting out of the house most days. at times i wonder if this is what life is supposed to be all about; these joyful moments shared with others, kept a secret from the rest of the world. i don't take many photos when i'm out like that. my mom gets mad i don't have anything to show for my outings. having a photo of the occasion makes me feel like i have cheated myself out of a memory by constraining it to a handful of pixels. who do i need prove i had a good time to?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making progress on routing security: the new White House roadmap]]></title>
        <id>10dR1e1P8WbOojN0JGTPOp</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/white-house-routing-security"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 3, 2024, the White House published a report on Internet routing security. We’ll talk about what that means and how you can help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Conlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A short film shot on the iPhone 15 Pro Max, with no lens, filter, or AI]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8394</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/short-film-iphone-15-pro-max/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T21:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I’m sure pretty no AI is involved. What’s really incredible about this three minute video, made by Faruk Korkmaz, is that it was filmed entirely by a device, a smartphone, many of us carry in our pockets. The narration is fitting also. It comes from a speech given by Canadian-American actor and comedian Jim […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Parallel Computing Service, Amazon EC2 status checks, and more (September 2, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>4fb73ba1739dd770b73cc79b69696086e450955f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-parallel-computing-service-amazon-ec2-status-checks-and-more-september-2-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T17:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the arrival of September, AWS re:Invent 2024 is now 3 months away and I am very excited for the new upcoming services and announcements at the conference. I remember attending re:Invent 2019, just before the COVID-19 pandemic. It was the biggest in-person re:Invent with 60,000+ attendees and it was my second one. It was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I mastered English through sheer Anger]]></title>
        <id>https://secemp9.bearblog.dev/how-i-mastered-english-through-sheer-anger/</id>
        <link href="https://secemp9.bearblog.dev/how-i-mastered-english-through-sheer-anger/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T22:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was once so angry that I reached this current level of understanding English, the level you see right now.
It was in the summer of 2016.
I wasn’t particularly angry at the time, until a certain event occurred. Looking back, it probably wasn’t that significant, but, to put it briefly, the main cause was an English teacher I had at the time. It might have been a childish reason, but I was just a kid back then.
During that summer, fueled by anger, I took the first hardcover English book I could find at home (I remember the title was "Frankenstein") and tried to read it.
I didn’t have my laptop, internet, TV, or even a paper dictionary at the time. I was furious and struggled to read the book.
On my first read, I understood only about 1-5% of the entire book. But I kept going. As I struggled…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Academic nepo babies ?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53118</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/01/academic-nepo-babies/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T21:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This study showing that US academic faculty members are 25 times more likely than Americans in general to have a parent with a PhD or Masters degree has attracted a lot of attention, and comments suggesting that this is unusual and unsatisfactory. But is it? For various reasons, I’ve interacted quite a bit with farmers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland: home of some of the best literature in the world]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8381</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ireland-home-best-literature-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication of Irish author Sally Rooney’s fourth novel, Intermezzo, on 24 September 2024, nears. It promises to be quite the event. I don’t know about Australia, but in Ireland and the UK, some bookshops will open early on the day, so eager Rooney fans can get hold of her latest offering. But Sally Rooney is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilians flock to Bluesky after authorities block X]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8376</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/brazilians-flock-bluesky-authorities-block-x/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T20:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilians are turning to Bluesky — the microblogging platform founded by then Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey — in droves, following a ban on X in the South American country. The surge in signups however has prompted warnings from Bluesky that the service may experience outages, as a result. But that seems like a good sort […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thought about conservative psychology re: the abortion issue]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53107</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/01/a-thought-about-conservative-psychology-re-the-abortion-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So is Trump going to be able to pivot to pro-choice in the run-up to the election? I mean: he’s trying. But will it work? And will his pro-life base accept it, because he’s Trump? I hope no pro-choice voters are fooled. I hope they hold him responsible for overturning Roe. It’s beyond obvious they […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>