<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-24T01:52:41.110Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-24T01:52:41.110Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Scheduling]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/24/sig-scheduling-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/24/sig-scheduling-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this SIG Scheduling spotlight we talked with Kensei Nakada, an
approver in SIG Scheduling.
Introductions
Arvind: Hello, thank you for the opportunity to learn more about SIG Scheduling! Would you
like to introduce yourself and tell us a bit about your role, and how you got involved with
Kubernetes?
Kensei: Hi, thanks for the opportunity! I’m Kensei Nakada
(@sanposhiho), a software engineer at
Tetrate.io. I have been contributing to Kubernetes in my free time for more
than 3 years, and now I’m an approver of SIG-Scheduling in Kubernetes. Also, I’m a founder/owner of
two SIG subprojects,
kube-scheduler-simulator and
kube-scheduler-wasm-extension.
About SIG Scheduling
AP: That's awesome! You've been involved with the project since a long time. Can you provide a
brief overview of SIG Schedu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing Tetris may ease post-traumatic stress disorder symptoms]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8549</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/playing-tetris-may-ease-post-traumatic-stress-disorder-symptoms/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara E. Teller, writing for Legal Reader: The research, published in BMC Medicine, focuses on the use of video games, particularly the well-known Tetris game that has been around for decades, to help reduce intrusive memories, a core and sometimes debilitating symptom of the condition. Invented in 1984 by Alexey Pajitnov, Tetris is a straightforward […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279230</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T18:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Latest on Trump assassinations; there's now a price on Trump's head; Spooks move toward authenticating election outcomes; Latest on MI, MT, NC, PA, etc.; Boeing $30 billion share issue to solve its $10 billion cash crunch? ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamba 1.5 family of models by AI21 Labs is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>6ded5a2482a6ceaea13f37bd0cb8dee31a204b7c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/jamba-1-5-family-of-models-by-ai21-labs-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI21's Jamba 1.5 models enable high-performance long-context language processing up to 256K tokens, with JSON output support and multilingual capabilities across 9 languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2 X8g Instances, Amazon Q generative SQL for Amazon Redshift, AWS SDK for Swift, and more (Sep 23, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>4aa4231deeeef984194acd947c69a278e49f9574</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-x8g-instances-amazon-q-generative-sql-for-amazon-redshift-aws-sdk-for-swift-and-more-sep-23-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Community Days have been in full swing around the world. I am going to put the spotlight on AWS Community Day Argentina where Jeff Barr delivered the keynote, talks and shared his nuggets of wisdom with the community, including a fun story of how he once followed Bill Gates to a McDonald’s! I encourage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On having outgrown a city]]></title>
        <id>https://coco-fraise.bearblog.dev/on-having-outgrown-a-city/</id>
        <link href="https://coco-fraise.bearblog.dev/on-having-outgrown-a-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This impression is staying on my skin like ink stays on the stamp after the paper has already been stamped.
It’s as if every step has already been had. Every smile has been smiled. Every breath has been breathed. Every corner has been explored. One unique place holds on so much memories that it is starting to feel crowded, like this one subway line at 6:38 at night when you come back from work.
I feel this way about Lyon, the city where I grew up. In a kind of weird way that I did not notice at first, this impression became tiring.
It felt like being physically attached to my past. When you see multiple memories at every corner of the street, it makes creating new memories a bit more difficult.
I’ll give you an example.
This morning, I was just out for a morning run and I turned the corner…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one week until i stop casually using social media]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/one-week-until-i-stop-casually-using-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/one-week-until-i-stop-casually-using-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:42:59.487Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this was crossposted from cohost. the original url was cohost.org/jkap/post/7810928-one-week-until-i-sto
one week until i stop casually using social media. if you see my ass again it's because i need to promote something or i'm reblogging art i like.
the past few years have taught me that i really don't like the microblogging style of social media. you would think that a shorter character limit would lead to concision but it doesn't; it just encourages you to split your thoughts across multiple posts.
i never really enjoyed "posting" on tumblr (which i realize sounds silly given that cohost lifted from tumblr's design the most) so i'm unlikely to start doing that. i genuinely think this might be it for me. i will retreat to my group chats with friends and move to the pre-social media model: if i want to know how my friends are doing, i'll ask them. if i'm gonna be in town somewhere and want to see someone, i'll message them instead of posting into the void.
it's all the same core theme: being deliberate. a focus on social media can hamper your relationships with your non-social media-using friends; they don't know what's going on because you're shouting into the void and they're not in it, but you don't actively talk to them because there's this subconscious assumption that everyone Important to you sees your posts.
anyway. i'm pretty sure i think about social media more than the average person. i'm looking forward to never thinking about social media again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by billyhoffman in "Cloudflare's new marketplace lets websites charge AI bots for scraping"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41626660</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41626660"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Common Crawl is shown in their screen shot of "Providers" along side OpenAI and Antropic. The challenge is that Common Crawl is used for a lot of things that are not AI training. For example, it's a major source of content for the Wayback machine.
In fact, that's the entire point of the Common Crawl project. Instead of dozens of companies writing and running their (poorly) designed crawlers and hitting everyone's site, Common Crawl runs once and exposes the data in industry standard formats like WARC for other consumers. Their crawler is quite well behaved (exponential backoff, obeys Crawl-Delay, will use SiteMaps.xml to know when to revisit, follows Robots.txt, etc.).
There are significant knock-on effects if CloudFlare starts (literally) gatekeeping content. This feels like a step down the path to a world where the majority of websites use sophisticated security products that gatekeep access to those who pay and those who don't, and that applied whether they are bots or people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>billyhoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Ag’s Road to Brazil]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279212</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/big-ags-road-to-brazil.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeSmog re-launches investigative series to track agribusiness’ influence over climate and nature policy in a critical year for decisions on the future of food and farming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start auditing and controlling the AI models accessing your content]]></title>
        <id>47pmgthPjmg2ZeYqTNmU8f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-ai-audit-control-ai-content-crawlers"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare customers on any plan can now audit and control how AI models access the content on their site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Ephemeral IDs: a new tool for fraud detection]]></title>
        <id>6V6W6JxQO7bnM0CbhuO1OA</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/turnstile-ephemeral-ids-for-fraud-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Internet evolves, Turnstile does too. Introducing Ephemeral IDs — a new dimension in detecting fraudulent activity, bot or human, that links behavior to a specific client instead of an IP address. This makes Turnstile better for everyone, everywhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oliver Payne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network performance update: Birthday Week 2024]]></title>
        <id>1CRWV43VAHSo5XHLkwPw2R</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-performance-update-birthday-week-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since June 2021, we’ve been measuring and ranking our network performance against the top global networks in the world. We use this data to improve our performance, and to share the results of those initiatives. 

In this post, we’re going to share with you how network performance has changed since our last post in March 2024, and discuss the tools and processes we are using to assess network performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Music</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making zone management more efficient with batch DNS record updates]]></title>
        <id>op0CI3wllMcGjptdRb2Ce</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/batched-dns-changes"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to customer demand, we now support the ability to DELETE, PATCH, PUT and POST multiple DNS records in a single API call, enabling more efficient and reliable zone management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Fattouche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Treasury Market Liquidity Improved in 2024?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31880</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/has-treasury-market-liquidity-improved-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard metrics point to an improvement in Treasury market liquidity in 2024 to levels last seen before the start of the current monetary policy tightening cycle. Volatility has also trended down, consistent with the improved liquidity. While at least one market functioning metric has worsened in recent months, that measure is an indirect gauge of market liquidity and suggests a level of current functioning that is far better than at the peak seen during the global financial crisis (GFC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Fleming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279198</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our balanced daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed’s Reactive-Looking Half-Point Rate Cut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279186</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/the-feds-reactive-looking-half-point-rate-cut.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed's half point rate reduction was unseemly large. What gives?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlanticism or Sovereignty? Fight in Germany Continues With Latest State Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/atlanticism-or-sovereignty-fight-in-germany-continues-with-latest-state-election.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T10:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Germany’s loyal servants to Washington are being backed into a corner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cheapflation and the Rise of Inflation Inequality in 2021-2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279179</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/cheapflation-and-the-rise-of-inflation-inequality-in-2021-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T08:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big companies victimized poor consumers via cheapflation: imposing greater price increases on low price goods than higher priced items]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving a Project: Intern Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16999</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/driving-a-project-intern-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a lot of hard work, you’ve landed that coveted internship. Now comes the next big challenge: delivering a meaningful project over the summer. Leading a project independently is an opportunity to sharpen your skills, demonstrate your capabilities, and experience personal growth. As you drive the project on your own, the support from your mentor […]
The post Driving a Project: Intern Edition appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dylan Steen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rapnie in "What's inside the QR code menu at this cafe?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41623005</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41623005"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T06:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Is this what the peak ordering experience looks like?
Call me old-fashioned, but to me the peak experience is a paper menu to choose from, and a waiter that patiently takes the order. Far prefer that to everyone at the table fiddling on their phones in some weird-ass website or even god forbid custom app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rapnie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Biggest Military Base Empire on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334330</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/the-biggest-military-base-empire-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T06:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The permanent stationing of more than 220,000 U.S. troops, weapons arsenals, and thousands of aircraft, tanks, and ships in every corner of the globe makes the logistics for U.S. aggression, and that of its allies, quicker and more efficient. Bases also facilitate the proliferation of nuclear weapons, with the United States keeping nuclear bombs in five NATO member countries, and nuclear-capable planes, ships, and missile launchers in many others. Because the U.S. is continually creating plans for military actions around the world, and because the U.S. military always has some troops “on the ready,” the initiation of combat operations is simpler. More
The post The Biggest Military Base Empire on Earth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greta Zarro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chickens Lack the Most Basic Legal Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334273</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/chickens-lack-the-most-basic-legal-protection/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T06:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chickens are the most populous bird on Earth and are widely considered among the most abused animals on the planet. Despite their ability to think and feel, billions of chickens are raised and killed for food each year and subjected to some of the worst living and slaughter conditions imaginable to meet the increasing demand for meat worldwide. More
The post Chickens Lack the Most Basic Legal Protection appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vicky Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Abuse Against Haitians in Ohio: Examined With Reference to Lewiston, Maine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334342</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/abuse-against-haitians-in-ohio-examined-with-reference-to-lewiston-maine/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Republican presidential and vice-presidential candidates expressed horror on learning from social media that Haitian migrants in Springfield, Ohio were eating dogs and cats, their pets. The reports were false. Bomb threats followed, schools and public buildings closed down. Longtime African-American residents felt threatened. More
The post Abuse Against Haitians in Ohio: Examined With Reference to Lewiston, Maine  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science vs Opinion: Consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334325</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/science-vs-opinion-consequences/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days it seems like there has been a death of expertise. On social media, virtually everyone is claiming to be an expert. Where does that leave our trust in actual solid, provable, documented information? We have measurements for time. People watching the Olympics saw small units of time in play when races were won  More
The post Science vs Opinion: Consequences appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wim Laven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Coming Electoral Storm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334323</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/the-coming-electoral-storm/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So here is some of the latest evidence that the United States now for the third quadrennial bourgeois electoral extravaganza in a row given put up a fascist maniac representing a fascist party atop its presidential ticket. There’s a not-so-subtle departure in Donald “They’re Eating the Cats and Dogs” Trump and his fascist running mate  More
The post The Coming Electoral Storm appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Circular Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334358</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/a-circular-economy/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between 1942 and 1964, migrant Mexican farm and railroad workers labored for low and often delayed pay under the U.S. Government’s Bracero Program. According to the 2023 paper “The Bracero Program and the Exploitability of Migrant Workers,” this program “operated by instilling fear and uncertainty among these people,” using threats of deportation and wage retention to control  More
The post A Circular Economy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why It’s Essential for America to Own Supply Chains]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/why-its-essential-for-america-to-own-supply-chains/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A knot formed in Sam Phillips’s stomach a few months ago when he learned that corroded titanium—sold with faked documents—somehow made it into doors and other components on civilian airliners. It was exactly the kind of nightmare scenario that Phillips and other members of the United Steelworkers (USW) warned of while trying to save the  More
The post Why It’s Essential for America to Own Supply Chains appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predatory Instincts: The Phoney Pharaoh of Harrods]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334362</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/predatory-instincts-the-phoney-pharaoh-of-harrods/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sticky slime streaming forth from the memory of the late Mohamed Al-Fayed, who died in August last year at the age of 94, has been unrelenting.  That the billionaire was an ogre of some proportion and influence during his time as the owner of Harrods in London was no secret.  His ego was so outsized it  More
The post Predatory Instincts: The Phoney Pharaoh of Harrods appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carne Ross - Anarchy is Love]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carne-ross-anarchy-is-love?v=1727069956</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carne-ross-anarchy-is-love?v=1727069956"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Carne Ross
Title: Anarchy is Love
Date: Summer 2024
Source: Dope 26

 I used to think that anarchism was “just” a political philosophy. I was wrong. It is much, much more than that. 
 By political philosophy, I mean a way of thinking about politics, institutions and decision-making. How people arbitrate their business with one another, theories of government – or self-government – or the abolition of all hierarchy. I liked to boil down anarchism into a few pithy phrases like, “anarchism is about no one having power over anyone else.” 
 I was not wrong. Anarchism is indeed about all of these things. It is indeed a political philosophy. It is indeed about how people take decisions together and manage their affairs collectively. But I thought this was its philosophy in toto, that ther…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[801 U.S. billionaires hold a combined $6.22 trillion in wealth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334373</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/801-u-s-billionaires-hold-a-combined-6-22-trillion-in-wealth/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are now 801 billionaires based in the United States with a combined wealth totaling $6.22 trillion, according to an Institute for Policy Studies analysis of the Forbes Real Time Billionaire List. The total number of billionaires is down 11 people as of September 13, 2024 from April when Forbes published their 38th annual World’s Billionaire List.  More
The post 801 U.S. billionaires hold a combined $6.22 trillion in wealth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chuck Collins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Connected Communities, One Circle at a Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334333</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/building-connected-communities-one-circle-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Guess what?!” A 12-year-old Pittsburgh schoolboy spoke excitedly with his teacher one-morning last fall. “My mommy and daddy were having a fight last night, and I asked them if we could have a peace circle! We sat and talked, and they’re not fighting anymore!” The boy had been involved in a program to introduce peace  More
The post Building Connected Communities, One Circle at a Time appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Burrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latin American Left Amid China, the United States,  Late Progressivism and the Far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/the-latin-american-left-amid-china-the-united-states-late-progressivism-and-the-far-right/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claudio Katz has just published a book in Spanish entitled America Latina en la encrucijada global [1] (“Latin America at the Global Crossroads”). Claudio Katz is a Marxist economist and professor at the University of Buenos Aires, author of some fifteen books concerning the  Dependency theory fifty years after its emergence, imperialism today, and issues faced by the  More
The post The Latin American Left Amid China, the United States,  Late Progressivism and the Far Right appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transcending the God of War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334327</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/23/transcending-the-god-of-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T05:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The man suspected in the incident . . . camped outside the golf course in West Palm Beach with food and a rifle for nearly 12 hours, according to court documents filed Monday. He is accused of lying in wait for the former president before a Secret Service agent opened fire, thwarting the potential attack.” The guy  More
The post Transcending the God of War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[P. B. - The Making of the Spanish CNT-IWA (2010–2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/p-b-the-making-of-the-spanish-cnt-iwa-2010-2024?v=1727043833</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/p-b-the-making-of-the-spanish-cnt-iwa-2010-2024?v=1727043833"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T22:23:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: P. B.
Title: The Making of the Spanish CNT-IWA (2010–2024)
Date: September 21, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 23rd September 2024 from libcom.org

 It is about 7 years since the spanish CNT-AIT organisation came into existence. Despite its name, which claims a historical trajectory, it is a split from the CNT. A split of almost an entire internal current which fought for control of the Confederation by all possible means, and eventually failed. In short, this is why it ended up outside. This (rather incomplete) article resumes the story of that conflict as seen through the eyes of what is now the CNT (CIT). 
The Cordoba Congress, 2010
 If we trace back the origins, some can go back to the debates at the Cordoba Congress in 2010. Other people might consider that the position of what woul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing a book may be a health hazard, just ask a writer]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8542</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/writing-book-may-be-health-hazard-just-ask-writer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T21:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American writer and researcher, Gwern Branwen: But how can I not want to write a book? And I get it: writing a book is sacred and unquestionable, the ultimate achievement for Western intellectuals — better than being arrested in a protest (because you don’t have to get sweaty), better than a PhD (because not so […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your coffee order, a subliminal yet revealing, job interview question?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8540</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/your-coffee-order-subliminal-revealing-job-interview-question/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T20:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying for a job, going through the interview process and what not, is much like walking on eggshells. Take one wrong step, and all your efforts may be for nothing. Even something as seemingly innocuous as the way you like your cup of coffee prepared, could be your undoing: I won’t say what work we […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fauci “Shares Insights on His Career” and the (On-Going) Covid Pandemic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279149</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/fauci-shares-insights-on-his-career-and-the-on-going-covid-pandemic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T20:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fauci's blind spots and the Covid public health debacle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unfortunately, colonising Mars is not a great idea]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8538</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/unfortunately-colonising-mars-not-great-idea/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T20:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s the challenge. There’s the adventure, the pioneering spirit, of setting off to another planet. Not everything is, or should be, easy. But are those really the right reasons for wishing to establish a human colony on the fourth rock from the Sun, Mars? Mars does not have a magnetosphere. Any discussion of humans ever […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be first in line for Intermezzo by Sally Rooney in Sydney tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8534</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/launch-intermezzo-sally-rooney-sydney-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T19:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow, Tuesday 24 September 2024, is the day Sally Rooney fans have been waiting for. That’s when the Irish author’s fourth novel, Intermezzo, is published. And from what I (and everyone else) can gather, anticipation is at fever pitch. The good news, for some Australian fans of Rooney, is they don’t have to wait until […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pembrook in "Does “building in public” work?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41619113</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41619113"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T18:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anecdotal, but it seems like all the people who “build in public” end up trapped by their chosen distribution strategy.
What I mean by this is, if you’re building in public there’s a 99% chance you’re going to end up building products for other indiehackers who are interested in following people who build in public.
This means you’re probably going to end up building yet another micro-Saas dev tool (Saas boilerplate, incident monitoring, etc) or growth hacking tool (for social media, SEO, cold email, AI content, etc).
And you’ll probably get modest success fast, since indiehackers like tools that help them indiehack and if they follow you on social media to hear stories of how they can get rich quick, they’ll definitely buy a product from you promising to help them do that.
However, I think you’ll struggle to ever “cross the chasm” so to speak into building a company that’s bigger than whatever online personality you build (no mass markets or low churn businesses without pyramid scheme dynamics).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pembrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xyst in "'I Don't Want to Die.' He needed mental health care. He found a ghost network"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41618353</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41618353"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T17:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s beating a dead horse at this point, but private health insurance is quite possibly the worst middleman I have ever dealt with.
They not only make the patients life worse but the doctors and hospitals as well. Dealing with insurance means small practices need a dedicated office staff to file the right paperwork and get paid for each patient visit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xyst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is heterodox economics?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45604</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/22/what-is-heterodox-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Based on our interviews, heterodox economics appears to be a positive project, inevitably deﬁned somewhat in terms of the mainstream but not exhaustively so. It is also eﬃcacious, with policy and real-world impact. It is a complex object, not amenable to deﬁnition by a single criterion. Its dimensions are partly intellectual, in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s 2024 Annual Founders’ Letter]]></title>
        <id>7puHT1ajSilk9b0LGo3s2H</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-2024-annual-founders-letter"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare launched on September 27, 2010. This week we celebrate our fourteenth birthday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snapplebobapple in "Incredibly Ambitious SMB 3 Hack Released After 12 Years"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41617590</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41617590"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T15:08:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks for making my heart skip a few beats thinking I was going to have a butt load of mitigation work to do for my cifs shares at the office starting immediately and ruining the last day of my weekend....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snapplebobapple</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Share Buttons]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-share-buttons/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-share-buttons/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Share Buttons
This add-on for the Bearming theme allows you to include buttons for emailing, printing, and sharing your blog posts on social media (see examples at the bottom of this page).
To use the add-on, which requires the latest version of the Bearming theme (1.3), add the code below to the end of your posts. If you prefer to avoid adding it manually each time, paste the code into your post template (Bear dashboard -> Posts -> Edit template).
<ul class="share">
<li><a href="mailto:?subject={{ post_title }}&body=Hey there,%0D%0A%0D%0AI saw this post and thought you might like it:%0D%0A{{ post_link }}"><span class="material-icons">mail</span> Email</a></li>
<li><a href="javascript:if(window.print)window.print()"> <span class="material-icons">print</span> Print</a></li>
<li><a href="https://www.addtoany.com/share#url={{ post_link }}&title={{ post_title }}" target="_blank"> <span class="material-icons">share</span> Share</a></li>
</ul>

Then add the following style to your theme:
/* Share buttons */
.share {
  margin: 30px 0;
  padding: 0;
  list-style: none;
  font-family: var(--font-secondary);
  font-size: 13px;
}
.share li {
  display: inline;
  margin-right: 7px;
  line-height: 41px;
}
.share a {
  padding: 6px 10px;
  color: var(--link-color);
  text-decoration: none;
  border: 1px solid var(--link-color);
  border-radius: 6px;
  background-color: var(--background-color);
}
.share a:hover {
  background-color: var(--accent-color);
}
.material-icons {
  font-family: 'Material Icons';
  font-size: 16px;
  color: var(--link-color);
  vertical-align: text-top;
  text-rendering: optimizeLegibility;
  -moz-osx-font-smoothing: grayscale;
  font-feature-settings: 'liga';
}

That's it! I hope your readers find this feature useful.
mail Email
 print Print
 share Share]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i got engaged!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/engagement/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/engagement/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T14:13:58.298Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I proposed in front of a castle :) she said yes!
Published {{ post_published_date }}, edited {{ post_last_modified }} ago]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forum on China-Africa Cooperation evades contradictions at the end of the Belt and Road: Chinese investment, finance and trade controversies in Southern Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Forum-on-China-Africa-Cooperation-evades-contradictions-at-the-end-of-the-Belt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Forum-on-China-Africa-Cooperation-evades-contradictions-at-the-end-of-the-Belt"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T12:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction 
English

/ 
South Africa, 
China, 
BRICS, 
Belt and Road, 
Sub-imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life's Simple Pleasures]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/life-s-simple-pleasures/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/life-s-simple-pleasures/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the ways that I'm fortunate is that I enjoy simple pleasures the most. I have no need for elaborate, constant, and expensive variety to be satisfied. It's not that I don't enjoy an occasional adventure—I do. It's just that I am very happy to have a nice time in my own home, surrounded by the things I've already accumulated that bring me pleasure. It was only as a teenager that I felt that restless call to get out and get away from home to experience something besides the same old, same old.
Granted, our at-home entertainment choices today are much more varied than they were in the 70s and 80s when I was coming of age. I don't have to spend an hour at the Record Bar to find new music. I enjoyed it then, but I also enjoy the way we discover music today. I've been to a few really enjoy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Asia in the New Global Debt Crisis – A Call for Collective Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/South-Asia-in-the-New-Global-Debt-Crisis-A-Call-for-Collective-Solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/South-Asia-in-the-New-Global-Debt-Crisis-A-Call-for-Collective-Solutions"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T10:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debt payments of developing countries exceed their national revenue. According to a new report, Resolving The Worst Ever Global Debt Crisis, 118 developing countries are experiencing debt distress, with a disproportionate share of their national revenue directed towards debt servicing in 2024 (Martin and Waddock 2024). Thirty-one countries have either defaulted or have access to external financing suspended due to high debt levels. Even though external debt is crippling economies in the (...)
English

/ 
Debt campaign, 
South Asia, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amali Wedagedara</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/22/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279133</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-22-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T10:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our dynamic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian and Western Nuclear Industries Remain Interdependent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279146</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/russian-and-western-nuclear-industries-remain-interdependent.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T10:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The close mutual industrial and market interdependencies between the Russian nuclear industry and its Western counterparts at least partially explain European hesitations to impose sanctions on the nuclear sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is There A Life Without IMF: Debunking The Myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Is-There-A-Life-Without-IMF-Debunking-The-Myth</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Is-There-A-Life-Without-IMF-Debunking-The-Myth"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T09:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given that Anura Kumara Dissanayake, the progressive presidential candidate from National People's Power, is leading in the election on September 21, 2024, it is crucial to consider the question: Could life exist without the IMF? 
Videos

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Audio Content: How Much Is Too Much?]]></title>
        <id>https://darrenhester.com/audio-content-how-much-is-too-much/</id>
        <link href="https://darrenhester.com/audio-content-how-much-is-too-much/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s nothing wrong with listening to podcasts and audiobooks. There’s a ton of great content out there. The problem is the amount I consume.
Most of what I listen to falls under the productivity/self-improvement category, things you'd classify as "good content." And in moderation, it can be helpful. Who doesn’t want to improve their life?
But I suck at moderation. I listen to back-to-back episodes, not giving myself time to process what I've heard. Hours of opinions and advice that rarely result in meaningful life change.
The constant audio stream prevents me from letting my mind wander. My thoughts are crowded out, and my attention is divided, making it difficult to fully engage with the present moment.
This weekend, I put my headphones away. I wanted to see how I felt without the distraction.
At first, it was uncomfortable because I have a habit of always listening to something. But after a few days, I appreciated times of silence. I felt more relaxed.
From now on, I want to be more intentional about how much content I consume. I could limit myself to one episode of a podcast or one chapter of an audiobook.
More doesn't necessarily mean better. You can only absorb so much in one day, and at a certain point, there are diminishing returns. Often, a slow and steady approach works best.
mail Email
 print Print
 share Share]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Big Tech’s Race to “Climate Safe-Havens”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334128</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/22/inside-big-techs-race-to-climate-safe-havens/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T06:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In David Pogue’s book, How to Prepare for Climate Change, he suggests readers consider relocating to what he deems “climate safe-havens,” or fifteen cities that offer protection from the worst of climate disaster. These so-called safe havens spread across the northeastern part of the United States, from Minnesota to New York, and as far south as Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, Pennsylvania, and the Virginias.  Like the “rust belt,” “bible belt,” or “cornbelt,” these post-industrial cities are being redefined by their legacy infrastructure access to freshwater and moderate weather. 
The designation of climate safe havens offers a little bit of hope alongside the litany of dire studies highlighting the irreversible effects of climate change. Studies like this one from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA)tell us that this past May was the hottest May recorded on Earth, marking it the 12th consecutive month of record-breaking heat. The National Centers for Environmental Information (NCEI) reports that last year brought 28 weather and climate disaster that cost over a billion dollars in damages—yet another record broken. 
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Inside Big Tech’s Race to “Climate Safe-Havens” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alyse Burnside</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: fountains in Altona]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53223</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/22/sunday-photoblogging-fountains-in-altona/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T06:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aetherspawn in "Sanding UI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41614261</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41614261"/>
        <updated>2024-09-22T02:42:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is so lost in Agile.
Engineers should get the time to “sand” their products, but we just don’t. If QA doesn’t make a ticket for the space between, it’ll never get fixed.
The customer probably notices this kind of a thing but it’s a miracle if the customer bothers to report it, and another miracle if it eventually turns into a ticket, and another miracle if someone prioritises it enough to spend time fixing it.
[In fact most companies have such opaque issue boards that as a customer I get so frustrated when I find a small issue or bug and have to spend like 50 hours back and forth to prove it’s a bug and actually get a ticket put in the tracker.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aetherspawn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by siskiyou in "FCC wants all phones unlocked in sixty days, AT&T and T-Mobile aren't so keen"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41612950</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41612950"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T22:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just adding a little bit of context about AT&T: I collect used cell phones, erase them, unlock when possible, and distribute them to unhoused people through several local food shelves, which allows those people to access benefits, housing, health care, jobs, etc which would otherwise be out of reach. With AT&T I can go to their website and unlock an old phone in minutes, allowing them to use a no-cost carrier like QLink Wireless. With T-Mobile or Consumer Cellular (or many others) they just give you the finger. The phone could be e-waste for all they care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siskiyou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by noman-land in "Forget ChatGPT: why researchers now run small AIs on their laptops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41611109</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41611109"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T16:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For anyone who hasn't tried local models because they think it's too complicated or their computer can't handle it, download a single llamafile and try it out in just moments.
https://future.mozilla.org/builders/news_insights/introducin...
https://github.com/Mozilla-Ocho/llamafile
They even have whisperfiles now, which is the same thing but for whisper.cpp, aka real-time voice transcription.
You can also take this a step further and use this exact setup for a local-only co-pilot style code autocomplete and chat using Twinny. I use this every day. It's free, private, and offline.
https://github.com/twinnydotdev/twinny
Local LLMs are the only future worth living in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noman-land</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photo Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.someplace-else.xyz/photo-mode-0/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.someplace-else.xyz/photo-mode-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<img src="https://natclayton.uk/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/dsc00033.jpg" width:100%/>
(note: this post is image-heavy)
I bought a new camera this week. Or, at least, a refurbished one, purchased on impulse as part of a mad scramble to fill my life with things to do that don't involve looking at a computer.
This isn't my first flirtation with photography. A brief obsession with the fantastic Umurangi Generation pushed me to pick up a cheap Centon df300 a few years back. I love film, I really do; the warm texture of shots, the ritual of getting it developed, the unpredictability of how things will turn out. But between the cost and time it took to see the results and the technical fussiness of keeping a decades-old handheld working, I slowly began to fall off.
<img src="https://natclayton.uk…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvester of Eyes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334184</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/21/harvester-of-eyes/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T14:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinian refugees stream out of the ruins of Gaza City. Image: Wafa.
Dr. Elias Warrack, a surgeon at Mount Lebanon University Hospital in Beirut, on treating victims of Israel’s pager bombs: “Some of the patients, we had to remove both eyes. It kills me. In my past 25 years of practice, I’ve never removed as many eyes as I did yesterday.”
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Harvester of Eyes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BRICS and De-Dollarization: An Alternative or Potential Disaster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/brics-and-de-dollarization-an-alternative-or-potential-disaster.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T12:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of some proposals for the BRICS de-dollarization project, suggesting a lack of convergence of ideas among key players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka's debt default]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-debt-default</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-debt-default"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T11:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, 21 September, Sri Lanka will hold its first presidential election since the July 2022 popular uprising known officially declared the worst economic crisis in the country in 73 years. Most foreign debt repayments were suspended after two years of money printing to support tax cuts. The economy contracted 7.8% and the percentage of the population earning less than $3.65 a day doubled to around 25% of the population. 
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
Debt crisis, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medicate.exe]]></title>
        <id>https://library.xandra.cc/medicate/</id>
        <link href="https://library.xandra.cc/medicate/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Being Medicated for ADHD
cw: medication, adhd, ocd, accommodations at work
i recently started medication for my adhd, despite being diagnosed about four years ago. i've had a longer stint with my ocd medication, venlafaxine, which has markedly improved my experience relating to my obsessive-compulsive behaviors. since being on my ocd medication, i've felt a lot better about not just those behaviors but my emotions as well. it made me want to take the leap into adhd medication, and i'm grateful to be in a position to get it.
it's incredibly frustrating to know that for some twenty-plus years i've been struggling with anxiety and depression, treatment wasn't working because it wasn't treating the underlying cause. i was adamant about not taking a stimulant, and bupropion has been an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[art programs (pt 1: my mains)]]></title>
        <id>https://platinumtulip.bearblog.dev/art-programs-pt-1-my-mains/</id>
        <link href="https://platinumtulip.bearblog.dev/art-programs-pt-1-my-mains/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T03:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i have, by my rough estimate, used over 30 different art programs over the years. i have reliable standbys, of course! but in general, i love experimenting with different tools. what kind of features are available in other art applications? do technical limitations make it more interesting to use, or more frustrating to use? what's the UI/UX like? how do the brushes look and feel to use? etc.
out of everything i've used over the years, here's my current lineup of preferred art programs.
krita
so, in the past year or so, i switched to Krita as my main "high resolution" drawing program. i used Clip Studio for several years (2016-2023) but ever since i switched to Linux as my main OS, i needed to familiarize myself with something that would run natively.
and... i've been pleasantly surprised …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by istoica in "Show HN: Container Desktop – Podman Desktop Companion"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41605256</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41605256"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T20:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is planned - my devops wants me to add it badly!
Author note - Most of you guys here are power users, for whom UI is a visual poem that you need or not.
This is not a commercial project, it is not following any business goals.
But this does not mean concessions to quality, it does try to offer minimal resource usage everywhere, easy experience, good UI/UX.
It explains all it does behind the scenes if you enable the developer console.
It can help one learn so at a certain moment one understands and automates with scripts and specs.
But everyone these days is either seen as too smart or too dumb, I don't consider users like this. I know everyone started somewhere and a gradual learning experience is the best.
I broke so many radios and toys when I was a kid and I learned so much, by looking at what was is inside.
It is a project done by one dude, after work and when it rains outside (In Belgium it rains a lot).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>istoica</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional Paper:  United Nations World Population Prospects, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53215</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/20/occasional-paper-united-nations-world-population-prospects-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T18:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every few years the UN publishes one of these big papers on “world population prospects”, which are… exactly what they sound like: a best guess at what’s going to happen with the world’s population over the next few decades. Nut graph after the jump: So the UN’s current best guess is that world population will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ayhanfuat in "Gaining access to anyones Arc browser without them even visiting a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41603984</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41603984"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T17:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was the post written for HN users only? I cannot see it on your blog page (https://arc.net/blog). It’s not posted on your twitter either. Your whole handling seems to be responding only if there is enough noise about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ayhanfuat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ha470 in "Gaining access to anyones Arc browser without them even visiting a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41603670</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41603670"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T16:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m Hursh, cofounder and CTO of The Browser Company (the company that makes Arc). Even though no users were affected and we patched it right away, the hypothetical depth of this vulnerability is unacceptable. We’ve written up some technical details and how we’ll improve in the future (including moving off Firebase and setting up a proper bug bounty program) here: https://arc.net/blog/CVE-2024-45489-incident-response.
I'm really sorry about this, both the vuln itself and the delayed comms around it, and really appreciate all the feedback here – everything from disappointment to outrage to encouragement. It holds us accountable to do better, and makes sure we prioritize this moving forward. Thank you so much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ha470</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From mom with love]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/mom-love/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/mom-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks exactly one year since my dear dad was laid to rest. I want to share the beautiful words that my mother wrote today:
”If I could give you one thing in life, it would be the ability to see yourself through my eyes. Only then would you truly understand how special you've been to me. If I did anything right in my life, it was when I gave my heart to you. I will love you forever and ever.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rizzo goes for the guild]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45601</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/20/rizzo-goes-for-the-guild/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T14:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Is it a cult? Is it a guild? Both perhaps? I remember reading sometime not long ago that Steve Levitt was leaving Chicago.  Two things stood out in the article bringing that news:  first, Levitt said he was concerned that economics was becoming irrelevant; second, someone had told him he was not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing uncertainty through "what-if" capacity planning]]></title>
        <id>13ueCTf2YFQfu3c1KeOlWj</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/scenario-planner"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s Capacity Planning team discusses planning for “what-if” type scenarios, and how they’ve introduced a new “Scenario Planner” system to quickly model hypothetical future changes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Curt Robords</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare incident on September 17, 2024]]></title>
        <id>2SwCyuXYfx1hPgiULhD2Pz</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-september-17-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 17, 2024, during planned routine maintenance, Cloudflare stopped announcing 15 IPv4 prefixes, affecting some Business plan websites for approximately one hour. During this time, IPv4 traffic for these customers would not have reached Cloudflare and users attempting to connect to websites using addresses within those prefixes would have received errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Abley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Fed DSGE Model Forecast—September 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31834</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/the-new-york-fed-dsge-model-forecast-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post presents an update of the economic forecasts generated by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s dynamic stochastic general equilibrium (DSGE) model. We describe very briefly our forecast and its change since June 2024. As usual, we wish to remind our readers that the DSGE model forecast is not an official New York Fed forecast, but only an input to the Research staff’s overall forecasting process. For more information about the model and variables discussed here, see our DSGE model Q & A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sophia Cho, Marco Del Negro, Ibrahima Diagne, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Borgz in "Gaining access to anyones Arc browser without them even visiting a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41599934</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41599934"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T08:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to this article, Arc requires an account and sends  Google's Firebase the hostname of every page you visit along with your user ID. Does this make Arc the least private web browser currently being used?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Borgz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Algerian people reiterate their rejection of military rule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Algerian-people-reiterate-their-rejection-of-military-rule</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Algerian-people-reiterate-their-rejection-of-military-rule"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T06:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the confusion that accompanied the announcement of the recent presidential elections' results in Algeria, one thing is clear and certain: the Algerian people overwhelmingly reject military rule... 
English

/ 
Algeria, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilbert Achcar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hypocrisy: The Conflict of Zionist Hawks and Vultures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Hypocrisy-The-Conflict-of-Zionist-Hawks-and-Vultures</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Hypocrisy-The-Conflict-of-Zionist-Hawks-and-Vultures"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T06:51:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the conflict within the Zionist power elite about? Do not believe that it is a conflict between hawks and doves as the Western media portrays it. 
English

/ 
Palestine, 
Israel, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilbert Achcar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Says That Israel’s Unlawful Occupation of Palestine Must End]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334026</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/the-world-says-that-israels-unlawful-occupation-of-palestine-must-end/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T06:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 18, 2024, the United Nations General Assembly (UNGA) passed a resolution that demanded that Israel immediately withdraw from the Occupied Palestinian Territory (OPT) of East Jerusalem, Gaza, and the West Bank. The resolution used strong language, saying that “Israel’s continued presence in the Occupied Palestinian Territory is unlawful” and that it is “under an obligation” to end its “unlawful presence” in the OPT “as rapidly as possible.” More
The post The World Says That Israel’s Unlawful Occupation of Palestine Must End appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Cat Scratch Political Fever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334053</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/roaming-charges-cat-scratch-political-fever/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T06:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miss Sassy started the biggest political fire since Mrs. O’Leary’s cow kicked over a lamp and burned down Chicago. Last month, Miss Sassy disappeared from the sight of her owner, Anna Kilgore, a Trump-Vance fanatic in Springfield, Ohio. After a couple of days, Kilgore called 9-11, claiming that her Calico cat may have been stolen and devoured by her Haitian neighbors, who she'd never bothered to get to know. More
The post Roaming Charges: Cat Scratch Political Fever appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s True Objectives in Gaza, and Why It Will Fail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334093</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/israels-true-objectives-in-gaza-and-why-it-will-fail/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Never in its history of war, and military occupation has Israel been so incapable of developing a coherent plan for its future, and the future of its victims. Even a quick glance at headlines in international media reveals the depth of the Israeli dilemma. While Tel Aviv continues to carry out a genocidal war against  More
The post Israel’s True Objectives in Gaza, and Why It Will Fail  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Media Against Julian Assange]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334031</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/the-media-against-julian-assange/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The liberation of the Australian journalist in late June closes an ordeal lasting fourteen years. On the other hand, it doesn’t lighten the responsibility of his persecutors. In this domain, Washington, London, and Stockholm have acted with the complicity of an institution supposed to speak truth to power and to protect the innocent—the press, for once, not very supportive of another journalist. More
The post The Media Against Julian Assange appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurent Dauré</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Between a Rock and a Hard Place: Egypt Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333966</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/between-a-rock-and-a-hard-place-egypt-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been thirteen years since the 2011 Revolution in Egypt toppled Hosni Mubarak. He had been at that point the president of Egypt for thirty years. A recent article, that in part recounted the revolution, spurred me to write what follows, which is in part a critique of the accounts of events in Egypt propagated in US media at that time, but also an account of my experiences in Cairo during and after those events. More
The post Between a Rock and a Hard Place: Egypt Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Beaumont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Death Rattle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334035</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/amazon-death-rattle/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Amazon rainforest is in deep trouble. Labeling it a “crisis” however seems too hackneyed and not descriptive enough because the devastation is beyond description. The magnificent rainforest is morphing into a tinder box that’s trapped in the worst drought of all time. According to MapBiomas, an all-time record amount of land is charred and  More
The post Amazon Death Rattle appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinians in Occupied Palestine: Defying Zionism and Imperialism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333958</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/palestinians-in-occupied-palestine-defying-zionism-and-imperialism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States has had no qualms about casting its lot with the most openly and thoroughly racist regime Israel has ever produced.  That fact has been obscured, or intentionally disappeared, in the fog of Israel’s war on Gaza. The coalition of far-right Jewish supremacists, homophobes and religious extremists Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu surrounded  More
The post Palestinians in Occupied Palestine: Defying Zionism and Imperialism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Would Be Better off Without NATO, Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/the-world-would-be-better-off-without-nato-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hyper-capitalist terror state that plots to rule the world keeps its fist in a mailed glove called NATO. But NATO is in trouble. As its massive, disastrous Ukraine adventure fails, a key member, Turkey, applied to, uh, essentially join the other side, namely BRICS. When Ankara does so, how will that work? One foot  More
The post The World Would Be Better off Without NATO, Revisited appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump Assassination Body Count]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334027</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/the-trump-assassination-body-count/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the end we know little about the latest assassination attempt against presidential candidate and career fraudster Donald J. Trump, who was playing a round at Trump International Golf Club when a member of the Secret Service opened fire on a fence running beside the sixth hole—a dogleg to the right that runs along South Congress Avenue and Summit Boulevard. More
The post The Trump Assassination Body Count appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten True Things Regarding the Election and America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334096</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/ten-true-things-regarding-the-election-and-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have no idea who is going to win the 2024 presidential election other than it will be either the open fascist Donald “Poisoning Our Blood” Trump or the lethal imperialist and mass incarcerator Kamala “Don’t Come” Harris. I am aware that the “presidential election Nostradamus” who has correctly predicted 9 of the last 10  More
The post Ten True Things Regarding the Election and America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burning Questions Put to Shaman Rufino of Venezuela]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334068</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/burning-questions-put-to-shaman-rufino-of-venezuela/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The July 28 presidential elections in Venezuela have sparked especially heated disputes, with President Nicolás Maduro’s right-wing challenger, Edmundo González, and several countries refusing to recognize Maduro’s landslide victory. Even the international Left has shown some wavering and division, with softer social-democratic factions and other imperialism sympathizers lingering in a kind of agnostic limbo, despite  More
The post Burning Questions Put to Shaman Rufino of Venezuela appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Gilbert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empire is Without Virtue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333905</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/empire-is-without-virtue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poet and antiwar priest Daniel Berrigan wrote in his book The Nightmare of God, “We would like to think that the empire is virtuous. Or that it can be made so, converted, so to speak, by a large dose of civic virtue.” He concludes that it is not virtuous nor can it be made so.  More
The post Empire is Without Virtue appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Ceasefire in Gaza is Not Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334061</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/a-ceasefire-in-gaza-is-not-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The numbers are clear. The temporary ceasefire between Israel and Hamas in November last year resulted in the release of 109 hostages. Compare that to Israeli military operations, which have managed to rescue 8 hostages while killing three by accident. The military has also recovered the bodies of another 34 hostages, including six killed shortly  More
The post A Ceasefire in Gaza is Not Enough appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Doherty: Public Science Communicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334045</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/peter-doherty-public-science-communicator/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lecture series can promise much.  But one run out of a corporatised university comes with its own burdens and blemishes.  There is the stifling sense of brand and name that hovers over proceedings.  The logo is everywhere, a permanent reminder about the role of the chief donor, sponsor or name of the individual associated with the event.  Then  More
The post Peter Doherty: Public Science Communicator appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving VW Off a Cliff]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334047</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/driving-vw-off-a-cliff/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time ever, Volkswagen intends shuttering factories across Germany and tearing up labor contracts with its workforce in a desperate bid to survive.  VW saw its profit margin crater in the second quarter of this year – hitting an unsustainable 0.9% – a reflection of tumbling sales across the planet.  Tens of thousands of  More
The post Driving VW Off a Cliff appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it Nicaragua That is “Weaponizing” Immigration or Washington?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334165</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/20/is-it-nicaragua-that-is-weaponizing-immigration-or-washington/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claims that Nicaragua is “weaponizing” immigration by allowing free passage of migrants towards the U.S. border have been appearing regularly in the media over the last twelve months. The claim was made on NPR in January, in the Associated Press last October, in El Pais last November and by the BBC this July, to cite  More
The post Is it Nicaragua That is “Weaponizing” Immigration or Washington? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Perry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by water-data-dude in "Gaining access to anyones Arc browser without them even visiting a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41598540</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41598540"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T03:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just wanted to say, I enjoyed the little pixel art cat that runs towards wherever you click immensely. It’s one of those fun, whimsical little touches that I don’t see all that often. A reminder that the internet can be a fun, whimsical place if we want it to be :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>water-data-dude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bhaney in "Gaining access to anyones Arc browser without them even visiting a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41598211</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41598211"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T02:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of major security vulnerabilities in the world that were made understandably, and can be forgiven if they're handled responsibly and fixed.
This is not one of them. In my opinion, this shows a kind of reputation-ruining incompetency that would convince me to never use Arc ever again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bhaney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beltrán Roca Martínez - Anarchism, anthropology and Andalucia]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/beltran-roca-martinez-anarchism-anthropology-and-andalucia?v=1726780577</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/beltran-roca-martinez-anarchism-anthropology-and-andalucia?v=1726780577"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T21:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Beltrán Roca Martínez
Title: Anarchism, anthropology and Andalucia
Subtitle: An analysis of the CNT and the ‘new capitalism’
Date: 2006
Notes: Published in Anarchist Studies 14.2, pp. 106–130. Translated by Sharif Gemie.
Source: Retrieved on 19th September 2024 from libcom.org

ABSTRACT
 Systems theory can show us how organizations develop, allowing them to survive changes in their environments. Such analyses also demonstrate why the CNT is passing through such a profound crisis: it is a trade union which is completely excluded from the world of work. The CNT began in a society very different from today. Despite the many significant changes which have occurred since 1910, its organizational structures and ideological assumptions have remained practically unchanged. 
 The need for c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another day, another problem with Voyager 1, solved]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8515</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/another-day-another-problem-voyager-1-solved/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T21:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data the nearly fifty-year old deep space probe was returning to Earth earlier this year, was getting all scrambled up. But dutiful mission controllers sorted that out. This despite Voyager 1 being so far away that it’d take a day to reach, assuming we had a vessel that could travel at the speed of light. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn is collecting user data for AI training]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8513</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/linkedin-collecting-user-data-ai-training/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Professional social network (assuming there’s such a thing) LinkedIn has started collecting user data to train its own AI bot. No surprise there. They’ve apparently auto opted all members in, whether they like it or not. No surprise there. Rachel Tobac, CEO of SocialProof Security, has posted instructions on how to opt-out, on X/Twitter. I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accidentally Wes Anderson exhibition now on in Melbourne]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8509</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/accidentally-wes-anderson-exhibition-melbourne/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photography exuding the aesthetic of American filmmaker Wes Anderson, is on show in Australia at the Accidentally Wes Anderson exhibition, in Melbourne, until early November 2024. “Accidentally Wes Anderson: The Exhibition” is a journey through more than 200 of the most beautiful, idiosyncratic, and interesting places on Earth — all seemingly plucked from the whimsical […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The disassociated podcast, web design in the wild west of 1997]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8519</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-disassociated-podcast-web-design-wild-west-1997/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always thought setting up a podcast show would be fun. But, you know, I have no proper recording equipment, nor any idea what sort of subject matter such a “show” would feature. So the idea has sat dormant all these years. But yesterday, I learned about NotebookLM, Google’s “personalized AI research assistant”, while reading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Sohcahtoa82 in "The Cheating Device (ChatGPT on a TI-84) [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41595142</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41595142"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T19:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in my Algebra II class, while learning polynomial expansion, I write a program on my TI-85 that would not only solve the problem, but it would show the work, so I literally just had to copy its output verbatim and I got full credit.
I showed it to my teacher and asked it if it would be considered cheating to use it on the test, and she said that if I knew the material so well that I could write a program that didn't just solve it, but showed the work, then clearly I knew the material so well that I'd ace the test even without the program, so I could go ahead and use it, just as long as I didn't share the program with my friends.
I didn't have any friends (This was 1998 where being such a nerd was still looked down on), so it wasn't an issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sohcahtoa82</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS named as a Leader in the 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Desktop as a Service (DaaS)]]></title>
        <id>6637fd169e644e80e110b9addb3ef4a3dab47479</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-in-the-2024-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-desktop-as-a-service-daas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Gartner Magic Quadrant positions AWS as a Leader, reflecting our commitment to diverse virtual desktop solutions and operational excellence - driving innovation for remote and hybrid workforces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bernardo Jurema: &ldquo;Green Brazil?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/green-brazil</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/green-brazil"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T18:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lula and the Amazon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by srndsnd in "FTC: Vast Surveillance of Users by Social Media and Video Streaming Companies"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41594375</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41594375"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T17:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To me, what's missing from that set of recommendations is some method to increase the liability of companies who mishandle user data.
It is insane to me that I can be notified via physical mail of months old data breaches, some of which contained my Social Security number, and that my only recourse is to set credit freezes from multiple credit bureaus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>srndsnd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cloin in "The Cheating Device (ChatGPT on a TI-84) [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41593770</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41593770"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T16:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have super fond memories of high school math classes. That calculator was my first introduction to programming. I’d take the time to write programs for each unit we covered so that I could just input the variables and quickly solve. I had to understand the concept before I could program it so I didn’t really think it was cheating. I did get nervous when SATs came up because I knew my calcs memory would be cleared. I remember my solution was to painstakingly recreate the memory cleared screen and pulled it up before the proctor came around in hopes that they’d assume they already cleared mine.
My programming didn’t improve much after high school but I’m still kind of proud of my not-totally-cheating cheating.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cloin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xnx in "The reason your Columbia shirt has a tiny pocket near your waistline (2019)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41593699</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41593699"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T16:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> certain women’s garments with “pockets below the waist” get lower duty rates than those without. Because of that, a number of the women’s shirts Columbia Sportswear makes are intentionally designed with tiny pockets near the waistline, which lowers the cost of importing them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xnx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David S. D’Amato - Separation Perfected]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/separation-perfected?v=1726762111</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/separation-perfected?v=1726762111"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T16:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David S. D’Amato
Title: Separation Perfected
Subtitle: Domination and Alienation in Stirner and Debord
Date: September 19, 2024
Source: Retrieved on September 19, 2024 from https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/19/333777/

 We have allowed the American ruling class[1]to abstract themselves almost entirely from their substantive political positions and practices. So deeply engrossed are we in their branding as products of consumption, in their spectacular representations, that we seem to have no capacity to grapple critically with the situation we find ourselves in. The moment calls for careful reengagement with French philosopher Guy Debord’s book The Society of the Spectacle, as well as one of its most important, if unsung, precursors, German philosopher (perhaps anti-philosopher) …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intentions to Respond]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/intentions-to-respond/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/intentions-to-respond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T15:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m finding myself falling into this habit of reading blog posts that resonate with me, with full intention of writing a response post for it, and never actually doing it.
Half the time, it’s because I answer it in my head, and forget that I didn’t actually answer it out loud (or in this case, via a blog post).
I do this often. Not just for blog posts.
If I’ve ever left you on Read1, it's (mostly) not because I am ignoring you. Most of the time, I respond in my head, exit out of the message, and completely forget about it. This can happen for text or email.
It's not you, it's me.
Sometimes, I just get really overwhelmed and may take me some time to respond. Again, it's me, not you.
Anyways, back to the blog posts.
I've been reading a ton of blog posts that I've wanted to reply to. Or mostly to spin off my own Reply post to it. I think I've only done one response post because I keep forgetting to physically write it down on my to-do list to start.
Essentially this is just a reminder to myself that I'd still like to do that. And to stop forgetting.
That's all. Maybe it can be a reminder for you too.
60/100
💬 Community Echoes
respond on sight by Imperfect
RE: Intentions to Respond by jedda by Marisabel
Week Notes #005 by Martin
Reply by email
"the act of reading a message but not respond to it"↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare is helping domain owners with the upcoming Entrust CA distrust by Chrome and Mozilla]]></title>
        <id>6JSSnYVglQtKPqyymp5Tst</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-is-helping-domain-owners-with-the-upcoming-entrust-ca"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome and Mozilla will stop trusting Entrust’s public TLS certificates issued after November 2024 due to concerns about Entrust’s compliance with security standards. In response, Entrust is partnering with SSL.com to continue providing trusted certificates. Cloudflare will support SSL.com as a CA, simplifying certificate management for customers using Entrust by automating issuance and renewals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do You Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/why-do-you-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/why-do-you-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've never been a big fan of the pressure to "Know your why." I'm not into buzzwords and pop psychology and I definitely don't like being put on the spot. I'm still at a loss to articulate why I've done some of the most difficult and incomprehensible things in my life other than it's just what I felt like at the moment. I think that's OK. Still, I do believe in self-examination and realize that sometimes figuring out our motives is helpful, depending on what we do with that information. To that end, I'm looking at my blogging and why it's become as important as it has
to me.
The personal essays I write every day serve as a record of sorts. I've never been good at the Dear Diary kind of journaling, writing for an audience of one, future me. It's hard to find inspiration there. Instead I wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jack Barron: &ldquo;In Parenthesis&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-parenthesis</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-parenthesis"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T10:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Mendelssohn’s radicalism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jesterswilde in "Ask HN: My son might be blind – how to best support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589348</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589348"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T07:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am blind, it was degenerative so it sounds different than what your kid has.
I have a few pieces of advice. This is more about my own upbringing, so don't take any of it as an accusation towards you.
1) Don't hide things about their condition or prospects.
I grew up in a very loving home. However, my parents found out I was going blind when I was ~8, I didn't find out until I was 13.  My mother wanted to protect me from 'being the blind kid'. But I was. Not knowing made everything so much harder and more confusing.
2) Don't rely too much on technology. Stick and dog are the best tools blind people have. Everything else, in my opinion, is a flash in the pan and won't have long term support. Not made by blind people and with minimal consulting for them. Like what a sighted person thinks a blind person needs after closing their eyes and walking around their house for a few minutes. (Screen readers are useful, I'm not talking about those.)
For a piece of tech I was excited for and is now dystopian: https://spectrum.ieee.org/bionic-eye-obsolete
3) Foster independence. The world is not made for us. It's also full of high speed metal deathtraps. The easiest thing to do is stay inside where I know where everything is. Even walking to the grocery store is a deeply uncomfortable endeavor. But I need to do it. I need to be able to live with that discomfort and not let it dissuade me from living the most human life I can.
The blind cane is very valuable. It took me too long to accept blindness as an identity, get over the shame, and start using it. I lost a lot of time to that.
Blindness sucks in every conceivable way. It affects every part of ones life. But I had a good childhood and I have a good life. All things considered, I'm extremely lucky for the circumstances of my birth because of the family I was born into. You can't take away the blindness but you can still give them a wonderful life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jesterswilde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by isoprophlex in "Ask HN: My son might be blind – how to best support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589088</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41589088"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T06:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have, I think, no real expert advice to offer you. Except this small anecdote.
One of the kids in my 4-year old son's class is blind. I went along for a day to help out on a school trip to some massive playground, which involved loading 60 kids into a bus (they usually walk/bike to school, so not everyone was used to the idea of large buses); keeping track of them in the playground, feeding them, etc etc. Lots of potential for disaster, haha.
Throughout the day, it struck me that for the most part this blind kid was just another kid amongst peers. It was very wholesome to see the kids understand his limits instinctively, help him out whenever needed but mostly just bantering and playing alongside him.
I never gave these things much thought before, but observing this I saw the importance of having quality, supportive peers to interact with. I hope you can find a supportive, nurturing environment for your boy: one that highlights and reinforces his strengths, not his weaknesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>isoprophlex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by modeless in "Nintendo Files Suit for Infringement of Patent Rights Against Pocketpair, Inc"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41588152</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41588152"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T03:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response, Pocketpair has hired lawyers identical to Nintendo's, except with guns.
https://hard-drive.net/hd/video-games/pocketpair-hires-ident...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>modeless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sobre o que o Musk tentou fazer hoje]]></title>
        <id>https://joselito.blog.br/sobre-o-que-o-musk-tentou-fazer-hoje/</id>
        <link href="https://joselito.blog.br/sobre-o-que-o-musk-tentou-fazer-hoje/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eu tenho a impressão que, no geral, temos a mania de achar que pessoas de mau caráter são burras. É um pouco tentador, pois elas quebram a cara com certa frequência, mas é inegável que burras elas não são.
Para conseguir explorar tanta gente e chegar onde chegaram, há um certo nível de esperteza envolvido. Quando falta inteligência própria, há riqueza suficiente para comprar a dos outros. Geralmente herança.
Desde que Alexandre ordenou o bloqueio do X no Brasil, certamente há funcionários da empresa trabalhando 24/7 para encontrar uma solução que traga o nosso país de volta à rede social. Várias matérias apontam o impacto negativo que a ausência dos brasileiros causa na plataforma.
Desde o primeiro dia, uma das formas mais disseminadas de continuar acessando o X era por meio de uma "brecha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patriotism Blinds]]></title>
        <id>https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/patriotism-is-blinding/</id>
        <link href="https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/patriotism-is-blinding/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T00:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an argument to be made about the nature of it—a form of confidence that benefits a community of like-minded individuals, a society, or in this case, a country. While I am no Nietzsche or Kafka, I live in one, like any person in today's world—a world undoubtedly centered around a prominent theme: patriotism.
What even is patriotism? The word often carries different meanings depending on who you ask. Some define it as love and loyalty to one's country, a commitment to uphold a national belief or the core values they personally hold dear. Others, however, may view it with suspicion—closely associated with nationalism, pride, and even exclusion. At its core, patriotism is often seen as an allegiance to a flag, regardless of a country’s flaws. Living within a status quo, steadfast in t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Netflix’s Key-Value Data Abstraction Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1ea8a0a11b30</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-netflixs-key-value-data-abstraction-layer-1ea8a0a11b30?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vidhya Arvind, Rajasekhar Ummadisetty, Joey Lynch, Vinay Chella]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by peppertree in "LinkedIn is now using everyone's content to train their AI tool"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41586188</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41586188"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is about to learn what a tragic car accident can teach them about leadership and drop shipping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peppertree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 15, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240918</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240918"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by raffraffraff in "LinkedIn is now using everyone's content to train their AI tool"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585796</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585796"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T21:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why on earth would you train AI on that? In the social media world it's already the closest thing resembling boring, unreadable machine generated content.
No matter what you ask it, it'll brag about what a great job it's doing answering you, announce that it's having a baby, then tell everybody that it's being let go because there are better AI. It'll thank a few key people who it worked with, and tell you that it's actually thrilled with this opportunity to take a break from answering your question, and will spend more time on its old hobby of being an online resume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>raffraffraff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sweden wants to curb screen time for children under two]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8490</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/sweden-curb-screen-time-children-under-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amelia Nierenberg, writing for The New York Times: The intention of Sweden’s policy — and others like it — is to cut down on distractions, promote healthy development and help preserve the innocence of childhood. But some experts wonder if the guidance — however well-intentioned — may be too unrealistic and too judgmental to stick. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by siva7 in "LinkedIn is now using everyone's content to train their AI tool"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585363</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41585363"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T20:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somehow i feel sad for this AI model. All the others are trained on authentic content and this boy gets socialised on the most shallow content imaginable. Poor, socially awkward AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siva7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The popular uprising in Ecuador on 22nd June 2022 and similarities with other rebellions in Europe and Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-popular-uprising-in-Ecuador-on-22nd-June-2022-and-similarities-with-other</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-popular-uprising-in-Ecuador-on-22nd-June-2022-and-similarities-with-other"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T19:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Below is the epilogue written by Éric Toussaint at the request of the authors for the book entitled Sinchi, published in Spanish in 2024 by Leonidas Iza, Andres Tapia and Andres Madrid. The book published in Spanish was translated into English and published in London by Resistance Books in 2023: Leonidas Iza, Andrés Tapia, and Andrés Madrid, Uprising : the October Rebellion in Ecuador], consists of 16 pages, which include the ten crucial points required to change the intolerable daily (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Ecuador, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now available: Graviton4-powered memory-optimized Amazon EC2 X8g instances]]></title>
        <id>7812a543b049dc928be3d9f6c4a97e0231eb9baa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-available-graviton4-powered-memory-optimized-amazon-ec2-x8g-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T19:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New memory-optimized X8g instances offer up to 3 TiB DDR5 memory, 192 vCPUs, and 50 Gbps network bandwidth, designed for memory-intensive workloads like databases, analytics, and caching with unparalleled price/performance and efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tedivm in "OpenAI Threatening to Ban Users for Asking Strawberry About Its Reasoning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41583996</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41583996"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd still love to understand how a non-profit organization that was founded with the idea of making AI "open" has turned into this for profit behemoth with the least "open" models in the industry. Facebook of all places is more "open" with their models than OpenAI is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tedivm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data engineering professional certificate: New hands-on specialization by DeepLearning.AI and AWS]]></title>
        <id>985360e0d64907d9a064c7b368f96ac8e90b72b5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/data-engineering-professional-certificate-new-hands-on-specialization-by-deeplearning-ai-and-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T18:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain indispensable data engineering expertise through a hands-on specialization by DeepLearning.AI and AWS. This professional certificate covers ingestion, storage, querying, modeling, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mistakes I Made When I Started Programming and How I Overcame the Self-Doubt Phase]]></title>
        <id>https://minami.bearblog.dev/my-mistakes-as-a-noob-programmer/</id>
        <link href="https://minami.bearblog.dev/my-mistakes-as-a-noob-programmer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I reflect on my journey as a programmer, from my university days to where I am now in 2024, I realize how much I've grown and learned. This blog post is about the mistakes I made, the self-doubt I faced, and how I ultimately found my way to becoming a more confident and skilled programmer.
The University Days: A Sea of Confusion
When I started my programming journey in university, I was like a ship without a compass, drifting from one technology to another without a clear direction.
Mistake 1: YouTube Tutorial Hell
I spent countless hours watching YouTube tutorials, jumping from one video to another. While these tutorials provided quick wins, they didn't help me build a solid foundation. I was coding, but not really understanding.
Mistake 2: Language and Framework Hopping
Instead of foc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights From the NAACL 2024 Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/58d913e4cc60</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/highlights-from-the-naacl-2024-conference-58d913e4cc60?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T16:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s AI Research team recaps the NAACL 2024 conference, including data set curation and reliable LLM evaluation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Cloud Journey using Amazon Outposts and AWS Local Zones]]></title>
        <id>63c78f6fcf3b64e017f261b1da4d12cd7beb0c91</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/hybrid-cloud-journey-using-amazon-outposts-and-aws-local-zones/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T16:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Amy Flanagan, Vice President of Architecture and leader of the Virtual Architecture Team (VAT) at athenahealth, and Anusha Dharmalingam, Executive Director and Senior Architect at athenahealth. athenahealth has embarked on an ambitious journey to modernize its technology stack by leveraging AWS’s hybrid cloud solutions. This transformation aims to enhance scalability, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Chellappa Ganesan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pdabbadabba in "Hezbollah hand-held radios detonate across Lebanon, sources say"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41581540</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41581540"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T15:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it should not be considered terrorism to the extent that the attack targeted legitimate military targets during a time of war — broadly speaking, combatants and other parts of the organization that affect its ability to wage war. Terrorism, at least least in my view, is an attack that either intentionally targets civilians or is truly indiscriminate, and is aimed at producing political cha age by causing fear.
By those definitions, I think this is clearly not terrorism. (Though we might learn more information about who was targeted that could change this assessment.) Admittedly, my definitions only imperfectly track the way the word is used in the west, but I think that's only due to frequent misuse of the term for political ends.
I would worry about a definition of terrorism that creates an incentive to avoid this type of warfare in favor of dropping bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pdabbadabba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Arch485 in "Hezbollah hand-held radios detonate across Lebanon, sources say"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41581321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41581321"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T15:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm genuinely curious: how is this not considered terrorism on Israel's part? (or is it considered terrorism?)
From a tactical standpoint, this is very similar, and the only big difference I see is that this is technologically more advanced/more complex than just planting a bomb or something.
If it's not terrorism, what is the differentiating factor(s)?
*side note: I'm quite sure other western countries have used tactics that I would call terrorism as well. This isn't meant to be a callout or anti-anything post. I'm genuinely curious where the line is drawn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arch485</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jon Las Heras and Beltrán Roca - New practices in industrial relations]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jon-las-heras-and-beltran-roca-new-practices-in-industrial-relations?v=1726671103</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jon-las-heras-and-beltran-roca-new-practices-in-industrial-relations?v=1726671103"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jon Las Heras and Beltrán Roca
Title: New practices in industrial relations
Subtitle: Radical unionism in the European periphery
Date: 2023
Notes: Published in Work and Employment Relations in Southern Europe, pp. 137–162.
Source: Retrieved on 18th September 2024 from www.researchgate.net

Introduction: Radical critique as a forward strategy
 Neoliberal globalization has substantially transformed the landscape in which organized labour sought to advance its interests during Fordism. The scaling up of market relations and capital movements, the subsequent erosion of national Keynesian fiscal and monetary policy paradigms, and deregulation of labour market institutions, including collective bargaining and flexibilization of contracts, has eroded the presence and capacity of unions to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[San Francisco in a Frame]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/san-francisco-in-a-frame/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/san-francisco-in-a-frame/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:50:40.887Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Still going through photos from my birthday weekend. These two were taken on the morning of 8/26 on the way to Carmel-by-the-Sea.

Pretty happy about the framing of this photo since it was taken from a moving car amidst rush hour traffic.

Part of the San Francisco skyline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by massysett in "Gentle Guide to Self-Hosting"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41580415</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41580415"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m an old-timer, I’m surprised that paying for shared hosting is now “self-hosting.” Nothing wrong with that, but that would never have been called self-hosting ten years ago.
I guess it’s like how “cooking from scratch” evolved. A cookbook from the nineteenth century might have said “1 hog” as an ingredient and instructed you to slaughter it. Now of course you buy hog pieces on foam trays.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>massysett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lorna Scott Fox: &ldquo;Family Ties&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/family-ties</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/family-ties"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T13:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Marie-Hélène Lafon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Modest Interpretation of Straussianism in Action]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53210</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/18/a-modest-interpretation-of-straussianism-in-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A class of a practical sequel (or, if you prefer, sequela) to my previous post on this topic. The great modern advocate of applied (as opposed to theoretical) Straussianism, is Tyler Cowen [update: Tyler Cowen says in email that he has a very different perspective on Straussianism – see here]. Plausibly, Straussianism provides a skeleton […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by voytec in "Why wordfreq will not be updated"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578924</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578924"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree in general but the web was already polluted by Google's unwritten SEO rules. Single-sentence paragraphs, multiple keyword repetitions and focus on "indexability" instead of readability, made the web a less than ideal source for such analysis long before LLMs.
It also made the web a less than ideal source for training. And yet LLMs were still fed articles written for Googlebot, not humans. ML/LLM is the second iteration of writing pollution. The first was humans writing for corporate bots, not other humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>voytec</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jgrahamc in "Why wordfreq will not be updated"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578834</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41578834"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T12:23:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I created https://lowbackgroundsteel.ai/ in 2023 as a place to gather references to unpolluted datasets. I'll add wordfreq. Please submit stuff to the Tumblr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jgrahamc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows in the past. Some words on glass, the importance of repairing broken windows and GDP.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45592</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/18/windows-in-the-past-some-words-on-glass-the-importance-of-repairing-broken-windows-and-gdp/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was written because of a tweet by David Andalfatto, who wondered why medieval and early modern Europe, a society that built cathedrals, did not show any per capita growth. Per capita growth is an average, and when the rich get richer, it can increase even when the number of poor and destitute increases. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The IMF and the World Bank in the time of Coronavirus: the failed campaign for a new image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-IMF-and-the-World-Bank-in-the-time-of-Coronavirus-the-failed-campaign-for-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-IMF-and-the-World-Bank-in-the-time-of-Coronavirus-the-failed-campaign-for-a"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Health, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emilie Paumard, Eric Toussaint, Milan Rivié</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Cross-Cluster Communication in EKS with VPC Lattice and Pod Identity IAM Session Tags]]></title>
        <id>7b5b1f91fdb5d401875ff465129b859d2f786a08</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/secure-cross-cluster-communication-in-eks-with-vpc-lattice-and-pod-identity-iam-session-tags/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T00:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solution overview When you create your applications and want to expose internal API endpoints, you can build your microservices using different compute options such as AWS Lambda, Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS), and Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). Then, you can deploy your applications across multiple AWS accounts and multiple Amazon Virtual Private Clouds […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastien Allamand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wulfinna - What Is A Woman]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-what-is-a-woman?v=1726617600</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-what-is-a-woman?v=1726617600"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wulfinna
Title: What Is A Woman
Subtitle: A Short Gender Egoist Simplification
Date: 17 Sep 2024
Source: https://ignitedindark.wordpress.com/2024/09/17/what-is-a-woman/

 Any feminine-aligned adult individual who develops self-content within womanhood, female identity/conventions which vary from cultural region to cultural region. 
 Any individual who activates certain — but not strictly all — social aesthetics and conduct in order to be in line with traits conventionally associated with women. 
 Any individual who dissolves the sacredness of taxonomy with her conscious existence as a woman, regardless of essentialist wailing about perceived "Flaws," "Defects" or "Inauthenticity". 
 (Cisgender women, that is, women who affirm their having been assigned "Female" at birth and who pursue femininity in agreement with this, experience much of the same hatred and dehumanization that transgender women face each and every day, especially when it comes to reproductive capability, physical appearance, etc. All women, transgender or cisgender, suffer patriarchy in similar but unique circumstances.) 
 A woman is a person who delivers raw self-contents into the versatile bounds that form the living picture of a woman.
 She is her own while engaging the social sensors that call out "Woman!" 
 She is free and she is entire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 Express One Zone now supports AWS KMS with customer managed keys]]></title>
        <id>892ccacd6d98028f49e7b3c867afd8276fe9246c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-express-one-zone-now-supports-aws-kms-with-customer-managed-keys/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T21:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure your mission-critical data with S3 Express One Zone's server-side encryption using KMS keys, combining top-notch performance and robust security for regulatory compliance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Bento: Jupyter Notebooks at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21690</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/09/17/data-infrastructure/inside-bento-jupyter-notebooks-at-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T17:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This episode of the Meta Tech Podcast is all about Bento, Meta’s internal distribution of Jupyter Notebooks, an open-source web-based computing platform. Bento allows our engineers to mix code, text, and multimedia in a single document and serves a wide range of use cases at Meta from prototyping to complex machine learning workflows. Pascal Hartig [...]
Read More...
The post Inside Bento: Jupyter Notebooks at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for the Complete Removal of IMF Surcharges: Historical Precedents and a Growing Burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-the-Complete-Removal-of-IMF-Surcharges-Historical-Precedents-and-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-the-Complete-Removal-of-IMF-Surcharges-Historical-Precedents-and-a"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T16:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abstract This paper argues for the elimination of the surcharge policy of the International Monetary Fund (IMF). It explores the legal history of surcharges and underscores that there are precedents (i.e., in 1974, 1981, and 1992) for their complete removal. The paper also shows that surcharges are a burden on indebted countries and that the Fund's official arguments for retaining them do not hold. 
English

/ 
External debt, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrés Arauz, Francisco Amsler, Ivana Vasic-Lalovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>