<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-12-30T06:35:43.628Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-12-30T06:35:43.629Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year Past and the Year Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/the-year-past-and-the-year-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global citizen agenda for 2025 is very much like that for 2024—and probably for some years afterward. It includes global warming and related environmental crises; US-China tensions; challenges to democracy and peace in Europe and Africa; interstate and intrastate violence in the Middle East; and nuclear weapons upgrading. A new addition to this list  More
The post The Year Past and the Year Ahead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cinema Beyond Cinemas: the Best Films of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347930</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/cinema-beyond-cinemas-the-best-films-of-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bibi Files Dir. Alexis Bloom Dahomey Dir. Mati Diop Ernest Cole: Lost and Found Dir. Raoul Peck Eno Dir. Gary Hustwi The Goldman Case Dir. Cédric Kahn Green Border dir. Agnieszka Holland The Night Won’t End: Biden’s War on Gaza  Dir. Laila Al Arian and Fault Lines No Other Land Dir. Basel Adra, Yuval  More
The post Cinema Beyond Cinemas: the Best Films of 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Dawson: Environmentalism from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348403</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/ashley-dawson-environmentalism-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T00:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Joshua Frank and Erik Wallenberg talk to Ashley Dawson about his new book, Environmentalism from Below: How Global People's Movements Are Leading the Fight for Our Planet (Haymarket Books).
Ashley is a Professor of English at the Graduate Center / City University of New York and the College of Staten Island. He is the author of several books on key topics in the environmental humanities, including People’s Power: Reclaiming the Energy Commons, Extreme Cities: The Peril and Promise of Urban Life in the Age of Climate Change, and Extinction: A Radical History. A member of the Public Power NY campaign and the founder of the CUNY Climate Action Lab, he is a long-time climate justice activist.  More
The post Ashley Dawson: Environmentalism from Below appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmclnx in "Jimmy Carter has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42543338</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42543338"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T21:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back, to me he was a much better president then people believed in the 80s.
I believe if he got re-elected in 1980, the US would be in a much better place.  One thing, it could be argued real work on Climate Change would have begun in 1981 as opposed to where we are now, which is just watching the average probably blowing past 3C in around 70 years from now.
For his loss in 1980, I still blame Kennedy.
RIP, he did a lot to help regular people through his life, far more than our current crop of politicians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmclnx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MAGA Can Stuff DOGE Back in Its Box and Win the Day on H1B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284746</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/how-maga-can-stuff-doge-back-in-his-box-and-win-the-day-on-h1b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T20:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A simple plan....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284718</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bearish daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The One-in-a-Thousand-Day Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284715</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/the-one-in-a-thousand-day-problem.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T11:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI's ability to handle complexity and respond rapidly means future crises are likely to be much more sudden and vicious than those we have experienced so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the End of the World and I Don’t Feel Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347506</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/its-the-end-of-the-world-and-i-dont-feel-fine/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post It’s the End of the World and I Don’t Feel Fine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Dolack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poetry From Today’s Frontlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348265</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/poetry-from-todays-frontlines/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis in December. (Screengrab from video posted to X.) Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis in December. (Screengrab from video posted to X.) Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Poetry From Today’s Frontlines appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jchw in "Apple Photos phones home on iOS 18 and macOS 15"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42537165</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42537165"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T03:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I want is very simple: I want software that doesn't send anything to the Internet without some explicit intent first. All of that work to try to make this feature plausibly private is cool engineering work, and there's absolutely nothing wrong with implementing a feature like this, but it should absolutely be opt-in.
Trust in software will continue to erode until software stops treating end users and their data and resources (e.g. network connections) as the vendor's own playground. Local on-device data shouldn't be leaking out of radio interfaces unexpectedly, period. There should be a user intent tied to any feature where local data is sent out to the network.
So why didn't Apple just simply ask for user permission to enable this feature? My cynical opinion is because Apple knows some portion of users would instantly disallow this if prompted, but they feel they know better than those users. I don't like this attitude, and I suspect it is the same reason why there is an increasing discontent growing towards opt-out telemetry, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jchw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scosman in "Apple Photos phones home on iOS 18 and macOS 15"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42534096</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42534096"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T20:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I don't understand most of the technical details of Apple's blog post"
I do:
- Client side vectorization: the photo is processed locally, preparing a non-reversible vector representation before sending (think semantic hash).
- Differential privacy: a decent amount of noise is added the the vector before sending it. Enough to make it impossible to reverse lookup the vector. The noise level here is ε = 0.8, which is quite good privacy.
- OHTTP relay: it's sent through a 3rd party so Apple never knows your IP address. The contents are encrypted so the 3rd party never doesn't learn anything either (some risk of exposing "IP X is an apple photos user", but nothing about the content of the library).
- Homomorphic encryption: The lookup work is performed on server with encrypted data. Apple can't decrypt the vector contents, or response contents. Only the client can decrypt the result of the lookup.
This is what a good privacy story looks like. Multiple levels of privacy security, when any one of the latter 3 should be enough alone to protect privacy.
"It ought to be up to the individual user to decide their own tolerance for the risk of privacy violations." -> The author themselves looks to be an Apple security researcher, and are saying they can't make an informed choice here.
I'm not sure what the right call is here. But the conclusion "Thus, the only way to guarantee computing privacy is to not send data off the device." isn't true. There are other tools to provide privacy (DP, homomorphic encryption), while also using services. They are immensely complicated, and user's can't realistically evaluate risk. But if you want features that require larger-than-disk datasets, or frequently changing content, you need tools like this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by HarHarVeryFunny in "I automated my job application process"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42533327</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42533327"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T18:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe not your company, but it seems hiring companies brought this upon themselves with immediate AI rejects of qualified candidates, ghost jobs, ghosting candidates after interview, etc, etc.
If it takes a qualified candidate 100's of applications to land a single interview, then can you blame someone for automating it? I'd say that having the initiative and ability to automate it well would make this guy a great hire, if he hadn't already found a job!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HarHarVeryFunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI tool will identify diabetes risk 13 years early + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/new-ai-tool-will-identify-diabetes-risk-13-years-early-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/new-ai-tool-will-identify-diabetes-risk-13-years-early-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T17:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NHS launches trial for AI diabetes prediction; Eni unveils €100 million supercomputer for energy; UN Security Council approves peacekeeping in Somalia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Left to Say?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348214</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/28/whats-left-to-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T15:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamal Adwan Hospital workers, doctors, and staff are being forcibly evicted from the grounds of the hospital by IDF soldiers. (Screengrab from a video posted to X.) Kamal Adwan Hospital workers, doctors, and staff are being forcibly evicted from the grounds of the hospital by IDF soldiers. (Screengrab from a video posted to X.) Kamal […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What’s Left to Say? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284623</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T11:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our agitating daily links: Milan smoking ban, Covid causes autism? China dam in Tibet, Gaza children freeze, moar Azerbaijan crash, Luttwak on Syria, no paper passports? MAGA v. Musk on H-1Bs, CNN loses viewers, bad AI muzak, Mangione's bad lockup, global fertility trade]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do We Have a Mental Health Crisis?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284707</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/why-do-we-have-a-mental-health-crisis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T11:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why neoliberalism is a major cause of mental health problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enrollment in Nature Schools Soars as Families Rediscover the Benefits of Outdoor Learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284709</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/enrollment-in-nature-schools-soars-as-families-rediscover-the-benefits-of-outdoor-learning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T11:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are nature schools an old answer to new childrearing and education challenges?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by noodlesUK in "The paper passport's days are numbered"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527809</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527809"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T01:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are significant downsides to the digitalization of travel documents. The biggest one I can think of is ownership - the UK is moving to an entirely digital visa system and bringing in an ESTA style system called ETA for visa free countries. Unfortunately this means that residency cards for noncitizens are being phased out. This means that when the Home Office messes up and accidentally deletes your immigration status, or you are at an airport with no internet access, you have no evidence whatsoever of what status you hold. It also means you will no longer be in possession of any records that might be useful years in the future when the current database containing immigration records will likely have been replaced. It’s much easier to keep a piece of paper around for 30+ years than it is to make sure a digital record doesn’t rot in that time.
I feel strongly that any future digital travel credentials that are offered by governments should be able to operate entirely offline, and provide records that can be retained by the data subject. That means that revocation is harder, but IMO that’s a tradeoff that is worth making to avoid another Windrush scandal.
This has already become a pain when dealing with countries that don’t stamp passports, because when you need to apply for something that asks for your travel history over the past 10 years, you might not have any records anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noodlesUK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dlisboa in "Should more of us be moving to live near friends?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527549</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527549"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T00:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming from a Latin American the idea of re-starting your life across the country for college and then again for work (multiple times sometimes) while away from family and friends is very foreign.
A lot of the conversation around modern American youth feeling isolated, lacking socialization and not building strong relationships seems that stem from this drive.
Another thing that’s really weird and related is another recurring theme in the American ethos: the cultural shame that comes with living “at home” or staying in the same small town for your whole life. Somehow they made it so living close to your family and friends for your 20s-30s  and maybe forever means you’re a “loser”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dlisboa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 12/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284666</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/200pm-water-cooler-12-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T19:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics:  MAGA eviscerates the Tech Bros on immigration; Mangione family investments  in health care (not pretty); New Covid charts  ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Why OpenAI's Structure Must Evolve to Advance Our Mission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42522209</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42522209"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't understand why they are spending so much time and effort trying to put a positive spin on this whole for-profit thing. No one is buying it. We all know what's going on. Just say "we want to make lots of money" and move on with your lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Cloudflare: MASQUE now powers 1.1.1.1 & WARP apps, DEX now generally available with Remote Captures]]></title>
        <id>1zc4C9M6VIkj5TrfugGxum</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/masque-now-powers-1-1-1-1-and-warp-apps-dex-available-with-remote-captures/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup blog post shares the latest new features and capabilities at Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mari Galicer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284651</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T11:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our lionized daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump Take On the Housing Cartels?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284645</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/will-trump-take-on-the-housing-cartels.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T11:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DOJ case against RealPage for orchestrating a rental housing price-fixing cartel will tell us a lot about the economic direction of Trump 2.0.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine’s Reckless Drone Attacks Are Responsible for the Azerbaijan Airlines Tragedy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284661</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/ukraines-reckless-drone-attacks-are-responsible-for-the-azerbaijan-airlines-tragedy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the information so far and finger-pointing about the Azerbaijan plane crash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Civil Discourse in a Time of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348069</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/civil-discourse-in-a-time-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T07:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Civil discourse is preferable to the alternatives of coerced silence and violence. Coerced silence means that one side has exercised power to end conversation—to say, in effect, there is no point in further discussion; be quiet and accept that our desires will prevail. Violence means that reason has failed and we are reduced to the condition of resolving disputes by means of fang and claw, rock and club, bullet and bomb. More
The post Civil Discourse in a Time of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Schwalbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sound of da Police: the Year Criminal Injustice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347882</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-sound-of-da-police-the-year-criminal-injustice/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For nearly two days, the NYPD covered up the fact that one of their officers had fired a gun inside Hind Hall, while they were arresting students. Ultimately, the shooting was only revealed by the New York City DA's office. If you call in the NYPD, you can pretty much guarantee there will be bang-bang...Is there any doubt now that the NYPD raid did more damage to the buildings at Columbia than the students? The people who invited these cops on their campus should never be guardians of students again. More
The post The Sound of da Police: the Year Criminal Injustice appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Days? World War, Tech Takeover, and Global Warming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348067</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-end-days-world-war-tech-takeover-and-global-warming/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One can be excused for worrying over what tomorrow might bring as expanded battle lines are redrawn across the globe, the world’s wealthiest nation ever consumes itself in a cataclysm of partisan hate amid a growing digital reformation, and unchecked carbon emissions continue to cause more environmental disaster by the day. Will nuclear conflict, machine control, or climate breakdown ultimately destroy our pale blue dot of a planet or is it all just more apocalyptic blather that never comes to pass? More
The post The End Days? World War, Tech Takeover, and Global Warming appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John K. White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorites of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348095</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/my-favorites-of-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a big fan of these “best of” lists, but of all the new(ish) arts entertainment (or edutainment, as KRS-One would say) I consumed these past twelve months, here’s what helped me most in surviving (and contemplating) the relentless horrors of 2024. FILMS No Other Land, co-directed by Basel Adra, Hamdan Ballal, Yuval Abraham, and  More
The post My Favorites of 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leading Edge of Global Heat – Arabian Peninsula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348087</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-leading-edge-of-global-heat-arabian-peninsula/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major portions of the Arabian Peninsula are already exceeding 2°C above pre-industrial and likely headed for a staggering temperature rise over coming decades. This disturbing news comes via a major new study by Saudi Arabia’s most prestigious university. The epicenter of world oil & gas production is in direct line of fire of unnerving acceleration  More
The post The Leading Edge of Global Heat – Arabian Peninsula appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesting on the Environment: Australian Mining Gets a Present]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348153</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/jesting-on-the-environment-australian-mining-gets-a-present/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining magnates seem to have it all.  Far more significant than royalty, such figures are the unelected captains of industry who know that governments will do whatever they can to accommodate their wishes and whims.  True, the official rhetoric might sometimes be sharp and seemingly at odds, especially when it comes to that great irritation known as  More
The post Jesting on the Environment: Australian Mining Gets a Present appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Not About What Class You’re From: It’s About What Class System You Serve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348117</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/its-not-about-what-class-your-from-its-about-what-class-system-you-serve/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Times columnist Bret Stephens recently published a widely read opinion piece claiming that Brian Thompson, the United Health Group insurance CEO that Luigi Mangione assassinated, is the “real working-class hero” in the story of Thompson’s murder. By Stephen’s reckoning, Thompson and not Mangione deserves the label because the murder victim came from a  More
The post It’s Not About What Class You’re From: It’s About What Class System You Serve appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, the Marlboro Man and the New Frontier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348021</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/trump-the-marlboro-man-and-the-new-frontier/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Marlboro Man are case studies of branding success. When Philip Morris introduced the cowboy on its ads in 1955, sales were at $5 billion. Two years later, sales were at $20 billion. Ellen Merlo, the vice president of marketing services at Philip Morris, described the cowboy image as “very rugged, individualistic, heroic.” Rugged and individualistic is exactly the image Trump tries to portray. Why else go to WWE Raw events or a college football game? How else to describe his raised fist cry “Fight, fight, fight,” when struck by a bullet during an assassination attempt. Trump’s mythological image has helped him to be re-elected president despite (because of) twice being impeached and convicted of 34 felony accounts. The Marlboro Man and Trump’s image portrayal are fundamental to the American mythology of the pioneer spirit exploring new frontiers which now includes the popular success of tech start-up heroes like Elon Musk. More
The post Trump, the Marlboro Man and the New Frontier appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arrested Grief: Liberal America’s Moral Problem?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348172</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/arrested-grief-liberal-americas-moral-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is not possible without an opening to the transcendent; in other words, human beings cannot live in chaos.  Once contact with the transcendent is lost, existence in the world ceases to be possible. –Mircea Eliade, quoted in The Cross and the Lynching Tree, by James Cone In Hinduism, the term Kali Yuga refers to the last of four  More
The post Arrested Grief: Liberal America’s Moral Problem? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Invisible Sports Betting Epidemic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348151</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/americas-invisible-sports-betting-epidemic/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What do Tiger Woods, Michael Jordan, Charles Barkley and Floyd Mayweather, Jr. have in common? They’re all sports superstars, of course. But they’re also something else: Hard-core gambling addicts. Mayweather, Jr. regularly gambles as much as $400,000 on college football games. He reportedly once won $3 million on a single Orange Bowl contest. But his biggest bet  More
The post America’s Invisible Sports Betting Epidemic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Left in Latin American and the Caribbean: Year 2024 in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348176</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/whats-left-in-latin-american-and-the-caribbean-year-2024-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The progressive regional current, the “Pink Tide,” could be better called “troubled waters” in 2024. The tide had already slackened by 2023 compared to its rise in 2022, when it was buoyed by big wins in Colombia and Brazil. Then, progressive alternatives had sailed into power replacing failed neoliberal policies. Since, they have had to  More
The post What’s Left in Latin American and the Caribbean: Year 2024 in Review  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger D. Harris - John Perry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Little Learning Is Not Such a Dangerous Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348180</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/a-little-learning-is-not-such-a-dangerous-thing/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Jew in a Catholic college, one of two Jewish students in my class, I had to take lots of philosophy. My motivation for going to this particular school was the high school teachers I admired who had graduated from there and the academic major I wanted to study. The school also had a  More
The post A Little Learning Is Not Such a Dangerous Thing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deception and Politics From Washington to Tel Aviv]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347986</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/deception-and-politics-from-washington-to-tel-aviv/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In these difficult times, the voice of the late Palestinian-American scholar, Edward Said is ever present, “Writing is the final resistance we have against the inhuman practices and injustices that disfigure human history.” For more than fourteen painful months Israel has passed off its inhuman actions against the people of Gaza as “defensive.” We are  More
The post Deception and Politics From Washington to Tel Aviv                               appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Afghanistan: Now It Can Be Told . . . After All the Harm Has Been Done]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348106</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/afghanistan-now-it-can-be-told-after-all-the-harm-has-been-done/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the New York Times reported that the U.S. government made war in Afghanistan while helping to “recruit, train and pay for lawless bands of militias that pillaged homes and laid waste to entire communities.” Those militias “tortured civilians, kidnapped for ransom, massacred dozens in vendetta killings and razed entire villages, sowing more than  More
The post Afghanistan: Now It Can Be Told . . . After All the Harm Has Been Done appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Militant Still, Cubans March Against US Blockade and Hybrid War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348147</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/militant-still-cubans-march-against-us-blockade-and-hybrid-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cubans numbering hundreds of thousands marched on December 20 along Havana’s emblematic Malecon roadway fronting the Florida Straits. (See photos and video here.)  President Miguel Díaz Canel and former President Raul Castro took the lead in a massive protest against stepped-up U.S. efforts to immiserate Cubans and bring down their socialist government. Earlier that day, President Díaz-Canel addressed this year’s closing session of Cuba’s  More
The post Militant Still, Cubans March Against US Blockade and Hybrid War   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cuban Five Victory: Reflections Ten Years Later]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348079</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-cuban-five-victory-reflections-ten-years-later/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can remember clearly the rush of joy I felt when I heard the almost unbelievable news that the last three members of the Cuban 5, Gerardo Hernández, Antonio Guerrero, and Ramón Labañino, had landed in Havana on December 17th, 2014 after sixteen years of unjust incarceration in U.S. prisons. (The other two members of  More
The post The Cuban Five Victory: Reflections Ten Years Later appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diana Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sacrificing Living Standards for War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348076</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/sacrificing-living-standards-for-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As inflation ravages the West, Europeans are told by NATO chieftain Mark Rutte to sacrifice more for the glorious cause of tyranny in Ukraine. Pensions must be trimmed, inflation accepted and any other social benefits put on the chopping block. What, you may ask, is the logic here? Well, there isn’t any, unless Rutte believes  More
The post Sacrificing Living Standards for War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading Napoleon in Vienna]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348098</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/348098/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the sixth part in a series about riding night trains across Europe and the Near East to Armenia — to spend some time in worlds beyond the pathological obsessions of President-elect Donald Trump. (This week Trump devoted himself to Lébensraum: planting the American flag in Canada, Greenland, and Panama.) Perhaps my favorite one-volume  More
The post Reading Napoleon in Vienna appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freedom with a Caveat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348183</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/freedom-with-a-caveat/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Does Uhuru, ‘freedom’ in Swahili, apply in the United States? It depends. It depends on how the First Amendment is interpreted; it depends on how cunningly the term terrorism is applied in these tenuous fearsome times; it depends on how determinedly people fight to protect and restore their democracy. Doubtless, a few institutions committed to  More
The post Freedom with a Caveat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>B. Nimri Aziz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Biden Become Another Pontius Pilate This Holiday Season?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348020</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/will-biden-become-another-pontius-pilate-this-holiday-season/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, the Jewish and Christian winter holidays are in cosmic synchrony. The evening of Dec. 25 — Christmas Day on the Gregorian calendar — falls on the 25th day of the Hebrew month of Kislev — the first night of Hanukkah on the lunar calendar. These popular festivals in turn align with the very  More
The post Will Biden Become Another Pontius Pilate This Holiday Season? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Zoosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Appreciating Forests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348175</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/appreciating-forests/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I walk almost daily up into the Santa Fe National Forest along with neighbors and our dogs, and I am always reminded how fortunate we are to have a relatively natural and beautiful forest just outside of Santa Fe. All the forests of the Southwest and across the West are critically important to the planet,  More
The post Appreciating Forests appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Hyden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Wasserman: Berzerkeley Heretic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348149</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/steve-wasserman-berzerkeley-heretic/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Born on the West Coast, educated at Cal, and now at the helm at Berkeley’s Heyday Books, Steve Wasserman has crafted a name and a career for himself over the past several decades as a polemical writer, brilliant editor, savvy publisher and as an (aging) enfant terrible who has declared cultural war on Berkeley, on  More
The post Steve Wasserman: Berzerkeley Heretic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Art and Money]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348090</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/art-and-money/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual art is the the artistic medium most directly associated with money. A successful writer or composer may become financially successful. And a famous actor is usually well paid. But the painting that becomes famous goes, in many cases, from being a low priced community when it is made to a well guarded luxury good,  More
The post Art and Money appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diary Entry: Visiting the Met, and Swastika Info]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348032</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/diary-entry-visiting-the-met-and-swastika-info/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the Saturday before Christmas, I accompanied my young aide (from Haiti) to the NY Metropolitan Museum of Art — The Met. I used to go every once-in-a-while, especially while Carl Lesnor was still alive since he lived right nearby, but I hadn’t been to the museum for four or five years. Manhattan’s streets were  More
The post Diary Entry: Visiting the Met, and Swastika Info appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitchel Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debt cancellation in the land of Canaan in the first millennium BC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Debt-cancellation-in-the-land-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Debt-cancellation-in-the-land-of"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt in History, 
Inegalites 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Ponet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mitchellh in "Ghostty 1.0"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42517852</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42517852"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T21:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://mitchellh.com/writing/ghostty-1-0-reflection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mitchellh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The web today is not necessarily worse than the early web]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8992</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-web-today-is-not-necessarily-worse-than-the-early-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xavier H.M., writing on his Mastodon page: Your neocities blog is cute but I can’t read the 5pt font and your cursor is the size of a bread crumb. The web page is loading so many gifs my computer sounds like a boeing 747. disassociated once, in a way, looked like a Neocities website. Or, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time, not dark energy, may be causing the universe to expand]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9004</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/time-not-dark-energy-causing-universe-expand/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark energy does not exist, and the universe, while continuing to expand, is not doing so in a uniform fashion. In other words, the cosmos may look more like a potato, rather than a sphere. This according to recent research by astronomers and scientists at the University of Canterbury (UC), based in Christchurch, New Zealand. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pack plenty of books and take yourself into internal exile in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9007</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/pack-books-internal-exile-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introverts among us live almost permanently in a sort of internal exile, or a rich inner life, as Waleed Aly referred to it during the COVID-19 lockdowns. But the idea of getting away from it all, without actually going anywhere, is gaining traction more widely, writes Jacqueline Maley, for The Sydney Morning Herald. This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Bottlerocket FIPS variants]]></title>
        <id>16e90ff8cb5363cf2d70b6dd873e01b284520e09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-bottlerocket-fips-variants/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T16:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In 2020, AWS announced Bottlerocket, an open source, container-optimized Linux distribution designed for hosting containers. Each Bottlerocket image, known as a variant, is specialized for a specific combination of container orchestrator and cloud environment. Bottlerocket variants are provided to users as a set of Amazon Machine Images (AMI), currently optimized for either Amazon Elastic Container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I cache: implementing lock-free probabilistic caching]]></title>
        <id>4Xek2BRcXVKNsI4vCa3Zuj</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/sometimes-i-cache/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know what cache revalidation is, how it works, and why it can involve rolling a die, read on. This blog post presents a lock-free probabilistic approach to cache revalidation, along]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thibault Meunier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by K0nserv in "Cognitive load is what matters"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42511276</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42511276"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T21:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been thinking about the notion of "reasoning locally" recently. Enabling local reasoning is the only way to scale software development past some number of lines or complexity. When reasoning locally, one only needs to understand a small subset, hundreds of lines, to safely make changes in programs comprising millions.
I find types helps massively with this. A function with well-constrained inputs and outputs is easy to reason about. One does not have to look at other code to do it. However, programs that leverage types effectively are sometimes construed as having high cognitive load, when it in fact they have low load. For example a type like `Option>` carries a lot of information(has low load): we might not have a set of user ids, but if we do they are unique.
The discourse around small functions and the clean code guidelines is fascinating. The complaint is usually, as in this post, that having to go read all the small functions adds cognitive load and makes reading the code harder. Proponents of small functions argue that you don't have to read more than the signature and name of a function to understand what it does; it's obvious what a function called last that takes a list and returns an optional value does. If someone feels compelled to read every function either the functions are poor abstractions or the reader has trust issues, which may be warranted. Of course, all abstractions are leaky, but perhaps some initial trust in `last` is warranted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K0nserv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by delibaltas in "Merry Christmas Everyone"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42507005</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42507005"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T05:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas of 1981 in Athens, Greece. I was 15. Father had died 3 years ago from heart attack at 42. His last words to my mother: "Educate the kids".
She did her best, given that my grandfather was old fashioned and had stopped her from going to school after she became twelve, although she was among the smartest in her class.
That Christmas she had bought me the brand new then Sinclair ZX81 personal computer. We were visiting the grandparents in a small village near Athens.
I spend the night by the fireplace with a small portable TV and the machine, typing in games published in the UK PC magazines of that time and occasionally watching the Chrstmas shows. Debugging my typos was the way I learned how programming works.
Nothing really interesting here, but I am remembering that night again and again so when I saw the prompt I felt I should share. Merry Christmas everyone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>delibaltas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jedberg in "Merry Christmas Everyone"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42506783</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42506783"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T04:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Jewish, so all my Christmas's growing up were kinda the same.  Sleep in, have brunch, wander over to my neighbor's house around noon to see what kind of loot they got and help them play with their new toys.  Sometimes we'd go out for Chinese food and a movie.
But my favorite was Christmas 1999.  My girlfriend was out of town with her family and there was no reason to go home to mine, so I was alone (my roommates were with their families too).  I decided to go to the movies in Emeryville.
I was going to see Galaxy Quest, Bicentennial Man, and Man on the Moon.  The timing lined up perfectly to see all three.  About 50 other people were there to do the same thing.  When it was time to go in for the first movie, a staff member came out and told us that it would start about 30 minutes late.  This would of course cause us to miss all the other movies.
About 30 people stepped forward at the same time and asked to speak to the manager. :). We explained to him that it would throw our whole schedule off.  Since it was Christmas, he was kind enough to adjust the schedule so that we could all see all three movies.
That was a great day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jedberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by voxelghost in "macOS menu bar app that shows how full the ISS urine tank is in real time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42506408</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42506408"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T02:22:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know why, but I imagine a situation where all communication has broken down, and the only working sensor is the one in the piss-tank, and the astronauts have to communicate in morse by modulating the delta in the tank. And some guy  with ADHD, and this menu bar app installed, is going to figure out whats going on what is going on, and  save them all. (Hey, Hollywood - if this turns into a movie - I want my royalties)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>voxelghost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by btown in "macOS menu bar app that shows how full the ISS urine tank is in real time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42505561</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42505561"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T22:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I found out about the data stream from https://iss-mimic.github.io/Mimic/, which has considerably more and more interesting stats than just how full the piss tank is.
> I will not be adding any of them.
This, right here, is how you communicate non-goals of a project. Just perfect open-source communication best practices. We all stand to learn from this project.
(Though, predictably, some of us sit to interact with it.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>btown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long cycles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Long-cycles</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Long-cycles"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T14:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have long been sympathetic to the concept of long cycles in capitalist production and accumulation. This is the idea that capitalist production moves in cycles, not just in booms and slumps every 8-10 years or so, but also there are longer periods of generally faster accumulation and output growth ie periods of relative prosperity followed by a periods of relatively slower accumulation and growth, with more recessions. These longer cycles or waves last around 50-60 years including the (...)
English

/ 
Crisis, 
Capitalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Un experimento rápido: translating Cloudflare Stream captions with Workers AI]]></title>
        <id>6OAfYNDjjJBccE1gFIVrnu</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/un-experimento-rapido-translating-cloudflare-stream-captions-with-workers-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How I used Workers AI to translate Cloudflare Stream’s auto-generated captions and what I learned along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the world logs off: Christmas, New Year’s, and the Internet’s holiday rhythm]]></title>
        <id>5hrEiGd7frxGgAirAdHCM0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/when-the-world-logs-off-christmas-new-years-and-the-internets-holiday-rhythm/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Christmas Eve dinners in Europe to New Year’s Eve countdowns in Asia, Cloudflare data reveals how global festivities have typically shaped Internet usage and cultural rhythms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by chollida1 in "Intel shareholders file case asking ex CEO, CFO to return 3 years of salary"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42500709</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42500709"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T09:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- No serious hedge funds or other activists involved in this, ie no adults involved, check
- Fully audited financials not being questioned, check
- CEO and CFO constantly acknowledging the Foundary unit wasn't profitable in quarterly updates, check.
The former CEO was brought in to to try and keep Intel a fully integrated business that designed and manufactured chips.  He was very clear upfront about his plan to not divest the foundry and instead to try and build it back up.
It didn't' work, that's not a crime.  He left because his plan didn't work.  That's what happens to CEO's who try and fail to implement a business plan.
This is just an ambulance chaser lawsuit that doesn't look like it will go anywhere at all.
If there was any merit at all then the board would also be involved in going after the former CEO and CFO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chollida1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by daltonpinto in "Ask HN: Programmers who don't use autocomplete/LSP, how do you do it?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42500195</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42500195"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T07:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This question reminds me of the first time I met a blind programmer.
I asked him how he managed to code, and he replied with something that stayed with me: a good programmer should organize software in such a way that every piece of code has a clear and logical place. The organization should be so intuitive that anyone could build a mental model of the structure and navigate it easily, even without seeing it.
It felt like something out of a Yoda or Mr. Miyagi lesson. Skeptical, I asked his colleagues if he was truly able to code or if he was just exaggerating. To my surprise, they told me not only was he capable, but he was the best programmer they had ever worked with. They said no one else came close to writing code as organized as his.
That conversation changed my perspective. Ever since, whenever I’m unsure where to place new code, I don’t think about DDD or any specific methodology. Instead, I try to follow the logic and structure of the project in a way that feels natural and easy to follow later.
Later in life, I met two other blind programmers and heard similar stories about their ability to produce well-organized code.
To bring this back to the original question: I view LSP/IDE features the same way those programmers view "visual aids." Code should be organized according to a clear and logical structure that makes it easy to navigate.
Relying on features like Ctrl+Click to find where things are located worries me. Why? Because it can mask structural flaws in the codebase. If we can't intuitively figure out where something belongs, that’s a sign the codebase lacks structure—and that should motivate us to refactor it.
Not only do I avoid using LSP features, but I’m also opposed to their use. While they can help with navigation, they may prevent developers from experiencing and addressing the underlying structural issues in their code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daltonpinto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Long Tradition of Debt Cancellation in Mesopotamia and Egypt from 3000 to 1000 BC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Long-Tradition-of-Debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Long-Tradition-of-Debt"/>
        <updated>2024-12-24T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
 The Hammurabi Code is in the Louvre Museum, in Paris. The term “code” is inappropriate, because what Hammurabi left us is a (...)
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt campaign, 
Debt in History, 
Histoire Jubi EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>