<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-20T06:31:24.083Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-20T06:31:24.083Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275292</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-19-2024-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T18:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Politics, syndemics;  Democrat Inner Party considered as a wretched hive of scum and villainy; new RCP polling averages ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 1024core in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008579</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008579"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T17:04:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read on Mastodon: https://infosec.exchange/@littlealex/112813425122476301
The CEO of Crowdstrike, George Kurtz, was the CTO of McAfee back in 2010 when it sent out a bad update and caused similar issues worldwide.
If at first you don't succeed, .... ;-)  j/k]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>1024core</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consistency Over Perfection: Why A Framework Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/consistency-over-perfection/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/consistency-over-perfection/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enter your email to get 1 free month to our overnight momentum trading chat. Please check your promotions and spam for the confirmation email.
You NEED a Framework and there is no way around it!
Without one, you will remain stagnant at best!
You see, I finally figured out my health and fitness after many years. Over the years, I have jumped from one fad to the next, trying keto, intermittent fasting, low fat, high fat, you name it!
Additionally, I have found myself committing to a workout program for a few weeks only to switch it up on myself and try something else that seemed more exciting in the moment. Because of this constant change, very little progress was being made. In fact, I was simply maintaining at best!
Finally, I made a change to my way of thinking!
I now buy into the idea of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hackerlytest in "Bangladesh imposes curfew after dozens killed in anti-government protests"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008128</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008128"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T16:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some context: Students are protesting to reform the quota system. Which was abolished in 2018 after protest but recently brought back again. The Quota system basically reserves 56% of public sector jobs, i.e. 30% to relatives of war veteran.
The war happened in 1971. To get public job and avail the quota, it must be their 3rd or 4th generation now. Which is plain unfair.
But it’s not about that, the gov loyalists and their goons fake these veteran certificates to land these jobs. Bangladesh is one of the most corrupted countries in the world after all. So real veteran relatives are seldom the beneficiary.
These students just wanted to reform this system. But our fascist gov and their goons used force and killed 50+ unarmed students until yesterday (3 from my alma mater alone.) This was completely unprovoked and unnecessary. Basically any forms of dissent have been dealt with this way since 2009. No one can criticize or protest the big brother.
We have a dictatorship since 2009. People are angry - due to corruption, inflation, joblessness and tyranny. This is just some outburst of it.
When you see the videos how the police are killing teenagers and university students in the road - our future generation - no one can tolerate this.
Now the fascist gov has closed all internet and phone connection to outside world. I can't contact my family anymore. I don't know their well being.
There is of course more to it. But this is the summary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hackerlytest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nimbius in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008009</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41008009"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T16:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work for a diesel truck repair facility and just locked up the doors after a 40 minute day :( .
- lifts wont operate.
- cant disarm the building alarms. (have been blaring 
nonstop...)
- cranes are all locked in standby/return/err.
- laser aligners are all offline.
- lathe hardware runs but controllers are all down.
- cant email suppliers.
- phones are all down.
- HVAC is also down for some reason (its getting hot in 
here.)
the police drove by and told us to close up for the day since we dont have 911 either.
alarms for the building are all offline/error so we chained things as best we could (might drive by a few times today.)
we dont know how many orders we have, we dont even know whos on schedule or if we will get paid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nimbius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bonestamp2 in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007836</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007836"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T16:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> without even the most basic level of qualification
That was my first thought too. Our company does firmware updates to hundreds of thousands of devices every month and those updates always go through 3 rounds of internal testing, then to a couple dozen real world users who we have a close relationship with (and we supply them with spare hardware that is not on the early update path in case there is a problem with an early rollout). Then the update goes to a small subset of users who opt in to those updates, then they get rolled out in batches to the regular users in case we still somehow missed something along the way. Nothing has ever gotten past our two dozen real world users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bonestamp2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia Hertäg: &ldquo;Remainders&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/remainders</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/remainders"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Heise (1955-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11:11, today's updates & tomorrow's plan]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/1111-updates-tomorrows-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/1111-updates-tomorrows-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am writing this in a café. 11:11, it's called, a make a wish banner conspicuously displayed in bright neon signs (I thought it was sweet, and I made a wish to be in good health for years to come). The upper floor is my psychiatrist’s office. I wasn’t planning on posting anything today, but I have a lot to process. So, let’s think out loud, shall we?
I think it was obvious from my last posts I wasn’t doing well. I made significant progress last month, but everything came crashing down the past weeks. I was fighting a battle I was rapidly losing. I ended up seeing my psychiatrist, though money is tight.
I love this clinic. My psychiatrist has adorned the waiting room with a chaotic display of colorful posters, rare words in English, inspirational quotes, and art. It makes me feel inspired …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify and automate bill processing with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>c6ac364a9cbf15333381e44f406fe89ede26cc9d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/simplify-and-automate-bill-processing-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Shyam Narayan, a leader in the Accenture AWS Business Group, and Hui Yee Leong, a DevOps and platform engineer, both based in Australia. Hui and Shyam specialize in designing and implementing complex AWS transformation programs across a wide range of industries. Enterprises that operate out of multiple locations such as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Shekhar Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by steelframe in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007570</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007570"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, this hits close to home. Doing a page fault where you can't in the kernel is exactly what I did with my very first patch I submitted after I joined the Microsoft BitLocker team in 2009. I added a check on the driver initialization path and didn't annotate the code as non-paged because frankly I didn't know at the time that the Windows kernel was paged. All my kernel development experience up to that point was with Linux, which isn't paged.
BitLocker is a storage driver, so that code turned into a circular dependency. The attempt to page in the code resulted a call to that not-yet-paged-in code.
The reason I didn't catch it with local testing was because I never tried rebooting with BitLocker enabled on my dev box when I was working on that code. For everyone on the team that did have BitLocker enabled they got the BSOD when they rebooted. Even then the "blast radius" was only the BitLocker team with about 8 devs, since local changes were qualified at the team level before they were merged up the chain.
The controls in place not only protected Windows more generally, but they even protected the majority of the Windows development group. It blows my mind that a kernel driver with the level of proliferation in industry could make it out the door apparently without even the most basic level of qualification.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steelframe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by casey2 in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007558</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41007558"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isn't Crowdstrike the same company the heavily lobbied to get make all their features a requirement for government computers?
https://www.opensecrets.org/federal-lobbying/clients/summary...
They have plenty of money for congress, but it seem little for any kind of reasonable software development practices. This isn't the first time crowdstrike has pushed system breaking changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>casey2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Internet traffic during the 2024 U.S. Republican National Convention]]></title>
        <id>669a608f58eb3b000a368a2e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exploring-internet-traffic-during-the-2024-us-republican-national-convention"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T15:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, the Republican National Convention was hosted in Milwaukee, Wisconsin from July 15 to 18, 2024. We examined traffic shifts and cyberattacks since June 2024 to see how these events have impacted the Internet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert: Why Covid and Future Pandemics Are a Bigger Threat than Nukes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275251</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/expert-why-covid-and-future-pandemics-are-a-bigger-threat-than-nukes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T13:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Persistent political and public health failures expose us to pandemics, while vastly underestimating their long-term health effects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by notaustinpowers in "FCC votes to limit prison telecom charges"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41006307</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41006307"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T13:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's absolutely grotesque to me.
Florida charges their inmates $50/day as a "bed fee" that they must pay when they are released. If you were found guilty and sentenced to 5 years in prison, but were released after 1 month because your charge was overturned, you still have to pay the fee for the full 5 years you would have been there.
It makes me ashamed to be an American.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>notaustinpowers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JackC in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005936</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005936"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T12:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crowdstrike did this to our production linux fleet back on April 19th, and I've been dying to rant about it.
The short version was: we're a civic tech lab, so we have a bunch of different production websites made at different times on different infrastructure. We run Crowdstrike provided by our enterprise. Crowdstrike pushed an update on a Friday evening that was incompatible with up-to-date Debian stable. So we patched Debian as usual, everything was fine for a week, and then all of our servers across multiple websites and cloud hosts simultaneously hard crashed and refused to boot.
When we connected one of the disks to a new machine and checked the logs, Crowdstrike looked like a culprit, so we manually deleted it, the machine booted, tried reinstalling it and the machine immediately crashes again. OK, let's file a support ticket and get an engineer on the line.
Crowdstrike took a day to respond, and then asked for a bunch more proof (beyond the above) that it was their fault. They acknowledged the bug a day later, and weeks later had a root cause analysis that they didn't cover our scenario (Debian stable running version n-1, I think, which is a supported configuration) in their test matrix. In our own post mortem there was no real ability to prevent the same thing from happening again -- "we push software to your machines any time we want, whether or not it's urgent, without testing it" seems to be core to the model, particularly if you're a small IT part of a large enterprise. What they're selling to the enterprise is exactly that they'll do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JackC</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by miki123211 in "FCC votes to limit prison telecom charges"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005738</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005738"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T12:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. The government decides that prisoners can make phone calls, but they can only use a single prison-approved phone operator, and that operator is a private company.
2. The private company realizes it has no competition, raises prices as much as it wants.
3. The government is surprised with the outcome.
I would say the government is at fault here for prohibiting competition, not the companies.
It's the 21st century, you could establish a system where any company, with an appropriate license and government approval, could offer tablets / cell phones for prisoner use, with appropriate limitations and restrictions placed on them of course. Prisoners could then choose which company they want to go with. That would instantly eliminate the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miki123211</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmmcd in "Want to spot a deepfake? Look for the stars in their eyes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005386</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005386"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They love saying things like "generative AI doesn't know physics". But the constraint that both eyes should have consistent reflection patterns is just another statistical regularity that appears in real photographs. Better training, larger models, and larger datasets, will lead to models that capture this statistical regularity. So this "one weird trick" will disappear without any special measures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmmcd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by frankohn in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005246</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005246"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows ecosystem typically deployed in corporate PCs or workstations is often insecure, slow, and poorly implemented, resulting in ongoing issues visible to everyone. Examples include problems with malware, ransomware, and Windows botnets.
In corporate environments, IT staff struggle to contain these issues using antivirus software, firewalls, and proxies. These security measures often slow down PCs significantly, even on recent multi-core systems that should be responsive.
Microsoft is responsible for providing an operating system that is inherently insecure and vulnerable. They have prioritized user lock-in, dark patterns, and ease of use over security.
Apple has done a much better job with macOS in terms of security and performance.
The corporate world is now divided into two categories:
1. Software-savvy companies that run on Linux or BSD variants, occasionally providing macOS to their employees. These include companies like Google, Amazon, Netflix, and many others.
2. Companies that are not software-focused, as it's not their primary business. These organizations are left with Microsoft's offerings, paying for licenses and dealing with slow and insecure software.
The main advantage of Microsoft's products is the Office suite: Excel, Word and Powerpoint but even Word is actually mediocre.
EDIT: improve expression and fix errors:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>frankohn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eitland in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005151</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41005151"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:29:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some Canonical guy I think many years ago mentioned this as their sales strategy a few year ago after a particularly nasty Windows outage:
We don't ask customers to switch all systems from Windows to Ubuntu, but to consider moving maybe a third to Ubuntu so they won't sit completely helpless next time Windows fail spectacularly.
While I see more and more Ubuntu systems, and recently have even spotted Landscape in the wild I don't think they were as successful as they hoped with that strategy.
That said, maybe there is a silver lining on todays clouds both WRT Ubuntu and Linux in general, and also WRT IT departments stopping to reconsider some security best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eitland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275257</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T10:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our imperial troopist daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens With the War in Ukraine if Trump Wins?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275255</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/what-happens-with-the-war-in-ukraine-if-trump-wins.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T10:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why a Trump win in November may make less difference to the future of the war in Ukraine than many assume.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking Ahead, But Not Forward, to Five More Years of “Queen” Ursula von der Leyen]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275202</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/five-more-years-of-queen-ursula-von-der-leyen.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T10:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After five years of overseeing creeping digital censorship, corruption, economic decline, war and institutional support for genocide, Von der Leyen has been given five more years to do more of the same, or worse. In late October, I posited that the walls may finally be closing in on EU President Ursula von der Leyen. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sidmkp96 in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41004691</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41004691"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T10:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The thing that amazes me is how they've rolled out such a buggy change at such a scale. I would assume that for such critical systems, there would be a gradual rollout policy, so that not everything goes down at once.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sidmkp96</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zmmmmm in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41004184</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41004184"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T09:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So CrowdStrike is deployed as third party software into the critical path of mission critical systems and then left to update itself. It's easy to blame CrowdStrike but that seems too easy on both the orgs that do this but also the upstream forces that compel them to do it.
My org which does mission critical healthcare just deployed ZScaler on every computer which is now in the critical path of every computer starting up and then in the critical path of every network connection the computer makes. The risk of ZScaler being a central point of failure is not considered. But - the risk of failing the compliance checkbox it satisfies is paramount.
All over the place I'm seeing checkbox compliance being prioritised above actual real risks from how the compliance is implemented. Orgs are doing this because they are more scared of failing an audit than they are of the consequences failure of the underlying systems the audits are supposed to be protecting. So we need to hold regulatory bodies accountable as well - when they frame regulation such that organisations are cornered into this they get to be part of the culpability here too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zmmmmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmcgough in "CrowdStrike Update: Windows Bluescreen and Boot Loops"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41002977</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41002977"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Took down our entire emergency department as we were treating a heart attack. 911 down for our state too. Nowhere for people to be diverted to because the other nearby hospitals are down. Hard to imagine how many millions of not billions of dollars this one bad update caused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmcgough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Politics on the Verge of Nervous Breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328366</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/politics-on-the-verge-of-nervous-breakdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T06:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's would-be assassin, Crooks didn’t seem overtly political. His politics were the politics of the gun. He searched for the names of Biden and Trump, equally, it seemed and was likely to have pulled the trigger on the first one who entered the sights of his AR-15. There was just a dime’s worth of difference between them as far as he was concerned. Crooks is the next variation on Kyle Rittenhouse, a fucked up white kid, working a dead-end job in a shabbily run nursing home, who ventured forth bound for glory with a semi-automatic rifle in the Republic of the Shooter. More
The post Politics on the Verge of Nervous Breakdown appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Academia and the Censoring of an Anti-Zionist Professor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328341</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/us-academia-and-the-censoring-of-an-anti-zionist-professor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this essay, I will describe my activism on behalf of Palestinians' human rights and their right to self-determination, from my graduate student days on a US campus, to the present in my position as a tenured full professor, and the ways in which I’ve experienced attempts at silencing and censorship. These attempts today are more blatant and worrisome than ever before on anyone speaking up for Palestine in the USA More
The post US Academia and the Censoring of an Anti-Zionist Professor appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fawzia Afzal-Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Day of the Jackal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328511</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/trumps-day-of-the-jackal/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T06:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump might well owe his next presidency to his would-be assassin, so perhaps, as it becomes clear that Crooks was in lockstep with Trumpism, a revived Warren Commission might be pressed into service to explain how the gunman himself was a victim of Deep State transgenderism and to attribute his rooftop violence to hormone blockers that robbed him of him of his manhood. More
The post Trump’s Day of the Jackal appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming changes to the discovery feed]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/discovery-feed-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/discovery-feed-changes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bear community is awesome. The discovery feed is vibrant with slices of life, letter circles, the sharing of tips on how to trick out your blog, and so much more. It's a special corner of the internet that needs to be nourished and protected.
But as with any growing community, this hasn't been without its own set of challenges. These challenges can be broadly categorised into 2 groups:
1. Spam blogs
Fighting spam is an ongoing battle, but mostly a solved problem. A combination of The Frustration Loop and the review process has taken care of it. However, due to a sharp increase in the number of signups recently (both legitimate and spam blogs), I've co-opted the help of Pam and Shraddha from Bonsai Digital to get through the never-ending stack of new blogs.
2. Unsuitable content
The dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fukushima Toxic Dumping]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/fukushima-toxic-dumping/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Plant is the world’s leading epicenter of toxic radioactive water released into the ocean. Yet, these activities are no longer closely monitored by mainstream media. As it happens, Tokyo Electric Power Company is the electric utility that manages the decommissioning of the collapsed nuclear reactors. This controversial ongoing release of radioactive  More
The post Fukushima Toxic Dumping appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To a Starving Orphan Who Died Alone in Rubble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328521</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/to-a-starving-orphan-who-died-alone-in-rubble/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tales of infants and young children dying because they can’t get enough to eat and distraught parents robbed of their dignity because they can do nothing for their kids (or themselves) are too numerous and ghastly to detail here. But just for a moment imagine that all of this was happening to your loved ones.  More
The post To a Starving Orphan Who Died Alone in Rubble  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hatch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Supporting Israel is a Liability: Is Gaza Changing the West?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328515</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/when-supporting-israel-is-a-liability-is-gaza-changing-the-west/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much has been written about the political earthquakes in Britain and France, the first resulting in the crushing defeat of the Conservative Party and the latter in the overpowering of the far right, by a largely leftist coalition. But these were not the only important outcomes of the July 4 and July 7 general elections  More
The post When Supporting Israel is a Liability: Is Gaza Changing the West?  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re-Opening a Permanently Shut Nuclear Reactor is a Dangerous Gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328547</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/re-opening-a-permanently-shut-nuclear-reactor-is-a-dangerous-gamble/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forty U.S. nuclear power reactors have shut permanently. But for the first time, an attempt is being made to re-start a closed reactor – the Palisades reactor in southwest Michigan. The American experience with nuclear power began as Cold War fears of nuclear war and health hazards from bomb test fallout were widespread. President Eisenhower’s  More
The post Re-Opening a Permanently Shut Nuclear Reactor is a Dangerous Gamble appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Mangano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism: the End of an Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328468</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/zionism-the-end-of-an-illusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the oddest arguments made by self-declared friends of Israel is that anti-Zionism is a form of antisemitism.  That assertion is comprehensible if the person making it believes that God Himself gave the Jews property rights from the river to the sea – but  Theodore Herzl and the founders of modern Zionism embraced no such belief.  On the contrary, that movement’s largely secularized leadership defined Zionism from the outset as a form of ethnic nationalism – a claim to the same “right of self-determination” as that asserted, say, by the Irish or the Serbs.  More
The post Zionism: the End of an Illusion appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard E. Rubenstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel: Where Genocide Meets Real Estate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328553</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/israel-where-genocide-meets-real-estate/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, real estate events in synagogues in Toronto, Los Angeles, and New Jersey, among other locations, have promoted property sales in Israel and the Occupied West Bank. In response, Palestinian communities have protested the sales and engaged in legal action. Marketing property assets in “Anglo neighborhoods,” events of this nature target Zionist Jews from the  More
The post Israel: Where Genocide Meets Real Estate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Hurtles Toward Political Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328528</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-u-s-hurtles-toward-political-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States was already headed for one of the most acute political crises in recent memory. Then former president and convicted felon Donald Trump was nearly assassinated at a rally in Pennsylvania. Having survived, Trump has consolidated his base and cornered the Democrats by blaming them for the attack. Trump will now position himself  More
The post The U.S. Hurtles Toward Political Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hymn from Hell:  Greenwood Burns for Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328647</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/hymn-from-hell-greenwood-burns-for-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country singer Lee Greenwood was born three weeks before Joe Biden. A self-styled evangelical Christian Republican, Greenwood is a wiry octogenarian, well-spoken and exuding a fiery intelligence. At 81, he pursues a performing schedule that would exhaust many a crooner or candidate half his age. It his piercing tenor voice, aided by electronic amplification  More
The post Hymn from Hell:  Greenwood Burns for Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Lunacy Down Under]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328539</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/nuclear-lunacy-down-under/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Politics and facts are not necessarily good dinner companions.  Both often stray from the same table, taking up with other, more suitable company.  The Australian opposition leader, Peter Dutton, has never been discomforted by facts, preferring the chimera-like qualities demagoguery offers.  His vision for Australia is admirably simple and simplistic. In foreign policy, he supports US interventions in  More
The post Nuclear Lunacy Down Under appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congressional Fiasco: The House Votes to Bring Back the Draft]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328632</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/congressional-fiasco-the-house-votes-to-bring-back-the-draft/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans hate the military draft. They revolted against it in stupendously high numbers in the 1960s and ‘70s, but the intellectual heavyweights in the House of Representatives idiotically brushed off that bit of relevant history with their odious vote June 14 to facilitate reinstatement of conscription. With any luck, they’ll reap the whirlwind they deserve.  More
The post Congressional Fiasco: The House Votes to Bring Back the Draft appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tribute to Happy Traum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328567</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/a-tribute-to-happy-traum/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1961 was a remarkable year, in which the USA was first being led by a young idealistic president, John F. Kennedy.  It was also the year of the Freedom Rides, when busloads of Freedom Riders had their buses attacked and burned when proceeding through the South, attempting to integrate restrooms and eating places. And it  More
The post A Tribute to Happy Traum appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden to Justices Alito and Thomas: “You’re Fired”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328544</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/biden-to-justices-alito-and-thomas-youre-fired/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Modest Proposal for Improving American Democracy The far-right ideologues celebrate With the Supreme Court’s recent decisions disempowering federal regulatory agencies (the “Chevron deference”) and granting the President criminal immunity for “official acts” in office, American democracy – long infirm – is nearly moribund. The far-right ideologues of the Claremont Institute, Foundation for Government Accountability,  More
The post Biden to Justices Alito and Thomas: “You’re Fired” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman – W.J.T. Mitchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden’s Symbolic Legacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328530</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/joe-bidens-symbolic-legacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, the fiasco that is Joe Biden’s presidential campaign goes on like the worst SNL sketch ever, one saved to use very late in the night when most have the television turned off. A sketch among already shitty sketches thrown in as filler. Certainly not high caliber fare like Fred Garvin, male  More
The post Joe Biden’s Symbolic Legacy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time for a Child Allowance With No Strings Attached]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328642</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/its-time-for-a-child-allowance-with-no-strings-attached/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the pandemic, the expanded Child Tax Credit was a lifeline for millions of families. However, I was one of the many who couldn’t benefit from it. Why? At 15, I gave my baby to family members. But because the adoption was never finalized, I actually ended up owing child support — and only found out after  More
The post It’s Time for a Child Allowance With No Strings Attached appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tia Simmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025’s Plan to Gut Medicare and Medicaid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328645</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/project-2025s-plan-to-gut-medicare-and-medicaid/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives have done the United States a huge favor by explaining in detail what they’ll try to do if Donald Trump is reelected. Project 2025, a “presidential transition project” of the Heritage Foundation, helpfully lays out how a group of former Trump officials would like to transform the country into a right-wing dystopia where the rich thrive  More
The post Project 2025’s Plan to Gut Medicare and Medicaid appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Solution to Homelessness is Housing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328641</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-solution-to-homelessness-is-housing/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard enough not having a safe place to live. Now it’s easier for cities to arrest you for it. “I am afraid at all times,” testified Debra Blake, who’d been forced to live outside in Grants Pass, Oregon for eight years after losing her job and housing. Her disability disqualified her from staying in the town’s only shelter.  More
The post The Solution to Homelessness is Housing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump the Survivor Exudes Power and Invites Sympathy at the Same Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328446</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/trump-the-survivor-exudes-power-and-invites-sympathy-at-the-same-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The expected electoral bump for Donald Trump after the failed assassination attempt could be because of his raised fist show of strength, urging the crowd to “Fight, fight, fight” while bleeding and being ushered away from the podium by Secret Service agents. Or it could be because of voters’ sympathetic feelings towards someone who narrowly  More
The post Trump the Survivor Exudes Power and Invites Sympathy at the Same Time appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ten Commandments: Coming Soon to a Public School Near You]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328478</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-ten-commandments-coming-soon-to-a-public-school-near-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louisiana has become the first state in the nation to require the Ten Commandments to be displayed in all public school classrooms, up to and including state-funded universities. Since Louisiana regularly places towards the bottom of state rankings in education, health, poverty, violent crimes, and overall quality of life, Louisiana must find it gratifying that  More
The post The Ten Commandments: Coming Soon to a Public School Near You appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles Pierson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Astonishing Success of the Wealthy at Accumulating More Wealth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328524</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-astonishing-success-of-the-wealthy-at-accumulating-more-wealth/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of July 15, 2024, the latest figures from the Bloomberg Billionaires Index shows that the wealth of the 10 wealthiest U.S. citizens continues to surge ahead–by over 24.5% during the first part of the year, an increase of $336.9 billion, bringing their total wealth to $1.71 trillion or $1,710 billion. The increase in their  More
The post The Astonishing Success of the Wealthy at Accumulating More Wealth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Baum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe at the ‘Hot Gates’!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328363</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/europe-at-the-hot-gates/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2500 years ago, the myth goes, 300 Spartans faced a much larger military force from the East at Thermopylae, a small mountain pass in ancient central Greece. Thermopylae is the Latin word for ‘Hot Gates’, as the area featured hot springs.  In European history the ‘hot gates’ battle ended with the 300 Spartans annihilated. The  More
The post Europe at the ‘Hot Gates’! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Rasmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Decline and Fall of Presidential America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328519</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-decline-and-fall-of-presidential-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not a happenstance or some sad mistake that, barring a surprise, Americans will go to the polls in November to vote for one of two distinctly ancient men, now 77 and 81, both of whom have clearly exhibited language and thought problems for a significant period of time. To put this in perspective, remember for a moment  More
The post The Decline and Fall of Presidential America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Eruption of the New Right: On “When the Clock Broke”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328655</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/the-eruption-of-the-new-right-on-when-the-clock-broke/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Hobsbawm has noted that the Soviet Union saved Western capitalism two times. The first time was when the USSR defeated Nazi Germany. The second time was that by displaying an alternative political-economic system to the rest of the world, the USSR compelled the West, and specifically the US, to reform its institutions. The reforms  More
The post The Eruption of the New Right: On “When the Clock Broke” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Sperber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labour Government: The Politics of Service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328551</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/labour-government-the-politics-of-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 14 years of Conservative incompetence, corruption and lies, the election of The Labour Party led by Kier Starmer, has ignited a feeling of hope and optimism in the country. In a historic election, on 4 July Labour won a landslide with 412 parliamentary seats (of 650 in total); the Tories, as if anyone cares,  More
The post Labour Government: The Politics of Service appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Peebles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chick-fil-A is Running a Child Labor Summer Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328543</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/chick-fil-a-is-running-a-child-labor-summer-camp/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Summertime, and the living is easy, fish are jumping, and”… wait a minute, what is this? It’s a summer camp for kids — but with a disturbing corporate twist. Some outlets of Chick-fil-A, the fast food chicken chain, are now promoting a summer camp where children as young as 5 can learn “how to be  More
The post Chick-fil-A is Running a Child Labor Summer Camp appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Hightower</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hope In Muddied Waters? Peeling Back The Curtain On PBS’s New “Hope In The Water” Series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328535</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/hope-in-muddied-waters-peeling-back-the-curtain-on-pbss-new-hope-in-the-water-series/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PBS has a new docu-series called “Hope in the Water,” full of feel-good stories about aquatic foods that come from the ocean and other waterways. As someone who does communications for a grassroots nonprofit rallying around a healthy ocean commons and local, values-based seafood, I have mixed feelings. On one hand, I fundamentally believe there’s  More
The post Hope In Muddied Waters? Peeling Back The Curtain On PBS’s New “Hope In The Water” Series appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Feini Yin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Purpose of NATO Remains USA Hegemony]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328536</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/true-purpose-of-nato-remains-usa-hegemony/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NATO’s new focus on China harkens back to the belligerent alliance’s early days. At the North Atlantic Treaty Organization’s 75th anniversary summit in Washington, DC, last week China was a big part of the agenda. The NATO summit’s final declaration mentioned the People’s Republic of China’s (PRC) 14 times. It noted that “the PRC continues to  More
The post True Purpose of NATO Remains USA Hegemony appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’re a Hypocrite, And So Am I]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328531</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/19/youre-a-hypocrite-and-so-am-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re all hypocrites. For the most part, it’s not our fault. We necessarily live in the systems we’re working to change. I’m writing this on a device made possible by conflict materials dug up by children in Congo. I’m sitting in an air-conditioned home that most likely requires dirty energy to operate. In a month,  More
The post You’re a Hypocrite, And So Am I appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eleanor Goldfield</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Burying Biomass Underground Curb Climate Change?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275152</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/will-burying-biomass-underground-curb-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T05:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some climate experts say biomass start-ups will limit global warming, but major questions remain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Removals and Major Changes In v1.31]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/07/19/kubernetes-1-31-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/07/19/kubernetes-1-31-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Kubernetes develops and matures, features may be deprecated, removed, or replaced with better ones for the project's overall health.
This article outlines some planned changes for the Kubernetes v1.31 release that the release team feels you should be aware of for the continued maintenance of your Kubernetes environment.
The information listed below is based on the current status of the v1.31 release.
It may change before the actual release date.
The Kubernetes API removal and deprecation process
The Kubernetes project has a well-documented deprecation policy for features.
This policy states that stable APIs may only be deprecated when a newer, stable version of that API is available and that APIs have a minimum lifetime for each stability level.
A deprecated API has been marked for remo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Project of Sorts: A Blog Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-blog-directory/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-blog-directory/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T22:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month, I wrote a blog post titled “To Blogroll, or to not?” With my thought process of not adding a Blogroll to my page, but opting to add a Postroll instead. Since that post went live, I have gotten replies from both ends of the spectrum agreeing and (respectfully) disagreeing with my thought process. I’ve highlighted some of those responses at the bottom of the post under the 💬 Community Echoes, if you were curious.
Anyways, this got me really thinking about Discovery and Community, especially since I’m seeing a few articles written ranging from “WTF Happened to Blogs” to “indie blogs are doing OK: here’s how to find them”. I wanted a way to contribute to the blogging community, which has made me feel immensely welcomed since I rejoined at the end of March.
So here we go…
E…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a leap of faith]]></title>
        <id>https://anotherjournal.bearblog.dev/a-leap-of-faith/</id>
        <link href="https://anotherjournal.bearblog.dev/a-leap-of-faith/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[u know that feeling when it's nearly impossible to achieve something..
either because you're too late
or you didn't prepare enough and it has high competition
your mind and logic says: there is no way
but your brain (or soul?) says: f*ck it we do it anyway.
and somehow (most of the time) it works out!
and even if it doesn't -- u don't feel thaaat bad..
u say gg and move on.
that leap of faith is real!
i hope such happy ending occurs again in my upcoming move inshallah.
if u reading this: wish me luck homie -- will need it fr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by WalterBright in "What would it take to recreate Bell Labs?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40999786</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40999786"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I liked Bell Labs ever since 1986 or 1987 or so. I was considering developing a C++ compiler, but was concerned about:
1. would I need a license to develop a C++ compiler?
2. would I need a license to call it C++?
So I called up their head intellectual property lawyer. He laughed, and said feel free, and thanked me for asking. He said other people just went ahead and copied things hoping BL wouldn't notice.
So thank you, Bell Labs! You guys were the best.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>WalterBright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn, a professional network, or a blogging platform?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8044</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/linkedin-professional-network-blogging-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2008, I had a brief tweet exchange with another Twitter member, about the merits of LinkedIn*. At that point, I was a member, but really didn’t like the platform. I thought having a personal website, showcasing your abilities, was a better idea. #IndieWeb me was thinking — all of sixteen years ago — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vzaliva in "USPS shared customer postal addresses with Meta, LinkedIn and Snap"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40999439</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40999439"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T20:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clickbait title: USPS did not share anything intentionally. They negligently allowed tracking pixels from certain companies on their Informed Delivery page.
Of course, it's terrible from a privacy point of view, but let's be honest and call things as they are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vzaliva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on being unemployed at 26]]></title>
        <id>https://pj.bearblog.dev/on-being-unemployed-at-26/</id>
        <link href="https://pj.bearblog.dev/on-being-unemployed-at-26/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T18:06:17.766Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this is the first time i'm revealing my age on bear, something i kept hidden for privacy's sake. 

i'm quitting my part-time job next week. 

is it okay to be unemployed at 26? 

i think it's mainly because i don't like where i am right now. 

when i was a kid i picked up on things very quickly. 

i know (i hope) i won't be stuck here forever. 

i'm still struggling, and even if i tell myself and others that there is no such thing as being behind, i can't help but feel dissatisfied with my current situation. 

i'm trying to have faith in myself but i'm not so good on my own, so please put your faith in me as well. 
and hope with me that this too shall pass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275213</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T18:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; A former Navy SEAL takes a view on Trump's assempted assassination;  the Republican National Convention  and  J.D. Vance; unelecting Biden: irresistible (albeit private) force, immovable (albeit ill) object; Marimekko patterns online. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinclair Thomson: &ldquo;Mutiny in Bolivia&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/mutiny-in-bolivia</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/mutiny-in-bolivia"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The crisis of the MAS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hudson on Super Imperialism 1]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45483</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/18/hudson-on-super-imperialism-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T17:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog In this sequence of posts, I will present the contents of the video podcast entitled “Michael Hudson: Why the US has a unique place in the history of imperialism? ” For me, Hudson’s book Super Imperialism: The Economic Strategy of the American Empire was an amazing eye-opener, essential reading […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[loose thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/loose-thoughts/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/loose-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T15:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[-Women are not allowed to be women. We're expected to look like teenagers for the rest of our lives, and it's exhausting.
-One of my favorite hobbies used to be reading books. Now, it feels impossible to read one page without having to backtrack and read that page again (and sometimes...again) because I have no idea what I just read. My mind is unable to keep focus. I buy a lot of books, but I don't read them. I'm a collector of nightstand-books.
-I started eating Kimchi for the first time ever this week and...I'm in love.
-A part of me wants to remove my blog archives page from the navigation, create a new page, and showcase only the posts I want to keep sharing. idk.
-Dating someone new is hard. Constantly making sure you're shaved, smelling wonderful, hair at its best, face presentable, worried about farting in front of them or taking a shit in your own bathroom, making sure you're wearing sexy underwear, not eating too much in front of them...honestly, it's like I'm afraid of being human. I just want to be a slob on my couch sometimes.
-Do you use Are.na? I want to, but it looks awful. I downloaded Cosmos, and I do like it so far. I wonder if there are any other apps similar to Are.na (not Pinterest).
-I sent out my weekly letter yesterday. Did you read it? I love writing these tiny missives through email. Are people reading it though? I don't know. But I shall keep writing and sharing, and hopefully, it will help someone out there feel a little less alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday 004 - Finding Nemo]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-finding-nemo/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-finding-nemo/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Throwback Thursday post brings us to the Philippines during that one time I finally found Nemo. He was just as surprised to see me as I was him -- although I think he was absolutely ready for his close up.
Taken while snorkeling on one of the islands (I think El Nido, Palawan).

August 2014, Philippines, GoPro Hero 3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Big Pharma Preys on Poor Countries – and Patients Pay the Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275208</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/how-big-pharma-preys-on-poor-countries-and-patients-pay-the-price.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New investigation reveals unequal access to life-saving meds across Europe thanks to Big Pharma system that favors the rich]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by volkadav in "My daughter (7 years old) used HTML to make a website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40995243</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40995243"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>volkadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Caddy – Meta’s next-gen mixed reality CAD software]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21495</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/18/virtual-reality/caddy-cad-mixed-reality-mr-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when a team of mechanical engineers get tired of looking at flat images of 3D models over Zoom? Meet the team behind Caddy, a new CAD app for mixed reality. They join Pascal Hartig (@passy) on the Meta Tech Podcast to talk about teaching themselves to code, disrupting the CAD software space, how [...]
Read More...
The post Meet Caddy – Meta’s next-gen mixed reality CAD software appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! A Dev Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://binarydigit.dev/dev-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://binarydigit.dev/dev-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all started with a post on my main blog where I still have the urge to revisit the art of learning software and web tools. Even if they are small things, I want to learn basics again other than simply editing templates or static site generators. I'll keep my main blog for everything else I want to share, but I had to buy-yet-another-domain as a nudge to see if I can seperate this tech space online. I also hope to actually put it on a resume one day.
I want to focus on fun projects that I might use, such as learning how to create a discord bot, a Twitch bot or overlay, or other tools that I'll use for my current hobbies. I think a to do list of sorts that I come back to now and again is a good start.
 Send a message]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275178</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T10:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our cuddly daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden 2024 Run Back in Play as Democratic Pushback Escalates, Covid Case Offers Face-Saving Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275179</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/biden-2024-run-back-in-play-as-democratic-pushback-escalates-covid-case-offers-face-saving-out.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T10:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden political survival watch has resumed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by weatherlite in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40992756</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40992756"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T05:29:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel really bummed out I am getting 1/2 (or less?) of Google compensation. But then I open my eyes - see the workers in my daughter's kindergarten slaving away taking care of 30 toddlers for less than half what I make, nurses and doctors working in conditions I wouldn't be able to tolerate for more than a few months without mentally collapsing, the people in the supermarkets, gas stations, police, fire departments, social workers, teachers etc etc.
Really I don't see what we have to complain about - whether its a 3 man startup with "low" compensation or anything else. 
You're getting paid for solving code riddles the whole day.  You're getting paid a lot. Quit comparing yourself to your friends that work in Google and try to learn how to cultivate a peaceful and happy mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>weatherlite</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Out Loud About My Photos Overload]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/thinking-out-loud-about-my-photos-overload/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/thinking-out-loud-about-my-photos-overload/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things I’m trying to make a habit of is posting more frequently (or often) in my photoblog page. My posts have always been slightly sporadic, and definitely not consistent since I started that site (last year). Maybe it’s because I have a problem.
When I go on photowalks, or a full day of shooting, I accumulate a lot of photos from that day. I upload all my photos to my external SSD. My folder hierarchy for photos is typically:
Year > Photos > Camera > Month > Folder Name with date
So in some instances that would look something like:
2004 > Photos > X100V > 07 July > 071724 aWalkInSF
(Yes, I am a supporter of camelCase instead of snake_case)
Anyways… my photos are not tagged, and keep their original names. If a particular photo is edited, the original is DSCF3415, and the edited…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 14, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240717</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240717"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To find #IndieWeb, more people need to know it exists]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8032</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/to-find-indieweb-more-people-need-know-exists/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JTR, writing at The Art Of Not Asking Why: Indie blogs are like good spots in town. Sure, they’re on the map, but you need to ask the locals to point them out. In terms of indie blogs, this means other bloggers. Word of mouth is sure a great way to spread the news about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by klyrs in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988832</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988832"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T18:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a literal graph theorist, I cannot tell you how frustrating it is that (a) nobody seems to understand my work except (b) interviewers use it as a shibboleth to exclude people from jobs that will never need high performance graph algorithms.  That, I never get called for these interviews because I don't use react angles or something, but if they did, I'd crush the interview and fall asleep at my desk once they start giving me work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>klyrs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing Karpenter: Transitioning Kafka to Amazon EKS with AWS solutions]]></title>
        <id>910ef3a53d9d7fb2e0aa32c2b41b897b162560a8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/harnessing-karpenter-transitioning-kafka-to-amazon-eks-with-aws-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AppsFlyer is a global leader in mobile attribution and marketing analytics. AppsFlyer helps businesses understand the impact and their marketing efforts across every channel and device, through a comprehensive measurement platform and privacy cloud that fosters ecosystem collaboration while preserving customers’ privacy. Within AppsFlyer, data is the core, it gives the ability to expose detailed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alicia Plotnikov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ykl in "TinyPod – Apple Watch case with scroll wheel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988078</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988078"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I unapologetically love this thing. It's of course very silly, and I'm sure commenters here are going to talk about all the ways that it isn't practical or that it's a niche idea, but I love whimsical silly niche hardware ideas that make it into actual hardware. I love that they put in all of the effort to figure out a mechanical linkage between the clickwheel and the digital crown!
I don't think all hardware needs to be take-over-the-world hundred-million-unit ideas; I think sometimes it's fine for hardware to be whimsical niche things like this Apple Watch case or Andrew McCalip's doomscroller doo-dad [1]!
[1] https://doomscroller.xyz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ykl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mrbluecoat in "Jailbreaking RabbitOS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988032</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40988032"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> logs include:
Your precise GPS locations (which are also sent to their servers).
Your WiFi network name.
The IDs of nearby cell towers (even with no SIM card inserted, also sent to their servers).
Your internet-facing IP address.
The user token used by the device to authenticate with Rabbit's back-end API.
Base64-encoded MP3s of everything the Rabbit has ever spoken to you (and the text transcript thereof).
Nasty :0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mrbluecoat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scottLobster in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987804</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987804"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's coding interviews and coding interviews.
Asking basic questions that will be directly applicable to the job?  Sure
Filtering for basic knowledge to make sure the candidate isn't lying about their experience?  Sure.
Examining my thought process and producing working code is a nice-to-have?  Sure.
Asking me to solve an extremely esoteric problem that has zero relevance to my day-to-day and if the solution I come up with on the spot under time pressure is incorrect or even just not the most efficient I'm rejected?  At that point you're just filtering for starry-eyed recent grads you can underpay.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scottLobster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[goodbye to all that]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/goodbye-to-all-that/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/goodbye-to-all-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last post I didn't finish writing everything I wanted to say before hitting Publish. My posts often get broken up like this in my desire to publish fast and often; when I find a nice place to stop, I put a bow on my draft and send it out, lest I dawdle too long and kill my momentum.
That said, this post will be a continuation of sorts. Here are the rest of the thoughts inspired by Misha's post.
it feels like people are moving forward with their lives, but i’m still stuck at the same place i was when i was when i was 18, choosing a college degree that will change the trajectory of my life.
i had bigger dreams as a teenager. i wanted to do things—get out more; live a little differently than how my 15 year old self did. instead, i became the type of person who waits for her paycheck twi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Thomson Reuters achieved 5X operational efficiency and 30% cost optimization with Plexus on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>cb24bb84b9abe4d08c13bcea2f3f6bb640f40ccf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-thomson-reuters-achieved-5x-operational-efficiency-and-30-cost-optimization-with-plexus-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In today’s dynamic business landscape, operational efficiency and cost optimization are two critical ingredients for a successful business outcome. This is especially true for companies navigating through digital transformation. In 2020, Thomson Reuters (TR), a leader at the intersection of content and technology with trusted data, committed to a cloud-first strategy with Amazon Web […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Yan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by caesil in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987450</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987450"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>According to all the interviews I’ve failed over the years (I don’t think I’ve ever passed an actual “coding interview” anywhere?), the entire goal of tech hiring is just finding people in the 100 to 115 midwit block then outright rejecting everybody else as too much of an unknown risk.
As a (now) senior/staff-level engineer back out on the job market for the first time in a while, I'm begrudgingly coming to accept that coding interviews might not actually be all that bad. Mostly because I find myself passing them due to having picked up skills in the past few years rather than spending a ton of time studying, which suggests they might actually be picking up some signal. I once thought they were purely hazing with zero relevance to day to day work, but as I get more senior I drift further away from that opinion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>caesil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lovich in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987359</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987359"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:03:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I generally like the article but the author seems to have a really inflated view of what jobs are paying. At one point he’s claiming that a stable non tech company like a tractor manufacturer is paying 5k-10k.
Even assuming that’s including taxes so divide by two, and constraining to just software employees for that claim. There is no way the average pay is nearly a million a year. The average software engineer in the US is making around 135-150k a year and that average is including all the faang engineers with the top end salary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lovich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by evrimoztamur in "Panic at the Job Market"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40987331"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will add my two cents for people who believe that this might be related only to the SWE and tangent industries: It's really not. I have many friends (in Europe) who are trying to get through to different jobs in unrelated industries ranging from finance to fashion, or just trying to get promoted vertically (or horizontally), failing rather miserably.
Most jobs are now hoops after hoops, not taking into consideration your particular profile or the contributions you can make. Keep in mind also that a CV in the pile via a job portal is always going to be sediment at the bottom of the barrel. Try to make use of your networks and friends as much as possible.
As for my situation, I too feel a bit burned by the diminishing number of tech jobs, as I was in the process of trying to get a job via a software consultancy firm, but remained benched for 8 months. I dropped it, went back to doing corporate and tax valuations. Being underemployed is, thus far, better than nothing at all, especially mentally.
P.S. Here's a nice little tidbit in the source:
  

I have to admit, I did slip up on this banana by being a lazy monkey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evrimoztamur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tomeraberbach in "Import and Export Markdown in Google Docs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40984859</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40984859"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey folks, I'm the engineer who implemented the new feature. Just clearing up some confusion.
A lot of you are noticing the preexisting automatic detection feature from 2022 [1], which I also worked on. That's NOT what this newly announced feature is. The new feature supports full import/export, but it's still rolling out so you're likely not seeing it yet!
Hope you like it once it reaches you :)
[1] https://workspaceupdates.googleblog.com/2022/03/compose-with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tomeraberbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: a life lived diligently]]></title>
        <id>https://therat.bearblog.dev/re-a-life-lived-diligently/</id>
        <link href="https://therat.bearblog.dev/re-a-life-lived-diligently/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:11:15.518Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Misha!
I've read your post a life lived diligently, and it made me want to write to you.
When I was younger, I dreamed every day of becoming a product designer. I had convinced myself I was going to go study abroad, become self-employed, and the riches and fame would be mine.
poor, depressed artist aesthetic, after which I would be discovered and prove everyone wrong about not chasing your dreams. My peers would see me on TV and gawk. Grand finale: let the curtain fall; everyone applauds.
I'm happy to say none of that came true.
The truth is, your 20s are a little bit of a bitch. These are the years someone can either be going steady with a child on each hip or they can be partying 'til the sun goes down. Comparison is hard to keep at bay since everyone is going at a different pace and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wage Insurance: A Potential Policy for Displaced Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30761</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/wage-insurance-a-potential-policy-for-displaced-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the existing safety net, worker displacement continues to have severe consequences that motivate the consideration of new social insurance programs. Wage insurance is a novel policy that temporarily provides additional income to workers who lose their job and become re-employed at a lower wage. In this post, we draw on evidence from our recent working paper analyzing the effects of a U.S. wage insurance program on worker earnings and employment outcomes. Among workers displaced by international trade, we find that eligibility for wage insurance increased the probability of employment in the first two years following job loss and led to higher long-term earnings. The program resulted in net savings to the government because workers collected fewer benefits and paid taxes on their increased earnings. Together, these findings suggest that wage insurance could support displaced workers more effectively than traditional social insurance programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Hyman, Brian Kovak, and Adam Leive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Towards an Especifista Feminism in North America]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/2022-towards-an-especifista-feminism-in-north-america?v=1721210769</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/2022-towards-an-especifista-feminism-in-north-america?v=1721210769"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Towards an Especifista Feminism in North America
Date: 2022
Source: Scanned from a zine.

Introduction
TO BEGIN...
 “We recognize that the feminist camp has made great efforts, by revealing the mechanisms that oppress women and dissidence, and by naming issues that used to be invisible. However, this does not mean that the concepts and categories, and therefore the theoretical frameworks, are all equally valid. As especifist anarchists we task ourselves with taking from these theoretical productions, the concepts and categories that are consistent with our own ideology. Referring to the guiding principles of other currents will not only lead us down a different ideological path but also have concrete effects on the militancy, on the political level as on the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Tolstoy - Three Deaths]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-three-deaths-bain-translation?v=1721203105</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-three-deaths-bain-translation?v=1721203105"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Leo Tolstoy
Title: Three Deaths
Date: 1859
Notes: Translated by Robert Nisbet Bain and published in 1902.
Source: <revoltlib.com/anarchism/three-deaths-bain-translation-tolstoy-leo>

I.
 It was Autumn. A carriage and a calesche were proceeding at a sharp trot along the high-road. In the carriage sat two women. One of them was the mistress, thin and pale. The other was the maid, smug, florid, and buxom. Her short dry tresses peeped forth from under her faded bonnet, her pretty hand in her torn glove readjusted them from time to time; her swelling bosom, covered by a rug, was full of the breath of health; her quick black eyes glanced at one moment out of the window at the scurrying fields, at another stared boldly at her mistress, or glanced uneasily at the corners of the carriage. B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging]]></title>
        <id>https://emmasdilemmas.bearblog.dev/emerging/</id>
        <link href="https://emmasdilemmas.bearblog.dev/emerging/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contrary to what the name may suggest, this is not a blog dedicated solely to my problems. As I make my debut into the realm of Bear — thrilled at the thought of reaching other bloggers through the ever-inspiring discovery feed — I must make one thing clear: I love a good rhyme. Sometimes more than logic. And in this case, the tradeoff for choosing a name that rhymes is that the content in my blog won’t always align with the title, and I’m okay with that.
My purpose here isn’t to please or to delight; it’s to express — something we rarely get the space to do authentically online. Being here takes a degree of vulnerability for me, but it comes with the gentle comfort of some anonymity.
Here, I am still Emma as I am in everyday life, but I am also imperceptible behind the words you read. While I plan to share with an open heart and freely exhibit the more anomalous corners of my mind, I know that the stakes are lower than what they seem to be on other platforms, where it often feels like I'm being observed too closely, or slipping into an alter-ego that doesn't truly capture me. Here, it feels like I can say what I want to say without the recurring fear of being perceived or held to a fixed identity. And, no matter who happens to stumble upon the musings of these pages — no matter who thinks what of the words I write — I still intend to make this a space where I can comfortably express whatever may come to the surface of my being.
And so, with a nod of thanks to you, the equally imperceptible reader, and also one to the creator of this charming platform — who happens to be the man I gladly spend my days with — so begins my emergence. Let’s see what this Bear blogness is all about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Words and History Mean Things]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing?v=1721164918</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing?v=1721164918"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T21:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Words and History Mean Things
Subtitle: A Response to “Addicted to Losing”
Date: 2024-05-02
Source: Retrieved on 2024-07-16 from https://bbnews.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/02/words-and-history-mean-things-a-response-to-addicted-to-losing/

 Most of what comes out in the text “Addicted to Losing” is not new. Black anarchists and anti-authoritarians have been critiquing black non-profits, Black academics, Black activists and black authoritarians for years before the 2020 uprising. Black anarchists who have been active PRIOR to 2020 have been deeply aware of these critiques, mainly based on their experiences. We are unsure how connected the author is to Black anti-authoritarians but, best believe Black anarchists been having these conversations. There has been so much ta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes my personal website looks like a bad photo of me]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8020</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/my-personal-website-looks-like-bad-photo-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T21:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stefan Bohacek writing on his Mastodon page: The problem with redesigning your personal website is that it looks great for about a week, and then you start to hate it. This is a problem of the ages. In the late 1990’s I’d redesign my websites (I had several back then) every few weeks. Or what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anarchist Library]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/special/index?v=1721150856</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/special/index?v=1721150856"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T17:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you in and/or from South Asia and literate in a South Asian language? 
 Check out the Initiative for a South Asian Anarchist Library and contact us in our chatrooms. 
 Also check out our guide on how to add a new language library. 
 There are also initiatives for an Arabic, Farsi, and Hungarian anarchist libraries. 
 Please contact us to get in touch with these initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Shower Incident 🦗🦗🦗]]></title>
        <id>https://usamainsights.com/morning-shower-incident/</id>
        <link href="https://usamainsights.com/morning-shower-incident/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T17:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⏱️ Takes about 3 minutes to read 
 

___________

Yesterday, when I woke up to go for work. I always take a shower & change cloths.
I was half sleep ironing my pant & shirt while yawning . Then, I went to bathroom to put my cloth on the hooks.
The bathroom door look like this ( I kinda trying my hand at pixel art)

Then I remember, I forgot to bring my towel. I went to get my towel and as I was putting the towel on the hook. I saw Grasshopper sitting on that hook .
My half sleep state was gone. My brain got in a panic mood, I cant move a muscle or scream. I knew if I did that it will fly and I dont want it to sit on me or near me. I slowly move one step at a time. Then, I slowly put my cloth and swiftly run from the bathroom after opening my door.
My grandma saw me shooting like a meteoroid from a bathroom. She worriedly inquired: is everything ok?
I told her that I saw grasshopper sitting on the door hook. My brother over heard my story as he was ironing cloth from a different room. I asked should I let it flew away or kill it by hitting with besom. He said smash the grasshopper with the besom.
I cant even say to my bro do it for me. :( Then with a bit of courage, I take a besom in my hand and went to a fight a ferocious battle for a noble cause  of disturbing my morning bath (hahha).
I was successful in my first strike but he was alive. He start to move that scared the shit out of me. After some more awful hitting it besom he died.
I felt both awful for killing it but cant have it flying it over my head or in my cloth. I even shudder just thinking about this event.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Finn: &ldquo;Same Blade&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/same-blade</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/same-blade"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T16:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palestine and Labourism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Lab: The secrets to keeping machine learning engineers moving fast]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21470</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/16/developer-tools/ai-lab-secrets-machine-learning-engineers-moving-fast/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T16:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The key to developer velocity across AI lies in minimizing time to first batch (TTFB) for machine learning (ML) engineers. AI Lab is a pre-production framework used internally at Meta. It allows us to continuously A/B test common ML workflows – enabling proactive improvements and automatically preventing regressions on TTFB.  AI Lab prevents TTFB regressions [...]
Read More...
The post AI Lab: The secrets to keeping machine learning engineers moving fast appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminating hardware with Load Balancing and Cloudflare One]]></title>
        <id>6690757a58eb3b000a367f33</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/eliminating-hardware-with-load-balancing-and-cloudflare-one"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is adding support for end-to-end private traffic flows to our local traffic management (LTM) load balancing solution, and allowing for the replacement of hardware load balancers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noah Crouch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q2 2024 Internet disruption summary]]></title>
        <id>6694b67558eb3b000a368051</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/q2-2024-internet-disruption-summary"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government directed shutdowns and cable cuts were both significant sources of Internet outages in Q2 2024. This post explores these disruptions, as well as others caused by power outages, maintenance, technical problems, military action, and unknown causes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Was Up with Grocery Prices?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30757</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/what-was-up-with-grocery-prices/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The consumer price index for groceries has risen more than the overall price index since the start of the pandemic, with a particularly large jump in 2022. In looking for explanations, a starting place is the behavior of raw commodity prices, which surged from early 2021 to mid-2022. In addition, wages for low-paid grocery workers have gone up faster than wages for the workforce as a whole. Finally, even though profit margins for grocery stores have gone up, the increase appears to be only a small contributor to the rise in food prices relative to the increase in their operating costs. This analysis suggests that the significant moderation in food inflation since the start of 2023 is due to still-high wage inflation for grocery workers being offset by the retreat in commodity prices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Klitgaard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by temporarely in "For advertising, Firefox now collects user data by default"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40975303</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40975303"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T10:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enough of this waiting for virtuous entities to address legitimate concerns of the public.
The "ad industry" is a cancer and we need legal protection against this "industry". The solution is political not technical and definitely can not be left to "the market".
Haven't you had enough?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>temporarely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[⭐️ i know love as a fading thing]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lost-dreams/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lost-dreams/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is inspired by Misha’s post a life lived diligently.
I started playing the piano when I was five. My first dream was to be a concert pianist like Lang Lang. I was drawn to the glitz and glamor of playing in cavernous concert halls to people in suits sitting on red velvet chairs. I let go of that dream a few years later when it became painfully apparent that I lacked both the talent and the dedication to fulfill it.
For a brief period after, I settled on a more realistic goal — playing the viola in a symphony orchestra. There were more orchestras than world-famous concert pianists, after all, and less violists than pianists to go around. I thought it a nice compromise between my childhood fantasies and reality.
Mom pulled the plug on my private lessons when I was seventeen, after …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crimsoneer in "The Delusion of the Polygraph"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40974648</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40974648"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T08:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who used to be a cop, this is absolute peak cops justifying the evidence not supporting their intuition by just making bullshit up.
If it actually worked, they'd have data and results.  But, spoilers, they don't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crimsoneer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a life lived diligently]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-life-lived-diligently/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-life-lived-diligently/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[two weeks ago, i had an existential crisis so bad, i had to take a leave from work. it was my first ever leave since joining the company in late february. i spent the evening rolling my thoughts around in the darkness of my room.
i started doing a lot of new things recently.
getting back into kpop
using actives in my skincare routine to curb my adult acne
mat pilates at home (i’ve been trying to do them daily, but it’s hard. some days just feel harder than others)
trying to lose weight healthily (a point proven difficult by my bulimia that’s graduated to restrictive eating (i barely have any full meals))
watching new kdrama to fill up my empty days
about the last point: i recently watched because this is my first life. in the show, we meet ji-ho, a 30 something who gave up on her dream to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Parker, Jane E Ferrie - Health and welfare]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tony-parker-jane-e-ferrie-health-and-welfare?v=1721112342</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tony-parker-jane-e-ferrie-health-and-welfare?v=1721112342"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Tony Parker, Jane E Ferrie
Title: Health and welfare
Subtitle: rejecting the state in the status quo — examples of an Anarchist approach
Date: December 2016
Source: International Journal of Epidemiology, Volume 45, Issue 6, December 2016, Pages 1754–1758, DOI: 10.1093/ije/dyx001

 For most of the 20th century, all mainstream political parties in Western Europe coalesced around the idea that, ultimately, the state should be the chief provider of social welfare and instrument of social reform. Although Feminist, Anti-Racist, Neo-Marxist, Green and other left-leaning critiques were put forward, particularly in the 1970s,[1] criticism of the welfare state has come predominantly from the free-market right. This has culminated in attacks on the direct provision of welfare by the state in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Stop Block Cop City!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Stop Block Cop City!
Date: 10/25/23
Source: https://berkmananarchy.noblogs.org/post/2023/10/26/stop-block-cop-city/

Tire fire barricade at the AirBnBs!
 Throw a molotov at the PowerPoint Presentations! Dump a smelly bucket of shrimp on the peaceful protest! We’re going to Stop Block Cop City!! 
 Why? 
 Because I’m mad that they wasted my time with their awful presentation/book-report/thinly-veiled-business-management-double-speak that tried to sell me and a bunch of other anarchists a program of non-violent civil disobedience to stop the police training facility from being constructed in the Old Prison Farm. 
I had to sit through:
 Being told about the history of the movement in a few awful slides 
 …know your fucking audience. 
 Being told not only about affinity…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nim Thorn - Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nim Thorn
Title: Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland
Subtitle: Tankies and Authoritarian Entryist Groups in Philadelphia
Date: July 10, 2024
Notes: From the original post: A general, group-by-group overview of some tankie and authoritarian entryist Left orgs in Philly (though partly relevant to other contexts; many are national groups), to help more autonomous, uncontrollable rebels better understand and defend against their manipulations. Includes some reflections and propositions at the end (‘Anti-Social Social War?’). pdf for reading pdf for printing
Source: Retrieved on July 15, 2024 from Reeking Thickets Press

Freedom from money, jobs, and education!
PSL (Party for Socialism and Liberation) and WWP (Workers World Party) and ANSWER Coalition (Act Now to Stop War and End …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating development feedback loops with AWS CDK hotswap deployments for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>ce26d458d598d4737adde02742504651c450ef09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/accelerating-development-feedback-loops-with-aws-cdk-hotswap-deployments-for-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T04:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Culture Amp is an employee experience platform that provides the insights into employee engagement, performance, and development that organizations need to build a category-defining culture. Culture Amp’s mission is to create a better world of work. Developer feedback loops An efficient developer feedback loop is a critical part of an effective development process – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoe Baker - What is the Proletariat?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T02:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zoe Baker
Title: What is the Proletariat?
Date: 2024/05/10
Source: Retrieved on 2024-07-16 from <anarchopac.com/2024/05/10/what-is-the-proletariat>

 In 1848 Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels published the Manifesto of the Communist Party. It famously ends by declaring, “let the ruling classes tremble at a communist revolution. Proletarians have nothing to lose in it but their chains. They have a world to win. Proletarians of all countries unite!” (Marx and Engels 1996, 30). The word proletariat continues to be used by socialists and communists today. This does not mean that the word is widely understood. Some people use it as a meaningless adjective whereby their ideas, attitudes, and activities are proletarian. Those of people they dislike are bourgeois. Others equate the proletaria…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anonymous - Train To Nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anonymous
Title: Train To Nowhere
Subtitle: Call for a week of world wide action and solidarity against the North Bothnia Line, August 11th to 17th, 2024!
Date: 2024
Source: https://de.indymedia.org/node/377193

1. THE NORTH BOTHNIA LINE
Why aiming at this beast?
 This is a call to action against the North Bothnia Line, a railway just beginning to be built along the coast of Swedish-occupied Sápmi. This project is a continuation of several hundred years of brutal colonization of the peoples and lands in Sápmi. Extractive industries are thriving on the increased demand for raw materials following the so-called “green transition”. This makes them continually stress the importance and urgency of the train line. So do the Swedish State and the European Union. 
 The track will be used f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seventy-five of the best sci-fi books, but I only ever read one]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8011</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/seventy-five-best-sci-fi-books-but-only-ever-read-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might be a fan of science-fiction stories, 2001: A Space Odyssey, Star Trek, Star Wars, and the like, but of the seventy-five titles listed by Esquire magazine, on their best sci-fi books of all time, I’ve only read one. The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy, by Douglas Adams. That’s it. 1984, by George Orwell? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions, great for IndieWeb, and, unfortunately, spammers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8007</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/webmentions-great-indieweb-unfortunately-spammers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T20:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions allow you to notify the publisher of a website that you’ve mentioned, or linked to, one of their pages, from your website or blog. Webmentions are commonly used in the Indie and Small Web communities, and have existed as a W3C recommendation since 2017. But Webmentions have also come to the attention of spammers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by modeless in "Run CUDA, unmodified, on AMD GPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40970717</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40970717"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T19:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people think AMD should support these translation layers but I think it's a bad idea. CUDA is not designed to be vendor agnostic and Nvidia can make things arbitrarily difficult both technically and legally. For example I think it would be against the license agreement of cuDNN or cuBLAS to run them on this. So those and other Nvidia libraries would become part of the API boundary that AMD would need to reimplement and support.
Chasing bug-for-bug compatibility is a fool's errand. The important users of CUDA are open source. AMD can implement support directly in the upstream projects like pytorch or llama.cpp. And once support is there it can be maintained by the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>modeless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Advanced capabilities in Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Q, and more (July 15, 2024).]]></title>
        <id>1fd3ff20bcccaf56da4bc38e70780bfd8ba588bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-advanced-capabilities-in-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-q-and-more-july-15-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T18:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[July 16, 2024: Updated link for “IDE workspace context awareness in Amazon Q Developer chat” As expected, there were lots of exciting launches and updates announced during the AWS Summit New York. You can quickly scan the highlights in Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2024. My colleagues and fellow AWS News […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Top 1% now have more wealth than the middle class]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45472</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/15/u-s-top-1-now-have-more-wealth-than-the-middle-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019
Subtitle: A collection of news, updates letters, texts and communiques
Date: 2019
Notes: This pamphlet has been put together by Act for freedom now. Check actforfree.nostate.net for updates in English.
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/SCRIPTA-pdf-2019.pdf>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Operation ‘Scripta Manent’ is one repressive operation among the many that have already occurred, and continue to occur, against comrades who dare to oppose the Italian State. The pretext here was of trying to find those who have taken part in Informal Anarchist Federation attacks since 2005, but it is also an attempt to destroy all insurrectional conflict in Italy and to cut off any solidarit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Putting into practice]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Putting into practice
Subtitle: Adding to the conversation on anarchist activity in Montreal
Date: March 21, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=26705>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 We’d like to respond with our thoughts to a text “Mise en Commun” (Putting in Common) that has been circulated critiquing insurrectionary projects and perspectives in Montreal. We appreciate that the authors of Mise en Common want to elaborate similarities and clarify differences, and move past bad faith. We’re taking this as an occasion to respond and to clarify ideas that we’ve been reflecting on for a few years now. We’ll try to use points of difference with Mise en Commun as an opportunity to delve further into ideas and how they inform practices, rather than…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Rain & Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Rain & Fire
Subtitle: Statement from a UK FAI sector
Date: September 13, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=6304>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This text was written during the course of the growing European social war, and our attempts to situate ourselves in the context of that, whilst in the midst of rising fascism, complicity from most of the society and a fractured and divisive anti-capitalist ‘movement’. These scant few pages cannot express the complexity of the various situations being described in any great depth, but we write so that other rebels at the edges can know how it is for us here. As we were putting the final touches to the text, cities in the UK exploded and remain volatile. However this is not an analysis of the riots –…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Fischer - An Essay on Total Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Fischer
Title: An Essay on Total Liberation
Subtitle: Marcusean Insights for Catalyzing Transformation
Date: 2024
Source: Building Multispecies Resistance Against Exploitation: Stories from the Frontlines of Labor and Animal Rights, edited by Zane McNeill (New York: Peter Lang, 2024)

 A 2021 study found that 56% of young people across ten countries believed “humanity is doomed.” The researchers rightly warned against narratives of “individualizing ‘the problem’ of climate anxiety, with suggestions that the best response is for the individual to ‘take action.’” However, they followed with the equally misguided suggestion that “such action needs to be particularly taken by those in power.”[1] Those of us influenced by Frankfurt School theorist Herbert Marcuse’s analysis consider…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism
Subtitle: 'Federation or Death'
Date: 2022
Notes: Anarchist Studies 30.1
Source: https://archive.org/details/05-anarchist-studies-30.1-pastellopoulos

Abstract:
 The article presents a first overview of the emergence and early development of anarchism in the Republic of Cyprus, utilising archival material. It contextualises Cypriot anarchism within the broader wave of political ideas making their appearance after the island’s de-facto partition in 1974, tracing the formation of the first anarchist groups and the circulation of early Cypriot anarchist publications. It moves on to briefly discuss three key historical moments of anarchist political expression, followed by an examination of early Cypri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)
Subtitle: “Cyprus Belongs to its Mouflons”
Date: 2017
Source: Retrieved on 23rd March 2022 from www.grin.com

Abstract
 This dissertation examines the structure of Cypriot anarchist ideology and the way it challenges Greek Cypriot ethnic nationalism, as it developed in the first decade following the partition of the island of Cyprus. It aims to contribute to the understanding of grass root political activity in Cyprus, by examining the early expressions of anarchism in the island. Ideology has been argued to function around the use of key discursive signifiers, through which the mediation of a fixed meaning is structured and social reality is experienced. This research…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - The only possible administration]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: The only possible administration
Subtitle: The question of cities
Date: October 4, 2018
Notes: “L’unica amministrazione possibile. La questione delle città”, “Vetriolo” #1, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=31586>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 These are times when it seems there are big discussions about the issue of cities, urban areas, about the possibilities of revolt inside them (even of living), of their reformability. Big discussions frequently focused on various topics relating to struggles carried out by many opponents, antagonists, often reformists, sometimes even by enemies of every order and authority; among these issues there is gentrification, a word not so unusual anymore, a word we now want to express some thoughts about. 
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should right to disconnect laws be scrapped because of lazy workers?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7997</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/should-right-disconnect-laws-scrapped-because-lazy-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne based Workplace Relations lawyer Paul O’Halloran, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald, on Australian “right to disconnect” workplace laws that come into effect on Monday 26 August 2024: Well, laziness is an increasing trend in the cases I defend for employers. Putting aside pandemic lockdowns where all sorts of things other than work were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell - Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: ‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell
Title: Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee
Subtitle: In solidarity with Monica Caballero and Francisco Solar
Date: November 20, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15603>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

We Are not Spectators but Enemies of all Forms of Dominion
 Today we wanted to give vent to a small anarchist impulse by brandishing the weapons of life and the ideas of rebellion. 
 As we are convinced that the status quo is being maintained not only by those who hold power but also by the servile attitude of those who tacitly support it, toady we decided to attack polling station 98a in the town of La Reina with an explosive/incendiary device. 
 The electoral committee is a piece of the democ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism
Subtitle: or: an imprecise definition of terms
Date: July 3, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 4th July 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 One time, maybe ten years back, I was on the DC metro with my family. My brother and I were happily talking about the feminist implications of GI Joe, because my brother is cool as hell, when a stranger looked over at my father (not knowing we were related) to complain about how I spoke. 
 “They really don’t teach people how to speak English anymore,” the stranger complained. 
 I’m not the world’s fighty-est person, but I’ve also never been the world’s least fighty person, so I confronted him immediately. “Oh?!” I asked. “What’s wrong with the way we’re talking?!” 
 He went on a tirade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Beniamino - Right you are… if you think you are]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anna Beniamino
Title: Right you are… if you think you are
Subtitle: Reflections and updates on a trial
Date: March 20, 2018
Source: actforfree.nostate.net>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 There’s not much to be said about an episode of repression, after all it’s the simple cyclical occurrence of action and reaction – or even on how repression plays dirty – another well-known fact. At most these are just a few notes on the development of techniques and strategies. 
 This I’ll try to do. More than a year after the arrests, with the trial already underway, a crack has opened in the censuring bell jar and the court papers been disclosed in all their misery after the short report on the last issue of Croce Nera and the latest developments on the closure of investigatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell - Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell
Title: Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)
Date: June 10, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?paged=174>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

PHOENIX PROJECT
Freedom for anarchists of praxis incarcerated in Italy
I ‘Return of the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire from the ashes’
 Only in those moments when our tension for freedom is rejoined with practice do we truly manage to live anarchy, here and now. Unfortunately the dream we carry in our hearts is too great to avoid the risk of finding ourselves up against the monstrous wall of authority raised in defense of the State and Capital. When we really put our life in play, inevitably we end up confronting the hardness t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity - Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity
Title: Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage
Date: January 27, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3553>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

The War Is on
 Today more than ever, the fortification of Power and it’s attack against the internal enemy becomes an urgent necessity. Under the fear of the oncoming rebellions and the dynamics that have been developed , mainly in the latest years, the Dominance has to protect it’s interests and will do it. 
 So, we ‘r leaving in an unprecedented upsurge of repression and control. Their mechanisms of chasing the enemy are being enforced and enriched in both human and technical level, while their legal arsenal expands and becomes more flexible. The new ‘anti-terror’ law that states thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial
Date: 2012
Source: <interarma.info/2012/02/02/dilwsi_xristou_tsakalou_synedriasi6/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 According to your court indictment, Conspiracy of Cells of Fire is a terrorist organization. But words were never, nor are or will ever be neutral. Words acquire the meaning given by the person who uses them. We do not speak the language of the judges and prosecutors. We speak the language of the hunted who have refused the victimʼs role, the wanted who have not handed themselves in to the authorities, the prisoners who have not caged their will for freedom, the anarchists who have never kneeled in front of Power. Solidarity, Dignity, Urban Guerrilla, Anarch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Letter about persecutory procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Letter about persecutory procedures
Date: May 10, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=4537>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

On the 27th of April, Christos Tsakalos, for the case of C.C.F. with the upgraded charge of the managerial executive, was transported to the prisons of Koridallos, after a call for appearance at the juridical council, where he denies to appear.
 Today therefore, Wednesday the 27th of April, I announce officially to the juridical authorities, to not “bother me again” with their repeated calls for my presence in the interrogative process, because they will receive my total refusal and my factual contempt. 
 There is not even a millimeter of dialogue to be shared with my judges. 
 As I have declared repeatedl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAFE Boulder - Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: SAFE Boulder
Title: Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside
Date: July 12th, 2024
Notes: We created this zine to hand out alongside ice packs and gatorade as a deadly heatwave swept accross our region. At time of posting, that heatwave is continuing east across North America, and more will certainly follow in the coming months and years as the climate crisis worsens. While this zine contains a couple sentences specific to so-called Boulder Colorado, it should still be broadly applicable, and we encourage people to print and distribute it anywhere that’s affected by extreme heat. We note that the advice contained within is not particularly useful without the supplies needed to follow it, and we recommend accompanying this zine with water, electrolyte powder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc - Against the Logic of the Guillotine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc
Title: Against the Logic of the Guillotine
Subtitle: Why the Paris Commune Burned the Guillotine—and We Should Too
Date: April 8, 2019
Source: Retrieved on June 11, 2019 from https://crimethinc.com/2019/04/08/against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine-why-the-paris-commune-burned-the-guillotine-and-we-should-too

 148 years ago this week, on April 6, 1871, armed participants in the revolutionary Paris Commune seized the guillotine that was stored near the prison in Paris. They brought it to the foot of the statue of Voltaire, where they smashed it into pieces and burned it in a bonfire, to the applause of an immense crowd.[1] This was a popular action arising from the grassroots, not a spectacle coordinated by politicians. At the time, the Commune controlled Paris, which was st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Dining with Vultures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Dining with Vultures
Subtitle: Bristol Anarchists & the UK Media
Date: 2015, February
Source: Retrieved on July 13, 2024 from https://darknights.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/13/dining-with-vultures-bristol-anarchists-the-uk-media/

 The purpose of this piece is to better understanding of mass media’s relationship to rebels (including anarchists of all stripes), in general as well as in the context of a repressive atmosphere in Bristol. As well as raising local specifics, it hopes to encourage stronger awareness around wider issues of representation and counter-insurgency. 
 It will speak critically, even harshly when deemed necessary, of some self-professed radicals’ interactions with the establishment – but not out of an impulse for character-assassination. Contrary t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: house martins]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52864</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sunday-photoblogging-house-martins/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my issue with online interactions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The longer I am off of any social media and not constantly bombarded with the language and digital mannerisms inherent to it, the more I notice how odd it feels to detect that kind of language in others outside of those timelines and feeds.
I am active in very few Discord servers and most of them are small, friends-only groups. However, in the few public ones I am in, I often see groups of people whose choices of words and how to express themselves, how to enter conversations, their tone and views make them feel eerily... unreal. I've thought about it, and the best way I could describe it is as if someone trained AI on the most active Twitter users. There is a specific flavor of overly cool, casually careless, sarcastic, flippant, at times vitriolic undertone to everything that is hard to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sex, lies and Videotape]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52862</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sex-lies-and-videotape/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T06:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What to do when we can’t trust our own eyes (or at least, the videos we are looking at. I spoke last weekend at a panel discussion on Navigating Lies, Deepfakes & Fake News, organised by McPherson Independent. This a group promoting the idea of an independent community candidate in the electorate of McPherson south of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>