<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-07T12:39:55.685Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-07T12:39:55.685Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Swift]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52856</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/07/sunday-photoblogging-swift-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T07:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent many hours trying to take pictures of these over the past three years and have a large collection of indistinct blurs as a result. But I went back to basics, studied the camera setting, watched a bunch of “how to” videos on YouTube and actually managed this one:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Awaited Bear Media Center]]></title>
        <id>https://jbrr.dev/long-awaited-bear-media-center/</id>
        <link href="https://jbrr.dev/long-awaited-bear-media-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope I'm not telling any tales out of school. If I am, bring the lifetime ban hammer down on me hard, Herman.
A recent update has exposed an experimental media library in your Bear dashboard. It was committed two weeks ago, so this might be old news, but this is a considerable improvement for general ease of use.
The URL is https://bearblog.dev/<subdomain>/dashboard/media/ and should look like this.

Pro Tip: Use the Customize Dashboard functionality to add a link in your footer for easy access.
Excellent work, Herman, as always!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genocide Then and Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327237</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/07/genocide-then-and-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T05:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times has been justifiably criticized, as you probably know, for its anti-Palestine bias in covering Israel’s war on Gaza. But you may not know that the Times building is located near Manhattan’s theater district. This is why a lot of show people tend to walk past the Times, and why my friend, […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Genocide Then and Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susie Day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migration is Not a Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327186</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/07/migration-is-not-a-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T05:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jocelyn Nungaray, a 12-year-old from Texas, was recently found dead in a creek near her home. Video footage from a convenience store and interviews with neighborhood residents led police to two men whom they later arrested. Both suspects are undocumented migrants from Venezuela. Her murder immediately became a narrative about the savagery of illegal aliens […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Migration is Not a Crime appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Slager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tonyarkles in "The magic of small engineering teams"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40892151</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40892151"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T18:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most interesting discussions I've had around this was at a small company who mass-hired a bunch of people from a big company. We went round and round in circles for a while because of issues similar to what you're describing. I ran a small 4-6 person hardware team (softly blurry on the edges) and the new people wanted significant amounts of design and documentation review as well as financial oversight. We needed $40 worth of solder and connectors and had to wait a week for PO approval as well as demonstrate that we had gotten multiple quotes... even though there was just a store down the block that sold exactly what we needed.
Anyway, after a month or two of this I started catching significant flak because my team was nowhere near as productive as it used to be. Complaining about slow POs was met with "maybe you should plan better". Complaining about design reviews for one-off boards that would go from idea-to-problem solved was met with "you're engineers, you need to document your work". It was painful and I came very close to resigning.
What ultimately worked, though, was figuring out a catch phrase that spoke the language of the new people: "accountability without authority". This ruffled some feathers but once I repeated "you are trying to hold me accountable for delivering a $500,000 project on time but are not giving me authority to buy $40 worth of stuff to execute on that" enough times it finally got through and the system started to change. But man did it suck for a while.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tonyarkles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You've Got Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T17:44:04.350Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading Veronique's post this afternoon, Just A Small Town Girl, and smiled at her lovely doodles. But there was one that caught my eye and then, brought a lump to my throat. It featured a stamp and the words, Post Air Mail. And it hit me. I hadn't had any real mail from anyone (not including birthday or Christmas cards) not since my mum passed back in 1999.
It sent a shiver down my spine not just because that was over 20 years ago, but because, the last handwritten letter I ever got, was from a dead woman: my mother.
Where ever I was in the world, travelling and or working, my mother almost religiously took time out of her day to write an aerogramme to me. Do you remember those? You buy them at any post office, singularly or in packs. I think my mother had a draw full of them—after …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwup238 in "First anode-free sodium solid-state battery"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40891799</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40891799"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T17:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The difference in their geochemistry is substantial so even if chromium isn't technically that much more abundant, it's significantly easier to mine.
The Gibbs free energy of formation for chromium oxides and chromite is much more negative than for lithium-bearing minerals so Cr compounds are thermodynamically favored to precipitate out of melts and solutions, forming minerals with high concentrations that then get pushed up by other processes. Li+, with its lone valence electron, just doesn't form strong bonds or highly stable mineral phases in comparison. On top of that the diffusion coefficients for Cr species in magmas and rocks are generally orders of magnitude lower than for Li. Cr gets locked into crystal structures early and stays put, while Li keeps migrating and diffusing in the form of water soluble minerals. There's also a whole biogeochemical cycle for Cr involving microbes that can concentrate it in sediments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwup238</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Human Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327368</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/06/moving-human-targets/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T14:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ This week’s Israeli seizure of nearly five square miles of land in the Jordan Valley of the occupied West Bank is the largest land grab in the more than three decades since the signing of the Oslo Accords. First, the lands were declared “closed military zones,” then the Netanyahu government reassigned them as “state […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Moving Human Targets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The joy of not knowing]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/joy-not-knowing/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/joy-not-knowing/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pete Doherty's reflection on happiness in the documentary Pete Doherty: Stranger in My Own Skin struck a chord with me:
Maybe happiness is not being able to know what’s gonna happen. Maybe if we knew the end of the story there wouldn’t be anymore story.
Thought-provoking. As if happiness is not essentially a phenomenon in itself, but rather the absence of something else: expectations, assumptions, preconceptions...
So much of our unhappiness would never take hold if we focused on the present instead of trying to predict the future. So much of our disappointment would more or less evaporate if we focused more on what we have than on what we think we lack.
This doesn't mean we should stop setting goals. We can continue to look forward with excitement and evolve along the way. This continuous journey is the real goal, not the imaginary endpoint that we may or may not make a brief stop at along the way.
Seeing the beauty and forward momentum of never reaching a final destination, perhaps this is the essence of true, lasting happiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by supermatt in "Apple okays Epic Games marketplace app in Europe"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40888774</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40888774"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T07:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That third party app stores are subject to review by apple is a problem in itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>supermatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelnos in "YouTube's eraser tool removes copyrighted music without impacting other audio"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40886120</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40886120"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T21:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess it's good that there's a new solution to this problem, but I wish it just wasn't a problem in the first place.  It's ridiculous that someone can't just walk around outside, making a video of what they're doing, and post it, without having to worry that some copyrighted music is playing in the background for some portion of it.
That sort of situation should be considered fair use, and copyright owners who attempt to make trouble for people caught up in this situation should be slapped down, hard, and fined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelnos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by inopinatus in "PostgreSQL and UUID as Primary Key"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40885948</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40885948"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T20:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best advice I can give you is to use bigserial for B-tree friendly primary keys and consider a string-encoded UUID as one of your external record locator options. Consider other simple options like PNR-style (airline booking) locators first, especially if nontechnical users will quote them. It may even be OK if they’re reused every few years. Do not mix PK types within the schema for a service or application, especially a line-of-business application. Use UUIDv7 only as an identifier for data that is inherently timecoded, otherwise it leaks information (even if timeshifted). Do not use hashids - they have no cryptographic qualities and are less friendly to everyday humans than the integers they represent; you may as well just use the sequence ID.  As for the encoding, do not use base64 or other hyphenated alphabets, nor any identifier scheme that can produce a leading ‘0’ (zero) or ‘+’ (plus) when encoded (for the day your stuff is pasted via Excel).
Generally, the principles of separation of concerns and mechanical sympathy should be top of mind when designing a lasting and purposeful database schema.
Finally, since folks often say “I like stripe’s typed random IDs” in these kind of threads: Stripe are lying when they say their IDs are random. They have some random parts but when analyzed in sets, a large chunk of the binary layout is clearly metadata, including embedded timestamps, shard and reference keys, and versioning, in varying combinations depending on the service.  I estimate they typically have 48-64 bits of randomness. That’s still plenty for most systems; you can do the same. Personally I am very fond of base58-encoded AES-encrypted bigserial+HMAC locators with a leading type prefix and a trailing metadata digit, and you can in a pinch even do this inside the database with plv8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>inopinatus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Barnay: &ldquo;Gaucho-Lepénisme?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On France’s far-right vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gcp123 in "Let's stop counting centuries"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40884673</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40884673"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T17:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author makes a good point. "1700s" is both more intuitive and more concise than "18th century". 
The very first episode of Alex Trebeck's Jeopardy in 1984 illustrates how confusing this can be:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KDTxS9_CwZA
The "Final Jeopardy" question simply asked on what date did the 20th century begin, and all three contestants got it wrong, leading to a 3-way tie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gcp123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Seymour: &ldquo;Majority Without a Mandate&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why so serious?]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/why-so-serious/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/why-so-serious/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently did work in the Swedish archipelago. So beautiful! On days like that, it's hard to believe you're at work.
This time, the sky opened up, and the rain poured down for a short while. The sky looked amazingly powerful as I stood on the shore and looked out over the ocean.
It's stunning how small you feel at times like this. Not only that, but your worries and problems also feel small. Things that you otherwise attach great importance to suddenly don’t feel all that important there and then. You just stand there with your smallness somewhere in the vastness of the universe and marvel — everything stops.
A few hours later, I stepped ashore, jumped on my bike, and felt how everyday life was slowly but surely making its way back…
"I have to stop at the grocery store on the way home. Oh, I almost forgot; I have to do laundry today. I wonder if I can make it to the gym. On the last day of the month, I have to remember to report my working hours. Oh yeah, I have to log and send in my expenses for the month.”
Things that need to be done. They don’t get done by standing and staring straight up at the sky in an attempt to make them small enough to disappear.
But now and then, we can try to remind ourselves of the emptiness that surrounds all these little musts and problems. Our inner, limitless space can teach us not to take everything so seriously.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK election day 2024: traffic trends and attacks on political parties]]></title>
        <id>6687ef98a4598c000bd710d0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/uk-election-day-2024-traffic-trends-and-attacks-on-political-parties"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we explore the dynamics of Internet traffic and cybersecurity during the UK’s 2024 general election, highlighting late-day traffic changes and a post-vote attack on a political party]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Familiar Faces&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The photography of Johny Pitts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "I have no constructor, and I must initialize"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40882247</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40882247"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T12:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Always obligatory https://mikelui.io/img/c++_init_forest.gif]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by marton78 in "I have no constructor, and I must initialize"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40881928</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40881928"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T11:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After almost 20 years of experience with C++, there are still some gnarly details I wouldn't have imagined. What a God awful language!
Kudos to that author for the great, eye catching title and the in depth detail!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>marton78</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bye bye, Tories, hello what?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52851</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/05/bye-bye-tories-hello-what/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T09:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the UK, we’re all waking up to the prospect of a new government. The election was an oddity: Labour has converted a modest 35% vote share into a whopping Parliamentary majority; the Tories did somewhat better than suggested, on around 24%, but have lost more than two-thirds of their MPs. (The final figures were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Presidential Debate Harmed US Foreign Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327205</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/how-the-presidential-debate-harmed-us-foreign-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T06:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s Biden-Trump debate harmed U.S. foreign policy, and the international community was left to debate what was said and what was left unsaid.  In view of the harmful potential for wider wars in East Europe and the Middle East in addition to the potential for China’s increased military pressure on Taiwan, it is shocking that only ten minutes of the 90-minute debate was devoted to national security policy.  The inept CNN moderators—Jake Tapper and Dana Bash—were partly responsible because of the dearth of questions on foreign policy.  Nevertheless, the answers provided by President Joe Biden and former president Donald Trump were shocking for their misinformation and their polemics.   More
The post How the Presidential Debate Harmed US Foreign Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animal Factories: On the Killing Floor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327256</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/animal-factories-on-the-killing-floor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T06:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up south of Indianapolis on the glacier-smoothed plains of central Indiana. My grandparents owned a small farm, whittled down over the years to about 40 acres of bottomland, in some of the most productive agricultural land in America. Like many of their neighbors they mostly grew field corn (and later soybeans), raised a few cows and bred a few horses.
More
The post Animal Factories: On the Killing Floor appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say It Ain’t So, Joe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327179</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/say-it-aint-so-joe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On screen, Biden looked and sounded like a somnambulist whose only connection to politics was a haphazard, recited laundry list of federal programs that have saved everyone from unwed mothers to homeless veterans, but at least the president came to the debate with malice toward none (Gazans might have been the exception), while from the other lectern Trump was little more than a fountain of bile. More
The post Say It Ain’t So, Joe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharon Revisited: Netanyahu’s Ultimate Aim in Gaza and Why It Will Fail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327322</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/sharon-revisited-netanyahus-ultimate-aim-in-gaza-and-why-it-will-fail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel never learns from its mistakes. What Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is trying to implement in Gaza is but a poor copy of previous strategies that were used in the past by other Israeli leaders. If these strategies had succeeded, Israel would not be in this position in the first place. The main reason  More
The post Sharon Revisited: Netanyahu’s Ultimate Aim in Gaza and Why It Will Fail  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paniai, West Papua: Politics of Displacement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327105</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/paniai-west-papua-politics-of-displacement/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As in Palestine, much of the displacement in West Papua is caused by settlers, but this time funded by the World Bank. Respectably called “transmigration” and officially lasting until 2015, this policy affects Kalimantan, Sumatra, Sulawesi, and Maluku but, above all, West Papua because the transmigrants aren’t Melanesian, so the possibility of ethnic and religious strife is high. More
The post Paniai, West Papua: Politics of Displacement appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unbelievable Stories About the Children of Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327333</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-unbelievable-stories-about-the-children-of-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story should not be real. It was the morning of January 29, 2024. The Israeli military had already bombed substantial parts of the affluent Tel al-Hawa neighborhood in Gaza City, including—in October 2023—the totality of the Gaza City campus of the Islamic University of Gaza. Following a warning from the Israeli military, seven members  More
The post The Unbelievable Stories About the Children of Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trusting the “Five Eyes” Only]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327317</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/trusting-the-five-eyes-only/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wherever he travels globally, President Biden has sought to project the United States as the rejuvenated leader of a broad coalition of democratic nations seeking to defend the “rules-based international order” against encroachments by hostile autocratic powers, especially China, Russia, and North Korea. “We established NATO, the greatest military alliance in the history of the  More
The post Trusting the “Five Eyes” Only appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael T. Klare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawmakers Abandon Congress – Maybe That is a Good Thing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327135</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/lawmakers-abandon-congress-maybe-that-is-a-good-thing/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A record number of Congress members will leave government come November, so many that the New York Times published an article May 30 bemoaning the phenomenon. But maybe it’s not so terrible. Maybe we’ll be better off without the people who gave us the Select Committee on (bashing) China, the (anti) Patriot Act, the trillion-dollar  More
The post Lawmakers Abandon Congress – Maybe That is a Good Thing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phrases for Thought: July 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327182</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/phrases-for-thought-july-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The linkages between phases are not “right” or “wrong,” but rather suitable or unsuitable, useful or superfluous, meaningful or senseless.” – Jean-Francois Lyotard, The Differend: Phrases in Dispute If Biden runs and wins, we go along with an order of things established in his first term, an order of things structured and carried out by  More
The post Phrases for Thought: July 4, 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dismantling of Democracy: A Grim Projection of American Fascism Under Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327236</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-dismantling-of-democracy-a-grim-projection-of-american-fascism-under-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The guardrails of democracy have been blasted into dust. The Supreme Court’s ruling on presidential immunity grants presidents carte blanche to commit crimes as long as they act within their “constitutional authority.” Welcome to gangster capitalism. Trump, the convicted felon, white nationalist, white supremacist, and aspiring dictator, can rest assured that his dream of unaccountable  More
The post The Dismantling of Democracy: A Grim Projection of American Fascism Under Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Weaponization of Open-Source Information]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327270</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-growing-weaponization-of-open-source-information/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within a day of the June 2, 2024, release of a video documenting the abuse of prisoners of war by a Russian soldier in Ukraine, open-source intelligence (OSINT) researchers had identified the Russian citizen and his involvement in Ukraine going back a decade. Ukrainian officials subsequently sent letters to the International Committee of the Red Cross and the  More
The post The Growing Weaponization of Open-Source Information appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism and the Academy Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327040</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/zionism-and-the-academy-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Background The background should be uncontroversial. Israel was created by terrorism, facilitated by prior settler colonialism under a British umbrella, and not by the UN General Assembly ‘partition’ Resolution 181 (II) of 29 November 1947 (Suárez 2017a; Suárez 2017b). The majority vote was obtained by great powers realpolitik, by threats (including letter bombs) and  More
The post Zionism and the Academy Revisited appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court’s Immunity Ruling Gives President’s George III-like Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327264</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/supreme-courts-immunity-ruling-gives-presidents-george-iii-like-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you hadn’t read the news in four years — or just arrived from another galaxy — the Supreme Court’s de facto grant of immunity to Donald Trump for his alleged federal crimes might sound almost reasonable. There are “unique risks,” six right-wing justices warned, that if a president were required to answer criminal charges, his energies would be  More
The post Supreme Court’s Immunity Ruling Gives President’s George III-like Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitchell Zimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extreme Inequality is a Threat to Free Speech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327269</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/extreme-inequality-is-a-threat-to-free-speech/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a student in the late 2000s when I had my first brush with “cancel culture.” A campus group had invited Nick Griffin — a racist Holocaust denier and leader of a fascist British political party, among other charming things — to speak. Many shocked students, including me, called Griffin’s views vile and warned  More
The post Extreme Inequality is a Threat to Free Speech appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Certo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stolen Land, Stolen Lives: Israel’s War on Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327196</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/stolen-land-stolen-lives-israels-war-on-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Zionists have always lusted after Palestine, but loathed its people.  Today is no exception. Ever since the birth of organized Zionism in 1897, its adherents have been bent on establishing a Jewish majority on a land not theirs and populated with a Palestinian Arab majority. Following the prison break of the Islamic Resistance Movement,  More
The post Stolen Land, Stolen Lives: Israel’s War on Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refusing the Language of Silence: Palestinian Resistance Goes Digital]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327197</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/refusing-the-language-of-silence-palestinian-resistance-goes-digital/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an increasingly familiar contradiction: digital platforms that position themselves as an accessible alternative to corporate media emerge as new censors in their own right. Social media and the internet make it possible to disseminate material that would otherwise have been suppressed, thereby helping to bring alternative conversations to the fore of mainstream awareness. And  More
The post Refusing the Language of Silence: Palestinian Resistance Goes Digital appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar Zahzah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French European Soccer Nationalism Transcends Xenophobia, at Least for the Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327189</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/french-european-soccer-nationalism-transcends-xenophobia-at-least-for-the-moment/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Impressive far-right anti-immigration electoral gains caused French President Emmanuel Macron to dissolve the French National Assembly and call for snap legislative elections. But on the soccer pitch, all right-wing talk of “invading hordes” disappeared as French fans cheered on their national team led by players of foreign origin in the quadrennial European soccer tournament. Successful  More
The post French European Soccer Nationalism Transcends Xenophobia, at Least for the Moment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 1930s Business Plot Redux: This Time Success!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-1930s-business-plot-redux-this-time-success/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:52:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard about the rumblings that happened during the FDR New Deal era that came from the business oligarchs. They were not pleased with the notion of any federal relief to mitigate the ongoing depression misery in the United States during the 1930’s. Some things certainly never change. Anyway, the banker-friendly oligarch types  More
The post The 1930s Business Plot Redux: This Time Success! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can the Democrats “Rehabilitate” Kamala Harris? They May Have No Choice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327267</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/can-the-democrats-rehabilitate-kamala-harris-they-may-have-no-choice/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like it or not, if Joe Biden does decide to step down, or is somehow forced out of office, there’s only one person who can possibly replace him:  VP Kamala Haris.  Thanks to the Democrats’ abject refusal to pressure Biden to step aside last year, and to Biden’s own Mexican-style kibosh on the idea of  More
The post Can the Democrats “Rehabilitate” Kamala Harris? They May Have No Choice appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fukushima’s Forever Quagmire of Radiation Hazards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327329</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/fukushimas-forever-quagmire-of-radiation-hazards/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earthquakes routinely threaten reactor site The dumping of radioactive wastewater from the rubbished Fukushima nuclear reactor site in Japan was suspended for a day last March, after a 5.98-magnitude earthquake struck off the coast of the site, the Malaysia Star and Arab News Japan report. Tokyo Electric Power Co. (Tepco) said through a spokesperson that  More
The post Fukushima’s Forever Quagmire of Radiation Hazards appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scab of a Nation-4th of July 2024 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327327</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/scab-of-a-nation-4th-of-july-2024-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been on the road most of the last three weeks. Right now, River Shook’s new disc Revelations with their band Sarah Shook and the Disarmers is playing in the car. The Disarmers replaced a couple of members since their last disc, providing a more rounded sound. Likewise, the lyrics are perhaps a bit more  More
The post Scab of a Nation-4th of July 2024 Edition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Presidential Debate That Wasn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327216</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-presidential-debate-that-wasnt/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the days immediately following the first US presidential debate between Joe Biden and Donald Trump, countless analyses have appeared. Nearly all have focused on the candidates’ delivery, less on what they said, and almost nothing about what should have been but was not said. Trump was obviously coached by his team to tone down  More
The post The Presidential Debate That Wasn’t appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Rasmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Science Fiction Can Inspire Climate Activism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327261</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/how-science-fiction-can-inspire-climate-activism/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is, by far, the biggest story of our era, an existential threat that has already profoundly affected life on Earth and promises to change it even more radically over the next few centuries. As our most pressing problem, it has inspired numerous non-fiction texts—news articles, science journalism, documentaries, academic monographs, and pop-science books  More
The post How Science Fiction Can Inspire Climate Activism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katherine Dolan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Madness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327331</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/supreme-court-madness/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a millionaire or billionaire, the United States in 2024 is a dream nation. Super rich Americans have converted the country from a permanent war “middle class” society to a permanent war oligarchy with monarchical greed and ambition. The Supreme Court favors the metamorphosis of the more or less democratic United States to  More
The post Supreme Court Madness appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Paradox of Public Health Situations That Worsen With Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327266</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/the-paradox-of-public-health-situations-that-worsen-with-climate-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Louisiana’s “Cancer Alley,” where the air is thick with pollutants and asthma rates are alarmingly high, a troublesome irony is unfolding. This region is home to sprawling petrochemical plants and toxic fossil fuels that disproportionately affect the respiratory health of the area’s majority-Black residents. Here, inhalers — one of the key tools for managing  More
The post The Paradox of Public Health Situations That Worsen With Climate Change appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rev. Lennox Yearwood Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gilded Age Organ Riches from long A. G. O. and Last Week]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327382</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/gilded-age-organ-riches-from-long-a-g-o-and-last-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From last Sunday evening through yesterday afternoon, some 2,000 organists have been shuttling around the San Francisco Bay Area for a program of lectures, workshops, and concerts. This installment of the bi-annual convention of the American Guild of Organists (A. G. O.) concluded with a Fourth of July solo recital by the American organist and  More
The post Gilded Age Organ Riches from long A. G. O. and Last Week appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let Canada Live Up to Its Name of Kanata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327106</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/let-canada-live-upt-to-its-name-of-kanata/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel greatly honored  with this honorary doctorate from Queen’s University in Kingston, Canada. But I have a little confession to make. When I first read your letter of invitation, the first words  that jumped in my mind were Kingston, Queens, and Canada. I thought there was a mistake. I used to love the song,  More
The post Let Canada Live Up to Its Name of Kanata appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ngũgĩ wa Thiong’o</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threads first birthday gift to users: advertising?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7958</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/threads-first-birthday-gift-users-advertising/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Break out the coffee and the cake: a celebration is on the cards. Tomorrow, Threads, Meta’s answer — and much needed foil — to X/Twitter, notches up its first birthday. I was there as the platform began rolling out, and managed to score (just) a relatively low (five-figure) badge number. 98,522 for the record. These […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by duffpkg in "Batteries: How cheap can they get?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40877710</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40877710"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T20:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lifepo4 (lithium iron phosphate) batteries for the home are pretty cheap as of today. Power storage for residential use in a 48v metal rackable linkable system with battery management system (BMS) is $89/kwh shipped/duty paid from reputable chinese suppliers CATL/Seplos etc. You have to wait for sea shipping, add $30/kwh if you want to buy it in the US today.
From the same suppliers sodium batteries are currently $130/kwh and about 26% less efficient in the same form factor. I look forward to this changing.
Due to rising power costs I moved one of my homes completely to solar and battery (lifepo4) and haven't had any problems. I can't imagine ever going back to the power company. Panels have gotten to the point of being ridiculously cheap. I have a lot of space. I purchased pallets of used panels for more or less the cost of transportation ($34 per panel 270w). They produce about 85% of their nominal rating.
I mention this because other comments mention costs that are much much higher.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>duffpkg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Schiphol in "Gravitational wave researchers cast new light on Antikythera mechanism mystery"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40877288</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40877288"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T19:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paper [here](https://bhi.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/07-HJJuly24-AOT...) makes it clear that these researchers (whose main topic is gravitational waves) have used Bayesian analyses to estimate how likely different counts for holes present in the full calendar ring are. This is cool, but the bit about "techniques developed to analyse the ripples in spacetime" is, well, making reference to Bayesian analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Schiphol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pembrook in "Twilio confirms data breach after hackers leak 33M Authy user phone numbers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40876410</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40876410"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T17:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While this sucks, my phone is in so many data breaches at this point it doesn’t matter.
The spam-to-ham ratio on my phone number is now far worse than any other channel for me. The traditional phone network is at risk of going the way of the fax machine if we don’t do something about the spam problem like we did with email.
If I’m on a call, even with family, it’s now almost exclusively on FaceTime/zoom/meet/etc. I can’t remember the last time I talked on the traditional phone network or received a legitimate call. Which isn’t great because those aforementioned platforms are all proprietary walled gardens with terrible incentives — once they capture the market fully they will eventually dump ads all over your calls. Don’t believe me? Just look at what Gmail did to monetize the lock-in on your inbox.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pembrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[William Gillis - What’s In A Slogan? “KYLR” and Militant Anarcha-feminism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/william-gillis-what-s-in-a-slogan-kylr-and-militant-anarcha-feminism?v=1720111778</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/william-gillis-what-s-in-a-slogan-kylr-and-militant-anarcha-feminism?v=1720111778"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T16:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: William Gillis
Title: What’s In A Slogan? “KYLR” and Militant Anarcha-feminism
Date: June 25, 2024
Notes: William Gillis: https://twitter.com/rechelon
Source: Retrieved on July 4, 2024 from https://c4ss.org/content/59691

 An anarchist walks out of a punk show to smoke. On her vest are anarchist patches with various standard slogans, “No Gods No Masters,” “Death To Transphobes,” “Kill Your Local Rapist,” “All Cops Are Bastards,” “Punch Nazis,” “From The River To The Sea Palestine Will Be Free,” “Make Total Destroy,” “The Only Good Cop Is A Dead Cop,” “Eat The Rich,” “Death Before Detransition” and… “Fire To The Prisons.” 
 A suddenly red-faced bystander trots up to her to argue. 
“Oh so you’re saying you support a blanket social policy of allowing anyone to burn anything they accus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 30, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240704</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240704"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare 1.1.1.1 incident on June 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>668519cda4598c000bd709a9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-1111-incident-on-june-27-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 27, 2024, a small number of users globally may have noticed that 1.1.1.1 was unreachable or degraded. The root cause was a mix of BGP (Border Gateway Protocol) hijacking and a route leak]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryton Herdes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by adamgordonbell in "Jeffrey Snover and the Making of PowerShell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40874156</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40874156"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Host here, thanks for sharing.
PowerShell faced extreme opposition at Microsoft, and its creator Jeffrey Snover was demoted for pursuing it.
Jeffrey was originally brought into Microsoft to help MS learn how to compete in the data center, but culturally they were so tied to the personal computer model of the world, that they fought him every step of the way.
Edit: Another interesting thing, is how Powershell exists because Windows isn't file based. Jeffrey's goal was server administration, but on Windows you can't just edit files to administer things, you need to call various APIs and get structured data back forth. The rich object model fell out of that. It was the only way.
( Also, apologies if the transcript has errors. I've gone from professional transcriptions to Descript and then a pass of GPT4 trying to find the right punctation breaks and then me doing a quick read through. I don't think its coming out as high quality as I'd like. )]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adamgordonbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read: Theory and reality in economics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45462</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/04/weekend-read-theory-and-reality-in-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll So, certainly, both non-theorists and some theorists have little patience for research that displays mathematical ingenuity but has no value as social science. But defining this work exactly is impossible. This sort of work is like pornography quite simple to recognize when one sees it. Jeffrey Ely As researchers, we (mostly) want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broken Britain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Broken-Britain</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Broken-Britain"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UK citizens vote in a general election on 4 July. The opinion polls currently forecast that the incumbent Conservative party will be heavily defeated after 14 years in government. The opposition Labour party is expected to gain a majority of over 250 seats, a record landslide, with the Conservatives getting less than 100 seats. 
English

/ 
United Kingdom, 
Capitalism, 
Inequality, 
Inflation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by febeling in "Shipt’s algorithm squeezed gig workers, who fought back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40873472</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40873472"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T09:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had similar thoughts. But let's not overlook the information asymmetry, which contributed to the dissatisfaction. I don't want to live in a world which is controlled unilaterally, and intransparently by a group of people who assume they have a full picture of the situation and assume they understand moral completely, and also don't think it necessary to explain how they think so highly of themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>febeling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MB Sundjata - How and Why the US Left Betrayed Tigray]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mb-sundjata-how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray?v=1720081541</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mb-sundjata-how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray?v=1720081541"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T08:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: MB Sundjata
Title: How and Why the US Left Betrayed Tigray
Subtitle: US organizations like PSL and Black Alliance for Peace cannot be trusted to advocate for Palestine’s liberation after they condemned nearly a million Tigrayans to genocide.
Date: June 18, 2024
Source: Retrieved from <redvoice.news/how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray> on July 3, 2024

 I thought further and said: “Why do men lie over problems of such great importance, even to the point of destroying themselves?” and they seemed to do so because although they pretend to know all, they know nothing. Convinced they know all, they do not attempt to investigate the truth. — Zara Yacob of Aksum (Tigray), 17th-century philosopher, in The Hatata Inquiries
 (Content Warning: this article describes acts of genocide and w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False identities]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/false-identities/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/false-identities/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I heard an interview with Rachel "Yoga Girl" Bråthén. She talked about how certain things in her past, like being vegan, became a kind of identity. It was all or nothing. "This is me. This is who I am. End of story!"
It's easy to get too attached to that kind of self-image, whether it's advocating for healthy eating or reviewing cell phones.
Looking back, I can relate to this myself. Yoga, meditation, mindfulness, weight training, blogging, and more have all served as a “false” sense identity for me at some point — at least to some extent.
Of course, it's not what we do that's the problem; it's how we see ourselves in relation to what we do. You can have a million followers and still be the most grounded person in the world.
No matter how "important" or "unimportant" our roles in life are, it's good to remind ourselves of this truth from time to time. Status and possessions come and go, but who we are on a deeper level remains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Di fraye arbeter shtime Editorial Board, An Anonymous Group of Polish Anarchists, Eyshe Beirich - Yiddish Anarchists’ Break Over Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-di-fraye-arbeter-shtime-editorial-board-an-anonymous-group-of-polish-anarchists-yiddish-ana?v=1720078025</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-di-fraye-arbeter-shtime-editorial-board-an-anonymous-group-of-polish-anarchists-yiddish-ana?v=1720078025"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T07:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: The Di fraye arbeter shtime Editorial Board, An Anonymous Group of Polish Anarchists, Eyshe Beirich
Title: Yiddish Anarchists’ Break Over Palestine
Date: 1929
Notes: An exchange in the anarchist newspaper Di fraye arbeter shtime after the 1929 Hebron massacre offers a case study in Jewish discourse and political reaction after immense violence. 
 Introduced and translated from the Yiddish by Eyshe Beirich
Source: Retrieved on 04/07/2024 from https://jewishcurrents.org/yiddish-anarchists-break-over-palestine-1929

On Friday, August 23rd, 1929, exaggerated rumors about the extent of Jewish violence against Palestinians and the desecration of holy sites in Jerusalem reached the Palestinian community of Hebron (Al-Khalil, in Arabic). What started as incensed Palestinians throwing stone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vouwfietsman in "The saddest "Just Ship It" story ever (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872836</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872836"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T06:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> It's worth repeating: Unless you have a stake in the company, it is NOT your job to make sure the company is the most profitable it can be. Your job is to create great software
This is a terrible take, and one I generally see as a signal of lack of seniority in a software dev. It is absolutely everybody's job in the company to make sure it is profitable, unless you work for a non-profit.
The thing is though, that profitable is not the same as "just ship it". If you're in a company where those things are conflated frequently, that's a sign of lack of seniority in management.
> Your job is to create great software
It really isn't, your job is to make a great product. Making a great product often, but not always, requires great software. Many great products have terrible software behind them. The tension between product, sales and development should result in a compromise that creates the most value short, middle and long term. It is 100% your job as a developer to understand what can and cannot be hacked, what priorities the company has beside delivering great software, and finally: when great software must be made, because compromise is unwise.
Just like the boy who cried wolf, the developer who can never compromise on software quality is powerless when there is an actual reason to not compromise on software quality, and rightfully so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vouwfietsman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by or_am_i in "Shipt’s algorithm squeezed gig workers, who fought back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872802</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872802"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T06:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am not defending Shipt and there is no doubt gig workers are in a very vulnerable position. However, the data analysis results as presented in the article do not support the article's main point. "40% are getting paid at least 10% less" is not unnatural to expect whenever pay is redistributed, especially since some 30+% are getting at least 10% more. Imagine a _hypothetical_ situation where Shipt is 100% on point and driving a fairer version of the algorithm patch removing a way for workers to "optimize" for short, well paid trips, resulting in pay cuts to those who had learnt how to do it, while not changing/increasing pay for everyone else. We would see the same kind of result: some portion of workers would get paid 10% less, some 10% more. This does show that workers are paid differently for the same work they have been doing, but does not prove the change is unfair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>or_am_i</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The indie web is saving my sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/the-indie-web-is-saving-my-sanity/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/the-indie-web-is-saving-my-sanity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T04:13:14.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of my posts have covered stuff I don't ever have the time of day to talk about. I work too much and almost all of my coworkers are conservative boomers. I don't talk to most of them  much but every once in a while I'll have to share a store with some of them. Sometimes they give me random phone calls. Luckily I have the option of just not picking up the phone.
I just don't relate with the people I have to interact with on the regular. I mean we aren't having heavy political conversations 24/7 but it just doesn't feel comfortable being around people who you know are the polar opposite of who you are.
I feel like being able to write about the stuff I never get to talk about is a healthy counterweight to that. I'm not a great writer, I know a lot of the stuff I write won't be read for weeks, or possibly ever. Some of it might be boring or come across cheesy. Sometimes I cover really broad, uninteresting things.
But it has had the unexpected effect of making me feel more valid as a person. It feels odd saying that, but it's true.
Maybe it's because I haven't had a hobby I can get lost in for too long. Making the rounds in different indie web neighborhoods, learning little bits of CSS and bringing my vision to life one piece at a time does a pretty good job at keeping me from getting bored and letting my mind wander to stress. Then when I'm done with that for a while I can write some more. Sometimes I'm proud of it, sometimes I delete it after a couple hours.
It feels... healthier than doomscrolling. I prefer this over traditional social media because of the ownership and freedom, and the fact that I sort of get to whisper what I'm saying rather than blasting it over a megaphone and putting myself on stage in front of an audience riding algorithmic dopamine waves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hansvm in "Beating NumPy matrix multiplication in 150 lines of C"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872149</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872149"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T03:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[- OpenBLAS isn't _that_ optimized for any specific modern architecture.
- The matrices weren't that big. Numpy has cffi overhead.
- The perf difference was much more noticeable with _peak_ throughput rather than _mean_ throughput, which matters for almost no applications (a few, admittedly, but even where "peak" is close to the right measure you usually want something like the mean of the top-k results or the proportion with under some latency, ...).
- The benchmarking code they displayed runs through Python's allocator for numpy and is suggestive of not going through any allocator for the C implementation. Everything might be fine, but that'd be the first place I checked for microbenchmarking errors or discrepancies (most numpy routines allow in-place operations; given that that's known to be a bottleneck in some applications of numpy, I'd be tempted to explicitly examine benchmarks for in-place versions of both).
- Numpy has some bounds checking and error handling code which runs regardless of the underlying implementation. That's part of why it's so bleedingly slow for small matrices compared to even vanilla Python lists (they tested bigger matrices too, so this isn't the only effect, but I'll mention it anyway). It's hard to make something faster when you add a few thousand cycles of pure overhead.
- This was a very principled approach to saturating the relevant caches. It's "obvious" in some sense, but clear engineering improvements are worth highlighting in discussions like this, in the sense that OpenBLAS, even with many man-hours, likely hasn't thought of everything.
And so on. Anyone can rattle off differences. A proper explanation requires an actual deep-dive into both chunks of code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hansvm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sfink in "The joy of reading books you don't understand"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872077</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40872077"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T03:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This reminds me of something that I heard once from a Chinese teacher. I can't vouch for the accuracy of it, but he was definitely on to something: In the West, it is assumed that it is the speaker's job to make himself understood to his listeners. In the East, it is the other way around.
In recent times, it seems like we've gotten even more extreme. The speaker or writer must not only spoon-feed the understanding, they also have to provide the motivation and the entertainment. Which I find sad, because some things you can't get unless you go to the effort of extracting them yourself. (See many reproducible psychology findings about retention being highly correlated with depth of processing, for example.) It's like the information equivalent of highly processed food.
I find myself falling into this trap on sites like this. An interesting but difficult article will be posted, I won't immediately know what to think or where I stand on the topic, and I'll flip to the comments so that I can get some part of the collective to tell me what to think and how to feel about it. Which is also sad.
In paintings, it is known that the viewer can get out more than the painter put in. It used to be the same with writing, but it feels like that is becoming more rare and less acceptable. If a reader can't follow the argument, it's automatically the author's fault and a waste of the reader's time. Heaven forbid the reader might need to exert some effort and grow in the gleaning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sfink</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anarhija.info - Horror Vacui]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-horror-vacui?v=1720049426</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-horror-vacui?v=1720049426"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anarhija.info
Title: Horror Vacui
Date: February 10, 2018
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=29728>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 There are anarchists who run after uprisings on other continents wherever the spotlights of the media fall. There are anarchists who talk about “fortress Europe” and they don’t even know which States are part of the EU. There are anarchists who struggle against the borders and they don’t even know where the Schengen frontier runs. There are anarchists who, like “good white men”, see in the “dark-skinned” non-EU people potential comrades, and they don’t even notice that there are European non-EU people. 
 There are anarchists who talk about internationalism and they don’t even know (or don’t give a fuck) what happens on their own conti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anarhija.info - Aut Aut]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut?v=1720049269</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut?v=1720049269"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anarhija.info
Title: Aut Aut
Date: 2016
Source: <anarhija.info/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut-en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 When I translated and published the pamphlet "Individuality and the anarchist group", signed by one of the CCF cells, Guerilla Urbana Cell, I added in a note that I didn’t do it because I agree with the content, but to make public how much this project, in my opinion, has turned away from its original form of tension to propose (or re-propose) an anarchist individualism which, in some ways, can be found in the pages of a different insurrectionist theory, but in this case approaching or even in some points leading to formal ideas, that is the formal organization. 
 Similar proposals (informal platform, structured and specific organization…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adriano - Communiqué from prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adriano-communique-from-prison?v=1720049064</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adriano-communique-from-prison?v=1720049064"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Adriano
Title: Communiqué from prison
Date: April 9, 2014
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=16535>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Violence generates violence. Regardless of what is right or wrong, no matter how abstruse is the boundary between opposites and how easily they can converge. The word violence and the concept it expresses present deep mystifications to those who have the monopoly on it. All expressions of dissent are being disproportionately repressed… no surprise… ‘go and tell them that it’s springtime’ [rough translation of ‘vagli a spiegare che è primavera’, a verse by the late anarchist singer and song-writer Fabrizio De Andrè]. 
 The modus operandi of cops and politicians is infamous enough, with their artistic architecture made of inexistent cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potentially habitable Earth size planet forty light years away]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7951</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/potentially-habitable-earth-size-planet-forty-light-years-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the good news. Tory Shepherd, writing for The Guardian, says the recently discovered exoplanet, dubbed Gliese 12b, might be able to host liquid water. We all know what that means. If there’s water, there may be life. Gliese 12b is so named because it orbits a star called Gliese. Now for the bad news. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by LarsDu88 in "AI's $600B Question"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40869863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40869863"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T20:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Jensen it takes about 8000 H100s running for 90 days to train a 1.8 Trillion param MoE GPT-4 scale model.
Meta has about 350,000 of these GPUs and a whole bunch of A100s. This means the ability to train 50 GPT-4 scale models every 90 days or 200 such models per year.
This level of overkill suggests to me that the core models will be commoditized to oblivion, making the actual profit margins from AI-centric companies close to 0, especially if Microsoft and Meta keep giving away these models for free.
This is actually terrible for investors, but amazing for builders (ironically).
The real value methinks is actually over the control of proprietary data used for training which is the single most important factor for model output quality. And this is actually as much an issue for copyright lawyers rather than software engineers once the big regulatory hammers start dropping to protect American workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LarsDu88</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring to Serverless: From Application to Automation]]></title>
        <id>0b8bd15cb28746b280e7ed11144ffd013485b5aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/refactoring-to-serverless-from-application-to-automation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T20:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refactor serverless apps by swapping application code with cloud automation: reduce costs, decouple logic from architecture, and leverage managed services' native capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sindhu Pillai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by philshem in "Tour de France: How professional cycling teams eat and cook on the road"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40868717</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40868717"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "The food I make is all transparent," says (chef) Blandy. "There are no rich sauces, it's all plain, simple cooking with a light amount of seasoning, light amount of oil, fresh herbs and citrus.
That’s some top-notch nominative determinism.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nominative_determinism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>philshem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by iforgotpassword in "The Cheapest NAS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40868676</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40868676"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My secret protip: old Fujitsu desktop/nuc PCs. At least in Germany (Europe?) they are cheap on ebay since a lot of businesses use them and upgrade on a regular schedule.
If you care about power consumption like I do, you can Google "$model energy consumption white paper" which contains very accurate data about idle usage, for example https://sp.ts.fujitsu.com/dmsp/Publications/public/wp-energy...
In one case I had a nuc where on Linux after enabling power saving features for the sata controller, idle usage even fell to 5W when the pdf claimed 9.
Having an actual pc instead of a random sbc ensures best connectivity, expandability, and software support forever. With almost all sbcs you're stuck with a random-ass kernel from when the damn thing was released, and you basically have to frankenstein together your own up-to-date distro with the old kernel because the vendor certainly doesn't care about updating the random armbian fork they created for that thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iforgotpassword</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Social Media Cause Anything?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52847</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/03/does-social-media-cause-anything/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 18 months since I quit Twitter, I can feel the atrophy of my vibe detector. I’m reading more than ever, on Substack and the FT, Discord and group chats — much of the same “content” I would’ve encountered on Twitter, in fact, but without the ever-present spiderweb of the social graph, the network […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Myself Beyond the Trading Floor]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/market-to-me/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/market-to-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*** Add your email below if you’d like to get access to our overnight momentum trading chat! Free for a month, then $6/month.
In it, you’ll find both retail and proprietary traders. Guys who work(ed) for SMB, KTG, Avatar, Chimera & Seven Points that you can network and trade alongside with.
Subscribe to my blog
Over the last 7 years, I have exclusively focused on trading. Well, to be fair, it's more so the last 5 years. The first 2 years as a retail trader, I had one of those so called "well-rounded lives". I traded, went out often, hung out after the close with friends & fam, enjoyed snowboarding, camping, and mountain biking more than most.
But, over the last 5 years as a professional trader living in NY and ATX and working out of both offices, I gave up everything, one by one to focus e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Blog Tips & Tricks Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-blog-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-blog-tips/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been here before, you may have visited the Blog Inspiration page. It contains a lot of good and useful resources when it comes to blogging: writing, design, blog challenges, webrings, shortcuts...
Now there's one more: Bear Blog.
It's the blogging platform I use and love. It's also used by many of my favorite bloggers and some of my readers. In other words, it deserves its own Bear section.
These are currently on the list (those marked with * requires an upgraded account):
Convert bear blog CSV exports to markdown files
Random link (external)
Random link (internal) *
Add external link markers
Add a search feature *
Estimated reading time *
Customizing the upvote button
Count your posts
Adding a "reply via email" button
Adding a private feedback box *
Do you have suggestions for things to include? Or maybe you have an idea for a "hack" you would like someone to put together?
Contact me and I will add it to this post.
Happy Bear blogging! 🐻
PS. For official changes and feature suggestions, see the changelog and roadmap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code June 2024 Release (1.91)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by notresidenter in "Proton launches its own version of Google Docs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40865594</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40865594"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Paying customer)
I wish they would focus more on their existing product(s). There's a huge synergy between Calendar and Mail, but Drive, Pass, VPN, are useless (but the VPN is well-done). There's still no Caldav support or scheduling, and a lot of things are annoying in Mail, of course some of these are hard to solve with E2E, but at this point, their E2E claim is also half-baked and mostly for marketing, why not fix all of things?
What's the rationale behind releasing yet another half-baked product?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>notresidenter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First round of French election: party attacks and a modest traffic dip]]></title>
        <id>66853348a4598c000bd709b9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/first-round-of-french-election-2024-party-attacks-and-a-modest-traffic-dip"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare mitigated DDoS attacks targeting French political parties during the 2024 legislative elections, as detailed in our ongoing election coverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Declare your AIndependence: block AI bots, scrapers and crawlers with a single click]]></title>
        <id>668274eea4598c000bd707cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/declaring-your-aindependence-block-ai-bots-scrapers-and-crawlers-with-a-single-click"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help preserve a safe Internet for content creators, we’ve just launched a brand new “easy button” to block all AI bots. It’s available for all customers, including those on our free tier]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distributional Consequences of Responding Aggressively to Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30686</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/on-the-distributional-consequences-of-responding-aggressively-to-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post discusses the distributional consequences of an aggressive policy response to inflation using a Heterogeneous Agent New Keynesian (HANK) model. We find that, when facing demand shocks, stabilizing inflation and real activity go hand in hand, with very large benefits for households at the bottom of the wealth distribution. The converse is true however when facing supply shocks: stabilizing inflation makes real outcomes more volatile, especially for poorer households. We conclude that distributional considerations make it much more important for policy to take into account the tradeoffs between stabilizing inflation and economic activity. This is because the optimal policy response depends very strongly on whether these tradeoffs are present (that is, when the economy is facing supply shocks) or absent (when the economy is facing demand shocks).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Keshav Dogra, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thrance in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40864609</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40864609"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T10:28:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember seeing a talk from Jonathan Blow where he made a comparison: in the 1960s top engineers worked for NASA and put a man on the moon in a decade, basically doing computations by hand. 
Today, we have super advanced computers and tech companies enjoy 100× times more of the top engineers than NASA ever had, and they are all working toward making you click on ads more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thrance</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structural Adjustment and the Washington Consensus Are Not Abandoned in 2000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T09:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by otherme123 in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863965</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863965"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T08:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The guy writes a post about how to send spam effectively, and then offers the subscription link in the end with "Promise we won't spam you". Yes, I totally trust you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>otherme123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ossyrial in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863919</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863919"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T08:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author links to the somewhat dystopian blog where the email sender is quite proud of their work. Their words (or perhaps that of an LLM):
> Could an AI agent craft compelling emails that would capture people's attention and drive engagement, all while maintaining a level of personalization that feels human? I decided to find out.
> The real hurdle was ensuring the emails seemed genuinely personalized and not spammy. I knew that if recipients detected even a whiff of a generic, mass-produced message, they'd tune out immediately.
> Incredibly, not a single recipient seemed to detect that the emails were AI-generated.
https://www.wisp.blog/blog/how-i-use-ai-agents-to-send-1000-...
The technical part surprised me: they string together multiple LLMs which do all the work. It's a shame the author's passions are directed towards AI slop-email spam, all for capturing attention and driving engagement.
How much of our societal progress and collective thought and innovation has gone to capturing attention and driving up engagement, I wonder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ossyrial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by taylorius in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863586</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863586"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T07:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future - megawatts of electricity being used, 24/7 as armies of LLMs email and debate each other, and try to sell each other programs at a great discount.
As for the humans, we went fishing instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>taylorius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian bookseller Booktopia in voluntary administration]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7947</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-bookseller-booktopia-voluntary-administration/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T03:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is sad and concerning news. The Melbourne based bookseller had become well ensconced in the Australian literary realm, since being founded about twenty-years ago. The company, which is also listed on the ASX (though trading of shares has been suspended), had been struggling financially in recent years though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Han Ryner - Ethical Individualism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T01:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Han Ryner
Title: Ethical Individualism
Subtitle: Selected Texts
Date: 2019
Notes: Translated from French to English by Kirk Watson.

Translator’s Introduction
 At the dawn of the 20th century, Europe hosted a brief blossoming of individualistic thought. Inspired by the great thinkers of the preceding century such as Stirner, Ibsen, Nietzsche, and Spencer, they offered a free-thinking, non-dogmatic alternative to the increasingly powerful Marxists and syndicalists of the left, and the economists and theologians of the right. Importantly, this generation of thinkers developed the critique of the State into a critique of society as a whole, which immunized them from recruitment by the anarchist movement. As Ryner says in the Handbook, the anarchists are naive: victory by the anarchist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize your Java application with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>405bbc736a74a4576b2623243a568f24e835610b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/modernize-your-java-application-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations have critical legacy Java applications that are increasingly difficult to maintain. Modernizing these applications is a necessary, daunting, and risky task that takes the focus off of creating new value or features. This includes undocumented code, outdated frameworks and libraries, security vulnerabilities, a lack of logging and error handling, and a lack of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chetan Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Shevek - Leave, Or Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Lee Shevek
Title: Leave, Or Else
Subtitle: Giving Ultimatums to Abuse Victims
Date: April 10, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2 July 2024 from butchanarchy.medium.com/leave-or-else-a60b0dbac2a6

 Abuse is ubiquitous in our society, and as a result there are very few among us, if any, who have not been abused themselves or in proximity to someone else being abused. Myths about why and how abuse occurs run rampant and the ones that dominate are ones that ultimately serve in the maintenance of the status quo that keeps victims disempowered and silent. As a result, even those few who do actually believe victims of abuse and see the danger such abuse poses to them still often respond to the conditions the victim is entrapped within in ways that ultimately affirm the abuser’s narrative and fur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I like your old music better than your new music]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7938</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-old-music-better-than-new-music/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might say that of U2, whose music I once really liked, especially the stuff they did in the nineties. Achtung Baby. Zooropa. Pop. Even 2000’s All That You Can’t Leave Behind. These albums mostly represented their electronic music phase. I’d have them on loop for days at a time. I drew the ire of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Blogroll, or to not?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really love the idea of having a Blogroll. When checking out a new blog, after reading and perusing said blog, I typically check to see if it has one. I think it’s one of the best ways to find new people to subscribe to, new content to read, and/or new perspectives to be exposed to. However, I don’t have one on my blog. Hypocritical? Maybe. Or maybe it’s just really personal preference.
I grew up in the days of MySpace, and this irrational want to be included in everyone’s Top 8. Then when you’re in their Top 8, you watch that list like a hawk in case you drop from Top 2 to Top 5, or even worse, drop off altogether. Granted, blogrolls are a bit different since there’s no hard limit on how many can be included (or specified order), but the idea is similar.
You see, I’m fine and OK with no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postroll]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/postroll/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/postroll/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Postroll
Looking for something to read?
Here's a rolling list of posts, blogs, and links that I've been enjoying. Links will roll off (from the bottom) when the list hits 30 posts and will be highlighted in my Week Notes for posterity purposes.
Want to learn why I opted for a Postroll instead of a Blogroll? Read the explanation here.
How Smolweb principles can foster more authentic online connections by Adële
The indie web is saving my sanity by gru:Bz
You've Got Mail by Alexandra
I am a grateful thief by Cornelius
Everyone Should Blog by Xandra
Theme Machine: A CSS Color Palette Tool by Keith Grant
We Can Be Free by Nathan Peterson
You have the mission by Riley
The Art of Dreaming as We Grow Up by Yordi
Am I doing it wrong? by Forking Mad
Some thoughts on killing your blogroll by rscottjones
a Polaroid summer project by VMB
This list was last modified {{ post_last_modified }} ago]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by erva in "Pattern of brain damage is pervasive in Navy SEALs who died by suicide"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40856990</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40856990"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T14:21:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualifier: Former US special operations operator that served in multiple wars.
My anecdotal take is there are many ways that shock and trauma can accumulate through training and war that are far beyond the minimal effects of an M4.
Firearms: While the primary weapons systems are the M4 and side arm (pistol), there are many weapons systems utilized by special operations such as sniper rifles, crew serve weapons, and niche small arms.
The M82 sniper rifle shoots a 50 BMG round. In either the bolt action or semi-auto versions they feel like you are getting punched in the face when you shoot them.
Crew serve weapons like the MK19 and M2 do pack a punch.  The MK19 is a machine gun that shoots 40mm grenades.  The M2 is a .50 cal machine gun.  These weapons systems are mounted, but the percussion of them is still far greater than an M4.
More niche arms like the M249 SAW, M16 HBAR, full-auto AKs, M240 Golf, MP9, etc are not as mild as the standard M4/M16.
Blasts: There are many types of blasts encountered such as Mortars (inbound and outbound), Flash Bangs, Entry charges, IEDs, Landmines, etc.  These do make your head ring if you are close enough to them.
In my own personal experience there are many other daily jarring events that aren't nearly as sexy to talk about.  Riding in the back of a 5 ton will almost shake your brain out of your head.  Riding in an LCAC (hovercraft) is like riding in a 5 ton.  Doing boat work in Zodiacs will bounce you all over the place, especially when doing surf passages.  Doing hydrographic surveys right where the surf breaks will pound you for hours and make you a little sick afterwards. When your chute opens on a jump, if jumping round chutes, will make you see stars...the landing is not a soft pretty one like rectangle chutes...you hit the ground hard.
There are many more ways your body gets pounded on a daily basis far in excess of the weapons you use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>erva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[micro tool to convert bear blog csv exports to markdown files]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/micro-tool-to-convert-bear-blog-csv-exports-to-markdown-files/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/micro-tool-to-convert-bear-blog-csv-exports-to-markdown-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#b2md{border:2px dotted var(--border-color);padding:20px}.b2mdcontainer{display:flex;justify-content:space-between;align-items:center}.b2mdcontainer input{order:1}.b2mdcontainer button{order:2}#InfoText{color:#8a2be2;font-size:90%;margin-bottom:0}.image-container{position:relative;display:inline-block}.modal,.toggle-input{display:none}.b2md-img{transition:transform .3s}@media (min-width:700px){.b2md-img:hover{transform:scale(1.05)}}.modal{position:fixed;z-index:1000;left:0;top:0;width:100%;height:100%;overflow:auto;background-color:rgba(0,0,0,.8)}.modal-content{background-color:#fefefe;margin:2% auto;padding:20px;border:1px solid #888;width:80%;max-width:700px;box-shadow:0 4px 8px rgba(0,0,0,.2);color:var(--text-color)}@media (prefers-color-scheme:dark){.modal-content{background-color:#012…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aryanam - Funeral, Theocracy, & Religious Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-funeral-theocracy-religious-capital?v=1719921893</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-funeral-theocracy-religious-capital?v=1719921893"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aryanam
Title: Funeral, Theocracy, & Religious Capital
Subtitle: Observations & Thoughts After a Comrade’s Death
Date: March 10th, 2024
Source: asranarshism.com/1402/12/20/funeral-theocracy-religious-capital-en

 An accident. An accident tore a family apart. An accident took a brave and kind comrade from us. We will remember the date. It was December 2023. 
 Death will come for us all. But, for now, we must put our shattered hearts back together. We need to organize. We need to fight. We need to grieve. Yet, we are not free to grieve, the same way we are not free to be. Not free to love. Not free to live. Countless surviving families and friends were vultured in one of their most vulnerable times. Countless victims of patriarchal honor killings were buried by their murderers. Count…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sheffield Action Group - What is School?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sheffield-action-group-what-is-school?v=1719921860</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sheffield-action-group-what-is-school?v=1719921860"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sheffield Action Group
Title: What is School?
Date: February 2024
Notes: From Sheffield Action Group’s Troublemakers zine, this important piece stands on its own

 As students at university, we have a lot more to say about the global and national role of our institutions — this will come at another point. For now we will focus on primary and secondary school. Many reading this will have left 13 years of schooling, likely hating most of it, and may not have thought a lot about the scale of its impact on our lives and how things could have been so, so different. 
 School is a class stratifier along eugenic lines. Those deemed more intelligent by their ability to absorb and spit out information in tests are seen as more suited for higher paying jobs and therefore, by this society’s lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Znore - Hermetic Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/znore-hermetic-anarchism?v=1719921672</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/znore-hermetic-anarchism?v=1719921672"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Znore
Title: Hermetic Anarchism
Subtitle: Othering the Other, Uttering the Otter and Uddering the Author
Date: 2014
Source: groupnameforgrapejuice.blogspot.com

I. Hermetic Anarchism and Othering the Other
 Imagination is a magic carpet 
 Upon which we may soar 
 To distant lands and climes 
 And even go beyond the moon 
 To any planet in the sky 
 If we came from nowhere here 
 Why can’t we go somewhere there? 
 Sun Ra – Imagination 
 I end up spending a lot of time in Jimbocho, the old bookseller’s district in Tokyo. Hours and hours I rifle through piles and stacks of dusty pulp hunting for gems. Usually my luck is good, and occasionally I find just the book that I need. There are two shops in particular, both specializing in used English books, where uncanny things can happen. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ersilia Cavedagni - The Woman]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ersilia-cavedagni-the-woman?v=1719921475</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ersilia-cavedagni-the-woman?v=1719921475"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ersilia Cavedagni
Title: The Woman
Date: 28 October 1899
Notes: Published in The Unstoppable Anarchist Ersilia Cavedagni & Her Selected Writings (pp. 32-34) at <thetransmetropolitanreview.files.wordpress.com> (PDF).
Source: Retrieved on 18 March 2024 from thetransmetropolitanreview.wordpress.com.

 Generally men, rightly or wrongly, claim to have an intellectual and moral superiority over women, in addition to physical superiority. So be it! I want to grant it. 
 Strangely enough, in the vast majority of cases the man who considers himself superior to the woman takes little or no effort to reduce her inferiority and to raise the woman to his level. 
 This happens more especially among men who have a wife or partner. It would be logical that, if only out of a feeling of pride, the h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Barnsley - If it Was Easy They Wouldn’t Call it ‘Struggle’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-barnsley-if-it-was-easy-they-wouldn-t-call-it-struggle?v=1719921397</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-barnsley-if-it-was-easy-they-wouldn-t-call-it-struggle?v=1719921397"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mark Barnsley
Title: If it Was Easy They Wouldn’t Call it ‘Struggle’
Subtitle: Mark Barnsley Talks About Repression and Resistance in British Prisons
Date: 2005
Source: <zinelibrary.files.wordpress.com/2016/01/barnsley.pdf>

 Mark Barnsley has been involved in the Anarchist movement all his adult life, spending time fighting in Lebanon, editing The Sheffield Anarchist, supporting striking miners, confronting fascists, and spending 10 years in prison. Held in 20 different maximum or high security prisons, and 18 different segregation units, he has always taken the fight to the Enemy in jail. Released from prison in 2002, Mark continues to be as active as ever, speaking all over Europe, and being involved in the Campaign Against Prison Slavery, the Anarchist Black Cross, and many oth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Barnsley - Palestinian Resistance veteran Mark Barnsley on why he joined up]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/palestinian-resistance-veteran-mark-barnsley-on-why-he-joined-up?v=1719921176</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/palestinian-resistance-veteran-mark-barnsley-on-why-he-joined-up?v=1719921176"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mark Barnsley
Title: Palestinian Resistance veteran Mark Barnsley on why he joined up
Date: 2009
Source: <duncanpickstock.co.uk/index.php/videos/testament>

 And they said, oh, are you the the lads that have come to fight in Lebanon? And we said yeah, that’s us. And we sat in the back of this Peugeot car and I remember Lero nudging me, and there was a handgun underneat the dashboard and there was a butt of what was a Kalashnikov underneath one of the seats. So I was like, well, this is the real deal isn’t it? 
Mark Barnsley fought with The Palestinian Resistance between 1978 and 1980
 Well, before I started school, me and my sister, who’s 18 months younger than me, used to on a Friday, we would go to town with my mum, to meet her mother, our grandma and we’d get dragged around the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antithesi - The Ecological Crisis and the Rise of Post-Fascism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antithesi-the-ecological-crisis-and-the-rise-of-post-fascism?v=1719921075</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antithesi-the-ecological-crisis-and-the-rise-of-post-fascism?v=1719921075"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antithesi
Title: The Ecological Crisis and the Rise of Post-Fascism
Date: January 28, 2024
Notes: Translated into English and posted by Illwill on February 17th, 2024
Source: Retrieved on March 19th, 2024 from https://illwill.com/antithesi.

 The ecological crisis profoundly impacts the material conditions of social reproduction, extending beyond “natural disasters” to encompass a deepening of the contradictions inherent in capitalism. This crisis does not only manifest itself in events like floods, droughts, and pandemics, it also plays a direct role in fueling conflicts, social unrest, and mass displacement. In what follows, we attempt to lay out a comprehensive argument for the connection between the ecological crisis and the rise of what we call the post-fascist current, a poli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pranay Somayajula - nationhood beyond nationalism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pranay-somayajula-nationhood-beyond-nationalism?v=1719920998</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pranay-somayajula-nationhood-beyond-nationalism?v=1719920998"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pranay Somayajula
Title: nationhood beyond nationalism
Subtitle: towards an anarchist politics of anticolonial liberation
Date: December 29th, 2023
Source: Retrieved on March 25th, 2024 from https://www.culture-shock.xyz/p/nationhood-beyond-nationalism.

 In its Spring 2001 issue, the Oregon-based magazine Green Anarchy ran an anonymous article with the title: “The EZLN is NOT Anarchist: Or Struggles at the Margins and Revolutionary Solidarity.” Writing from an anarchist perspective, the author advanced a fierce critique of the Zapatista National Liberation Army—the militant anticolonial, anticapitalist Indigenous movement which had led an uprising and established autonomous zones in southern Mexico several years before, and which is often cited by anarchists as an example of a suc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imanol - Blind Spot]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/imanol-blind-spot?v=1719920664</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/imanol-blind-spot?v=1719920664"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Imanol
Title: Blind Spot
Subtitle: Manuel Huet and the libertarian underground in France
Date: 2023
Notes: Translated by Paul Sharkey from El Angulo Muerto : Manuel Huet y la clandestinidad libertaria en Francia.
Source: English translation published by the Kate Sharpley Library www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 
 
 The Kate Sharpley Library aims to preserve the history of the anarchist movement and record and commemorate the lives of the people who made up the movement. It’s always good to see other people plugging away at the same task. The first translation of a piece by Imanol that we put up was ‘The Massana Gang’ which went in KSL: Bulletin of the Kate Sharpley Library No. 97–98, February 2019. Since then we’ve been glad to host translations of his studies from El Salto which are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harsha Walia - What Is Border Imperialism?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/harsha-walia-what-is-border-imperialism?v=1719919583</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/harsha-walia-what-is-border-imperialism?v=1719919583"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Harsha Walia
Title: What Is Border Imperialism?
Subtitle: Excerpt from Undoing Border Imperialism
Date: 2013
Source: Undoing Border Imperialism. AK Press / Institute for Anarchist Studies, 2013. Pages 35 to 74.

What Is Border Imperialism?
 The world was born yearning to be a home for everyone. 
 —Eduardo Galeano, “Through the Looking Glass: Q & A with Eduardo Galeano” 
 For the past several years, Indigenous organizations in Australia have been issuing “Original Passports” to asylum seekers who have been detained or denied legal status by the Australian government. Most recently, in May 2012, passports were issued to two detained Tamil asylum seekers. During the ceremony, Ray Jackson of the Indigenous Social Justice Association said, “The Australian Government must stop imprisonin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frott - Bulldoze SCI Rockview]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/frott-bulldoze-sci-rockview?v=1719918854</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/frott-bulldoze-sci-rockview?v=1719918854"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frott
Title: Bulldoze SCI Rockview
Subtitle: Abolition, Prisoner Support, and Resistance to Genocide in PA-DOC
Date: 4/7/24
Notes: 4/7/24 The Final Straw Radio — Episode Transcription
Source: https://ia600308.us.archive.org/5/items/tfsr-202404072024-SCIRockview/Bulldoze-sci-rockview.pdf

 Intro SCI Rockview is a prison in central Pennsylvania where incarcerated comrades have been facing repression for demanding justice in the face of impunity by racist COs and following a year of prisoner deaths due to institutional toxicity and guard violence. We speak to an outside supporter about the situation at Rockview, the reactions of administration, inside / outside relationships and solidarity that have flared up. We hope that this conversation contributes to increased and thickened ties …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Israel is pioneering new methods of genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-israel-is-pioneering-new-methods-of-genocide?v=1719918743</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-israel-is-pioneering-new-methods-of-genocide?v=1719918743"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Israel is pioneering new methods of genocide
Subtitle: Killing by algorithm
Date: April 16th, 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 18th, 2024 from https://petergelderloos.substack.com/p/israel-is-pioneering-new-methods.

 Israel is making sure it will be remembered in history as a pioneer of genocide. Multiple Israeli military sources have testified that the Israeli military is using AI to guide missile and bomb strikes against Palestinians[1]. If the Israeli military’s Artificial Intelligence determines that a person is a military member of Hamas, the Israeli military will systematically approve of a missile or bomb strike to murder that person and any civilians in the immediate vicinity. 
 The AI program used by the IDF, called ‘Lavender,’ can also determine th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loren Goldner - The Spanish Revolution, Past and Future: Grandeur and Poverty of Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/loren-goldner-the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism?v=1719918699</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/loren-goldner-the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism?v=1719918699"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Loren Goldner
Title: The Spanish Revolution, Past and Future: Grandeur and Poverty of Anarchism
Subtitle: How the Working Class Takes Over (or Doesn’t), Then and Now
Date: 2013
Source: Retrieved on April 19th, 2024 from <breaktheirhaughtypower.org/the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism-how-the-working-class-takes-over-or-doesnt-then-and-now>.

Introduction: Why the Spanish Revolution Today?
 “…anarchism and revolutionary syndicalism in general lacked a vision of the problems of political orientation, without which the most powerful and most heroic revolutionary surge is condemned to failure.” — Helmut Rüdiger, AIT, Ensayo critico sobre la revolucion española (1940)[1]
 For many years, I had held the classical left anti-Stalinist view that after the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Fleischmann - “Red Mutualism” Series at Mutualism Co-Op]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/red-mutualism-series-at-mutualism-co-op?v=1719918555</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/red-mutualism-series-at-mutualism-co-op?v=1719918555"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eric Fleischmann
Title: “Red Mutualism” Series at Mutualism Co-Op
Date: April 23rd, 2024
Source: Retrieved 4/25/2024 from https://c4ss.org/content/59582.

 If there are two contemporary anarchist theorists whose work occupies and influences my thought the most, they are Kevin Carson and Wayne Price. Carson has spent a huge segment of his career not just reconstructing a mutualist political economy as an alternative to the anarchist default to the economics of Karl Marx but also making incredibly original contributions to the fields of decentralized technology/production and spontaneous organization theory. Wayne Price in turn has dedicated his mind to a task that at first seems wholly opposite to Carson’s: working to adapt Marxist economics and political strategy to an anarchist co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, CrimethInc. - Campus Building Occupations, 2008–2010 and Today]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-campus-building-occupations-2008-2010-and-today?v=1719918476</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-campus-building-occupations-2008-2010-and-today?v=1719918476"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, CrimethInc.
Title: Campus Building Occupations, 2008–2010 and Today
Date: April 22 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 25th 2024 from <crimethinc.com/2024/04/22/campus-building-occupations-from-2008-2010-to-today>

 A wave of campus building occupations took place in response to austerity measures following the recession of 2008. As today’s Gaza solidarity movement begins to experiment with encampments and building occupations, it could be instructive to learn from the previous generation of student activists. 
 On April 22, 2024, inspired by the resilience of the Gaza solidarity encampment at Columbia University and other demonstrators around the country, students at Cal Poly Humboldt in Arcata, California occupied Siemens Hall. This represented the first confrontational bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by awesomekling in "Ladybird Web Browser becomes a non-profit with $1M from GitHub Founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40855435</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40855435"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, we are aware of how permissive licenses work.
If someone forks our code and does a better job with it than we do, fair game. :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>awesomekling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, CrimethInc. - “It Is an Honor to Be Suspended for Palestine”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine?v=1719918373</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine?v=1719918373"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, CrimethInc.
Title: “It Is an Honor to Be Suspended for Palestine”
Subtitle: Dispatches from the Solidarity Encampment at Columbia University
Date: April 21 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 25th 2024 from https://crimethinc.com/2024/04/21/it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine-dispatches-from-the-solidarity-encampment-at-columbia-university

 On April 17, students at Columbia University and Barnard College set up an encampment in solidarity with Palestinians facing genocide at the hands of the Israeli military. On April 18, the university administration brought in massive numbers of police to arrest the demonstrators and crush the encampment; yet in response, students established a new encampment, bigger than the first, inspiring copycat actions from Yale to St. Loui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Rules Hitler Immune from Prosecution for Burning Down Reichstag, Seizing Absolute Power]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52835</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/02/supreme-court-rules-hitler-immune-from-prosecution-for-burning-down-reichstag-seizing-absolute-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the current Supreme Court had held comparable office in Weimar Germany, that is, its opinion in Trump v. United States would have rendered the judgment in this post’s headline. Never mind that the Weimar Constitution was different from the U.S. Constitution (importantly, in granting emergency powers to the President to rule by decree under […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distributional Effects of Inflation and Inflation Stabilization]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30644</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/on-the-distributional-effects-of-inflation-and-inflation-stabilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post and the next discuss the distributional effects of inflation and inflation stabilization through the lenses of a theoretical model—a Heterogeneous Agent New Keynesian (HANK) model. This model combines the features of New Keynesian models that have been the workhorse for monetary policy analysis since the work of Woodford (2003) with inequality in wealth and income at the household level following the seminal contribution of Kaplan, Moll, and Violante (2018). We find that while inflation hurts everyone, it hurts the poor in particular. When the source of inflation is a supply shock, fighting inflation aggressively hurts the poor even more, however, while the opposite is true for demand shocks, as discussed in the companion post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Keshav Dogra, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angie Barbosa - Marginal Ontologies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies?v=1719917880</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies?v=1719917880"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Angie Barbosa
Title: Marginal Ontologies
Subtitle: Challenges of a Transfeminist Anarchism
Date: 08.03.2023
Notes: Translation by Cello Latini Pfeil [mltpfeil@gmail.com]
Source: Original translation of “Ontologias Marginais: Desafios de um Anarquismo Transfeminista”. Retrieved on 04.28.2024 from https://revistatapuia.com.br/ojs/index.php/revista/article/view/29/19

Abstract
 In this text, written as a speech for the 1st Anarchist Fair in Rio de Janeiro, contradictions of the historically predatory relationship of brazilian democracy with brazilian travestis and transsexuals are presented, paying attention to the ontological marginality of the travesti body under the capitalist patriarchy of white supremacy. Based on this reflection, transfeminist challenges to radical and anarchist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mother Earth - If We Must Fight, Let It Be For The Social Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-if-we-must-fight-let-it-be-for-the-social-revolution?v=1719917731</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-if-we-must-fight-let-it-be-for-the-social-revolution?v=1719917731"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mother Earth
Title: If We Must Fight, Let It Be For The Social Revolution
Date: 1914
Notes: From “Mother Earth”, October 1914, New York City, published by Emma Goldman, edited by Alexander Berkman

 Society has plunged into a world-wide war, but we Anarchists, we cannot shed tears over its horrors, as do the Socialists and other so-called philanthropists. WE KNOW how industriously those same weepers have been piling up the fuel which made this conflagration certain. 
 Governments have made this war. The Austrian government ordered its slaves to sweep Servia with fire and sword. The German government snapped its fingers at the four million and odd Socialist voters, and ordered its slaves to invade Belgium. The American government with hypocritical sobs and sighs, ordered its slaves …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by awesomekling in "Ladybird Web Browser becomes a non-profit with $1M from GitHub Founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40855179</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40855179"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks F3nd0! There are currently no plans to switch to a less permissive license.
And we're perfectly happy using proprietary services like GitHub and Discord as long as they make our work easier and more enjoyable. We recently evaluated a number of alternatives, and found that they all introduced more friction than we were comfortable with.
Although the task of building a browser is itself challenging, we're a pragmatic project :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>awesomekling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by awesomekling in "Ladybird Web Browser becomes a non-profit with $1M from GitHub Founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40854904</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40854904"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T09:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello friends, Ladybird founder here!
Here's a short video from Chris Wanstrath announcing our non-profit yesterday, and kicking things off with a $1M donation: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k9edTqPMX_k
Happy to answer questions :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>awesomekling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Efficiency and Performance: Navigating the Spark 3 and EMR 6 Upgrade Journey at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16763</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/unlocking-efficiency-and-performance-navigating-the-spark-3-and-emr-6-upgrade-journey-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slack Data Engineering recently underwent data workload migration from AWS EMR 5 (Spark 2/Hive 2 processing engine) to EMR 6 (Spark 3 processing engine). In this blog, we will share our migration journey, challenges, and the performance gains we observed in the process. This blog aims to assist Data Engineers, Data Infrastructure Engineers, and Product […]
The post Unlocking Efficiency and Performance: Navigating the Spark 3 and EMR 6 Upgrade Journey at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilanjana Mukherjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Finland, the Left Alliance Just Trounced the Far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/In-Finland-the-Left-Alliance-Just-Trounced-the-Far-Right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/In-Finland-the-Left-Alliance-Just-Trounced-the-Far-Right"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T08:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's elections saw gains for anti-immigration parties — but the breakthrough act in Finland was the Left Alliance, with 17% support. Its leader, Li Andersson, told Jacobin about why it did so well and how it defeated the far right. 
English

/ 
Antifascism, 
North, 
Finland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Dite, Li Andersson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin shortlist for Australian fiction]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7935</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-shortlist-australian-fiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shortlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for works of Australian fiction, was announced earlier today. Of the ten novels named on the longlist in May, the following six titles have been included today: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen Craig Anam, by André Dao The Bell of the World, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice on faculty job application letters]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52810</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/02/advice-on-faculty-job-application-letters/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m hosting a couple of professionalization discussions for our PhD candidates and postdocs this summer, informal conversations to help them navigate the crazy academic job market. A few weeks ago we discussed job talks as the department had just had a bunch of candidates visit (very different schedule here in Europe than the US) and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eszter Hargittai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Bored!]]></title>
        <id>https://nikhil.bearblog.dev/get-bored/</id>
        <link href="https://nikhil.bearblog.dev/get-bored/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:21:57.176Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity gurus and hacks have killed the essence of getting bored. Do you think Da Vinci was obsessed with utilising every minute of the day? Do you think Tolstoy wrote with discipline? I am not suggesting you go ahead and waste your time, but if you are a creative person, productivity will only get you so far.
But what do I mean by getting bored? Getting bored implies your brain is free of pressing thoughts. There’s no sense of urgency in your mind. It could be for any reason. When there’s no sense of urgency in your mind, there’s calmness. People suffering from anxiety do not get bored; their thoughts and fears keep them occupied.
When your mind is free from pressing tasks, fear, and worries, it tends to get lost. It wanders. In these wanderings, you dwell upon the thoughts buried deep in the subconscious. Every writer would swear by the benefits of walking. When you go out to walk, your mind is tranquil. It is in sync with nature. That’s when your body digs deeper into the subconscious and helps you find the pearl.
Productivity hacks are excellent when you are focused on a singular task. They are excellent in improving your efficiency by inculcating discipline, like writing a book or a bunch of essays. That’s when you need productivity hacks to stay motivated and meet the deadline. The Pomodoro technique is good for helping you finish tasks. It does not invoke creativity, though.
When you want to create something, you need to get bored. You need to let your thoughts mingle with each other and discover a new perspective on the problem. Creation requires empty space and time. The more successful you are in creating this, the better your overall output will be. So, get bored.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by willio58 in "Code reviews do find bugs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40852271</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40852271"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T00:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agreed. I mainly manage and review code at this point in my career. I find many bugs, every once in a while finding something that would have caused an outage or notable problem for users.
What I find more though is code that isn't thought through. Tech debt and code smell are real, and they affect the performance of a team. Nipping that in the bud takes quality PR reviews and time to meet with submitters around issues you find.
Knock on wood but working at the company I do now where I, along with my team, have made quality PR reviews normal.. our codebase is now enjoyable and fun to work on. I highly recommend it!
One key aspect is being “kind, not nice”. Be helpful when leaving comments in PRs, but don’t be nice for the sake of avoiding conflict.
Also if you find code reviews to be a waste of time I can reccomend one thing I do often - give warnings. I approve and give comments around things I’d like to be fixed in the future for similar PRs. I don’t hold up the merge for little things, but at the same time I won’t let the little things slide forever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>willio58</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teleportation: the superpower of choice of superheroes]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7933</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/teleportation-superpower-choice-superheroes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the choice, a regular person, like you or me, who decides they’d like to become a superhero, will choose teleportation as their superhero superpower. In preference to three other choices they could have made: mind-control, flight, or supernatural physical strength. This is the long-story-short conclusion of some recent research into the subject, by Julian […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Anti-Social Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-anti-social-anarchy?v=1719855971</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-anti-social-anarchy?v=1719855971"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T17:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Anti-Social Anarchy
Subtitle: A Short Response to Ausonia Calabrese’s “Against Individualism”
Date: Mar 20, 2020
Notes: Warzone Distro
Source: anarchistnews.org

 Marxism shares one thing in common with other authoritarian ideologies: they are against the individual. Even when Marxists claim to be anarchists or “anti-state communists,” they make sure that masses and classes are always more important than actual people. This is as obvious in Tiqqun or Theory of Bloom as it is in Stalin’s “Anarchism” or “Socialism”, and now, in Ausonia Calabrese’s Against Individualism. The fact that someone identifying themselves as an anarchist or a Stirnite could ever claim to be against individualism is beyond me, but I digress. 
 The main gist of the essay is that individuals ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AI21 Labs’ Jamba-Instruct in Amazon Bedrock, Amazon WorkSpaces Pools, and more (July 1, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>f2b2f1eca783c03eca935bbe7a8b88226b14d5e3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-ai21-labs-jamba-instruct-in-amazon-bedrock-amazon-workspaces-pools-and-more-july-1-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit New York is 10 days away, and I am very excited about the new announcements and more than 170 sessions. There will be A Night Out with AWS event after the summit for professionals from the media and entertainment, gaming, and sports industries who are existing Amazon Web Services (AWS) customers or have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the TIPS‑Treasury Valuation Puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30548</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/exploring-the-tips-treasury-valuation-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the late 1990s, the U.S. Treasury has issued debt in two main forms: nominal bonds, which provide fixed-cash scheduled payments, and Treasury Inflation Protected Securities—or TIPS—which provide the holder with inflation-protected payments that rise with U.S. inflation. At the heart of their relative valuation lie market participants’ expectations of future inflation, an object of interest for academics, policymakers, and investors alike. After briefly reviewing the theoretical and empirical links between TIPS and Treasury yields, this post, based on a recent research paper, explores whether market perceptions of U.S. sovereign credit risk can help explain the relative valuation of these financial instruments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Roussellet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities need more trees]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up just outside of Johannesburg, which is touted to be "the greenest city in the world". During the summer, when seen from above, it's a verdant, green landscape, with the tops of buildings popping through the canopy.

Yes, there's a full city beneath those trees.
However, this is not what the land originally looked like.
To cut a long story short, Johannesburg was established following the discovery of gold in 1886. It's known colloquially as eGoli, or "The City of Gold". Gold extraction here is vastly different to other parts of the world. We don't have gold veins running through the rock like in old Western movies. Instead it's mineralised into the rock itself which requires significant processing to extract.
This form of extraction leads to the crushing of millions of tons of ro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez - Up Against the Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T04:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez
Title: Up Against the Firewall
Date: June 2024
Source: XRDS: Crossroads, The ACM Magazine for Students, Volume 30, Issue 4 Pages 26–30, DOI: 10.1145/3665595

In a revolt against techno-optimism and the real-world violence it upholds, members of radical research collective Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL) call for an empiricism rooted in technopolitical critique. Drawing from their own years of labor in the struggles against racial and surveillance capitalism, current work in HCI, and radical theorists like Alfredo M. Bonanano and Modibo Kadalie, LPL invites us to incorporate an ethics of rebellion and progress our tech practices into principled, anti-authoritarian praxis.
 Our organization, Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL), is a collective of researchers, journ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>