<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-07-03T02:21:24.773Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-07-03T02:21:24.773Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checking in on the “going all-in on alienating your core consumers” strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152232</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/checking-in-on-the-going-all-in-on-alienating-your-core-consumers-strategy"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T01:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently still not going well: Tesla has posted its second quarter delivery numbers — and they’re not looking good. As the New York Times reports, the company reported it had delivered just 384,000 vehicles between April and June, a massive drop from 444,000 vehicles over the same period last year. Meanwhile, CEO Elon Musk has focused his […]
The post Checking in on the “going all-in on alienating your core consumers” strategy appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Lemieux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Defund Red America Act]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152231</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-defund-red-america-act"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T00:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Inflation Reduction Act deliberately titled its benefits toward red states to protect it politically. Alas, this greatly underestimated the nihilistic contempt Republican legislators have for their own constituents: In a December speech on his economic legacy, President Joe Biden predicted that clean energy investments stemming from his signature climate law were “so deeply rooted […]
The post The Defund Red America Act appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Lemieux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – July 2, 2025 (#580)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23468</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/02/daily-reading-list-july-2-2025-580/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T23:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the landscape of IaC tools, what agentic coding recommendations you should follow, and which warning signs tell you its time to switch CI/CD platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Third American Republic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152228</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-third-american-republic"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T22:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m always looking for productive frameworks to use in analyzing our national situation. Over the weekend, the Bluesky account called Shower Cat Love (a friend of the blog) came up with one that resonates with some things I’ve been thinking. I won’t claim any great insight or one weird trick, just a potentially useful way […]
The post The Third American Republic appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheryl Rofer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prices of Both Housing And Rent Are Decreasing In China]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA1-1moKa7EEmNqeJq5hArn</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA1-1moKa7EEmNqeJq5hArn"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T21:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, Xi said that houses were for living in, not for speculating. The Chinese government took steps to reduce prices, those steps took time to bear fruit.
 
 
Likewise, rent prices have been dropping recently:

And yes, this is a result of government policy:
While, according to the PBOC, in the pre-pandemic decade, the annual rental inflation in China exceeded 1.2%, it slowed significantly in recent years and has been in the negative in the last twelve months. In March 2025, the rent of the rental housing component of the consumer price index (CPI) showed a 0.1% year-on-year decline, trending upwards, however, from -0.4% and -0.3% annual change rates previously registered in September 2024 and December 2024, respectively.
“In recent years, rents have declined due to lower income expect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wisconsin Supreme Court strikes down state’s anachronistic abortion law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152223</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/wisconsin-supreme-court-strikes-down-states-anachronistic-abortion-law"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most important election of the year has already paid a major dividend: Women in Wisconsin will continue to have access to abortion services under a new ruling from the state’s highest court that invalidates a 176-year-old state law that had banned abortions in nearly every situation. In a 4-3 ruling July 2, the liberal-controlled […]
The post Wisconsin Supreme Court strikes down state’s anachronistic abortion law appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Lemieux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Close Trump advisor advocates physical genocide of USA’s 65 million Latinos]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152222</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/close-trump-advisor-advocates-physical-genocide-of-usas-65-million-latinos"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T19:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh yes I know it’s a “joke.” BTW Laura Loomer is Jewish. One of the more peculiar developments of the Trumpist decade has been prominent Jewish members of the Trumpist orbit who seem remarkably enthusiastic about ethnic genocide of the most literal sort (see Miller, Stephen).
The post Close Trump advisor advocates physical genocide of USA’s 65 million Latinos appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting the AI/energy conundrum]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/confronting-ai-energy-conundrum-0702</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/confronting-ai-energy-conundrum-0702"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT Energy Initiative’s annual research symposium explores artificial intelligence as both a problem and a solution for the clean energy transition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leda Zimmerman | MIT Energy Initiative</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOLTS survey for May still consistent with “soft landing” scenario]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177986</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/jolts-survey-for-may-still-consistent-with-soft-landing-scenario"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat ﻿As promised, let me parse the JOLTS survey for May, which was reported yesterday.  As a quick refresher, this survey decomposes the employment market into openings, hires, quits, and layoffs. In 2024 the data were most consistent with a “soft landing,” but the actions of the new Administration, especially on trade, […]
The post JOLTS survey for May still consistent with “soft landing” scenario appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Nova Canvas update: Virtual try-on and style options now available]]></title>
        <id>6ac1eaa9636e9ef2e508335e409e187b714352f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-nova-canvas-update-virtual-try-on-and-style-options-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T18:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Nova Canvas has introduced two new AI-powered image generation capabilities: virtual try-on for visualizing clothing on people and style options for applying predefined artistic styles to images, both accessible through the Amazon Bedrock console with straightforward API implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sean Combs verdict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152218</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-sean-combs-verdict"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T18:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven’t followed either this case or the trial at all, so this thread is for people who want to discuss it. I did find this Vox explainer both interesting and disturbing “There’s so much physical violence in this case, and I think it’s easy to extrapolate how fear of physical violence could coerce somebody […]
The post The Sean Combs verdict appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Rahm Emanuel’s Kayfabe Candidacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294837</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/rahm-emanuel-president-2028-kayfabe-candidate-ari-trump.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T18:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rahm Emanuel is teasing a run for President in 2028. His brother Ari, a Democratic power-broker and a Trump insider will be a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Wilson Turner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kristi Noem is deranged, but will she cannibalize her own words?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177980</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/kristi-noem-is-deranged-but-will-she-eat-her-own-words"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T16:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noem is busy protecting Americans against self-eating cannibals: “Speaking at a press conference in Florida with Donald Trump, Noem claimed that the president’s deportation push, which she is overseeing, is about “upholding freedom…the freedom to live safely in this country and to do things legally and to have justice.” The administration, she said, is “going […]
The post Kristi Noem is deranged, but will she cannibalize her own words? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rule of Law Is Key to Capitalism − Eroding It Is Bad News for American Business]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294882</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/the-rule-of-law-is-key-to-capitalism-%e2%88%92-eroding-it-is-bad-news-for-american-business.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T13:57:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is a sad sign of the extent of libertarian propaganda that an apple-pie-and-motherhood issue like the rule of law needs defending.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The racism, misogyny, and corruption are also the points]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152214</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-racism-misogyny-and-corruption-are-also-the-points"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T13:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing our largely useless political media could do is put scare quotes around “Trump presidential library” when there’s a story about how an open bribe to Trump is being funneled through this completely imaginary entity. Another thing that would be worth noting is that when Trump’s fascist lawyers file a sub-frivolous lawsuit against CBS […]
The post The racism, misogyny, and corruption are also the points appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Is Going to Be Entertaining…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152212</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/this-is-going-to-be-entertaining"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T12:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kentucky’s GOP Senate primary is kicking into gear: Among the claims being made: Nate Morris has undergone an “embarrassing” political makeover, and Andy Barr is “bought by woke banks.” And “Fake Nate” Morris is the subject of a whole website created by Daniel Cameron’s team. Morris, a Lexington tech and insurance entrepreneur, entered the race […]
The post This Is Going to Be Entertaining… appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Farley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attacking the FED again]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177940</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/attacking-the-fed-again"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there not one person in Congress who will be our leader who will tell Tr__P to shut up? Is it up to the constituency to do the dirty work every 4 years? I can only imagine where we would be it Tr__p succeeds. Trump attacks Fed again in open letter to Powell calling for […]
The post Attacking the FED again appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Erik Visits an American Grave, Part 1,916]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152149</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/erik-visits-an-american-grave-part-1918"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the grave of Emmett Till. You know, I don’t really have anything to say here. We all the know the story of Emmett Till. We all know the horrors of lynching and the terribleness of a murderous Jim Crow society that allowed and even encouraged crackers to kill Black men or even small […]
The post Erik Visits an American Grave, Part 1,916 appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Loomis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Round Abouts and Traffic Circles]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177970</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/round-abouts-and-traffic-circles"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, we were discussing Round Abouts (AZ) or what they call Traffic Circles (New Jersey) in this article. My first experience at navigating one such creature was in Asbury Park, New Jersey. I was temporality stationed (as a Marine) at Fort Monmouth going to Crypto-Tech training for six months. I was able to borrow a […]
The post Round Abouts and Traffic Circles appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/2/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294836</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/links-7-2-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T10:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our peripatetic daily links: communicating cat? H5N1 human outbreak, Vietnam v. China in Spratlys, Denmark to draft women, IAEA MI6 agent outed, US cutting Ukraine arms, 23&Me data sold, "Big bill" casualites, Trump threatens Musk, ICE custody death, US construction wobbles, Meghan hawks wine, Amazon robots]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust in Science, Public Health, and Politics: Lessons from COVID-19]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294844</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/trust-in-science-public-health-and-politics-lessons-from-covid-19.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T10:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after COVID-19 was recognized as a worldwide catastrophe, my much better half asked me how long I thought this would this last.  Based on my then 45 years of biomedical research experience I replied, “Three years.”  I was wrong.  That was more than five years ago, when the refrigerated makeshift morgues were parked on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broligarchs Demand Silicon Valley Bank 2.0: What Could Go Wrong?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294872</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/broligarchs-demand-silicon-valley-bank-2-0-what-could-go-wrong.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T09:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems no idea is too stupid not to get a following. This one is to recreate Silicon Valley Bank, a standout failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We are led by fools]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177939</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/we-are-led-by-fools"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T09:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. has appointed a clown car to the CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP). And it shows: “If observers were waiting for a moment when the newly anointed members of the CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) made a clear case against U.S. vaccine science, it didn’t happen during the group’s 2-day […]
The post We are led by fools appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sustainable Investment Stumbles on Uncertain Pace of Energy Transition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294868</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/sustainable-investment-stumbles-on-uncertain-pace-of-energy-transition.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T07:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Green energy investment goes wobbly....again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – July 1, 2025 (#579)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23448</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/01/daily-reading-list-july-1-2025-579/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T23:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at what an AI-native engineer does, why one company swapped Kafka for gRPC, and what good system design looks like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vortex]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177967</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/vortex"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T23:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable genius, me arse.  Veritable idiot, more like.  And, a neanderthal.  Abysmally ignorant of state craft, of economics, of finance, of trade, of government, of science, of history, … of anything other than his own own oral anal.  From anal to oral, gut to mouth, sixteen and more hours a day.  But for Fred and […]
The post Vortex appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Melvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Construction spending continues contraction, amplifying yellow flag caution from manufacturing]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177963</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/construction-spending-continues-contraction-amplifying-yellow-flag-caution-from-manufacturing"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T22:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat I concluded last month’s post on construction spending by writing “Putting this report together with this morning’s other report on manufacturing from ISM, it appears the goods-producing part of the economy as a whole is very slightly contracting. It will be interesting to see if this is reflected in a decline […]
The post Construction spending continues contraction, amplifying yellow flag caution from manufacturing appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Additional Thoughts and Reading . . . Fellow Rats]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177943</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/some-additional-thoughts-and-reading"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T18:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– Supreme Court limits nationwide injunctions, but fate of Trump birthright citizenship order unclear. The Copper Courier. “the decision left unclear the fate of President Donald Trump’s restrictions on birthright citizenship.” – States can cut off Medicaid funding to Planned Parenthood, the Supreme Court rules. Associated Press. “authored by Justice Neil Gorsuch and joined by the […]
The post Some Additional Thoughts and Reading . . . Fellow Rats appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preliminary economically weighted ISM average for June continues in “recession watch” territory]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177959</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/preliminary-economically-weighted-ism-average-for-june-continues-in-recession-watch-territory"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat As usual, we start out the month with reports on both manufacturing and construction. Ill post separately on construction. Additionally, the May JOLTS reports was posted, but I’ll discuss that tomorrow. So let’s start with the ISM manufacturing report, a recognized leading indicator for the past 60+ years, although of diminished […]
The post Preliminary economically weighted ISM average for June continues in “recession watch” territory appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s what AI-native engineers are doing differently than you]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23436</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/01/heres-what-ai-native-engineers-are-doing-differently-than-you/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T18:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “what” and the “how” in software engineering occasionally change at the same time. Often,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – Are You Not Entertained?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294709</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-are-you-not-entertained.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T18:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have entered an era in which warfare has departed from the conventional (Clausewitzian) concept of attaining clear objectives. Instead, modern armed conflict is characterized by limited and generally inconclusive military clashes motivated by factors disconnected from the practical concerns of the affected citizens. War has turned away from decisive conflict and embraced performative spectacle. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verdun Then and Now]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArs6JAgBSty9ORkGH5jZGe</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArs6JAgBSty9ORkGH5jZGe"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T17:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thirty-one years ago on my first trip overseas I visited Verdun in France. Specifically to see the battlefield of Verdun, where von Falkenhayn sought to bleed the French white. From 21 February 1916 to 18 December 1916, 9 months, 3 weeks and 6 days  I’d written my senior’s honor thesis in history on Verdun and felt it was right to visit.

Fallen Lion of France at the Verdun Battlefield

I’m not going to go into too much detail. You can read about it in its fullness here. I only want to add a few things. First, this was the first time any general attempted a strategy of attrition. Von Falkenhayn knew he could not break through the ring of forts surrounding the Meuse Heights and the medieval city of Verdun. His aim was to take the heights and dig in and then take the strategic defensive, for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doomed Tesla (RoboTaxi Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTEbF3ZUHrj9MnMhfkJSMi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTEbF3ZUHrj9MnMhfkJSMi"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T13:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll keep this one short and sweet.
Tesla was contacted by the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on Monday after videos posted on social media showed the company’s robotaxis driving in a chaotic manner on public roads in Austin, Texas.
Elon Musk’s electric vehicle maker debuted autonomous trips in Austin on Sunday, opening the service to a limited number of riders by invitation only.
In the videos shared widely online, one Tesla robotaxi was spotted traveling the wrong way down a road, and another was shown braking hard in the middle of traffic, responding to “stationary police vehicles outside its driving path,” among several other examples.

Elon Musk is not that smart. He chose to use cameras only, and not Lidar, against the advice of his own engineers.
China has robotaxis already. They work fine. They have Lidar.
Tesla is doomed. Their cars are worse than those of their competitors and more expensive. Robotaxis aren’t going to work. The only thing saving Tesla right now is 100% tariffs on Chinese autos, but even non Chinese electric cars are better and often cheaper.
Meanwhile Musk is in a feud with Trump, Trump has threatened to remove subsidies for Musk enterprises and Musk (again, an idiot) has said Trump should go ahead. And yes, he does need those subsidies.
The majority of Musk’s wealth is tied up in Tesla, and it’s days are numbered. Meanwhile Starship keeps exploding, the last time during fueling, not even after launch. There are a lot of competitors to SpaceX, and w/o NASA contracts SpaceX doesn’t look so hot either. Right now NASA is stuck with Musk, but that’s not going to last.
Musk isn’t going to be the world’s richest man much longer.
If you’ve read this far, and you read a lot of my articles, you might wish to Subscribe or donate. I’ve written over 3,500 posts, and the site, and Ian, take money to run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest Trouble In Russian-Azerbaijani Relations Might Be Part Of A Turkish-US Powerplay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294828</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/the-latest-trouble-in-russian-azerbaijani-relations-might-be-part-of-a-turkish-us-powerplay.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T13:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how Turkish and US interests benefit from recent upset in the relations between Russia and Azerbainan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s America: shrinking our way to excellence]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177936</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/trumps-america-shrinking-our-way-to-excellence"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T12:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abroad, Trump is sending American hard power in retreat by pulling back on NATO and threatening to invade and take over a NATO country. American soft power under Trump is also in retreat, with the abandonment of USAID and Voice of America. At home, Trump is shrinking American agriculture by the USAID cuts. He’s levied […]
The post Trump’s America: shrinking our way to excellence appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Turns are Dangerous to Make while Driving, What is the Solution?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177913</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/if-turns-are-dangerous-yo-make-while-driving-what-is-the-solution"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where I live the roads are typically 4 lanes, or two each way, and have an island in the middle. The speed limit is set at 45 mph which I have stated time and time again, it is merely a suggestion. People are going well over 45 mph which makes it more dangerous to make […]
The post If Turns are Dangerous to Make while Driving, What is the Solution? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down the BBB Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177923</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/breaking-down-the-bbb-bill"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dean Baker critiquing and breaking down Tr__p’s BBB Bill That’s the question Republicans in Congress will be debating as they struggle to put Donald Trump’s “Big Beautiful Bill (BBB)” in final form to pass and send to his desk. The essence of the bill should be well known at this point. It extends Trump’s 2017 […]
The post Breaking Down the BBB Bill appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/1/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294724</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/links-7-1-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our zany daily links: model train find, earth trapping heat, Chinese blackout bomb? India v. Pakinstan, Thai PM suspended, BIS risk warning, UK poverty, Argentina asset seizure, Israel gloating, Hezbollah capulation? Trump big bill wobbles, Trump v. Musk, epic Zitron v. bafflegabbing CEOs, corsets, US household $ on hand worst]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Washington Trying to Provoke a Full-Blown Banking Crisis in Mexico?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294759</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/is-washington-trying-to-provoke-a-financial-crisis-in-mexico.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This time round, it wouldn't be just US banks that would be heavily exposed to the resulting fallout; so, too, would European lenders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Content Independence Day: no AI crawl without compensation!]]></title>
        <id>1pmK0OnvzPIip01yjWXj0x</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/content-independence-day-no-ai-crawl-without-compensation/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Content Independence Day: Cloudflare, along with a majority of the world's leading publishers and AI companies, is changing the default to block AI crawlers unless they pay creators for content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crawl before the fall… of referrals: understanding AI’s impact on content providers]]></title>
        <id>2pLY5VumUNgntdcfkU9Ua3</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-search-crawl-refer-ratio-on-radar/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Radar now shows how often a given AI model sends traffic to a site relative to how often it crawls that site. This helps site owners make decisions about which AI bots to allow or block.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control content use for AI training with Cloudflare’s managed robots.txt and blocking for monetized content]]></title>
        <id>44HBJInoaQRMqVRmSaqjg6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/control-content-use-for-ai-training/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is making it easier for publishers and content creators of all sizes to prevent their content from being scraped for AI training by managing robots.txt on their behalf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin-Hee Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing pay per crawl: enabling content owners to charge AI crawlers for access]]></title>
        <id>7AJ8tUOFDvk5mCTrDjBPDq</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-pay-per-crawl/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pay per crawl is a new feature to allow content creators to charge AI crawlers for access to their content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Googlebot to GPTBot: who’s crawling your site in 2025]]></title>
        <id>7KJiiS1zdIyBiVgoT6SgKf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/from-googlebot-to-gptbot-whos-crawling-your-site-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From May 2024 to May 2025, crawler traffic rose 18%, with GPTBot growing 305% and Googlebot 96%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Message Signatures are now part of our Verified Bots Program, simplifying bot authentication]]></title>
        <id>5K5btgE8vXWGaGxCrs5yFH</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/verified-bots-with-cryptography/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bots can start authenticating to Cloudflare using public key cryptography, preventing them from being spoofed and allowing origins to have confidence in their identity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mari Galicer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Brushy Mountain State Prison of the Everglades]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177922</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/the-brushy-mountain-state-prison-of-the-everglades"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T09:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up about 20 miles from Brushy Mountain State Prison. You may remember it as the place James Earl Ray was held until, briefly, he wasn’t. He escaped and was re-captured. The appeal of Brushy Mountain included rough terrain and venomous snakes that inhabited the surrounding area. Copperhead Alcatraz. I once visited the prison […]
The post The Brushy Mountain State Prison of the Everglades appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Changing Interpretations of Gobekli Tepe]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB0dY60phSKT1nDZfY58bKN</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB0dY60phSKT1nDZfY58bKN"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T02:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The foreman in 2008 and his sons offer me tea.

Before Gobekli Tepe became an internet sensation by psuedo-archeologist Graham Hancock, I visited the site in 2008. That was 17 years ago. It was not a tourist site at the time. It was a working archeological dig. I was greeted by the foreman and I asked if I could take photos. He said yes, and I did. Some of you might recall them. Here is what it looked like then and here is a link to the photos:

Gobekli Tepe in 2008

And here is how awful it looks now:

Gobekli Tepe at present

A lot of change. The Turkish government co-opted it for its own reasons and turned it into a mega-tourist attraction in the Kurdish regions as a way of asserting some control, but also as a way of dishing out some money to keep the Kurds, at the very least, content.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russo-Ukraine War Update June 30, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBweAnCWulTk_wEODyNaIi_</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBweAnCWulTk_wEODyNaIi_"/>
        <updated>2025-07-01T00:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before we get into the most recent developments of the war between Russia and the Ukraine, I want to focus a little bit about how Russia is outstripping the West technology. We all know necessity is the mother of all invention. And war is the mother of all necessity. The Russians haven’t missed a beat innovating. One of the most terrifying weapon systems is Russia’s thermobaric weapons. They now have at least three operating platforms to deliver these utterly destructive weapons. Thermobaric weapons are not illegal under the rules of war. They are accepted as valid and while the Ukrainians might complain, no one is listening.
If you recall the MOAB–so called Mother of all Bombs, was a thermobaric weapons. Thermobaric weapons explode and aerosolize fuel in the air before they ignite. They a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 30, 2025 (#578)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23417</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/30/daily-reading-list-june-30-2025-578/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T23:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at context engineering and "fixing" your context, using platform engineering to simplify devex, and how to overcome negative thoughts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US federal deficit isn’t the scariest deficit]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177920</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/the-us-federal-deficit-isnt-the-scariest-deficit"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T21:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Congress debates just how much to goose the federal deficit, the global climate budget is even further out of balance that previously feared: “But another approach can give us a very clear sense of what’s going on: track how much heat enters Earth’s atmosphere and how much heat leaves. This is Earth’s energy budget, […]
The post The US federal deficit isn’t the scariest deficit appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build the highest resilience apps with multi-Region strong consistency in Amazon DynamoDB global tables]]></title>
        <id>760cf7d1ab9debd764182009eed986de1b4616a7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-the-highest-resilience-apps-with-multi-region-strong-consistency-in-amazon-dynamodb-global-tables/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T20:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon DynamoDB now offers multi-Region strong consistency capability for global tables, providing the highest level of application resilience and enabling your applications to be always available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Democratic party in trouble?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177882</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/is-the-democratic-party-in-trouble"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T19:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m seeing a lot of doom and gloom navel-gazing about the Democratic Party these days. I’m not a political pundit, but Josh Marshall is, and this ain’t his first rodeo. The weakness, in his eyes, lies with the party leadership and not with the party or its voters. “A lot of the weirdness of press […]
The post Is the Democratic party in trouble? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon EC2 C8gn instances powered by AWS Graviton4 offering up to 600Gbps network bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>854516174b593a5c3244a7cde62636a0b0f88ec4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-ec2-c8gn-instances-powered-by-aws-graviton4-offering-up-to-600gbps-network-bandwidth/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T18:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 announces general availability of C8gn network optimized instances powered by AWS Graviton4 processors, offering up to 600Gbps network bandwidth for demanding network-intensive workloads with 30% higher compute performance over previous Graviton3-based instances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pay close attention to real personal spending on goods]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177915</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/pay-close-attention-to-real-personal-spending-on-goods"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat  This week data arrives in two batches: a smaller batch (ISM manufacturing and construction spending) tomorrow, and a huge tranche (nonfarm payrolls, jobless claims, ISM services, and factory orders) on Thursday. Which means I might take Wednesday off, and/or delay reporting on some of Thursday’s data until Friday. In the meantime, […]
The post Pay close attention to real personal spending on goods appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Project Rainier, Amazon CloudWatch investigations, AWS MCP servers, and more (June 30, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>ca8d997acb0509227bac46b8aa28ac062631a301</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-project-rainier-amazon-cloudwatch-investigations-aws-mcp-servers-and-more-june-30-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T16:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I visit Seattle, the first thing that greets me at the airport is Mount Rainier. Did you know that the most innovative project at Amazon Web Services (AWS) is named after this mountain? Project Rainier is a new project to create what is expected to be the world’s most powerful computer for training […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating scientific discovery with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/futurehouse-accelerates-scientific-discovery-with-ai-0630</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/futurehouse-accelerates-scientific-discovery-with-ai-0630"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FutureHouse, co-founded by Sam Rodriques PhD ’19, has developed AI agents to automate key steps on the path toward scientific progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Winn | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful in a Primary? Don’t expect the Right Wingers Will Let you Pass . . .]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177902</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/successful-in-a-primary-dont-expect-the-right-wingers-will-let-you-pass"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bit of a rewrite . . . Democratic socialist who would become the first Muslim to be NYC mayor if elected. He first has to get past the right-wingers who have come out of hiding since Zohran Mamdani’s success in the Democratic primary for New York City mayor. Being a Democrat is one thing. Being […]
The post Successful in a Primary? Don’t expect the Right Wingers Will Let you Pass . . . appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaining Ground after a Political Shooting? It did Not Happen Like it was Supposed to . . .]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177583</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/gaining-ground-after-a-political-shooting-it-did-not-happen-like-it-was-supposed-to"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the shootings, Utah Representative Lee wrote on X: “This is what happens when Marxists don’t get their way.” In another post, he posted a photo of Boelter with the caption “Nightmare on Waltz Street.” The caption appeared to be a reference to Minnesota Governor Tim Walz, a Democrat. Lee has since deleted the posts […]
The post Gaining Ground after a Political Shooting? It did Not Happen Like it was Supposed to . . . appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source AI Editor: First Milestone]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2025/06/30/openSourceAIEditorFirstMilestone</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2025/06/30/openSourceAIEditorFirstMilestone"/>
        <updated>2025-06-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are open sourcing the GitHub Copilot Chat extension. It’s the first milestone in making VS Code an open source AI editor.
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans are Anti-Democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177888</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/republicans-are-anti-democracy"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T19:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Anti-De) Not all republicans, all Republican politicians.  Who weren’t always.  In my lifetime, in my children’s lifetimes, patriotic, democracy loving Republican politicians were common.  Now, I challenge anyone to name one Republican congressional member worth spit. Before the Republican party’s infamous ‘southern strategy’, liberal, honest Republican politicians were not uncommon.  One could easily name a […]
The post Republicans are Anti-Democracy appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Melvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Problematic Rare Earths]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177875</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/problematic-rare-earths"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T19:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“China Rare Earth Ban Disrupts Automotive Production,” Automotive Manufacturing Solutions Since early April, Chinese customs officials have blocked shipments of rare earth magnets at numerous ports. This halt comes as Beijing drafts a new regulatory framework for export licensing, a move interpreted as retaliation for the US government’s latest round of tariffs. The materials in […]
The post Problematic Rare Earths appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 29, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDrZ1P4ZdhfZUMWPihZVx8c</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDrZ1P4ZdhfZUMWPihZVx8c"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T18:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 29, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
Remembering Bill Moyers: A Colossus of Journalism and Public Service
Jonathan Alter, June 28, 2025 [Washington Monthly]
‘We Have Lost a Giant’: Broadcast Legend Bill Moyers Dies at 91
Jessica Corbett, June 26, 2025 [CommonDreams]
Free Press Mourns Bill Moyers
[Free Press, June 26 2025, via CommonDreams]


The (anti)Federalist Society assault on the Constitution
Amy Coney Barrett and the Supreme Court Give Birth to a Disaster
Garrett Epps, June 27, 2025 [Washington Monthly]
…Three federal district courts concluded that the birthright citizenship order is almost certainly unconstitutional and barred the executive branch from enforcing it pending a final decision. The issue seemed headed to the Supreme Court, where it would b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean-Paul Kelley]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA33ZpyIYbfNKPeL2qpKFR1</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA33ZpyIYbfNKPeL2qpKFR1"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T17:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a quick word that my friend and ex-boss Sean-Paul Kelley is posting fairly often now. Sean-Paul founded the (now defunct) Agonist blog back in the day, which was very important during the Iraq War. He also gave me my first salaried job as the managing editor of the Agonist. (I received some money for writing at BOPNews, but only some.)
I’m pleased to have him here. Do take the time to read the author byline above posts so you know if it’s him or me. Because almost all writing here has been mine, historically, people often assume all posts are from me. Sean-Paul’s more of an old school blogger than I am. Remember that guest posters publish in part to give different takes than I would and I don’t pre-approve their posts, unless they’re very infrequent or new.
(Those who remember Mandos will get this. Out of a hundred Mandos posts I might have agreed with one.) That said, Sean-Paul and I agree about most things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk: quack or idiot savant?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177879</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/elon-musk-quack-or-idiot-savant"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T16:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So it looks like Elon and I agree on something. Great minds think alike. Fools seldom differ. “WASHINGTON (AP) — Elon Musk on Saturday doubled down on his distaste for President Donald Trump’s sprawling tax and spending cuts bill, arguing the legislation that Republican senators are scrambling to pass would kill jobs and bog down […]
The post Elon Musk: quack or idiot savant? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ACIP validates the thimerosal hoax]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177822</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/acip-validates-the-thimerosal-hoax"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T15:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that a notorious anti-vaxxer is Trump’s Secretary of Health and Human Services, fringe theories on vaccines are being mainstreamed at the CDC and other governmental agencies. On example is the fake thimerosal-autism connection: “Thimerosal, an ethyl-mercury based preservative, has been employed since the 1930s to keep multi-dose vials of vaccines safe and free of […]
The post ACIP validates the thimerosal hoax appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Deals Weekly Indicators June 23-27]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177893</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/new-deals-weekly-indicators-june-23-27"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat My “Weekly Indicators” post is up at Seeking Alpha. There have been a number of reversals since April, most notably the stock market going from a 12 month low to a new all-time high, but also the front-running by consumers apparent in the weekly Redbook report has also reversed, from over 7% […]
The post New Deals Weekly Indicators June 23-27 appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN and major aid groups have refused to work with the Gaza Humanitarian Foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177864</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/un-and-major-aid-groups-have-refused-to-work-with-the-gaza-humanitarian-foundation"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Defeated them on the field, Now, eliminating them in defeat. No humanitarian effort in the Gaza as legitimate aid groups are pulling out due to the dangers at the sites to the Palestinians and the relief effort. Tr__p needs to get off of his ass and stop the slaughter. Jared Kushner has praised the “very […]
The post UN and major aid groups have refused to work with the Gaza Humanitarian Foundation appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Still Free Preventative Affordable Care Services]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177860</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/still-free-preventative-affordable-care-services"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least one issue resolved by SCOTUS benefits the public. This ruling preserves a federal mandate for insurers to cover, without copays, certain preventive medical tests and treatment. Meanwhile Trumps bill of destruction is still alive and moving through Congress. The case reached the Supreme court through the efforts of Braidwood Management, a Christian-owned firm. […]
The post Still Free Preventative Affordable Care Services appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling Out the the National Guard for California]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177855</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/calling-out-the-the-national-guard-for-california"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T19:26:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joyce Vance discussing Tr__p’s calling up the National Guard in California. While the Nineth COA did allow Tr__p to call up California’s National Guard, it was for other reasons it was allowed. “We disagree with Defendants’ primary argument that the President’s decision to federalize members of the California National Guard under 10 U.S.C. § 12406 […]
The post Calling Out the the National Guard for California appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do congressional Republicans justify to themselves their total abdication of responsibility]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177853</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/how-do-congressional-republicans-justify-to-themselves-their-total-abdication-of-responsibility"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T18:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vulgar side of Robert Reich. “Office Hours: WTF do they tell themselves?” As Trump siphons away their power, how do congressional Republicans justify to themselves their total abdication of responsibility? Trump’s decision to strike Iran without congressional authorization has renewed debate over Congress’s constitutional role in the use of American forces. At almost every […]
The post how do congressional Republicans justify to themselves their total abdication of responsibility appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCsiJe4uqrx7kHVzdL_0VhC</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCsiJe4uqrx7kHVzdL_0VhC"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T17:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts. No vax/anti-vax this week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Tr__P’s BBB is Going to Do to Those Who Can Least Afford What is Going to Happen . . .]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177803</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/what-tr__ps-bbb-is-going-to-do-to-those-who-can-least-afford-what-is-going-to-happen"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I do not see much commotion about this occurring. It is almost like an “oh well” moment as people sit back and wait for it to happen. Yesterday, I gave readers a table of contents for three separate posts as itemized here: “Rural Hospitals at Risk of Closing,” Angry Bear. The prior sentence listing the […]
The post What Tr__P’s BBB is Going to Do to Those Who Can Least Afford What is Going to Happen . . . appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-worker policies, Crony Capitalism, and Privatization Keep the South locked out of Shared Prosperity]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177839</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/anti-worker-policies-crony-capitalism-and-privatization-keep-the-south-locked-out-of-shared-prosperity"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How anti-worker policies, crony capitalism, and privatization keep the South locked out of shared prosperity: Rooted in Racism and Economic Exploitation: Part Five, Economic Policy Institute EPI’s Nina Mast covers how Southern lawmakers blocked shared prosperity by neglecting basic worker protections and disinvesting in social safety net programs while offering hefty subsidies to corporations, privatizing […]
The post Anti-worker policies, Crony Capitalism, and Privatization Keep the South locked out of Shared Prosperity appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 27, 2025 (#577)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23395</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/27/daily-reading-list-june-27-2025-577/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T23:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how much AI impacts development speed, the best way to prompt text-to-video model Veo, and what context engineering is all about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Income and Outlays, May 2025, BEA]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177824</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/personal-income-and-outlays-may-2025-bea"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T21:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personal Income and Outlays . . . “Personal Income and Outlays, May 2025, U.S. Bureau of Economic Analysis,” BEA Personal income decreased $109.6 billion (0.4 percent at a monthly rate) in May, according to estimates released today by the U.S. Bureau of Economic Analysis. Disposable personal income (DPI)—personal income less personal current taxes—decreased $125.0 billion […]
The post Personal Income and Outlays, May 2025, BEA appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tesla update]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177820</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/tesla-update"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T20:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Tech Viral: “Tesla has abruptly stopped Cybertruck and Model Y production, triggering a nearly 3% stock drop to $348.29, as shown in the finance card above. “The pause, Tesla’s third Cybertruck halt this year at its Austin Gigafactory, compounds delays in Robotaxi plans and Elon Musk’s controversies. “As EV competition intensifies, Tesla’s frequent […]
The post Tesla update appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetishizing numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177817</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/fetishizing-numbers"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T18:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nate Silver makes lemonade from lemons: “Is Trump less popular than he was a few weeks ago? Yes. Is he now firmly underwater on his best issue (immigration)? Also yes. But he’s still more popular today than he was at this point during his first term. On day 159 of term 1, Trump’s net approval […]
The post Fetishizing numbers appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Suffering]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArEFXEPRXhTvhg6exDPqRd</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArEFXEPRXhTvhg6exDPqRd"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Canadian, the issue of people removing snow from the sidewalk is a big deal. Some years ago I lived near a house where they never removed the snow. It piled up till it was almost four feet high, and some partial thaws meant that underneath all that snow was ice. Every time I had to walk in that direction I cursed the owners (there was an SUV that came and went, so I knew it wasn’t uninhabited.) And one time I did slip and I was furious, even though the pain of the fall was minor.
Thing is, I don’t enjoy being furious or upset. Oh, a little anger is sometimes nice enough, but overall it’s an unpleasant feeling unless you’ve been having even worse emotions like fear, despair, powerlessness or self-pity.
This is what Buddha called the second arrow. If you’ve been shot by an arrow, you’re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump approved bombing of US airbase]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177747</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/trump-approved-bombing-of-us-airbase"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“President Trump said Iranian leaders cleared their plan with the U.S. to fire retaliatory strikes against an American airbase in Qatar, and even requested a specific time to attack. “They said, ’We’re going to shoot them. Is one o’clock OK?’ I said it’s fine. And everybody was emptied off the base so they couldn’t get […]
The post Trump approved bombing of US airbase appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIT and Mass General Brigham launch joint seed program to accelerate innovations in health]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-mass-general-brigham-launch-seed-program-innovations-health-0627</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-mass-general-brigham-launch-seed-program-innovations-health-0627"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT-MGB Seed Program, launched with support from Analog Devices Inc., will fund joint research projects that advance technology and clinical research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Beth Gallagher | Office of Innovation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using generative AI to help robots jump higher and land safely]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/using-generative-ai-help-robots-jump-higher-land-safely-0627</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/using-generative-ai-help-robots-jump-higher-land-safely-0627"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIT CSAIL researchers combined GenAI and a physics simulation engine to refine robot designs. The result: a machine that out-jumped a robot designed by humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shipps | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ursula von der Leyen faces no-confidence vote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ursula-von-der-leyen-faces-no-confidence</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ursula-von-der-leyen-faces-no-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T16:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if driven by right-wing factions within the European Parliament, the motion reveals growing cross-party unease with the EU’s escalating techno-authoritarian regime]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Term Toxic Masculinity is Nothing But A Gratuitous Insult to Men.]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBjcaEIu3BaRz2NcPWUnK_W</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBjcaEIu3BaRz2NcPWUnK_W"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a woman with solid feminist bona fides can make this argument in modern America. The high tech economy has leveled the playing field between men and women. This is a great development. But it ignores, like the Democratic party in general, a larger reality: blue collar men. White collar men are indoctrinated in high school and college now how to behave around women. But blue collar men are not. And there are more of them than white collar Ivy Leaguers. Give the video a watch. It refreshing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May personal income and spending: consumer payback for Tariff-palooza! is a B!t©h]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177813</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/may-personal-income-and-spending-consumer-payback-for-tariff-palooza-is-a-bth"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat ﻿The last significant data for the first half of 2025, personal income and spending for May, was released this morning. It was the first month that reflected the impact of Tariff-palooza!, and boy howdy was it impacted. Not a single metric was positive. One metric was unchanged; everything else was negative. […]
The post May personal income and spending: consumer payback for Tariff-palooza! is a B!t©h appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate Micro-Small, and Medium-sized Enterprises Day with Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>RZxPGrzjOiPmMdVhXUdSi</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrate-micro-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-day-with-cloudflare/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate United Nations Micro, Small, and Medium Sized Enterprises Day, Cloudflare is sharing success stories of small businesses building and growing on our platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frédéric Lordon: &ldquo;Endgame&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/endgame</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/endgame"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism and its destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff Dyer <em>&amp;</em> Leo Robson: &ldquo;Theory in the Air&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/theory-in-the-air</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/theory-in-the-air"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Geoff Dyer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rural Hospitals at Risk of Closing]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177791</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/rural-hospitals-at-risk-of-closing-2"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Rural_Hospitals_at_Risk_of_Closing,” Center for Healthcare Quality & Payment Reform The issue being detailed here being: Smaller and rural hospitals are under the threat of closing as the Tr__p administration cuts funding to pay for the 2017 tax break. A tax break which Trump promised it would pay for itself. It did not. So, Tr__p will keep […]
The post Rural Hospitals at Risk of Closing appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncertainty on Tariffs by the President May have Caused a Delay of a Fed Rate decrease]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177715</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/uncertainty-on-tariffs-by-the-president-may-have-caused-a-delay-of-a-fed-rate-decrease"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is almost laughable. TR__p’s wishy-washy back and forth on tariffs may have have caused the Fed Chair to delay a decrease. It sure sounds or reads like it. Federal Reserve Chair Jerome Powell told lawmakers this last Tuesday, the recent economic data would have likely justified continuing to lower the Fed rates if not for concerns […]
The post Uncertainty on Tariffs by the President May have Caused a Delay of a Fed Rate decrease appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should Student Loans Be Forgiven?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177772</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/should-student-loans-be-forgiven"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of May 24, 2024, the SBA had forgiven over 10.5 million PPP loans to businesses, totaling ~$800 billion. Another 37,938 owe an ~ $4.6 billion) and are labeled potential clawback or a code 70 (potential claw back).  Not so for student loans. These are the people who should have greater productivity at a younger […]
The post Should Student Loans Be Forgiven? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobless claims indicate employment market continues to weaken, but still not recessionary]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177779</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/06/jobless-claims-indicate-employment-market-continues-to-weaken-but-still-not-recessionary"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T00:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat Jobless claims continue to tell us two things: (1) the jobs market continues to slowly weaken, but (2) it is not recessionary. This week I’ve changed my graphing scheme slightly, to emphasize the less noisy four week moving average of initial claims, to better show the residual post-COVID seasonality, and to […]
The post Jobless claims indicate employment market continues to weaken, but still not recessionary appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 26, 2025 (#576)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23374</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/26/daily-reading-list-june-26-2025-576/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T23:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at choosing the right host for your AI agents, how to prepare APIs for AI agents, and whether it matters if your manager writes code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The War in the Ukraine Enters A New Phase]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMBgbFOo9fbF8i5kwdxT2n</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMBgbFOo9fbF8i5kwdxT2n"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T22:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russo-Ukrainian War of 2021-present has entered a new phase. In the wake of the Ukraine’s hybrid/asymmetric attack on Russia’s strategic bomber fleet–aka Operation Spiderweb–Russia is getting its revenge in the smartest way possible. Russia has begun a massive month long air/missile/drone campaign that is systematically attacking command and control centers all over the country. The latest was a Russian X-22 missile attack on a former drilling rig disguuised as a seaborne command and control center. A Tu-22M3 Backfire bomber launched the X-22 cruise missile where it reached Mach 4 and then dove into the command center and obliterated it. There are dozens of videos out now on reputable sites indicating this campaign is ongoing and will continue.
This is very, very bad news for the Ukraine. This might not be the beginning of the end, but it is the end of the middle.
The site for reasonably unbiased updates is Military TV. But, viewer beware, this is uncensored warfare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Internet users are unable to access the open Internet]]></title>
        <id>vyxFL3zp5DqpF5RpHznRv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/russian-internet-users-are-unable-to-access-the-open-internet/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T22:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since June 9, 2025, Internet users located in Russia and connecting to the open Internet have been throttled by Russian Internet Service Providers (ISPs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tremante</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Zohran Mamdani Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAljUbemCh_wgFivPETZmjk</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAljUbemCh_wgFivPETZmjk"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T19:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Democratic Socialist (ie. has politics a 70s liberal would have agreed with, but is less racist) Zohran Mamdani has won the nomination for Democratic candidate for New York city Mayor.
The best analysis I’ve read of this is definitely from Matt Stoller. He defines this win as a “system defining election”, that is an attempt to not just to change who runs a system, but how that system is run. Read the article.
I’ll point out here that there have been a few such attempts. Matt talks about Lamont’s challenge to Lieberman, where Lamont won the primary, then Lieberman won the election. That is what will be tried here: the oligarchical part of the party will align behind another candidate, possibly even the Republican one. Those who don’t will try to co-opt Mamdani and turn him into a centri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying sustainability reporting using AWS and generative AI in banking]]></title>
        <id>232ff3b2fb66dde737470efdab18cf1de7afed37</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/simplifying-sustainability-reporting-using-aws-and-generative-ai-in-banking/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T17:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, you learn how you can use generative AI services on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to automate your sustainability reporting requirements, reduce manual effort, and improve accuracy. You do this by implementing an automated solution for extracting, processing, and validating data from corporate reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sachin Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemini CLI might change how I work. Here are four prompts that prove it.]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23311</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/26/the-gemini-cli-might-change-how-i-work-here-are-four-prompts-that-prove-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T16:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday morning, we took the wraps off one of the most interesting Google releases of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Tiratelli <em>&amp;</em> Ali Helwith: &ldquo;Stagnation State&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stagnation-state</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stagnation-state"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T15:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the UK economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to save Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/how-to-save-europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/how-to-save-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T15:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is necessary to articulate a confederal Europe capable of overcoming the technocratic, militaristic, post-national and Atlanticist design of the European Union]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>