<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-29T18:32:24.995Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-29T18:32:24.995Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comrade President? Change and Continuity in Sri Lanka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Comrade-President-Change-and-Continuity-in-Sri-Lanka</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Comrade-President-Change-and-Continuity-in-Sri-Lanka"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T15:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anura Kumara Dissanayake's (AKD) victory on 21 September as the candidate of the centre-left National People's Power (NPP) coalition is highly significant for symbolic and substantive reasons. His predecessors have been from the social and political elite that has mis-ruled Sri Lanka since independence from Britain in 1948. Some were born into that elite, while a couple (Ranasinghe Premadasa, Maithripala Sirisena) made their way into it through the business of politics before they occupied (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nihil: Embracing Digital Minimalism]]></title>
        <id>https://andout.bearblog.dev/nihil-embracing-digital-minimalism/</id>
        <link href="https://andout.bearblog.dev/nihil-embracing-digital-minimalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of endless notifications, feature-bloated apps, and constant digital noise, I found myself yearning for simplicity. That's why I created Nihil - a suite of minimalist tools designed to help you focus on what truly matters.
The Vision Behind Nihil
Nihil was born out of a personal need. As a developer and a user, I was frustrated with the complexity of many digital tools. I wanted something that would strip away the unnecessary and leave only the essential. Something that would help me think clearer and live more intentionally.
That's the core of Nihil's philosophy: less is more. Each tool in the Nihil suite serves a single, specific purpose. No bloat, no distractions - just pure functionality.

What Makes Nihil Different?
Purposeful Design
Every feature in Nihil is there because …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM welcomes the sovereign stance of the new Government of Mexico of not inviting King Felipe VI of Spain to attend the inauguration ceremony]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-welcomes-the-sovereign-attitude-of-the-new-Government-of-Mexico-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-welcomes-the-sovereign-attitude-of-the-new-Government-of-Mexico-of"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T13:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the ceremony of the transfer of power from the President of Mexico, Andrés Manuel López Obrador, to the new President, Dr. Claudia Sheimbaum Pardo, next Tuesday, October 1, there will be a notable absence, that of King Felipe VI de Borbón of the Kingdom of Spain. 
English

/ 
Mexico, 
Neocolonialism, 
Colonialism, 
Human Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;Consequences of Nasrallah&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/consequences-of-nasrallah</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/consequences-of-nasrallah"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T11:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel and the Resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279490</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T10:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking US Foreign Policy for a Multipolar World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279504</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/rethinking-us-foreign-policy-for-a-multipolar-world.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T10:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagining a new set of American values with the help of Whip Randolph’s “One Disease, One Cure."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brown Bananas, Crowded Ports, Empty Shelves: What to Expect if There’s a Big Dockworkers Strike in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279499</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/brown-bananas-crowded-ports-empty-shelves-what-to-expect-if-theres-a-big-dockworkers-strike-in-the-us.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T09:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[East and Gulf coast dockworkers are about to strike against low wages, unsafe working conditions and the threat of automation while the ruling class demands Collective Biden to intervene.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jewish National Fund Canada Funnels Charity to Israeli Military, Settlers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334604</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/29/jewish-national-fund-canada-funnels-charity-to-israeli-military-settlers/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T06:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flag of the Jewish National Fund.
In 1967, in the course of the Israeli invasion of the West Bank, the Israeli military razed three Palestinian villages which stood along a corridor connecting Tel Aviv and Jerusalem. In keeping with longstanding practice, the Israeli government turned the land over to the Jewish National Fund, which sought to permanently displace the Palestinian villagers through “afforestation,” or redevelopment of the area as a public park, where the former residents would be considered squatters if they tried to return to their homes. To fund the displacement-as-conservation, JNF solicited the Jewish community in Canada, whose contributions also lent the park its name: Canada Park.
Now, more than half a century later, as the Israeli occupation of the West Bank persists amid its ongoing genocide in the Gaza Strip, JNF’s activities have come under new scrutiny. Most significantly, the Jewish National Fund of Canada has lost its charitable status due to even more outright support for Israeli violence: financing projects for the Israeli military in violation of regulations prohibiting charities from supporting foreign armed forces and activities contrary to public policy, such as illegal Israeli settlements in the West Bank.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Jewish National Fund Canada Funnels Charity to Israeli Military, Settlers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Salisbury Cathedral]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53241</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/29/sunday-photoblogging-salisbury-cathedral-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T06:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Doc Unlocks America’s Deep, Dark Anti-Democratic Secrets by Exposing Electoral College]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332052</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/29/new-doc-unlocks-americas-deep-dark-anti-democratic-secrets-by-exposing-electoral-college/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T05:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Allison Saeng.
America and its origin story are full of unexamined assumptions, one of the biggest being that voters actually cast their ballots for presidential candidates. Is democracy – which comes from the Greek words for people (demos) and rule (kratos) – the USA’s foundational “Big Lie”? Consider that, according to Ari Berman’s new book Minority Rule, only 1.8% of the population of the 13 original states voted in George Washington’s 1789 presidential election. In One Person, One Vote? director Maximina Juson goes behind the closed doors of 1787’s Constitutional Convention, when America’s anti-democratic original sin was enshrined in the new nation’s framed rules, and – like Howard Zinn’s People’s History and Oliver Stone’s Untold History of the United States – reveals hidden truths about “the land of the free.”
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post New Doc Unlocks America’s Deep, Dark Anti-Democratic Secrets by Exposing Electoral College appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mannyv in "SpaceX launches mission for 2 NASA astronauts who are stuck on the ISS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41684333</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41684333"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T02:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well hmm. NASA decided Starliner wasn't safe enough to use for the return journey, so the astronauts stayed on the ISS until the next ride became available.
Originally the astronauts were supposed to go back on Starliner. Now they're taking another ride back. Is that considered a rescue? Well, it depends.
If you get left behind on an island because your ride wasn't safe and another boat picks you up, is that a rescue? Now what if you're 420 kilometers up and another boat has to come get you. Is that a rescue?
If there wasn't another ride from the ISS available, would the astronauts be stranded? Yes.
In that case, if a ride suddenly became available would it be considered a rescue? Probably, yes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mannyv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Citizens’ Assemblies in Michigan and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52701</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/29/citizens-assemblies-in-michigan-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-29T01:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Citizens’ assemblies are a hot topic these days in democratic theory. Hélène Landemore gave her Tanner Lecture at University of Michigan last semester, describing her experience on the governance committee of the French Citizens’ Convention on the End of Life. Her account of how ordinary citizens could not only deliberate seriously about a contentious issue, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austria: stuck in the middle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Austria-stuck-in-the-middle</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Austria-stuck-in-the-middle"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T18:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, Austria has a general election for its parliament. The 183 members of the National Council are elected by open list proportional representation at three levels; a single national constituency, nine constituencies based on the federal states, and 39 regional constituencies. Seats are apportioned to the regional constituencies based on the results of the most recent census. For parties to receive any representation in the National Council, they must either win at least one seat in (...)
English

/ 
Antifascism, 
Recession, 
Austria]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Block-Busting Beirut]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334854</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/28/block-busting-beirut/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T14:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ Recall that this week of ferocious Israeli airstrikes inflicting mass civilian casualties across Lebanon began with Emanuel Macron and Joe Biden introducing a plan for a 21-day ceasefire in Lebanon that they said had the support of Netanyahu… + Shortly after Netanyahu delivered his lunatic rant at the UN, where he gave Israel the […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Block-Busting Beirut appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Do Laundry Together (Goodbye Cohost)]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/lets-do-laundry-together-goodbye-cohost/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/lets-do-laundry-together-goodbye-cohost/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T14:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My first time watching Everything, Everywhere, All At Once (EEAAO) was at a friend's house with about ten other Asian immigrants. There's a scene where the male lead, Waymond Wang (Ke Huy Quan), was putting googly eyes all over the lanterns and doing a sneaky shush at the camera before running away.
"Oh, that's [deadname]," said someone. Laughter echoed in the living room.
Eh? That's me?
I'll admit, when my brain was mostly still concentrated on the movie, pre-transition, still stuck in my "I have to be a man" phase, I wondered if that was a snide comment. It's very easy to read it that way because Waymond's character is the opposite of the stereotypical male lead. He is presented as effeminate, weak, and his voice is high-pitched and lacks a full range. As a knee-jerk gut reaction, we foc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing Your Software Supply Chain with Amazon CodeCatalyst and Amazon Inspector]]></title>
        <id>84a25e2a3fa6cf4b4c03c40b15b88d2a5c5edaa8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/securing-your-software-supply-chain-with-amazon-codecatalyst-and-amazon-inspector/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T13:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst is a unified service that streamlines the entire software development lifecycle, empowering teams to build, deliver, and scale applications on AWS. DevSecOps is the practice of integrating security into all stages of software development. Rather than prioritizing features, it injects security into an earlier phase of the development process – baking it into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Mattoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You're Not Me]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/youre-not-me/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/youre-not-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T12:24:28.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["If I were you, I would..."
Do you sometimes hear that? I think it's such an incredibly stupid thing to say. If you were me, which you clearly aren't, then you would do something that I, as myself, wouldn’t do.
It's just a way of expressing oneself, someone might think. I beg to differ.
My feeling is that the person who expresses themselves in that way has a lot of their own issues that should be addressed. Instead of doing that, they get a momentary, false sense of "I got my shit together" by explaining what others should do.
Do you want to share your own experiences? Please do, I love listening to that. Do you have specific advice to give? Bring it on, and I'll take what applies to who I am here and now.
Do you want to explain what's best for me right now? Keep it to yourself, please, and sort out your own shit first. Good luck!
mail Email
 print Print
 share Share]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UPDATED: Hezbollah Confirms Nasrallah Is Dead; Netanyahu Condemned Over Massive Beirut Bombing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279465</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/this-maniac-must-be-stopped-netanyahu-condemned-over-massive-beirut-bombing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T12:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Hezbollah's leader Hassan Nasrallah survived an attack in Beirut, Israel may still get the regional war it wants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279466</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T10:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our oceanic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hello new blog]]></title>
        <id>https://taylordrew.me/hello-new-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://taylordrew.me/hello-new-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T09:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone and welcome to my blog!
This is a project I've started many times before without a lot of success on several different WordPress sites—all of which no longer exist. The first was a free blog I set up when I first came to Japan in 2015 as a student. I'd seen so many blogs by other exchange students and thought it'd be pretty exciting. The only problem was that I didn't think that anything I was doing was very exciting, so I quickly stopped doing it. I've tried since to make several paid sites that focus on my reading and writing book reviews. There were a lot of problems with that, most of which came down to the fact that I was extremely worried about making the "perfect" site even though it was just something that I wanted to do for fun. WordPress has always just also been r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TaxCast on Green Laundering, Combatting Big Corporate Tax Dodging with Joseph Stiglitz, EU Competition Minister Margrethe Vesterger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279463</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/taxcast-on-green-laundering-combatting-big-corporate-tax-dodging-with-joseph-stiglitz-eu-competition-minister-margrethe-vesterger.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T07:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at corporate misbehavior, here extreme tax avoidance and green laundering, and the progress of efforts to combat it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Communist Study Group - Ripples and Waves]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-haters-cafe-ripples-and-waves?v=1727485961</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-haters-cafe-ripples-and-waves?v=1727485961"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T01:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Some Communist Study Group
Title: Ripples and Waves
Subtitle: Notes on Ukraine in the Long Crisis
Date: May 11th, 2022
Source: Retrieved on 9/27/24 from haters.noblogs.org/post/2022/05/11/ripples-and-waves-notes-on-ukraine-in-the-long-crisis

This long-form essay was sent to us for publication by “some communist study group“. It discusses the historical role of Ukraine in the contemporary political economy, the response from radicals in the West towards the Russian invasion, and the material effects on the global political economy emanating from the disruption of a major bread basket, specifically with an eye towards revolt. The questions raised here are important not just for the current moment, but also for any social movement that desires to truly engage with “present state of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Array of Structs and Struct of Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/array-of-structs-and-struct-of-arrays/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/array-of-structs-and-struct-of-arrays/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T21:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Data structures play a crucial role in determining the performance and efficiency of algorithms. The Array of Structs (AoS) and Struct of Arrays (SoA) are two popular data structures used to represent complex data. Although they can store similar data, they differ in memory layout, access patterns, and performance.
Here's an excellent video on Data Oriented Design by Andrew Kelley the creator of Zig programming language.
Array of Structs (AoS)
An AoS is a data structure composed of an array of structures, where each structure represents a single entity with multiple fields or members. The structures are stored contiguously in memory, one after the other.
typedef struct {
    int id;
    float x;
    float y;
} PointAOS;

PointAOS is a struct containing three fields: id (an int…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sometimes i wish depression was a physical illness]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/sometimes-i-wish-depression-was-a-physical-illness-new/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/sometimes-i-wish-depression-was-a-physical-illness-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's from my experience that people are a lot more sympathetic when they can actually see you hurting. For the millionth time in my life, I wished depression manifested like the flu or some other recognizable disease, just to make it simple for me and for the people around me.
How much easier would it be if mental illness were physical - visible and tangible? A runny nose and a sore throat - people would understand. They would offer me tissues, a warm cup of tea, and a sympathetic get well soon. But a shitty compilation of mental symptoms and an even shittier chemical make up? How do I explain an intangible pain?
What can I say, anyway? Sometimes I feel like I am carrying around a heavy suitcase full of sadness everywhere that I go. The smallest task feels impossible. Everything is dull yet heavy, all at once.  Everything matters too much yet nothing matters. Anything would be easier to explain than what's really going on.
I think this topic further resonates with me as someone with high-functioning depression. I recall an attempt to open up about my state with a close friend, who reacted with amusement and disbelief, as if I was exchanging lighthearted banter. But you are so put together, Tala. You are successful, ace tests, and excel at work - it must be a misdiagnosis.
I was overwhelmed with shame that later transformed into rage. I found it impossible to articulate the depth of pain - that yes, I am waking up everyday, leaving bed, fulfilling my obligations. But I am still struggling, still fighting a relentless battle with the energy I have left.
And there are millions of us suffering a silent, invisible battle against our mental illnesses, while we present a facade of normalcy to world. Because sometimes silence is the easier option.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by testfoobar in "Fraud, so much fraud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673954</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673954"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar - when I was younger, I would never have suspected that a scientist was committing fraud.
As I've gotten older, I understand that Charlie Munger's observation "“Show me the incentive and I will show you the outcome.” is applicable everywhere - including science.
Academic scientists' careers are driven by publishing, citations and impact.  Arguably some have figured how to game the system to advance their careers.  Science be damned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>testfoobar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279422</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T18:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics;  Friday charts: The election (tied), and Covid (improved); Kamala's speeches on economics; New 737 malfunction (rudder pedals) discovered as negotiators back at the table ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dekhn in "Fraud, so much fraud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673680</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673680"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T17:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These sorts of articles raise so many thoughts and emotions in me.  I was trained as a computational biologist with a little lab work and ran gels from time to time.  Personally, I hated gels- they're finicky, messy, ugly, and don't really tell you very much.  But molecular biology as a field runs on gels- it's the priimary source of results for almost everything in molbio.  I have seen more talks and papers that rested entirely a single image of a gel which is really just some dark bands.
At the same time, I was a failed scientist: my gels weren't as interesting, or convincing compared to the ones done by the folks who went on to be more successful.  At the time (20+ years ago) it didn't occur to me that anybody would intentionally modify images of gels to promote the results they claimed, although I did assume that folks didn't do a good job of organizing their data, and occasionally published papers that were wrong simply because they confused two images.
Would I have been more successful if fewer people (and I now believe this is a common occurrence) published fraudulent images of gels?  Maybe, maybe not.  But the more important thing is that everybody just went along with this.  I participated in many journal clubs where folks would just flip to Figure 3, assume the gel was what the authors claimed, and proceed to agree with (or disagree with) the results and conclusions uncritically.  Whereas I would spend a lot of time trying to understand what experiment was actually run, and what th e data showed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dekhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by steveklabnik in "Rewriting Rust: A Response"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673056</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41673056"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T17:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am always glad to see people pursuing creating their own programming language. More people should give it a try, IMHO.
A tricky thing that comes up with Rust comparisons is that often, Rust has a feature that's weird or hard to use, but it's because that's the only solution that makes sense within the constraints Rust has placed upon itself. Clicking some links gets me to https://git.yzena.com/Yzena/Yc/src/branch/master/docs/yao/de...
> Yao's biggest goals are: Correctness, Convenience, Performance, in that order.
Having clear goals is a great thing when making a language, because they give you guidance on what is appropriate to include and what is not.
Rust has certainly demonstrated having similar goals, but in a slightly different order: Correctness, Performance, and then Convenience. So it wouldn't shock me if Yao could do some things better than Rust, in accordance with its goals. But that also means that sometimes, Rust would be useful where Yao cannot be. Everything is tradeoffs.
Incidentally, I actually think that figuring out what your values are, and what your needs are, is a great way to pick a programming language. Decide what matters to you as an engineer, and then find a language that shares similar values. I gave a conference talk a few years back on this idea, and how I viewed Rust's values at the time https://www.infoq.com/presentations/rust-tradeoffs/
This was based off of bcantrill's Platform as a Reflection of Values, which was very influential on me. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xhx970_JKX4
If you've ever heard about Oxide's focus on values, this is some of the older background on that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steveklabnik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dmoy in "CA law means stores can't say you're buying a game if you're merely licensing it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41672834</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41672834"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T16:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the idea of reclaiming the word "buy" to only be the traditional type of ownership transfer (first sale doctrine or whatever if it's a copyrighted thing).  Mandate the use of the word "license" or "rent" if it's something else]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dmoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aantix in "The best $4 ever spent"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41672140</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41672140"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We took our kids to Disney World once.
When asked what their favorite part of the trip was, they responded..
The hot tub.
At the hotel.
My kids light up the most when I am fully engaged with them, fully present, entertaining their ideas, and asking questions.
Their favorite family trip so far?  When we traveled to Arkansas to mine for crystals.  AKA, dig in the dirt all day.  They saw it on a YouTube video. They asked to go.  So we obliged. I had never been to Arkansas.  It's beautiful.
We stayed at a resort, Diamonds Old West Cabins, with a huge playground outside the cabins, archery, and a bubble party every evening at 6 pm.
They still talk about that trip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aantix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Ruby: &ldquo;Like a Prayer&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/like-a-prayer</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/like-a-prayer"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sally Rooney.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategic Reflections on the Escalation of Israeli Intimidation in Lebanon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Strategic-Reflections-on-the-Escalation-of-Israeli-Intimidation-in-Lebanon-22909</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Strategic-Reflections-on-the-Escalation-of-Israeli-Intimidation-in-Lebanon-22909"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On intimidation, terrorism, asymmetric war, deterrence, counter-deterrence, and the Dahiya doctrine in the ongoing Israeli onslaught on Lebanon 
English

/ 
Lebanon, 
Palestine, 
Israel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilbert Achcar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fall Fashion’s Economic Forecast]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279408</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/fall-fashions-economic-forecast.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sampling of fall/winter women's frocks does not make for an upbeat economic forecast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TheOtherHobbes in "I Am Tired of AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41670530</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41670530"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google didn't change it, it embodied it. The problem isn't AI, it's the pervasive culture of PR and advertising which appeared in the 50s and eventually consumed its host.
Western industrial culture was based on substance - getting real shit done. There  was always a lot of scammery around it, but the bedrock goal was to make physical things happen - build things, invent things, deliver things, innovate.
PR and ad culture was there to support that. The goal was to change values and behaviours to get people to Buy More Stuff. OK.
Then around the time the Internet arrived, industry was off-shored, and the culture started to become one of appearance and performance, not of substance and action.
SEO, adtech, social media, web framework soup, management fads - they're all about impression manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TheOtherHobbes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snapcaster in "Legalizing sports gambling was a mistake"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41670122</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41670122"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The older I get the more I hate gambling. When i was younger I tended to think "hey it's their choice" but i've realized how unfair our society is in terms of things like this.
Food, gambling, etc. are all backed by hordes of brilliant well paid people trying to get you to ruin your life so they make money. On the other side is just regular people like us stressed out trying to survive.
This isn't some "freedom" issue, it's an incredibly huge power asymmetry and I think "we the people" need protection from these forces]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snapcaster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding Cloudflare's support for open source projects with Project Alexandria]]></title>
        <id>5LrF3eCtonOcP2Sf5BSVpe</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/expanding-our-support-for-oss-projects-with-project-alexandria"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we believe in the power of open source. With Project Alexandria, our expanded open source program, we’re helping open source projects have a sustainable and scalable future, providing them with the tools and protection needed to thrive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veronica Marin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our container platform is in production. It has GPUs. Here’s an early look]]></title>
        <id>5KJejYd85inMDIZUZ6z17D</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/container-platform-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been working on something new — a platform for running containers across Cloudflare’s network. We already use it in production, for AI inference and more. Today we want to share an early look at how it’s built, why we built it, and how we use it ourselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Irvine-Broque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing cybersecurity: Cloudflare implements a new bug bounty VIP program as part of CISA Pledge commitment]]></title>
        <id>6PcliMGa9hJMvd9HafSMwe</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cisa-pledge-commitment-bug-bounty-vip"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare strengthens its commitment to cybersecurity by joining CISA's "Secure by Design" pledge. In line with this commitment, we're enhancing our vulnerability disclosure policy by launching a VIP bug bounty program, giving top researchers early access to our products. Keep an eye out for future updates regarding Cloudflare's CISA pledge as we work together to shape a safer digital future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sri Pulla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering builders: introducing the Dev Alliance and Workers Launchpad Cohort #4]]></title>
        <id>2Q277uIpNI04K4kTcUXLkf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/launchpad-cohort4-dev-starter-pack"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering developers with the Dev Starter Pack and Workers Cohort #4: get free or discounted access to essential developer tools and meet the latest set of incredible startups building on Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Kargiannakis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network trends and natural language: Cloudflare Radar’s new Data Explorer & AI Assistant]]></title>
        <id>4R2kUv9mZSgnAXmKOKTbLz</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-data-explorer-ai-assistant"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloudflare Radar Data Explorer provides a simple Web-based interface to build more complex API queries, including comparisons and filters, and visualize the results. The accompanying AI Assistant translates a user’s natural language statements or questions into the appropriate Radar API calls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Everywhere with the WAF Rule Builder Assistant, Cloudflare Radar AI Insights, and updated AI bot protection]]></title>
        <id>6HqKUMoXg0wFIQg9howLMX</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/bringing-ai-to-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year for Cloudflare’s birthday, we’ve extended our AI Assistant capabilities to help you build new WAF rules, added new AI bot & crawler traffic insights to Radar, and given customers new AI bot blocking capabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Martinetti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reaffirming our commitment to free]]></title>
        <id>P8TeQwTekaAHzlEGB8bLG</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflares-commitment-to-free"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Cloudflare reaffirms its commitment to offering a robust Free service tier that continues to improve. We share why Free is a cornerstone of our business strategy, and how it contributes to building a better Internet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Barker: &ldquo;False Hopes&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/false-hopes</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/false-hopes"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T12:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza and the DNC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bdndndndbve in "TSMC execs allegedly dismissed OpenAI CEO Sam Altman as 'podcasting bro'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41669232</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41669232"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T11:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current AI hype wave has really hit a nerd soft spot - that we're steps away from AGI. Surely if a computer can make plausible-looking but incorrect sentences we're days away from those sentences being factually accurate! The winter after this is gonna be harsh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bdndndndbve</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279395</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T10:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our gale-force daily links.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle Surprise: Ecuador’s US-Born President, Daniel Noboa, Plans to Scrap Constitutional Ban on Foreign Military Bases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=279369</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/quelle-surprise-ecuadors-us-born-president-daniel-noboa-seeks-to-scrap-constitutional-ban-on-foreign-military-bases.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T10:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his first ten months in power, Noboa has done everything he can to place Ecuador even more firmly under Washington's thumb.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lifetime payment vs. subscription]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/saas/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/saas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something I’ve mentioned in my yes/nope page is that I won’t subscribe. This is a bit crass of course; that page is for things I generally don’t want to do and isn’t meant for explanation, exceptions and nuance. Of course there are services I subscribe to - I currently pay for Proton, Spotify and Apple Fitness.
One reason is, of course, that these services don’t offer lifetime payment. But in their cases, I understand how that’s not feasible - their services are heavily dependent on serving content via cloud and development of new content and improved features. The bandwidth needs to be paid for, artists, devs and fitness trainers need to be paid constantly.
But I try to limit what I subscribe to. Everyone has a maximum amount of subscriptions they’re willing to have at the same time and p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by low_tech_love in "I Am Tired of AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41668054</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41668054"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most depressing thing for me is the feeling that I simply cannot trust anything that has been written in the past 2 years or so and up until the day that I die. It's not so much that I think people have used AI, but that I know they have with a high degree of certainty, and this certainty is converging to 100%, simply because there is no way it will not. If you write regularly and you're not using AI, you simply cannot keep up with the competition. You're out. And the growing consensus is "why shouldn't you?", there is no escape from that.
Now, I'm not going to criticize anyone that does it, like I said, you have to, that's it. But what I had never noticed until now is that knowing that a human being was behind the written words (however flawed they can be, and hopefully are) is crucial for me. This has completely destroyed my interest in reading any new things. I guess I'm lucky that we have produced so much writing in the past century or so and I'll never run out of stuff to read, but it's still depressing, to be honest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>low_tech_love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sovietmudkipz in "I Am Tired of AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41667942</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41667942"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:10:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am tired and hungry…
The thing I’m tired of is elites stealing everything under the sun to feed these models. So funny that copyright is important when it protects elites but not when a billion thefts are committed by LLM folks. Poor incentives for creators to create stuff if it just gets stolen and replicated by AI.
I’m hungry for more lawsuits. The biggest theft in human history by these gang of thieves should be held to account. I want a waterfall of lawsuits to take back what’s been stolen. It’s in the public’s interest to see this happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sovietmudkipz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jdietrich in "Legalizing sports gambling was a mistake"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41667643</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41667643"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports gambling has been legal in the UK since 1960. Gambling wasn't seriously problematic in this country until 2005, when regulations were substantially liberalised. Pre-2005, sports betting was something that old men did in dingy backstreet shops; post-2005, it became a widespread social phenomenon, turbocharged by advertising and the growing influence and accessibility of the internet.
There's a false dichotomy between prohibition and laissez-faire, which the US seems particularly prone to. You've seen similar issues with the decriminalisation of cannabis, where many states seem to have switched abruptly from criminalisation to a fully-fledged commercial market. There is a broad spectrum of other options in between those points that tend to be under-discussed.
You can ban gambling advertising, as Italy did in 2019. You can set limits on maximum stakes or impose regulations to make gambling products less attractive to new customers and less risky for problem gamblers. You can have a single state-controlled parimutuel operator. Gambling does cause harm - whether it's legal or not - but it is within the purview of legislators to create a gambling market in which harm reduction is the main priority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jdietrich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Nazi Now? The Dangerous U.S. War on Immigrants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334595</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/whos-nazi-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T06:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faced with two wars, nuclear confrontation, extreme economic inequality, and a climate crisis -- not to mention threats to reproductive rights, forever chemicals, housing shortages, gun violence, and rising educational debt – what do 82% of Republican and 39% of Democratic voters, according to a Pew Research poll, say is the most important issue in the Presidential election? Immigration. A nation of immigrants, with dying main streets, empty classrooms, and labor shortages in key industries, is about to cast its votes based in large part on which candidate can best be trusted to reduce rates of both legal and illegal immigration. More
The post Who’s Nazi Now? The Dangerous U.S. War on Immigrants appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Talented Mr. Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334685</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/the-talented-mr-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read the polls (hard as it is to imagine Americans with landlines deciding the election), so you don’t have to, but about the only thing they tell me is that the country is close to electing as its next president someone who is criminally insane, and then perhaps further enabling his psychosis with a House, Senate, and Supreme Court safely in the hands of Republicans such as cinema vaper Lauren Boebert, human trafficker Matt Gaetz, and the paid vacationer, Clarence Thomas. More
The post The Talented Mr. Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Judicial Murder of Marcellus Williams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334698</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/the-judicial-murder-of-marcellus-williams/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T06:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Missouri executed Marcellus “Khalifah” Williams on Tuesday night despite knowing he was most likely innocent of the crime he was condemned for. More
The post The Judicial Murder of Marcellus Williams appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s War on Lebanon and Netanyahu’s October Surprise to Pick the Next U.S. President]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334694</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/israels-war-on-lebanon-and-netanyahus-october-surprise-to-pick-the-next-u-s-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The launching of the widespread terror campaign targeting civilians in Lebanon is an integral part of the Israeli war strategy to achieve tactical military objectives. The new Israeli strikes which started on September 17 with the exploding pagers have resulted so far in more than 5000 killed and injured Lebanese.
For the past 11 months, the Lebanese Resistance limited its attacks exclusively to Israeli military bases, in or near, the "Jewish-only" colonies along the Lebanese border. The current Israeli assault was likely planned to take place on September 16 ahead of the aexplosion of the pagers, but had to be postponed due to an unforeseen clash with the visit of Biden’s envoy Amos Hochstein. Consequently, Israel may have failed, either due to confusion or technical difficulties, to reprogram the pagers’ activation to another date. More
The post Israel’s War on Lebanon and Netanyahu’s October Surprise to Pick the Next U.S. President appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Week/NYC – Oh, Well!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334681</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/climate-week-nyc-oh-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Week/NYC September 22-29, 2024, is underway and expects 100,000 attendees for cocktails, hors d’oeuvres, and expensive rooms in NYC’s ultra-expensive hotels amidst breast-pounding speeches and promises to fix civilizations’ biggest threat to continued existence. For over 30 years, climate change conference commitments to do something constructive have been embarrassing flops. What will Climate Week/NYC  More
The post Climate Week/NYC – Oh, Well! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stormy Weather:  Trump and Stormy Daniels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334730</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/stormy-weather-trump-and-stormy-daniels/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels could not have foreseen how what was supposed to be a dinner date with Donald Trump on at a Lake Tahoe resort would change her life, would transform her from an obscure porn star to one of the most famous people in the world. Nor could Donald Trump anticipate that his sexual escapade  More
The post Stormy Weather:  Trump and Stormy Daniels appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Beaumont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the West Normalise Genocide?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334553</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/will-the-west-normalise-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the last London protest – the 18th National march against the Genocide in Gaza – a solitary protester held up a home-made sign which read, ‘Imagine Being Stupid Enough to Actually believe A Genocide Doesn’t Affect You’, which I took not only as an exhortation to remember our common humanity, but also as a  More
The post Will the West Normalise Genocide? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Good is a Conference to Counter Ongoing Violations of the Laws of War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334601</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/what-good-is-a-conference-to-counter-ongoing-violations-of-the-laws-of-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to react to the recent violence in the Middle East? While international law, especially the laws of war, may be soft law, there seem to be no limits on how the Middle East conflict is being conducted. Despite internationally signed treaties, pagers explode in Lebanon killing at least 12 people — including two children  More
The post What Good is a Conference to Counter Ongoing Violations of the Laws of War? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From a Hurting Heart: On the Execution of Marcellus Williams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/from-a-hurting-heart-on-the-execution-of-marcellus-williams/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no other way to write this outside of the extensive curse words I want to use: What, the actual, hell? How on earth does the United States have such a deeply flawed system of injustice that the state of Missouri executed a man that both the defense and prosecution believed was innocent? My heart  More
The post From a Hurting Heart: On the Execution of Marcellus Williams appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laura Finley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hanging by a Thread: US-led War Drills in the Korean Peninsula and the Threat of Global Nuclear War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334577</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/hanging-by-a-thread-us-led-war-drills-in-the-korean-peninsula-and-the-threat-of-global-nuclear-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In her closing speech during the 2024 Democratic National Convention, U.S. Vice President Kamala Harris presented the most openly militaristic take on Washington’s Korea policy “since the GOP convention that nominated [Senator Barry] Goldwater in 1964”. Harris’s hawkish view all but discards diplomacy to focus on herding South Korea and Japan together to form a  More
The post Hanging by a Thread: US-led War Drills in the Korean Peninsula and the Threat of Global Nuclear War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simone Chun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wars, Propaganda Wars and Funding Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334551</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/wars-propaganda-wars-and-funding-them/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now it’s clear even to the thick-skulled nabobs running our government, that the U.S. can’t win actual wars. It puts up a more respectable performance with propaganda campaigns, probably because those are things the mighty intellects in the CIA truly enjoy, but even those, with their ferocious philippics against malevolent Moscow in The New  More
The post Wars, Propaganda Wars and Funding Them appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proposal for Military Expansion in the Southwest is Rife with Negligence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334746</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/proposal-for-military-expansion-in-the-southwest-is-rife-with-negligence/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Warplane practice over the civilian countryside is reckless endangerment of anyone intent on recreation, schooling, research or spiritual practice in remote areas where peaceful activities are not only a way of life, but an economic anchor. There’s little incentive to fish, hunt, birdwatch, study or pray in once pastoral wild lands where fighter jets weighing  More
The post Proposal for Military Expansion in the Southwest is Rife with Negligence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Matson Spina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[African Union Must Intervene – Asylum Seekers Enlisted to Kill Palestinians in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334740</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/african-union-must-intervene-asylum-seekers-enlisted-to-kill-palestinians-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If one is to visit the Mahal website, a pop-up reminder, reading ‘Apply online’, keeps appearing. It is as if the repeated beep is a reminder of the state of emergency, if not outright panic, in the Israeli military. Mahal is one of several recruiting agencies that aim to entice mercenaries from all around the  More
The post African Union Must Intervene – Asylum Seekers Enlisted to Kill Palestinians in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unfriendly Fire in Weapons-Flooded War Zone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334732</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/unfriendly-fire-in-weapons-flooded-war-zone/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Giant weapons contractors just may be too big when their weapons systems so overcrowd a warzone that their own missiles destroy their own warplanes. This could be what happened in Ukraine in August, when a Lockheed Martin F-16, piloted by Ukrainian Lt. Col. Oleksiy Mes, was most likely shot down by a Lockheed Patriot air-defense  More
The post Unfriendly Fire in Weapons-Flooded War Zone appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Genuine Hell on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334691</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/creating-a-genuine-hell-on-earth/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine yourself in space, looking down on our world and yet unable to return any time soon. Consider it our bad luck, in fact, that Barry “Butch” Wilmore and Sunita Williams were the two Americans sent to the International Space Station, 250 miles above this planet, for a few days in June and now find themselves stuck  More
The post Creating a Genuine Hell on Earth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Left Wins Presidential Election in Sri Lanka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334560</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/the-left-wins-presidential-election-in-sri-lanka/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 22, 2024, the Sri Lankan election authority announced that Anura Kumara Dissanayake of the Janatha Vimukthi Peramuna (JVP)-led National People’s Power (NPP) alliance won the presidential election. Dissanayake, who has been the leader of the left-wing JVP since 2014, defeated 37 other candidates, including the incumbent president Ranil Wickremesinghe of the United National  More
The post The Left Wins Presidential Election in Sri Lanka appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atul Chandra – Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disgusted German Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334504</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/disgusted-german-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Germans are sick and tired. Some are still angry at the way the COVID epidemic was dealt with (there are those who still insist that there really was no epidemic). Far more are angry at the worsening medical system. It is still far, far better than in the USA, of course, but that doesn’t  More
The post Disgusted German Voters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venetian Art and American Art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334753</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/venetian-art-and-american-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We philosophers believe that there is something called ‘art’, which has an essence. And so our goal is to offer a general definition, encompassing all art made anywhere anytime. Art historians have a different goal. For the art historian, the aim is to describe diverse visual cultures, treating art as a form of cultural expression.  More
The post Venetian Art and American Art appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Campus Life Killers: Ending Face-to- Face Lectures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/the-campus-life-killers-ending-face-to-face-lectures/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bells are tolling for the demise of the university classroom – at least its physical manifestation.  Administrative barbarians are readying their knives and brandishing their drivel-fed visions about pedagogy, a word they scant define, let alone spell.  They find it unseemly that an academic could turn up, in person, to teach students who, likewise, turn up  More
The post The Campus Life Killers: Ending Face-to- Face Lectures appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black MAGA: How, Why, and What is to be Done?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334678</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/black-maga-how-why-and-what-is-to-be-done/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“What, there’s such a thing as Black MAGA? That’s insane. Trump hates Black people. No way! It can’t be anything more than Astroturf.” So exclaimed a liberal Democratic white friend of mine, aghast when I told him about a recent confrontation violent and self-described Black MAGAts and about recent polling data suggesting that Trump has  More
The post Black MAGA: How, Why, and What is to be Done? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are Biden and Harris Endangering Trump’s Security?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334756</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/how-are-biden-and-harris-endangering-trumps-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Donald Trump blames Vice President Kamala Harris for the assassination attempt on him. He told Fox News Digital that the would-be assign had “believed the rhetoric of Biden and Harris, and he acted on it.” What did the potential assassin believe that the Democrats had said? Harris posted on X, Sept 9, she said, “Take it from the people who  More
The post How are Biden and Harris Endangering Trump’s Security? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Formula for Healthy Relating: How the Psychology of Oppression Perpetuate Harm to Animals and the Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334771</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/the-formula-for-healthy-relating-how-the-psychology-of-oppression-perpetuate-harm-to-animals-and-the-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was four years old, I killed someone. And 43 years later, I received the Ahimsa Award for my work on global nonviolence. On that fateful day in 1970, I had no idea that my actions would set me on a journey of discovery that would transform the way I understood and related to myself and  More
The post The Formula for Healthy Relating: How the Psychology of Oppression Perpetuate Harm to Animals and the Environment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie Joy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Back In The US, Back In The US, Back In The USSR”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334768</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/back-in-the-us-back-in-the-us-back-in-the-ussr/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title is misleading in a number of ways. This is not about going back to the past, this is not about only the US and the USSR, and this is not about being lucky. This is an observation about what appears to be the ill-fated inevitability of human frailty when imbued with the goal  More
The post “Back In The US, Back In The US, Back In The USSR” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clark T. Scott</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Newest Abortion Supporters: Men in Red States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334762</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/meet-the-newest-abortion-supporters-men-in-red-states/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like it or not, abortion access has always been viewed as a “women’s problem.” Men rarely talked about it, at least not publicly, and it didn’t seem to rank very high on their list of political priorities. Not anymore. Since Donald Trump proudly took credit for overturning Roe v. Wade with his anti-choice Supreme Court appointments, men  More
The post Meet the Newest Abortion Supporters: Men in Red States appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martha Burk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failure to Indulge to Oren Cass’s Nationalist Delusions Isn’t An “Externality”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334752</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/failure-to-indulge-to-oren-casss-nationalist-delusions-isnt-an-externality/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Donald Trump’s proposal to impose tariffs as high as 60 percent on imports from China, and a global tariff of 10 to 20 percent,” Oren Cass argues at The Atlantic, “takes the right approach to addressing globalization’s failures — but it has drawn resounding mockery from economists, and, in turn, from the mainstream media.” While Cass, usually described  More
The post Failure to Indulge to Oren Cass’s Nationalist Delusions Isn’t An “Externality” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caring for a Child Shouldn’t Cause Financial Ruin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334757</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/caring-for-a-child-shouldnt-cause-financial-ruin-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every mother in America knows this struggle well: how do you afford to raise a child? My daughter was born almost 14 years ago and my family is still financially recovering from the struggle of supporting a newborn. And we’re not alone — American families are spending a greater and greater portion of their income on child  More
The post Caring for a Child Shouldn’t Cause Financial Ruin appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iletha Joynes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sunbelt Disaster? Latest Polls Suggest Harris Could Be Losing Women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=334751</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/27/a-sunbelt-disaster-latest-polls-suggest-harris-could-be-losing-women/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Kamala Harris in danger of losing the women’s vote?  It sounds like an absurd proposition, but the latest New York Times/Siena College polls among voters in Georgia, Arizona and North Carolina reveal a dangerous hemorrhaging of support among female voters.  She’s not losing women outright but her lead over Donald Trump has shrunk to single digits  More
The post A Sunbelt Disaster? Latest Polls Suggest Harris Could Be Losing Women  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mlsu in "Legalizing sports gambling was a mistake"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41666372</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41666372"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T04:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sports gambling, like all gambling, ruins lives. It's certainly worth having the discussion about whether people should be able to run a train through their life and the lives of their families via app.
But a much easier argument against sports betting is that it ruins the sports. Players throw. They get good at subtly cheating. The gambling apparatus latches itself to the sport, to the teams and players, the umpires and judges, the sporting organizations. With this much money on the line, it's not a matter of if but when games are thrown, cheated -- the bigger the game, the bigger the incentive. It's even easier now because of the amount of side/parlay betting that is available. It exhausts the spirit of competition.
Sports gambling is diametrically opposed to sport itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mlsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In their plaintive call for a return to the office, CEOs reveal how little they are needed]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53233</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/27/in-their-plaintive-call-for-a-return-to-the-office-ceos-reveal-how-little-they-are-needed/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T02:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My latest in The Guardian Announcements from major employers, including Amazon and Tabcorp, that workers will be required to return to the office five days a week have a familiar ring. There has been a steady flow of such directives. The Commonwealth Bank CEO, Matt Comyn, attracted a lot of attention with an announcement that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Thoughts - Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/micro-thoughts-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/micro-thoughts-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T23:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month, I decided to try something different on my blog. Some people caught on since some new older posts appeared on their RSS reader from me. I haven’t gotten a chance to explain it and since it’s nearing the end of the month, and a similar post will be popping up shortly, I figured I’d explain what I’m trying to do.
It’s a reverse POSSE of sorts that I’m calling #microthoughts
But first to understand what a reverse of something is, we must understand what it is.
POSSE is an abbreviation for Publish (on your) Own Site, Syndicate Elsewhere, the practice of posting content on your own site first, then publishing copies or sharing links to third parties (like social media silos) with original post links to provide viewers a path to directly interacting with your content. (source…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oversized Hoodie :)]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/oversized-hoodie/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/oversized-hoodie/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T23:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thrifted an XXL hoodie to use as a one-piece at home. Very comfortable. I really love the massive size.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did We Leave San Francisco (the U.S., Actually)?]]></title>
        <id>https://otavio.cc/why-did-we-leave-san-francisco-the-us-actually/</id>
        <link href="https://otavio.cc/why-did-we-leave-san-francisco-the-us-actually/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T22:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story starts a long time ago. My wife had just returned from Canada, had finished her PhD, and I was a Software Designer working for one of the founding companies of Silicon Valley, though I was based in Brazil.
In one of those unfortunate coincidences in life, I had the opportunity to relocate to the United States, while scientist was offered a postdoctoral research position in Canada—both at the same time.
After putting all the cards (offers, spreadsheets, etc.) on the table, my wife rejected the offer from the Canadian university, and I accepted the one in the U.S.
In Canada, scientist would have had a salary and health insurance, but I wouldn’t. Additionally, I wouldn’t be able to work as her dependent. In the U.S., however, we would both have everything—health insurance, the abil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Archive Wayback Machine link replaces Google search cache]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8577</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/internet-archive-wayback-machine-link-replaces-google-search-cache/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google search does away with its cache, an archived copy of an earlier version of a webpage, but now links to the Internet Archive’s (IA) Wayback Machine copy instead. Try it on your own website, assuming it’s indexed by Google that is. On the search result, click the “more about this page” button, which will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Builder Day 2024: 18 big updates to the Workers platform]]></title>
        <id>6ct91ZmJYzPu9n9pt8sNBm</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/builder-day-2024-announcements"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate Builder Day 2024, we’re shipping 18 updates inspired by direct feedback from developers building on Cloudflare. This includes new capabilities, like running evals with AI Gateway, beta products like Queues and Vectorize graduating to GA, massive speed improvements to KV and Workers AI, pricing simplifications, and bringing key features from Pages into Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanushree Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSWEduChat, an AI tool for Australian teachers in NSW]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8573</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/nsweduchat-generative-ai-tool-australian-teachers-nsw/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian teachers in NSW, now have access to NSWEduChat, a generative artificial intelligence (AI) tool, intended to help educators get a grip on AI tools: The tool aims to provide additional support to staff in developing and delivering teaching experiences, easing workload demands, and empowering users to advance their AI skills in a safe environment. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by RGBCube in "Attacking UNIX Systems via CUPS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41662656</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41662656"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone exposing CUPS to the internet is living a level of not giving a fuck that CVEs cannot reach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RGBCube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is the social web not the social web? When it is THE social web]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8582</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/when-social-web-not-social-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago, a group called the Social Web Foundation was launched. A coming together of “leaders of the open social networking movement“, the foundation aims to make “connections between social platforms with the open standard protocol ActivityPub.” Rather than me reinventing the wheel, here’s the Wikipedia definition of ActivityPub: ActivityPub is a protocol […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwaway314155 in "OpenAI to become for-profit company"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661883</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661883"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's about the narrative they tried to create. The spin. It doesn't matter much if they were technically behaving as a for-profit entity previously. What matters is that they wanted the public (and likely, their talent) to _think_ that they weren't even interested in making a profit as this would be a philosophical threat to the notion of any sort of impartial or even hopefully benevolent originator of AGI (a goal which is laid plainly in their mission statement).
As you've realized, this should have been (and was) obvious for a long time. But that doesn't make it any less hypocritical or headline worthy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway314155</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by randomstring in "Hacking Kia: Remotely controlling cars with just a license plate"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661764</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661764"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The obvious next step is to crawl the whole database of vulnerable Kia cars and create a "ride share" app that shows you the nearest Kia and unlocks it for you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>randomstring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Building multi-tenant SaaS systems]]></title>
        <id>2c4ac69958eb7ffd74f8ddce0a45e334dbc042ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-building-multi-tenant-saas-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software as a Service (SaaS) applications offer a transformative solution for businesses worldwide, delivering on-demand software solutions to a global audience. However, building a successful SaaS platform demands on meticulous architectural planning, especially given the inherent challenges of multi-tenancy. It’s also essential to ensure that each tenant’s data remains isolated and protected from unauthorized access […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "Hacking Kia: Remotely controlling cars with just a license plate"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661403</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661403"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T18:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This won't have nearly the same impact, but when you're considering how vulnerabilities like this might influence your future purchasing decisions, remember that Kia's decision to omit interlocks from their US vehicles (but not Canadian ones!) led to a nationwide epidemic of Kia thefts so large it fed a crime wave, something a number of US cities are suing Kia over. If you've read about carjacking waves in places like Milwaukee and Chicago: that was largely driven by a decision Kia made, which resulted in the nationwide deployment of a giant fleet of "burner" cars that could be stolen with nothing but a bent USB cable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by philsquared_ in "WordPress.org bans WP Engine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661086</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41661086"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T17:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem I have with this is simple and has to do with the lack of separation of entities.
Automattic is a competitor with WPEngine.
Wordpress.com is a competitor with WPEngine.
Wordpress.org and the Wordpress Foundation IS NOT a competitor with WPEngine.
There is a dispute between Automattic and WPEngine. The resources of Wordpress.org and the Wordpress Foundation should not be leverage in this dispute.
The fact that those boundaries are crossed means that anyone who is in competition with Automattic might have any and all ecosystems that Matt has any control over leveraged against them if they upset Matt or Automattic in any way.
It is very poor taste and changes the perspective of the product. Instead of a professional entity who will engage professionally it is now a form of leverage that a single person could wield against anyone who crosses them.
To be clear these same exact actions can be taken against anyone who insults one individual. This look is embarrassing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>philsquared_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ziddoap in "DoNotPay has to pay $193K for falsely touting untested AI lawyer, FTC says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41659665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41659665"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T15:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>DoNotPay also did not "hire or retain any attorneys" to help verify AI outputs or validate DoNotPay's legal claims.
Wow, that's brave. Create a wrapper around ChatGPT, call it a lawyer, and never check the output. $193k fine seems like peanuts.
Sometimes I think about where I would be in life if I had no moral or ethical qualms. I'd probably be running a company like this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ziddoap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Kunkel: &ldquo;Singularity&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/singularity</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/singularity"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T14:44:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fredric Jameson (1934-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s bigger, better, faster AI platform]]></title>
        <id>2lS9TcgZHa1fubO371mYiv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-ai-bigger-better-faster"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you want the fastest inference at the edge, optimized AI workflows, or vector database-powered RAG, we’re excited to help you harness the full potential of AI and get started on building with Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Workers AI faster and more efficient: Performance optimization with KV cache compression and speculative decoding]]></title>
        <id>29PAMer5L0do12OtNa557I</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/making-workers-ai-faster"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With a new generation of data center accelerator hardware and using optimization techniques such as KV cache compression and speculative decoding, we’ve made large language model (LLM) inference lightning-fast on the Cloudflare Workers AI platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaac Rehg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-latency SQLite storage in every Durable Object]]></title>
        <id>44R2ywetTc9l1c6D7oWTsz</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/sqlite-in-durable-objects"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional cloud storage is inherently slow because it is accessed over a network and must synchronize many clients. But what if we could instead put your application code deep into the storage layer, such that your code runs where the data is stored? Durable Objects with SQLite do just that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenton Varda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We made Workers KV up to 3x faster — here’s the data]]></title>
        <id>76i5gcdv0wbMNnwa7E17MR</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/faster-workers-kv"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speed is a critical factor that dictates Internet behavior. Every additional millisecond a user spends waiting for your web page to load results in them abandoning your website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Gauvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break Up Economics — continued]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45610</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/26/break-up-economics-continued/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T12:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford What?  Surely not!  How dare he suggest such a thing. What, you are correct in asking, am I talking about? The recent speech by a Department of Justice official who dared suggest that it is getting quite difficult to find a truly neutral technocratic expert to give testimony in court.  Imagine the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by FL33TW00D in "Orion, our first true augmented reality glasses"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41657337</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41657337"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T11:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible amount of negativity here.
Huge kudos to Meta for breaking new ground and doing a ton of R&D/M&A to get to this point. Once MicroLED comes on a little further and the form factor shrinks this could be the next consumer electronics platform.
Silicon carbide is really interesting, we need high RI materials to make this work.
Hopefully glass 3D printing or similar will make cheap, Rx waveguides possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FL33TW00D</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bayindirh in "OpenAI to become for-profit company"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41656762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41656762"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T10:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The most surprising thing to me in this is that the non-profit will still exist.
That entity will scrape the internet and train the models and claim that "it's just research" to be able to claim that all is fair-use.
At this point it's not even funny anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bayindirh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mtlmtlmtlmtl in "OpenAI to become for-profit company"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41656743</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41656743"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T10:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most surprising thing to me in this is that the non-profit will still exist. Not sure what the point of it is anymore. Taken as a whole, OpenAI is now just a for-profit entity beholden to investors and Sam Altman as a shareholder. The non-profit is really just vestigial.
I guess technically it's supposed to play some role in making sure OpenAI "benefits humanity". But as we've seen multiple times, whenever that goal clashes with the interests of investors, the latter wins out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mtlmtlmtlmtl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Israel's accomplices accustom us to a monstrous, heartless and inhuman world!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/When-Israel-s-accomplices-accustom-us-to-a-monstrous-heartless-and-inhuman</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/When-Israel-s-accomplices-accustom-us-to-a-monstrous-heartless-and-inhuman"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T10:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Worse than Israel's crimes is the fact that the entire so-called “civilized” world follows and comments on them as if they were just a video game. When, of course, it's not celebrating them by arming the criminal. Or approving them by letting them go unpunished. And it has been doing so for decades. And live on our TV screens. Day after day, hour after hour. As if these daily massacres were a never-ending TV series, interspersed with commercials, that we can follow lying on our sofas, while we (...)
English

/ 
Palestine, 
Israel, 
Colonialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gideon Levy, Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by liquidise in "Xkcd 1425 (Tasks) turns ten years old today"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41655883</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41655883"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T08:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software is a house. The more you lean into the analogy, the better.
I often tell clients "The first thing you asked me to do was to move a dining room chair into the living room. Then you asked me to do the same with the toilet. The latter only works if we tear out all the plumbing."
Non-coders seem to understand these analogies intuitively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>liquidise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i would like to die but i dont want to die]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/i-would-like-to-die-but-i-dont-want-to-die/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/i-would-like-to-die-but-i-dont-want-to-die/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T07:37:17.140Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two blog posts in the same week… this is the first time this has happened - maybe this is cool or good?
I believe everyone here must know what depression is, right? Well, if you don’t know, you can click here and read more about it… Well, what probably some people don’t know is that there is chronic depression, meaning no matter how much you try to improve, change, take medication, find hobbies, or whatever the attempt may be; you will die with depression. And I’ve had it since I was 16, but I’m not going to tell you my age, right (I’m in my 20s, lol).
In the past, I have tried to kill myself, but I was saved by a guy who is a great friend, and at the time, I went to live at his house, to be away from everything and everyone, with my phone turned off, just studying 5/6 hours a day, creatin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexander Dunlap - Book Review: “We Are Forests: Inhabiting Territories in Struggle”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alexander-dunlap-book-review-we-are-forests-inhabiting-territories-in-struggle?v=1727332502</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alexander-dunlap-book-review-we-are-forests-inhabiting-territories-in-struggle?v=1727332502"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T06:35:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alexander Dunlap
Title: Book Review: “We Are Forests: Inhabiting Territories in Struggle”
Date: 2024/09/25
Source: https://undisciplinedenvironments.org/2024/09/25/book-review-we-are-forests-inhabiting-territories-in-struggle-cambridgepolity-2023/

 Jean-Baptiste Vidalou, “We Are Forests: Inhabiting Territories in Struggle” (Cambridge: Polity, 2023) 
 It’s shameful. The original French publication of We are Forests: Inhabiting Territories in Struggle by Jean-Baptiste Vidalou was in my hands since April 2018. Frequently described as “the French Seeing Like a State,” the book explores the art of state making in France. Having been in stimulating dialogues with Jean-Baptiste Vidalou (JBV) since 2018, and being linguistically challenged, I knew the general ideas and points in the book—…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ml_basics in "Xkcd 1425 (Tasks) turns ten years old today"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41654809</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41654809"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T05:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's quite remarkable how much the goal posts have shifted when it comes to what is impressive with AI/ML. Things like this are a good reminder.
10 years ago the GAN paper came out and everyone was excited how amazing the generated image quality was (https://arxiv.org/abs/1406.2661)
The amount of progress we've made is mind boggling.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ml_basics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 22, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240925</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240925"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "Llama 3.2: Revolutionizing edge AI and vision with open, customizable models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41652377</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41652377"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T22:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm absolutely amazed at how capable the new 1B model is, considering it's just a 1.3GB download (for the Ollama GGUF version).
I tried running a full codebase through it (since it can handle 128,000 tokens) and asking it to summarize the code - it did a surprisingly decent job, incomplete but still unbelievable for a model that tiny: https://gist.github.com/simonw/64c5f5b111fe473999144932bef42...
More of my notes here: https://simonwillison.net/2024/Sep/25/llama-32/
I've been trying out the larger image models to using the versions hosted on https://lmarena.ai/ - navigate to "Direct Chat" and you can select them from the dropdown and upload images to run prompts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run your compute-intensive and general purpose workloads sustainably with the new Amazon EC2 C8g, M8g instances]]></title>
        <id>46b20f1379c6ec23d9613e71305a3bf8d5fa79a7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/run-your-compute-intensive-and-general-purpose-workloads-sustainably-with-the-new-amazon-ec2-c8g-m8g-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash unparalleled computing prowess and energy efficiency for memory-intensive workloads, from in-memory databases to real-time analytics, with C8g and M8g instances powered by AWS Graviton4 processors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI is changing the way photos are classified, photos or memories]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8565</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ai-changing-photos-classified-photos-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhone 16, Apple’s latest smartphone, has arrived on shop shelves. There are four versions of the device: 16, 16 Plus, 16 Pro, and 16 Pro Max. In time all will feature Apple Intelligence, Apple’s artificial intelligence (AI) offering, which will be “deeply integrated” into iOS18 and other Apple operating systems. From what I can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lacker in "Mira Murati leaves OpenAI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651562</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651562"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's easy to have missed this part of the story in all the chaos, but from the NYTimes in March:
Ms. Murati wrote a private memo to Mr. Altman raising questions about his management and also shared her concerns with the board. That move helped to propel the board’s decision to force him out.
https://www.nytimes.com/2024/03/07/technology/openai-executi...
It should be no surprise if Sam Altman wants executives who opposed his leadership, like Mira and Ilya, out of the company. When you're firing a high-level executive in a polite way, it's common to let them announce their own departure and frame it the way they want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lacker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GlenTheMachine in "How to avoid a BSOD on your 2B dollar spacecraft"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651310</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651310"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T20:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thee are a bunch of comments here asking why one would run Windows on a spacecraft.
I am a spacecraft engineer. I don’t see anything in the linked article indicating that they are actually running Windows - the BSOD claim is tongue-in-cheek, or at least that’s how I read it. I also don’t know of anyone anywhere that runs Windows on a spacecraft, with the exception of laptops used by astronauts. Typically one runs vxWorks, or maybe QNX. Some experimental (high risk, low cost) systems run Linux. Older spacecraft don't run any OS at all, everything is running on bare metal, and that may be true for a handful of current spacecraft as well.
Windows is used in some places by ground controllers, but these days they tend to be running Linux a lot more often.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GlenTheMachine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Imnimo in "Mira Murati leaves OpenAI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651210</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41651210"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T19:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard for me to square "This company is a few short years away from building world-changing AGI" and "I'm stepping away to do my own thing". Maybe I'm just bad at putting myself in someone else's shoes, but I feel like if I had spent years working towards a vision of AGI, and thought that success was finally just around the corner, it'd be very difficult to walk away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imnimo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Llama 3.2 models from Meta in Amazon Bedrock: A new generation of multimodal vision and lightweight models]]></title>
        <id>6e2dafa9117525fa56be8f04b271bd8b598b52ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-llama-3-2-models-from-meta-in-amazon-bedrock-a-new-generation-of-multimodal-vision-and-lightweight-models/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pushing the boundaries of generative AI, Meta unveils Llama 3.2, a groundbreaking language model family featuring enhanced capabilities, broader applicability, and multimodal image support, now available in Amazon Bedrock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wilsonnb3 in "Orion, our first true augmented reality glasses"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41650222</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41650222"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T18:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decent hands on article from the verge with more info
https://www.theverge.com/24253908/meta-orion-ar-glasses-demo...
Wireless compute puck. 70 degree FOV. Resolution high enough to read text. Wrist band detects hand gestures and will be used in another product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wilsonnb3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a three-tier architecture on a budget]]></title>
        <id>1bfaecac76d979dc915e1d060b70e31e9259c7d9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/building-a-three-tier-architecture-on-a-budget/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS customers often look for ways to run their systems within or under budget, avoiding unnecessary costs. This post offers practical advice on designing scalable and cost-efficient three-tier architectures by using serverless technologies within the AWS Free Tier. With AWS, you can start small and scale cost-effectively as your business demand increases. You can begin […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Nemeth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JohnMakin in "Why I still blog after 15 years"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41648513</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41648513"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T15:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "I keep this blog for me to write, not necessarily for others to read."
This is now to me the "old school" internet creator attitude (that I still possess). I don't blog as much any more but do create content elsewhere - a lot of it is for my own enjoyment and creative outlet, to blow off steam, whatever - the fact that other people may want to watch it is secondary. I do try to do things people want, but only if I want to do it.
The only reason I highlight this is that the up and coming generations absolutely do not see content creation in the same way. I got in an absurd argument with an early 20 something on a social media platform about how annoying ads were that were disguised as content. The response was overwhelmingly "Well, how else do you expect content creators to make a living?"
I do not disagree that creators should be able to monetize their content however they please, but the fact that people see that as the end and only goal of content creation is baffling to me and almost certainly making it worse. This same person tried to tell me it's been the same way since the earliest days of youtube - which they would have been in diapers around that time - is absolutely not true. The idea of content creation as a full time career is relatively new, and I hate it. The worst part is if you don't participate in the type of obnoxious engagement hacking or buried ads that these "professional" creators do, the algorithms punish you for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JohnMakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Speed Brain: helping web pages load 45% faster]]></title>
        <id>sC3G9YR2M9IIoRMg8slDl</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-speed-brain"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the latest leap forward in speed – Speed Brain. Speed Brain uses the Speculation Rules API to prefetch content for the user's likely next navigations. The goal is to download a web page to the browser before a user navigates to it, allowing pages to load instantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Krivit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New standards for a faster and more private Internet]]></title>
        <id>6YLU1FUKD4lioSrbpOnb5r</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-standards"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare's customers can now take advantage of Zstandard (zstd) compression, offering 42% faster compression than Brotli and 11.3% more efficiency than GZIP. We're further optimizing performance for our customers with HTTP/3 prioritization and BBR congestion control, and enhancing privacy through Encrypted Client Hello (ECH).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Bullock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TURN and anycast: making peer connections work globally]]></title>
        <id>EkJICbovEPPuOSElg8poy</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/webrtc-turn-using-anycast"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TURN servers help relay media and data between devices when direct peer-to-peer connections are blocked or fail. Cloudflare Calls' TURN server uses anycast to eliminate the need to think about regions or scaling, improving reliability of WebRTC applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nils Ohlmeier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s 12th Generation servers — 145% more performant and 63% more efficient]]></title>
        <id>sdvPBDBwhcEcrODVeOE7A</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/gen-12-servers"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is thrilled to announce the general deployment of our next generation of server — Gen 12 powered by AMD Genoa-X processors. This new generation of server focuses on delivering exceptional performance across all Cloudflare services, enhanced support for AI/ML workloads, significant strides in power efficiency, and improved security features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JQ Lau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon ECS Multi-region Deployment with Amazon CodeCatalyst]]></title>
        <id>732e837a33a0bac22b031107313b5c620ea3746f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-ecs-multi-region-deployment-with-amazon-codecatalyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T11:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many AWS customers run their mission-critical workloads across multiple AWS regions to serve geographically dispersed customer base, meet disaster recovery objectives or address local laws and regulations. Amazon CodeCatalyst is a unified software development service designed to streamline and accelerate the process of building and delivering applications on AWS. It is an all-in-one platform for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Mattoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flood Risk Outside Flood Zones — A Look at Mortgage Lending in Risky Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31680</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/flood-risk-outside-flood-zones-a-look-at-mortgage-lending-in-risky-areas/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In support of the National Flood Insurance Program (NFIP), the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) creates flood maps that indicate areas with high flood risk, where mortgage applicants must buy flood insurance. The effects of flood insurance mandates were discussed in detail in a prior blog series. In 2021 alone, more than $200 billion worth of mortgages were originated in areas covered by a flood map. However, these maps are discrete, whereas the underlying flood risk may be continuous, and they are sometimes outdated. As a result, official flood maps may not fully capture the true flood risk an area faces. In this post, we make use of unique property-level mortgage data and find that in 2021, mortgages worth over $600 billion were originated in areas with high flood risk but no flood map. We examine what types of lenders are aware of this “unmapped” flood risk and how they adjust their lending practices. We find that—on average—lenders are more reluctant to lend in these unmapped yet risky regions. Those that do, such as nonbanks, are more aggressive at securitizing and selling off risky loans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kristian Blickle, Evan Perry, and João A.C. Santos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “gender equity” farce: a feminist reading of World Bank policies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-gender-equity-farce-a-feminist-reading-of-World-Bank-policies</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-gender-equity-farce-a-feminist-reading-of-World-Bank-policies"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Feminisms, 
World Bank, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camille Bruneau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Final Choruses and Outros Apparently]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53226</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/25/final-choruses-and-outros-apparently/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T06:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was going to write this super cool music thread with more songs in there than an Erik Loomis “I took time off writing my 1600th American grave post and 547th this day in labor history series to write a 27-part ‘I chance to have been listening to these songs,'” post where I talked about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Purge: invalidating cached content in under 150ms]]></title>
        <id>11EWaw0wCUNwPTM30w7oUN</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/instant-purge"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re excited to share that we’ve built the fastest cache purge in the industry.  We now offer a global purge latency for purge by tags, hostnames, and prefixes of less than 150ms on average (P50), representing a 90% improvement since May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Krivit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethel Mannin - Bread and Roses]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ethel-mannin-bread-and-roses?v=1727218691</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ethel-mannin-bread-and-roses?v=1727218691"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T22:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ethel Mannin
Title: Bread and Roses
Subtitle: An Utopian Survey and Blueprint
Date: December 1944
Notes: London, December, 1943 -May, 1944.
Source: https://archive.org/details/in.ernet.dli.2015.213271/page/n7

I. UTOPIA — THE EVERLASTING DREAM
 Throughout the ages, from the earliest times, men of all nations have dreamed of that ‘ideal commonwealth whose inhabitants exist under perfect conditions’. What constitutes ‘perfect conditions’ is obviously a matter of personal preferences and prejudices, but there is a common basis to the visionary dream in all its forms — the increase of human happiness, or, perhaps, more accurately, well-being — the greatest good for the greatest number, whether it is the Golden Age of ancient Greek and Roman mythology, or the confused contemporary dream…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Zerzan, Derrick Jensen - Enemy of the State: An Interview with John Zerzan]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/enemy-of-the-state-an-interview-with-john-zerzan?v=1727218416</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/enemy-of-the-state-an-interview-with-john-zerzan?v=1727218416"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T22:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Zerzan, Derrick Jensen
Title: Enemy of the State: An Interview with John Zerzan
Date: September 1, 1998
Source: Retrieved on December 11, 2020 from <derrickjensen.org/1998/09/enemy-state-interview-john-zerzan>

DJ: What is Anarchism? 
JZ: I would say Anarchism is the attempt to eradicate all forms of domination. This includes not only such obvious forms as the nation-state, with its routine use of violence and the force of law, and the corporation, with its institutionalized irresponsibility, but also such internalized forms as patriarchy, racism, homophobia. Also it is the attempt to expose the ways our philosophy, religion, economics, and other ideological constructions perform their primary function, which is to rationalize or naturalize–make seem natural–the domination tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing everyone back to the workplace does little for company culture]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8552</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/bringing-everyone-back-workplace-does-little-company-culture/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon, the online retailer and tech company, has directed all employees to return to the office by early January 2025. Presently workers are required to be in the workplace at least three days a week. In a recent companywide announcement, CEO Andy Jassy says he wants to do away with the current hybrid working arrangement […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intermezzo by Sally Rooney: early thoughts, reviews from critics]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8562</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/intermezzo-sally-rooney-early-reviews-thoughts-critics/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T20:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m guessing a few people had a sleepless night on Monday/Tuesday, after getting hold of the new Sally Rooney novel, Intermezzo, at one of the midnight release events earlier this week. Book reviewers, meanwhile, were probably lucky enough to score an advanced reader copy (ARC), at some point beforehand. Anyway, no spoilers here, just some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections on solitude and superficiality]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-solitude-and-superficiality/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-solitude-and-superficiality/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey,
How long has it been since I last created a blog post? 3 or 4 months? It’s been a long time and it has also been exhausting, both mentally and physically.
Honestly, when I thought about posting something here, I had an idea of what I wanted to write, that is, I knew what the topic would be, but I didn’t know when I would write it because I am mentally exhausted.
Have you ever wished that people wouldn’t talk to you? Because the only thing I’ve been thinking and wishing for is exactly that… I don’t want people to talk to me, I don’t care who it is, passerby or close friend, I just don’t want to talk or respond, so it can take me anywhere from seconds to weeks to respond, and it’s not because something happened or because I’m “afk” temporarily, but because I don’t feel like opening the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[five years of hrt]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.ruby.gay/five-years-of-hrt/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.ruby.gay/five-years-of-hrt/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T18:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[five years! of estrogen!
five years! of breasts!
five years! of watching myself slowly morph into my mother
five years...
the lead up to getting on hrt nearly killed me. i came out to my mother when i was 17, and then to the rest of my family about a year later, just a few weeks before starting hormones. in the year between was a lot of counseling and therapy, working with specialists to try to figure out if this was really what i wanted (it was).
coming out wasn't really my choice; the doctor said that they could "try to do some creative billing," but that ultimately the bill would go through from the gender clinic, and the main insurance holder (my dad) would be able to see that. i was lucky enough that nobody in my (immediate) family cared too much. they all eventually moved over to my new name and pronouns (they/them, at the time -- being referred to as a woman then was, strangely, dysphoria inducing -- but she/her nowadays).
five years...
five years ago i was fresh out of high school. five years ago i had no direction. five years ago i had only barely begun to separate from my abusive father. five years ago i felt powerless.
five years later and a lot has changed. i'm away from him now! i broke into the software industry. i moved twice, i'm living with my partner (whom i met within the last five years). i've met so many wonderful friends. i've lost a few. i've bought a car. i've gotten over my long-standing fear of roller coasters. i've had more than a few mental health episodes... i've also healed a lot of trauma and anxiety. i've learned to be so much of a better person.
and yes, five years of hormones. five years of ruby.
wonder what'll happen in the next five!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[there just isn’t much to say]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/there-just-isnt-much-to-say/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/there-just-isnt-much-to-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve found that bloggers on this site are very passionate about the idea that you should challenge yourself to blog every day. it’s good for you to work out the writing muscle in your brain, it documents your thoughts, you have an archive of who you are, etc etc.
I don’t have much to say. it’s not that I lead some boring life, sometimes you just don’t have anything to comment on. this is a remarkable change for me as someone who tweeted at least 20 times a day over the past three years, but even then most twitter posts are just reactions to other twitter posts. I’ve never really just posted status updates of what I’m doing that day, I’m just commenting on something that came up on my for you.
I have the same issue with journaling. sometimes there is just nothing to say and no introspection to be done. I went to work, my coworkers did this, my kids did this, my parents are doing this, I’m doing whatever. it’s just, like, nothing.
this isn’t to say that everyone that blogs everyday is some sort of super genius with so much insight to offer the world so it’s only natural that they post everyday, because that’s not the case either. a lot of posts I see recently are quotes of something someone found elsewhere, responses to other blogs, blogging about blogging (like I’m doing now), or the typical introspective post.
I don’t know. I’m in the middle. viewing this from a quality over quantity perspective, you wouldn’t want to post everyday so you can just put out your best stuff, but isn’t blogging supposed to be about you? isn’t it supposed to be for you? and not the clamor for engagement and eyes on your post?
but it’s different for everyone, I guess. some people use bearblog like a portfolio, others like a diary, and others like a media dumping ground.
do what you want I guess is the answer here, if there’s an answer at all. no need for an answer, really.
on my end, I don’t think I’ll be a daily blogger. there just isn’t much to say. 🤷🏾‍♀️
reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting the Stimulating STEM Summer Program at USC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5d18c4782911</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/supporting-the-stimulating-stem-summer-program-at-usc-5d18c4782911?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T18:13:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One is proud to support USC’s Stimulating STEM Summer Program to promote STEM education among underrepresented students.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latin American Left amid China, the United States, late progressivism and the far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Latin-American-Left-amid-China-the-United-States</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Latin-American-Left-amid-China-the-United-States"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claudio Katz has just published a book in Spanish entitled America Latina en la encrucijada global [1] (Latin America at the Global Crossroads). Claudio Katz is a Marxist economist and professor at the University of Buenos Aires, author of some fifteen books concerning the Dependency theory fifty years after its emergence, imperialism today, and issues faced by the Latin American Left. His new book concentrates on Latin America and deals with the continent's relations with China and with (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Latin America, 
China]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from AWS App Mesh to Amazon ECS Service Connect]]></title>
        <id>cc8f6cbda91dd5f0445993ecc9602a415fd063e9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/migrating-from-aws-app-mesh-to-amazon-ecs-service-connect/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T15:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After careful consideration, we have made the decision to discontinue AWS App Mesh, effective September 30th, 2026. Until this date, existing AWS App Mesh customers will be able to use the service as normal, including creating new resources and onboarding new accounts via the AWS CLI and AWS CloudFormation. Additionally, AWS will continue to provide […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare partners with Internet Service Providers and network equipment providers to deliver a safer browsing experience to millions of homes]]></title>
        <id>6ZZuN3gorGpsi4nPVR284G</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/safer-resolver"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is extending the use of our public DNS resolver through partnering with ISPs and network providers to deliver a safer browsing experience directly to families. Join us in protecting every Internet user from unsafe content with the click of a button, powered by 1.1.1.1 for Families.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly May Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically generating Cloudflare’s Terraform provider]]></title>
        <id>1M8zVthnUiMpJpGylQuptu</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/automatically-generating-cloudflares-terraform-provider"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cloudflare Terraform provider used to be manually maintained. With the help of our existing OpenAPI code generation pipeline, we’re now automatically generating the provider for better endpoint and attribute coverage, faster updates when new products are announced and a new API documentation site to top it all off. Read on to see how we pulled it all together.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Bednarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A safer Internet with Cloudflare: free threat intelligence, analytics, and new threat detections]]></title>
        <id>3hUMWCRTsPTuqyUixn3aXp</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-safer-internet-with-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are taking some big steps forward in our mission to help build a better Internet. Cloudflare is giving everyone free access to 10+ different website and network security products and features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tremante</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare helps verify the security of end-to-end encrypted messages by auditing key transparency for WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>4tzeNEI3qyBtnWskn5TbUa</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/key-transparency"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is now verifying WhatsApp’s Key Transparency audit proofs to ensure the security of end-to-end encrypted messaging conversations without having to manually check QR codes. We are publishing the results of the proof verification to https://dash.key-transparency.cloudflare.com for independent researchers and security experts to compare against WhatsApp’s. Cloudflare does not have access to underlying public key material or message metadata as part of this infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thibault Meunier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End‑of‑Month Liquidity in the Treasury Market]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31859</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/end-of-month-liquidity-in-the-treasury-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trading activity in benchmark U.S. Treasury securities now concentrates on the last trading day of the month. Moreover, this stepped-up activity is associated with lower transaction costs, as shown by a smaller price impact of trades. We conjecture that increased turn-of-month portfolio rebalancing by passive investment funds that manage relative to fixed-income indices helps explain these patterns.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Dyer, Michael Fleming, and Or Shachar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye, Cohost]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.aurahack.jp/new-post/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.aurahack.jp/new-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T00:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was originally written for Cohost.org
I’ve not… really… spent a lot of energy thinking of a “my time on Cohost” retrospective post like some folks have done (which have all been a pleasure to read!) because I’m not sure I really can. I think it’s easy to pick apart the stuff that’s individually made Cohost such a wonderful place to exist on, and certainly added to the greater whole of the thing, but trying to sum up everything into A Post feels impossible. How do you sum up years of emotion and attachment in a way that’s, like, understandable to others outside your specific lived experience on a website built to let the individual tailor it to their desires.
I tried tackling some of it in my last blog post in a more pointed manner. I’ve been spending a lot more time sorta doomer-think…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Scheduling]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/24/sig-scheduling-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/09/24/sig-scheduling-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this SIG Scheduling spotlight we talked with Kensei Nakada, an
approver in SIG Scheduling.
Introductions
Arvind: Hello, thank you for the opportunity to learn more about SIG Scheduling! Would you
like to introduce yourself and tell us a bit about your role, and how you got involved with
Kubernetes?
Kensei: Hi, thanks for the opportunity! I’m Kensei Nakada
(@sanposhiho), a software engineer at
Tetrate.io. I have been contributing to Kubernetes in my free time for more
than 3 years, and now I’m an approver of SIG-Scheduling in Kubernetes. Also, I’m a founder/owner of
two SIG subprojects,
kube-scheduler-simulator and
kube-scheduler-wasm-extension.
About SIG Scheduling
AP: That's awesome! You've been involved with the project since a long time. Can you provide a
brief overview of SIG Schedu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing Tetris may ease post-traumatic stress disorder symptoms]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8549</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/playing-tetris-may-ease-post-traumatic-stress-disorder-symptoms/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T21:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sara E. Teller, writing for Legal Reader: The research, published in BMC Medicine, focuses on the use of video games, particularly the well-known Tetris game that has been around for decades, to help reduce intrusive memories, a core and sometimes debilitating symptom of the condition. Invented in 1984 by Alexey Pajitnov, Tetris is a straightforward […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamba 1.5 family of models by AI21 Labs is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>6ded5a2482a6ceaea13f37bd0cb8dee31a204b7c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/jamba-1-5-family-of-models-by-ai21-labs-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI21's Jamba 1.5 models enable high-performance long-context language processing up to 256K tokens, with JSON output support and multilingual capabilities across 9 languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2 X8g Instances, Amazon Q generative SQL for Amazon Redshift, AWS SDK for Swift, and more (Sep 23, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>4aa4231deeeef984194acd947c69a278e49f9574</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-x8g-instances-amazon-q-generative-sql-for-amazon-redshift-aws-sdk-for-swift-and-more-sep-23-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Community Days have been in full swing around the world. I am going to put the spotlight on AWS Community Day Argentina where Jeff Barr delivered the keynote, talks and shared his nuggets of wisdom with the community, including a fun story of how he once followed Bill Gates to a McDonald’s! I encourage […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On having outgrown a city]]></title>
        <id>https://coco-fraise.bearblog.dev/on-having-outgrown-a-city/</id>
        <link href="https://coco-fraise.bearblog.dev/on-having-outgrown-a-city/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This impression is staying on my skin like ink stays on the stamp after the paper has already been stamped.
It’s as if every step has already been had. Every smile has been smiled. Every breath has been breathed. Every corner has been explored. One unique place holds on so much memories that it is starting to feel crowded, like this one subway line at 6:38 at night when you come back from work.
I feel this way about Lyon, the city where I grew up. In a kind of weird way that I did not notice at first, this impression became tiring.
It felt like being physically attached to my past. When you see multiple memories at every corner of the street, it makes creating new memories a bit more difficult.
I’ll give you an example.
This morning, I was just out for a morning run and I turned the corner…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one week until i stop casually using social media]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/one-week-until-i-stop-casually-using-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/one-week-until-i-stop-casually-using-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:42:59.487Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[this was crossposted from cohost. the original url was cohost.org/jkap/post/7810928-one-week-until-i-sto
one week until i stop casually using social media. if you see my ass again it's because i need to promote something or i'm reblogging art i like.
the past few years have taught me that i really don't like the microblogging style of social media. you would think that a shorter character limit would lead to concision but it doesn't; it just encourages you to split your thoughts across multiple posts.
i never really enjoyed "posting" on tumblr (which i realize sounds silly given that cohost lifted from tumblr's design the most) so i'm unlikely to start doing that. i genuinely think this might be it for me. i will retreat to my group chats with friends and move to the pre-social media model: if i want to know how my friends are doing, i'll ask them. if i'm gonna be in town somewhere and want to see someone, i'll message them instead of posting into the void.
it's all the same core theme: being deliberate. a focus on social media can hamper your relationships with your non-social media-using friends; they don't know what's going on because you're shouting into the void and they're not in it, but you don't actively talk to them because there's this subconscious assumption that everyone Important to you sees your posts.
anyway. i'm pretty sure i think about social media more than the average person. i'm looking forward to never thinking about social media again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Crump - Not Quite an Anarchist]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-crump-not-quite-an-anarchist?v=1727094416</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-crump-not-quite-an-anarchist?v=1727094416"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T12:26:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Crump
Title: Not Quite an Anarchist
Date: October 1964
Notes: Published in Anarchy #44.
Source: Retrieved on 23rd September 2024 from libcom.org

 “THOMAS PAINE … WAS NEVER ENOUGH of an optimist to let his natural anarchism run its full course.”[1] His contemporary, William Godwin, said in his “Enquiry Concerning Political Justice” (1793), “With what delight must every well-informed friend of mankind look forward to the dissolution of political government, of that brute engine which has been the only perennial cause of the vices of mankind … and no otherwise to be removed than by its utter annihilation.” Paine takes a more negative stance:— “Some writers have so confounded society with government as to leave little or no distinction between them; whereas they are not only diff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Treasury Market Liquidity Improved in 2024?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31880</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/09/has-treasury-market-liquidity-improved-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standard metrics point to an improvement in Treasury market liquidity in 2024 to levels last seen before the start of the current monetary policy tightening cycle. Volatility has also trended down, consistent with the improved liquidity. While at least one market functioning metric has worsened in recent months, that measure is an indirect gauge of market liquidity and suggests a level of current functioning that is far better than at the peak seen during the global financial crisis (GFC).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Fleming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving a Project: Intern Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16999</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/driving-a-project-intern-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a lot of hard work, you’ve landed that coveted internship. Now comes the next big challenge: delivering a meaningful project over the summer. Leading a project independently is an opportunity to sharpen your skills, demonstrate your capabilities, and experience personal growth. As you drive the project on your own, the support from your mentor […]
The post Driving a Project: Intern Edition appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dylan Steen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>