<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-24T12:40:52.448Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-24T12:40:52.448Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/24/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our sporty daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOUTHCOM Commander Laura Richardson Just Described “Plan Colombia” As A Success, A Model for the Region]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272099</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/southcom-commander-laura-richardson-just-described-plan-colombia-as-roaring-success-a-model-for-region.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even the US House of Representatives Foreign Affairs Committee has admitted that Plan Colombia was a resounding failure from a counter-narcotics perspective while providing short-term benefits from a counter-insurgency perspective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[National Grid Wants to Heat More Homes With Converted Food Waste — and Make You Pay For It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272124</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/national-grid-wants-to-heat-more-homes-with-converted-food-waste-and-make-you-pay-for-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:28:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Grid's biogas plant is performing poorly, as shown by downtimes and methane flaring, yet it wants more consumer subsidies to expand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Some Myths Regarding the Genesis of Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272120</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/michael-hudson-some-myths-regarding-the-genesis-of-enterprise.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Modern” elements of enterprise were present  in Mesopotamia in the third millennium BC and the institutions supported long-term growth]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set the Killers Free: the Pardoning of Daniel Perry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323471</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/set-the-killers-free-the-pardoning-of-daniel-perry/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one of the most egregious uses of the pardon power since Bill Clinton freed billionaire tax cheat, Israeli agent and international fugitive Marc Rich as the clock struck midnight on his lamentable administration, last week Texas Gov. Greg Abbott freed an avowed racist who ran a red light, before plunging his car into a crowd of protesters and fatally shooting a man who was trying to protect people from being run over. Abbott granted the killer a pardon, even though the gunman had been obsessed for months with the idea of killing BLM activists. More
The post Set the Killers Free: the Pardoning of Daniel Perry appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s Mouthpiece for Israel: David Ignatius]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-washington-posts-mouthpiece-for-israel-david-ignatius/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s David Ignatius has always been an apologist for the Central Intelligence Agency; then he added the Pentagon to his list for institutional apologies.  But now Ignatius is going much further; he has become the mouthpiece for both the administrations of President Joe Biden and Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu.  His most recent editorial (“The U.S. is assembling the pieces of a Gaza war endgame”) foresees the “contours of a possible exit ramp” in Gaza that is constructed out of sheer fantasy. More
The post The Washington Post’s Mouthpiece for Israel: David Ignatius appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Tested Nukes on Its Own People. It’s Time to Apologize and Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323539</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-u-s-tested-nukes-on-its-own-people-its-time-to-apologize-and-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tina Cordova is intimately familiar with the legacy of the atomic bomb. Her hometown, Tularosa, New Mexico, is just thirty-four miles downwind from the Trinity Test Site, where Manhattan Project scientists first detonated what they called “the Gadget.” When both of her great-grandfathers, who were in Tularosa during the blast, succumbed to stomach cancer ten years later, it was just the beginning of her family’s troubles. More
The post The U.S. Tested Nukes on Its Own People. It’s Time to Apologize and Pay appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Sinclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing University: How the California State University Became Complicit in Palestinian Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323614</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/boeing-university-how-the-california-state-university-became-complicit-in-palestinian-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Over the years, Boeing and its employees have played a vital role in the advancement of Cal State Long Beach.” Jane Close Conoley, President, California State University, Long Beach Pro-Palestinian student protests and encampments have bloomed this spring across U.S. universities. Unsurprisingly, campus administrators have responded with calls for civility and peace — that is,  More
The post Boeing University: How the California State University Became Complicit in Palestinian Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JAKE ALIMAHOMED-WILSON, SABRINA ALIMAHOMED-WILSON, ARACELI ESPARZA, STEVEN OSUNA, DENNIS LÓPEZ AND AZZA BASARUDIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear of Violent Retribution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323653</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/fear-of-violent-retribution/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bit of recent history seems worth recalling as the nation careens towards an election that seems somewhat likely to put a man Noam Chomsky once rightly called “the most dangerous criminal in human history” back in the world’s most powerful office. It’s quite possible that the fascist monster Donald “Take Down the Metal Detectors” Trump would  More
The post Fear of Violent Retribution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Lahore, With Love: Musings of a Traveling Feminista, From Pakistan to Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323581</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/to-lahore-with-love-musings-of-a-traveling-feminista-from-pakistan-to-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So many trips back and forth from the US to Pakistan ever since I "left" Lahore on Sep 12th, 1979. My 21st birthday. I was off to conquer the world, become the free and independent woman I had always dreamt of being, away from the strictures of desi patriarchy- or so I imagined. So many tearful and joyful reunions, departures, and arrivals over four and a half decades that now appear to have passed in the blink of an eye. More
The post To Lahore, With Love: Musings of a Traveling Feminista, From Pakistan to Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fawzia Afzal-Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Three Penny Media Opera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323616</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/trumps-three-penny-media-opera/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has to be some irony that as Donald Trump sits in the dock in lower Manhattan, on charges of cooking his corporate books for $130,000 after paying off a porn star (only the flag-waving Supreme Court would let him walk), while slightly to the west, on Wall Street, the same grifter (here as the  More
The post Trump’s Three Penny Media Opera appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Indicted Congressman’s Club]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323491</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-indicted-congressmans-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-deserved indictments keep hitting Congress. The latest indicted legislator is Texas Democrat Henry Cuellar, the politician backed by former House speaker Nancy Pelosi in his last election, against a more progressive opponent, of course. On May 3, the justice department charged Cuellar with accepting roughly $600,000 from Azerbaijan’s state-owned oil company and a Mexican bank.  More
The post The Indicted Congressman’s Club appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s Above the Law? Israel, Hamas and the ICC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323514</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/whos-above-the-law-israel-hamas-and-the-icc/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While statements that “No one is above the law,” are repeated in the U.S. over the trials of former President Donald Trump, can the same be said internationally? By analogy, Chief Prosecutor Karim Khan of the International Criminal Court (ICC) said yes when he announced he was seeking arrest warrants for Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on charges of war crimes and crimes against humanity. More
The post Who’s Above the Law? Israel, Hamas and the ICC appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constant Killing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323600</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/constant-killing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are constants in this world — occurrences you can count on. Sunrises and sunsets. The tides. That, day by day, people will be born and others will die. Some of them will die in peace, but others, of course, in violence and agony. For hundreds of years, the U.S. military has been killing people.  More
The post Constant Killing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Turse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At Western Sahara: Visiting a Forgotten People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323637</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/at-western-sahara-visiting-a-forgotten-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South of the Algerian town of Tindouf on the border with Western Sahara are five refugee camps. The camps are home to the Sahrawi people of Western Sahara and are administered by their freedom movement Polisario, which is fighting to liberate their homeland from Morocco. Life in the desert camps leaves a deep impression and  More
The post At Western Sahara: Visiting a Forgotten People appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc B. Sanganee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nakba Resurrected – How the Gaza Resistance Ended Segmentation of Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323602</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/nakba-resurrected-how-the-gaza-resistance-ended-segmentation-of-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inadvertently, Israel has pressed the reset button on its war with the Palestinian people, taking back the so-called conflict to square one. Save for a few self-serving Palestinian officials affiliated with the Palestinian Authority (PA), most Palestinians do not seem consumed with the return to the peace process, or even engaged in discussions about two-state  More
The post Nakba Resurrected – How the Gaza Resistance Ended Segmentation of Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Rainforest Collapse?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323589</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/amazon-rainforest-collapse/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A major question is whether a large-scale collapse of the Amazon forest system could actually happen within the twenty-first century.” (Source: Bernardo M. Flores, et al, Critical Transitions in the Amazon Forest System, Nature, Feb. 14, 2024). It may seem absurd to consider collapse of the Amazon rainforest (65-million-years-old) which seems impossible, too far out,  More
The post Amazon Rainforest Collapse? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radical Feminism and the Failures of the Left]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323644</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/radical-feminism-and-the-failures-of-the-left/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was politicized and radicalized fairly late in life, beginning at the age of 30 at the end of the 1980s, when I embraced left politics and radical feminism at the same time. Despite tensions between the two philosophies, I remain committed to both. Back to the ‘80s: Until then, I had been a fairly  More
The post Radical Feminism and the Failures of the Left appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifting the Veil: Demystifying Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323631</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/lifting-the-veil-demystifying-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel has, for decades, created many versions of itself—Israel in politics, in history, in the United States, in books, in movies and on television.  The real Israel, however, has been shrouded behind a veil of deception.  After 7 October 2023, the undisguised coarse Israel has revealed itself.   For years, Israel has made sure that Palestine, with its  More
The post Lifting the Veil: Demystifying Israel  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Misplaced Purity: Democracies and Crimes Against International Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323639</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/a-misplaced-purity-democracies-and-crimes-against-international-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The application for arrest warrants by the Prosecutor of the International Criminal Court, Karim A.A. Khan in the Israel-Hamas War gives us a chance to revisit a recurring theme in the commission of crimes in international humanitarian law.  Certain states, so this logic goes, either commit no crimes, or, if they do, have good reasons for doing so,  More
The post A Misplaced Purity: Democracies and Crimes Against International Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War Cuts the Heart Out of Humankind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323634</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/war-cuts-the-heart-out-of-humankind/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the apartment of my friends in Baghdad (Iraq), they tell me about how each of them had been impacted by the ugliness of the 2003 U.S.-imposed illegal war on their country. Yusuf and Anisa are both members of the Federation of Journalists of Iraq and both have experience as “stringers” for Western media companies  More
The post War Cuts the Heart Out of Humankind appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where, Now, the Big Dream? An Amen for Ambivalence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323642</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/where-now-the-big-dream-an-amen-for-ambivalence/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No symbolic system [i.e., basis for culture] in history has been able to rival religious faith, which forges a bond between the routine behavior… of individuals and ultimate, imperishable truths.  It’s the most enduring, deep-rooted universal form of popular culture that history has ever witnessed….            – Terry Eagleton, Where Does Culture Come from? London Monthly Review 4/25/24  More
The post Where, Now, the Big Dream? An Amen for Ambivalence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of an Illusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323488</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-future-of-an-illusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Eastern race well versed in Western culture and profoundly in sympathy with Western ideals will be established in the Orient. Furthermore, a Jewish state will inevitably fall under the control of American Jews who will work out, along Jewish lines, American ideals and American civilization. —William Yale, US State Department consultant, 1919 Unrelenting mass  More
The post The Future of an Illusion appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iain Boal, T.J. Clark, Joseph Matthews, and Michael Watts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memorium: H. Bruce Franklin (1934-2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323586</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/in-memorium-h-bruce-franklin-1934-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American cultural historian called the creation of the US Space Force an “open declaration of our national insanity.” This CounterPunch feature, in honor of Professor Franklin who passed away on May 19, 2024, is from a previous discussion with him in 2018 and found in Foreign Policy Journal). Bruce Franklin is a US academic who specializes in  More
The post In Memorium: H. Bruce Franklin (1934-2024) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Myths Regarding the Genesis of Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/some-myths-regarding-the-genesis-of-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a colloquium on early entrepreneurs had been convened in the early 20th century, most participants would have viewed traders as operating on their own, bartering at prices that settled at a market equilibrium established spontaneously in response to fluctuating supply and demand. According to the Austrian economist Carl Menger, money emerged as individuals and  More
The post Some Myths Regarding the Genesis of Enterprise appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Labor Today and the Way Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323583</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/us-labor-today-and-the-way-forward/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The labor movement in the United States used to be respected and looked to for leadership; people cared about what positions labor took, watched when they mobilized, and noticed the causes they supported.  This was especially true among the left. Today, for most of the country, crickets.  Including much of the left.  And yet, labor  More
The post US Labor Today and the Way Forward appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Scipes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Ten Ways to Soften a Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323625</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/top-ten-ways-to-soften-a-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Gen·o·cide: the deliberate killing of a large number of people from a particular nation or ethnic group with the aim of destroying that nation or group.” -Oxford Dictionary “Now we all have one common goal— erasing the Gaza Strip from the face of the earth.” — Nissim Vaturi, Deputy Speaker of the Knesset [Israeli parliament].  More
The post Top Ten Ways to Soften a Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamus Cooke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024: People Starve As The Rich Get Richer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323622</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/2024-people-starve-as-the-rich-get-richer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earning enough to pay the rent or mortgage, cover utility bills and travel costs, buy food and have the occasional coffee is impossible for many. But its not hard for everyone, is it; there are a small number of people living among us who don’t have to worry about the bills, are not troubled when  More
The post 2024: People Starve As The Rich Get Richer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Peebles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edgelords and Snowflakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323605</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/edgelords-and-snowflakes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Libertarianism is a people’s movement and a liberation movement. it seeks the sort of open, non-coercive society in which the people, the living, free, distinct people may voluntarily associate, dis-associate and, as they see fit, participate in the decisions affecting their lives. This means a truly free market in everything from ideas to idiosyncrasies. It  More
The post Edgelords and Snowflakes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicky Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Asian American Renters Are Struggling to Pay for Housing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323519</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/many-asian-american-renters-are-struggling-to-pay-for-housing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Asian American households have the highest median income of the major racial and ethnic groups. Although Asian Americans have a higher median income than the non-Hispanic white population, they also have a higher poverty ratethan the white population on the Supplemental Poverty Measure (SPM). (The SPM is a more comprehensive poverty measure that also makes  More
The post Many Asian American Renters Are Struggling to Pay for Housing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is the Literary World Silent on Gaza?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323485</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/why-is-the-literary-world-silent-on-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anis, I’m disturbed by the banner image you chose which paints Israel as a [sic] evil monolith—this is a particularly disturbing image as it draws on the antisemitic trope of blood libel. But beyond that, the image shows the Star of David with an impaled child—again, this pulls on some of the very worst anti-Semitic  More
The post Why Is the Literary World Silent on Gaza? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANIS SHIVANI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture of Cities: Shapeshifters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323629</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/architecture-of-cities-shapeshifters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The oasis that was once Africa: Travel is neither romantic nor adventurous: It is biblical: It is about a past not yet seen. It is about a place known as our plane.: I have grappled with the significance and pleasures of my photography from series and series series of historical compositions and recitations. My mind  More
The post Architecture of Cities: Shapeshifters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Schulman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Missive from an American Patriot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323560</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/missive-from-an-american-patriot/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Important missive from Gladys Flagg, Patriot: They say courage is just another word for bravery, but on that fateful day, I learned the real meaning of courage is refusing to give in to the woke leftist mob. On that fateful day, I was going to the store. A harmless ordinary woman (born that way, thank  More
The post Missive from an American Patriot appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Tripp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rebirth of “Ban the Bomb” in an Era of an increase of the Danger of Nuclear War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/24/the-rebirth-of-ban-the-bomb-in-an-era-of-an-increase-of-the-danger-of-nuclear-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During a recent visit to a hospital, where I had the chance to speak extensively with Doctors and Staff members, I heard a number of them state that they were worried and apprehensive about the increasing danger of Nuclear War, and the rise of warfare in general. I think that the once powerful cry of  More
The post The Rebirth of “Ban the Bomb” in an Era of an increase of the Danger of Nuclear War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of the Mini Navals]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:08:26.314Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed a proliferation of a new essayist archetype on the internet in recent years - the "Mini Navals." Modeled after angel investor, entrepreneur, and philosopher Naval Ravikant, these mini me's desperately want to become the next big thought leader by aping Naval's pithy, maxim-filled style. Naval has achieved success through decades of experience, and he reflects on it. In contrast, Mini Navals try to compress "wisdom" into a handful of tweets and blog posts.
Most Mini Navals tend to be in their early-to-mid 20s, still figuring things out but portraying themselves as gurus who have life all figured out. They boldly proclaim hot takes on everything from tech trends to philosophy to politics, with little credibility to back it up other than having read Naval's entire archive. With the Mini Navals, it's usually just word salad dressed up as profundity.
Sometimes, the best philosophy is just living intentionally without needing to proselytize your process. In a world that could use more wisdom, perhaps we don't need so many more mini-versions when the original is still strong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Karpenter Nodes with Multus on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>66b95967b06e8c62395ccb2841f747f47b41fe13</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/deploying-karpenter-nodes-with-multus-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T04:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container based Telco workloads use Multus CNI primarily for traffic or network segmentation. Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) supports Multus CNI enabling users to attach multiple network interfaces, apply advanced network configuration and segmentation to Kubernetes-based applications running on AWS. One of the many benefits of running applications on AWS is resource elasticity (scaling out and scaling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rolando Jr Hilvano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Gossip]]></title>
        <id>https://erickrueger.com/good-gossip/</id>
        <link href="https://erickrueger.com/good-gossip/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[⏲ 3-minute read | last updated {{ post_last_modified }} ago
Difficult to control and spreads quickly - but unlike fires, not always dangerous.(photo credit: sippakorn yamkasikorn)

Humans are social creatures, and we receive a lot of information about the world when we gossip - it isn't (necessarily) a bad thing.
Evolution
Gossip is in our blood. Humans who shared information among social circles had an evolutionary advantage. They were able to find those among the group they could trust, and (more importantly) identify bad actors. At the most basic level, gossip was a tool for survival. It answered important questions that helped the group function:
Who wields the most power/influence in the group? (alliances to make)
Who has limited resources? (alliances to avoid)
Whose sleeping with who…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telstra redundancies, AI robots come in, the future is now]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/telstra-redundancies-ai-robots-future-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s largest telecommunications company, Telstra, announced this week it was making about three thousand employees, or ten percent, of its workforce redundant. About three hundred people were sent home straightaway — hopefully with some sort of pay-out — while the remainder will depart between now and the end of the year. This is terrible news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build bases on the Moon, instead of going for a week]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7671</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/build-bases-moon-instead-going-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA is dead set keen to return to the Moon. But their current plan, called Artemis, is dead set crazy, writes Polish-American entrepreneur and writer, Maciej Cegłowski: You don’t have to be a rocket scientist to wonder what’s going on here. If we can put a man on the moon, then why can’t we just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272083</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics;  can the Democrats allow Trump to take office, White House issues corrections, Marijuana policy ("and boogie they will") ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G7: Whether or not to maintain the suspension of Ukrainian debt payments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the G7 discussing Ukraine's debt? 
English

/ 
G7 / G20, 
Debt in Northern countries, 
Ukraine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[沈阳 photo dump（mostly 老北市）]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:19:59.869Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some photographs from the Chinese city of 沈阳 (Shenyang).

I could spend all day browsing these five-story malls. This one boasted restaurants, cafes, daycares, basketball courts, go-karting, and live fish.

Fine dining in 沈阳. These are the food models in the lobby. My mom fighting with my aunt and uncle-in-law to first pay the bill, and when she loses that battle, to order fewer items. Lots of 客气 to go around. 

Although it may look the part, those flowers are not lavender. You can't see it here, but the whole time we were in Shenyang it looked as though it were snowing. I later learned that the "snow" was actually the seed hairs of the willow and the poplar trees. It looks cool until the fuzz gets in your eyes, on your clothes, everywhere. (source)
老北市
A popular night market in 沈阳 which runs every night. If you're there at the right time, you can catch the show with flying drone-powered phoenixes shooting fireworks from their wings. Sadly I don't have any good photos of that show — my senses were overwhelmed for most of the night (in a good way).










Night markets have been ruined for me forever. How can anything measure up to that? Not to mention we passed two markets en route to 老北市 that also looked better than anything I'd ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masks Work, Our Comprehensive Review Has Found]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272067</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/masks-work-our-comprehensive-review-has-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, a rigorous study on mask use shows definitively that masks do indeed work, as in reduce transmission of respiratory diseases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272059</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our crepuscular daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das: The Economic Costs of  Modern War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271986</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/satyajit-das-the-economic-costs-of-modern-war.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How economic, military and political costs and consequences are intersecting in the Ukraine and Israel-Palestine conflicts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skill Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:37:22.552Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term skill issue is thrown around Twitter a lot. It comes from gaming culture. If you can't beat a level. It is a skill issue. Just level up and win. If you think about it, it is a powerful term. It gives power to the player.
Applied to life everything is a skill issue. Can't do the perfect juggle? Skill issue. Can't write awesome distributed performant code? Skill issue. Can't convince a penguin to try your awesome new ice cream? You guessed it. Skill issue. It is a powerful mindset. Gives you extreme ownership.
But there is a catch. Do you take ownership of other people's shitty behavior? No. You can take ownership of the triggers and environment you perhaps created to lead to that shitty behavior. Especially if you are in positions of power to have a big impact(ie: manager/CEO). Otherwise, constant shitty behavior is their burden to bear. Avoid such people. People rarely change and you don't need the negativity in your life.
Here the skill issue is effectively able to isolate and weed out the negativity. This is purely in a professional context. In a more personal context, things are a lot more messy. I don't have an answer for that which works. A skill issue on my end. Need more life experience to resolve it.
Make everything a skill issue and just level up!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272061</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/why-corporations-choose-lawlessness-to-fight-unions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers at companies like Apple and Starbucks face armies of union-busting lawyers advising employers to repeatedly violate labor laws.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collapse of the Thwaites Glacier Has Accelerated]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272054</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/collapse-of-the-thwaites-glacier-has-accelerated.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The timetable for the collapse of the Thwaites Glacier is collapsing, and why that matters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running clubs, the IndieWeb of the dating realm?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7657</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/running-clubs-indieweb-dating-realm/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Marshall, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Run South Yarra co-founder Tom Adair is wary of any suggestion that run clubs are the new Tinder, yet relationships are born here, and side-by-side chats while jogging, he notes, are definitely less pressurised than face-to-face interactions. (Plus, you can always pick up the pace and scoot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16644</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/balancing-old-tricks-with-new-feats-ai-powered-conversion-from-enzyme-to-react-testing-library-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of frontend development, one thing remains certain: change is the only constant. New frameworks emerge, and libraries can become obsolete without warning. Keeping up with the ever-changing ecosystem involves handling code conversions, both big and small. One significant shift for us was the transition from Enzyme to React Testing Library (RTL), prompting […]
The post Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergii Gorbachov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composable data management at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21235</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/data-infrastructure/composable-data-management-at-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, Meta’s data management systems have evolved into a composable architecture that creates interoperability, promotes reusability, and improves engineering efficiency.  We’re sharing how we’ve achieved this, in part, by leveraging Velox, Meta’s open source execution engine, as well as work ahead as we continue to rethink our data management systems.  Data is at [...]
Read More...
The post Composable data management at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21222</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/22/security/post-quantum-readiness-tls-pqr-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:35:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the internet (like most digital infrastructure in general) relies heavily on the security offered by public-key cryptosystems such as RSA, Diffie-Hellman (DH), and elliptic curve cryptography (ECC). But the advent of quantum computers has raised real questions about the long-term privacy of data exchanged over the internet. In the future, significant advances in quantum [...]
Read More...
The post Post-quantum readiness for TLS at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans in the Labor Market: 2024 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29773</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/veterans-are-doing-better-in-the-labor-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans constitute a significant segment of the male labor force, and understanding labor market disparities between veterans and non‑veterans is an important component of studying disparities in the economy as a whole. In a previous Liberty Street Economics post, we have shown that even relative to a group of comparable non-veterans, veterans have lower employment and labor force participation rates. One year later, we see that veterans continue to experience lower labor market attachment and the employment gap has widened, though the earnings gap has closed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Dan Garcia, and Maxim Pinkovskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanding Regional Services configuration flexibility for customers]]></title>
        <id>66448139abf9e2000aee8587</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/expanding-regional-services-configuration-flexibility-for-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we're happy to announce expanded capabilities that will allow you to configure Regional Services for an increased set of defined regions to help you meet your specific requirements for being able to control where your traffic is handled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wesley Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is generally available: a unified interface for managing and scaling your generative AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>664cf64607441c000a06e4ed</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-gateway-is-generally-available"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Gateway is an AI ops platform that provides speed, reliability, and observability for your AI applications. With a single line of code, you can unlock powerful features including rate limiting, custom caching, real-time logs, and aggregated analytics across multiple providers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Liao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A genuine selfmade billionaire]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52714</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/22/a-genuine-selfmade-billionaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe that no-one deserves to be a billionaire. In the public realm, defenders of wealth concentration often come up with an example of a person who has created all their wealth themselves – the selfmade billionaire. They didn’t get their money from inheritance or some other form of luck, but from entrepreneurial instincts and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[James Wolfensohn switches on the charm (1995-2005)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/James-Wolfensohn-switches-on-the-charm-1995-2005"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[apartment hunting, and finding meaning in living alone]]></title>
        <id>https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/</id>
        <link href="https://pesto.bearblog.dev/apartment-hunting-and-finding-meaning-in-living-alone/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:38:01.193Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fall, I'll be moving to a new city to pursue graduate studies. I thought it'd be a good idea to move in a few months early to get a feel for the area - and also avoid fighting over good areas around campus, especially if I wait too long.
Next week I'm flying out to visit some apartments. It dawned upon me that this would be the first time where I live truly alone - no housemates, roommates, parents, pets - it'll be just me, in a new city. I'm excited of course, but also quite scared. The thought of being free and landing into a new city is something amazing, but for the first time, I'm really on my own.
I moved back with my parents to save on rent a year ago. And while I do appreciate them for their generosity, I think it's time for me to leave; I've been paying rent with my mental health, something a lot of Asian kids can relate to. I also feel restricted when I came back to the city where I attended high school. It was like I'm in purgatory: suffering for some time before entering heaven (a place of my own).
It's a big step, despite something I'm excited for. Yet very scary. But if I'm scared to do it, it's exactly because I'm scared that I should do it.
I think I'm ready now. Ready to take that big leap, into a new home, nearly a thousand miles away from where I grew up.
The (paper) journal I've kept since 2020 is reaching the last few pages, appropriately. It's as if it knew that my journey here was coming to an end, and a new one will begin soon.
I'll be buying a new notebook once in Seattle. Only appropriate when closing a chapter, no?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do I have to write my own Anki cards?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.memothon.com/why-do-i-have-to-write-my-own-anki-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.memothon.com/why-do-i-have-to-write-my-own-anki-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T01:14:11.309Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You really shouldn't have to write your own Anki cards today.
There's a really common sentiment that using pre-made or llm generated decks can't replace creating your own.
This is probably true. Writing your own flashcards forces you into a state where you have to actually think and organize the concepts together in your head into things that are digestible.
Often the flashcards that people create are not conducive to review. It's hard to create cards that aren't easy to remember the "shape" of later on instead of actually remembering the content. And drilling one small piece of the puzzle doesn't fill in the rest of the pie.
LLMs are sophisticated enough now to generate variations on flashcards on-demand. But nobody has wired up LLMs natively with spaced repetition for learning. It seems like everyone has stopped at "generate 100 flashcards for me based on this pdf," which does result in flashcards that aren't going to help you remember things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental selling point of all productivity advice is getting more done in less time. It's a good hook. I have over the years consumed a lot of content around productivity. It took me a long time to realise I was making a fundamental mistake.
I assumed I would stumble upon some specific protocol that I can follow perfectly and my life is set. So I have tried it all. All kinds of wake-sleep times. Journaling. All kinds of productivity apps and timing techniques. Trying to get as much damn sunlight in my little eye holes within x minutes of waking up(yes, I had a Huberman era). Nothing worked.
The fundamental mistake in all of this is I thought of my mind as some unmotivated child that I could be strict with and discipline into getting stuff done. But if you have ever taught young children( I have) you will know that discipline and fear only get you so far. Getting them interested in the topic changes the game.
This realisation drastically changed my life. I can get my mind interested in doing things through self-programming. Everyone is different on how to do this. Many of these routines and techniques that we hear about are just outcomes of effective self-programming unique to that individual. Each of us needs to find our unique way.
How to program your mind? You can introspect and the documentation of your mind will reveal itself to you. Also, there are some ways you can make the mind more malleable to programming. I have given a framework I follow for this in my 'Hacking Hardwork' post.
There is no golden technique that will save you. Only you can save yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My 2001: A Space Odyssey remake joke post trained Google AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7631</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2001-a-space-odyssey-remake-joke-post-trained-google-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two and bit years ago, I spotted an entry on Fandom about a “remake” of the Stanley Kubrick sci-fi classic, 2001: A Space Odyssey. Being a 2001 fan, I naturally wrote about it. I’ve had a lot of fun with the post ever since. People stumble upon it every now and again, and link to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth wins NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of year 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7637</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/she-is-the-earth-wins-nsw-premiers-literary-awards-book-year-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[She is the Earth, a work of verse, written by Yankunytjatjara (South Australia) poet Ali Cobby Eckermann, was named the NSW Premiers Literary Awards book of the year, on Monday 20 May 2024. Award judges were unstinting in their praise of Eckermann’s writing: She is the Earth is a stunning verse novel that takes the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An indie guide to the IndieWeb, by Wing Pang]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7641</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indie-guide-indieweb-wing-pang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based product designer Wing Pang, whom I wrote about last week, has published a comprehensive guide to the IndieWeb. Coming from a design background, joining the IndieWeb was an incredibly exciting and rewarding, yet maze-like journey. To be honest, almost every step of the way was like a leap! But I’ve learnt so much […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring fair bandwidth allocation for Amazon EKS Workloads]]></title>
        <id>6094b32da7c2d5cacc202444ec0b024d73ee06c4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/ensuring-fair-bandwidth-allocation-for-amazon-eks-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Independent Service Vendor (ISV) users often offer their end-user solutions hosted on a multi-tenant architecture to reduce cost and operational management. However, this approach can lead Kubernetes clusters to resource exhaustion or network starvation issues that impact neighboring workloads. By default, Kubernetes provides capabilities to enforce resource availability such as CPU and memory to prevent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, bringing back the blogosphere one blog at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7643</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/blog-of-the-day-bringing-back-blogosphere-one-blog-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog of the .Day, yes, styled as Blog of the .Day, a collaboration between James of James’ Coffee Blog, and Joe Crawford, will highlight a new blog every day. Aside from casting the spotlight daily on a blog, another goal of the project is to bring the term blogosphere back into popular usage. For those […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouth Dildos]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/mouth-dildos/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:41:59.234Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People that use mouth dildos annoy the shit out of me. Either commit and smoke a cigarette, or give it up.
I hate smoking. I think it's fucking disgusting and I don't understand why anyone would want to do it. I especially hate it when there's a gaggle of smokers huddled around the front door of a pub, tooting away on their fags. It's vile and I don't want my pink fluffy lungs affected by that shit.
But do you know what I hate more than smoking?
Mouth dildos.
What the fuck is a mouth dildo?
-- Everyone
This is a mouth dildo:

Not only do you look ridiculous putting that stupid fucking contraption in your mouth, but the plumes of flavoured vapour that bellow from these things make you look even more like an utter cunt.
I don't want to be subjected to the cherry ice cream vapour pouring from your mouth dildos, seemingly by the bucket load. At least smokers are committing, knowing they're gonna kill themselves, have decided to enjoy it while they're here.
But you mouth dildo fuckers are the worst. We don't want to smell your stupid fucking vape. So put it away because you look (and smell) like a dick head.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Changing Landscape of Corporate Credit]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29223</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/the-changing-landscape-of-corporate-credit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firms’ access to credit is a crucial determinant of their investment, employment, and overall growth decisions. While we usually think of their ability to borrow as determined by aggregate credit conditions, in reality firms have a number of markets where they can borrow, and conditions can vary across those markets. In this post, we investigate how the composition of debt instruments on U.S. firms’ balance sheets has evolved over the last twenty years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Boyarchenko and Leonardo Elias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Mr. Mitsotakis criminalizes, threatens and represses students who defend international legality!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/When-Mr-Mitsotakis-criminalizes-threatens-and-represses-students-who-defend"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If some people think they can repeat what they've seen in other countries and occupy universities, pitch tents and make a mess, they're deeply mistaken”. This - so eminently delicate - statement by the Greek Prime Minister, which followed the brutal “evacuation” of the law faculty on Tuesday May 14 (28 arrests), can only surprise the uninformed: the Greek state and its governments have always had a soft spot for anything to do with apartheid and apartheid regimes! Today Israel, formerly South (...)
English

/ 
Greece, 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ilya Kharkow - The Advice Led to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ilya-kharkow-the-advice-led-to-hell-cs?v=1716239906"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ilya Kharkow
Title: The Advice Led to Hell
Date: May 16, 2024
Source: https://actionweek.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/16/rady-vedou-do-pekla-ilya-kharkow/#more-1104

 I wrote about how difficult it was to get from Kyiv to Lviv on the first day of a full-scale war in the novel THE MINING BOYS. But when I finally got there, it only got worse. 
 The people who sheltered me sincerely did not understand why I did not want to defend the country with weapons in my hands. My hope to go to Europe seemed like a betrayal to them. At the same time, I had to hide from them not only my fear, but also my culture and my orientation. 
 These same people advised me to voluntarily join the territorial defense. Their acquaintances, who also didn’t want to fight, deliberately signed up there so they wouldn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The health benefits of giving up drinking coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/health-benefits-giving-up-drinking-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with many things we consume, the science on coffee can be conflicted. One decade caffeine consumption is a no-no, the next it seems coffee is quite beneficial. Regular readers will know I’m a coffee drinker, but in — what I consider to be — moderation: two (large serve) cups per day. But some people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I'm blogging again]]></title>
        <id>https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/</id>
        <link href="https://quincyzikmund.com/why-im-blogging-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:55:38.443Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the glory days of the internet, when social media was just becoming mainstream, I used to blog regularly. I would write and publish a post anywhere from 1 - 3 times a week.
I didn't monetize my blog and I had no dreams of my personal site becoming a business. It was simply a place for me to share things that were on my mind and lessons learned from books I was reading.
Fast forward many years and what we have is the current state of the internet.
Everything is an ad. Everyone is an influencer. And the algorithms determine what we see and dictate what we post. And for some reason they insist on the entire population becoming video producers.
It's an endless game that I lost my taste for long ago.
That's why I'm attempting to blog again. I need somewhere to get my thoughts and opinions out without distraction and without too much tech.
If the internet stresses you out as much as it does me, might I suggest starting your own blog?
Or heck, maybe just quit the social internet altogether.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;A Reprieve for Assange&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism as ‘espionage’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Application Load Balancer IPv6, Amazon S3 pricing update, Amazon EC2 Flex instances, and more (May 20, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3ec4a6e752f974d277f95d9da7228e9f5bba4ba4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-application-load-balancer-ipv6-amazon-s3-pricing-update-amazon-ec2-flex-instances-and-more-may-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is in full swing around the world, with last week’s events in Bengaluru, Berlin, and  Seoul, where my blog colleague Channy delivered one of the keynotes. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon S3 will no longer charge for several HTTP error codes – A customer reported […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O povo pelo povo e o RS acaba em menos de seis meses]]></title>
        <id>https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/o-povo-pelo-povo-e-o-rs-acaba-em-menos-de-seis-meses/</id>
        <link href="https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/o-povo-pelo-povo-e-o-rs-acaba-em-menos-de-seis-meses/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:31:41.361Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A direita, os anarcocapitalistas (embora este termo seja discutível) e a extrema-direita brasileira, diante do crime ambiental praticado no Rio Grande do Sul, conseguiram emplacar uma bela história: o povo pelo povo.
É muito importante salientar como o povo brasileiro se uniu para ajudar o povo do Rio Grande do Sul. É reconfortante observar que o próprio povo, especialmente os mais pobres, uniu-se no próprio RS para ajudar os outros. Voluntários que não têm muito em casa saem às 5h para atender 12h em um abrigo onde as pessoas perderam tudo. Isso é significativo, especialmente após o período de 2018 a 2023, em que o Brasil parecia uma poça de sangue (e ainda parece, em certa medida), pois mostra que o povo ainda é solidário, mesmo que precise de uma tragédia para uni-los.
O problema é que …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruptions Have Eased, But Remain a Concern]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30028</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/supply-chain-disruptions-have-eased-but-remain-a-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain disruptions became a major headache for businesses in the aftermath of the pandemic. Indeed, in October 2021, nearly all firms in our regional business surveys reported at least some difficulty obtaining the supplies they needed. These supply chain disruptions were a key contributor to the surge in inflation that occurred as the economy recovered from the pandemic recession. In this post, we present new measures of supply availability from our Business Leaders Survey and Empire State Manufacturing Survey that closely track the New York Fed’s Global Supply Chain Pressure Index (GSCPI). We will begin publishing these data on a monthly basis starting in June. These indexes indicate that supply availability had generally been improving since early 2023, but over the past couple of months, improvement has stalled. This trend is concerning since our May Supplemental Survey indicates that between a third and a half of businesses in the region are experiencing difficulties obtaining supplies, and many are reducing operations and raising prices to compensate, though to a lesser extent than a few years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel and Richard Deitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Godfrey Wood: &ldquo;Battle Machine&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrospectives on Podemos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSGE models — a total waste of time]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45375</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/20/dsge-models-a-total-waste-of-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll While one can understand that some of the elements in DSGE models seem to appeal to Keynesians at first sight, after closer examination, these models are in fundamental contradiction to Post-Keynesian and even traditional Keynesian thinking. The DSGE model is a model in which output is determined in the labour market as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchy In Action - Anarchy in the Haitian Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchy-in-action-anarchy-in-the-haitian-revolution?v=1716166084</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchy-in-action-anarchy-in-the-haitian-revolution?v=1716166084"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchy In Action
Title: Anarchy in the Haitian Revolution
Source: Retrieved on 19 May 2024 from anarchyinaction.org/index.php?title=Anarchy_in_the_Haitian_Revolution

 Following many years of hidden and small-scale resistance, African slaves in the French colony of Saint Domingue (or San Domingo) rose up in 1791 against their colonizers and slave masters. By 1804, they abolished slavery, expelled the French colonizers, and established the independent republic of Haiti. Haiti was the name given to the Caribbean island by the Tainos before colonizers arrived, slaughtered the entire indigenous population, and imported African slaves. 
 While the 1776 and 1789 revolutions of the USA and France were grounded in exclusionary “citizens’ rights,” the Haitian Revolution stood out for a com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Completing the largest migration in Kubernetes history]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since as early as Kubernetes v1.7, the Kubernetes project has pursued the ambitious goal of removing built-in cloud provider integrations (KEP-2395).
While these integrations were instrumental in Kubernetes' early development and growth, their removal was driven by two key factors:
the growing complexity of maintaining native support for every cloud provider across millions of lines of Go code, and the desire to establish
Kubernetes as a truly vendor-neutral platform.
After many releases, we're thrilled to announce that all cloud provider integrations have been successfully migrated from the core Kubernetes repository to external plugins.
In addition to achieving our initial objectives, we've also significantly streamlined Kubernetes by removing roughly 1.5 million lines of code and reduci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What has happened to cover versions of popular songs?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7624</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-happened-cover-versions-popular-songs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, Australian radio station Triple J, invites a band or musician to record a cover of a song, for their Like A Version show. Anything goes here. About two years ago, Sydney based Australian DJ Dave Winnel performed a cover of Africa, by Toto, not the sort of music you’d usually hear on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World, I guess?]]></title>
        <id>https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/</id>
        <link href="https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:28:15.910Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay... exhales
Here we go.
Hi, I'm Meï ! And welcome to this blog. Or this attempt at a blog.
It's been a few weeks since I felt a lot of nostalgia for the Internet of old, the one I discovered as a lil' kid, on my tenth birthday, circa 2007.
A friend, Seeker, began working on his own blog a few months back. I really liked his articles about DIY and Game Dev, and on a whim asked him his tech stack with the intent of setting something up for myself.
I used to write quite a bit a few years ago. Especially when I got to the big city after high school. Welcome to Fucktopia1 was a small series detailing my new life far from the countryside.
As of late, I've been trying to get back into writing. Essays to recommend some games, some small fictions, and lore for TTRPGs, I've been slowly but surely getting back into it. But I didn't really manage to find a public, even for the essays in places (well, Discord servers in this case) dedicated to the exact IP I was trying to promote.
This built up as a bit of frustration, and is another of the reasons I felt like doing a blog. I wanted to be more open to the world, able to write in a place anyone could read if they stumble on the place.
So once again, here we go!
1. As a note, the "Fucktopia" is a reference to Souillon's comic book "Hello Fucktopia". Couldn't find a listing in English, sorry! It's available in French & Spanish, at least..
My small rules of writing
Try to write regularly. Not necessarily everyday, but I should strive for a post per week at least.
Focus! I'm super prone to tangents and often stray off-topic. A post should be on a single subject, unless this is a post consciously made for tangents and chaos.
No stressing over this. I already stress over too much, let's keep this place as my comfy Internet place.
Let's hope it goes well. And I hope you'll enjoy this blog and its topics.
Fan-art of Cyberpunk Bartender Action: VA-11 HALL-A, by rnna_7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Pézenas]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52709</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/19/sunday-photoblogging-pezenas-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T07:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Generalist]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bear in a circus is interesting. So is a juggler and a man on the unicycle. A bear on a unicycle juggling swords on the other hand is something extremely unique. Something you would pay good money to see. A smart generalist is kinda like that.
A smart generalist is a person who is 80/20 across multiple fields. This means they have reached 80 Percent understanding/capability across multiple fields leveraging around 20 percent of the effort that would typically be needed to fully master it. It makes them unique.
The primary skill of a smart generalist is the ability to get from 0 to 80 in a new field quickly. They can quickly identify high ROI leverage points of a subject. It is a learned skill. They also have strong convictions that anything can be learned and learned fast. Even things considered 'tough' by society.
On the other hand, we have the cracked specialists. People really good at one thing. Getting to the frontiers and advancing human knowledge. Creating absolutely beautiful works in that 'one thing'.
It is a sliding scale. We all lie somewhere between a specialist and a generalist. But we could all do some good to realise we are not limited. We can do multiple things if we want to. It is easy to be hemmed in. To define your identity as 'Software Engineer' or 'Writer' or 'XYZ'. That is what school teaches -'Specialisation'. But humans are versatile. We are the OG general intelligence. Capable of adapting and doing multiple things.
Don't forget the 'General' in General Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>