<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-20T18:41:14.606Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-20T18:41:14.606Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Healthcare and the State of Science, Plus Baseball and Abundance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294308</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-healthcare-and-the-state-of-science-plus-baseball-and-abundance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part the First. How Did the United States Get This Healthcare System?  I distinctly remember the first time this question occurred to me, because as the child of a union household a visit to the doctor or the Emergency Room (trees were made to fall out of) was never a problem.  I was twenty years […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Robin: &ldquo;Waiting Game&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On ‘late capitalism’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Hear It or Actually Witness It?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICE’s Rap Sheet Grows With Continuing Defiance of Congressional Oversight at Facilities, Attempt to Write Its Own Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294305</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/ices-rap-sheet-grows-with-continuing-defiance-of-congressional-oversight-at-facilities-attempt-to-write-its-own-rules.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T13:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICE is becoming even more high-handed in its defiance of legally mandated Congressional oversight rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Lagarde’s “global euro” is a fantasy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T12:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The euro remains plagued by structural and political flaws that make this impossible — and thank God for that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/20/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294279</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-20-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T10:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our luminous daily links, including Trump says he needs two weeks to decide if he wants to start WWIII and how moths use the Milky Way for GPS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Lagarde’s Delusions of Grandeur(o)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294215</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/christine-lagardes-delusions-of-grand-euro.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the US dollar's decline deepens, is this the EU's "global Euro moment"?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What if MAGA Has a Point About Science?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294287</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/what-if-maga-has-a-point-about-science.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T07:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the fallen legitimacy of science in the US, and what might be done about that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Is Taxing the World’s Poorest — and Is Disguising It as Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294276</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-us-is-taxing-the-worlds-poorest-and-is-disguising-it-as-regulation.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T05:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet more mean-spirited US conduct, here via taxing remittances, hurting families of (often legal) migrants and their home countries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Big One]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several months ago I wrote two essays on Russian grand strategy. (My apologies on never completing the nuclear one, an extremely necessary but far too grim subject for my taste.) In that series of essays I made a few assertions I want to bring to your attention again in a more contemporary context. First, that the result of wars tend to confirm strengths of the coalition arrayed against the main combatants before the war even started. This is, in fact, not an assertion, but an iron law of warfare that still exists in chimpanzee warfare. See Strategy: a history, chapter one, by Freedman if you disagree.
 
Second, that big global dustups tend to run in about 100 year cycles these days.
So, take a look around–got a big hot war in the Ukraine slightly analogous to the Sino-Japanese war of the 1930s. Next, you got weird, unresolved shenanigans in the Middle East that have a weird reverse-appeasement type feal.
We’re quite possible looking at the two opening battles of WWIII, right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Operational Troubleshooting with Amazon Q Developer CLI]]></title>
        <id>6ca0238df379c9f06e7af49f9ea247df0b913de3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/streamline-operational-troubleshooting-with-amazon-q-developer-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is the most capable generative AI–powered assistant for software development, helping developers perform complex workflows. Amazon Q Developer command-line interface (CLI) combines conversational AI with direct access to AWS services, helping you understand, build, and operate applications more effectively. The Amazon Q Developer CLI executes commands, analyzes outputs, and provides contextual recommendations […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new AWS CDK EKS v2 L2 Constructs]]></title>
        <id>99b0d8b7cbff701292b81232dbf10edca9376525</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/announcing-the-new-aws-cdk-eks-v2-l2-constructs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today, we’re announcing the release of aws-eks-v2 construct, a new alpha version of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) L2 construct for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). This construct represents a significant change in how developers can define and manage their EKS environments using infrastructure as code. While maintaining the powerful capabilities of its predecessor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Luigi Restelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate development with secure access to Amazon Q Developer using PingIdentity]]></title>
        <id>a2400f3bcbd784c93bb5d83c61721efb7a0b8517</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-development-with-secure-access-to-amazon-q-developer-using-pingidentity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Customers adopting Amazon Q Developer, a generative AI-powered coding companion, often need authentication through existing identity providers like PingIdentity. By leveraging AWS IAM Identity Center, organizations can enable their developers to access Amazon Q Developer with their existing PingIdentity credentials, streamlining authentication and removing the need for separate login procedures. Amazon Q Developer can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sid Vantair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nihilism is at the Core of the Israel-Iran Conflict — Not Nuclear Weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294274</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/nihilism-is-at-the-core-of-the-israel-iran-conflict-not-nuclear-weapons.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nihilism, understood as the absence of a transcendental purpose, lies at the heart of the conflict that Israel initiated against Iran]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Curro Jimenez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Iran Didn’t Target A Hospital (+Iran Update)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDHLivp9EXYVTSrnr1-fvTf</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDHLivp9EXYVTSrnr1-fvTf"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel uses hospitals as human shields for their military targets, which is what they claimed Hamas did.
#Soroka Hospital is located between two major Israeli military sites: the IDF’s main intelligence headquarters and a central command facility, both of which are situated in the Gav-Yam Technology Park. These installations reportedly serve as critical hubs for Israel’s cyber operations, digital command systems, and military intelligence infrastructure (including IDF C4I and C4ISR systems). While the hospital sustained shockwave damage from nearby blasts, it was not directly hit, Iranian reports emphasize. 

Sororka is the primary hospital for military casualties, I understand, but it wasn’t targeted. It got hit in the blast.

Now, of course, Israel complaining about a hospital attack is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Reportedly Greenlights Plan for US Attack on Iran Without Congressional Approval]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294256</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/trump-reportedly-greenlights-plan-for-us-attack-on-iran-without-congressional-approval.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration barrels toward U.S. intervention in Iran, with neither reality nor Congress serving as a check.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about NIST’s new guidance in “SP 1800-35: Implementing a Zero Trust Architecture”]]></title>
        <id>4Py1QO6TikGfaBeGSPBmFv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/nist-sp-1300-85/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We read NIST’s new guidance on “Implementing a Zero-Trust Architecture” so that you don’t have to.  Read this to get the key points on the newly-released NIST Special Publication 1800-35.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron McAllister</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending the Internet: how Cloudflare blocked a monumental 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack]]></title>
        <id>4BIcJ46lxWU4w1NytPTCsu</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/defending-the-internet-how-cloudflare-blocked-a-monumental-7-3-tbps-ddos/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-May 2025, Cloudflare blocked the largest DDoS attack ever recorded: a staggering 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Yoachimik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/19/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294229</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-19-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T10:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daily links, including the US as organized crime state, inching closer towards war with Iran, and your nails as recession predictor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Iran Actually Close the Strait of Hormuz? Eni CEO Weighs In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294243</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/will-iran-actually-close-the-strait-of-hormuz-eni-ceo-weighs-in.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T07:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Investors seem unduly chill about the risk that a US attack on Iran will produce a formal or de facto closure of the Strait of Hormuz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 18, 2025 (#571)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22976</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/18/daily-reading-list-june-18-2025-571/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T00:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at a new "cloud finder" API, what has a bigger impact than AI coding tools on your team, and writing docs for an AI world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason For French Collapse At The Outset Of WWII]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T17:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I doubt one in ten of you know the importance of the Battle of the Marne? Quite simple, had the French plus a smallish-medium but crucial contigent of soldiers from the UK, not halted the invading Germans at the Marne, the 20th century would have looked very different. Sure, von Moltke the Younger lost his nerve and pulled two corps from his right flank, shipped East to help fend off the Russian hordes. But, the French were glorious at the Marne and each and every one of us owe a debt a gratitude to France for the elan and courage.
As Holger Herwig writes in The Marne, 1914, “At dawn on 6 September, 980,000 French and 100,000 British soldiers with 3,000 guns assaulted the German line of 750,000 men and 3,300 guns [across a front stretching from] Verdun and Paris.” The Miracle of the Marne …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine and Iran: two fronts of a piecemeal world war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T15:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukraine war and the Israel-Iran conflict are not separate crises, but interlinked fronts in a piecemeal world war — one that pits the US against a de facto alliance of of Russia, Iran and China]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Continues To Accelerate Its Decline (+Iran)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T14:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wavered between writing another Iran war update and this article, so I’ll say a few things about the Iranian war. There’s evidence that Israeli intelligence networks in Iran and elsewhere are being compromised fast. It appears that:
In simple terms:
Israel’s attack on Iran exposed a hidden network. For 25 years, India’s RAW and Israel’s Mossad have worked together using Indian tech workers across the Gulf as quiet access points into sensitive infrastructure. This network runs through millions of Indian… https://t.co/zkJRVuSoPx
— Thomas Keith (@iwasnevrhere_) June 17, 2025


 
That India, a Hindu/Brahmin supremacists state which is increasingly treating its minorities the way Israel used to treat Palestinians before it went full genocidal is allied this deeply with Israel is not a surpris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Log Explorer is now GA, providing native observability and forensics]]></title>
        <id>kg7dxMzYcRnJdVFrxQmCw</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/logexplorer-ga/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the General Availability of Cloudflare Log Explorer, a powerful product designed to bring observability and forensics capabilities directly into your Cloudflare dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Sells</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect any React application to an MCP server in three lines of code]]></title>
        <id>4gk3k2ZiTN6DZoHu3e090r</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/connect-any-react-application-to-an-mcp-server-in-three-lines-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're open-sourcing use-mcp, a React library that connects to any MCP server in just 3 lines of code, as well as our AI Playground, a complete chat interface that can connect to remote MCP servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 17, 2025 (#570)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22952</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/17/daily-reading-list-june-17-2025-570/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the expanded family of Gemini models, why you should "trust but verify" with AI in engineering, and why developers hate their tech stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining technology, education, and human connection to improve online learning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/caitlin-morris-combines-tech-education-human-connection-improve-online-learning-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/caitlin-morris-combines-tech-education-human-connection-improve-online-learning-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlin Morris, a PhD student and 2024 MAD Fellow affiliated with the MIT Media Lab, designs digital learning platforms that make room for the “social magic” that influences curiosity and motivation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denise Brehm | MIT Morningside Academy for Design</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the bias of large language models]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/unpacking-large-language-model-bias-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/unpacking-large-language-model-bias-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers discover the root cause of a type of bias in LLMs, paving the way for more accurate and reliable AI systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A sounding board for strengthening the student experience]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/sounding-board-for-strengthening-student-experience-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/sounding-board-for-strengthening-student-experience-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composed of “computing bilinguals,” the Undergraduate Advisory Group provides vital input to help advance the mission of the MIT Schwarzman College of Computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danna Lorch | MIT Schwarzman College of Computing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;Nuclear Options&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/nuclear-options</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/nuclear-options"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T18:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regime change in Tehran?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Inforce roundup 2025: top announcements]]></title>
        <id>b0ad377a4e23c937899926a46ac90dab8f257761</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-reinforce-roundup-2025-top-announcements/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T17:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Inforce 2025 (June 16-18, Philadelphia), AWS Vice President and Chief Information Security Officer Amy Herzog delivered the keynote address, announcing new security innovations. Throughout the event, AWS announced additional security capabilities focused on simplifying security at scale and enabling organizations to build more resilient applications in the cloud. Below is a comprehensive roundup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty expands Extended Threat Detection coverage to Amazon EKS clusters]]></title>
        <id>0c90d66a232b00eab18ce300f6d25e027a484483</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-expands-extended-threat-detection-coverage-to-amazon-eks-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T16:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded Amazon GuardDuty Extended Threat Detection for EKS clusters uses proprietary correlation algorithms to identify sophisticated multi-stage attack sequences across Kubernetes audit logs, container runtime behaviors, and AWS API activities through a new critical severity finding type: AttackSequence:EKS/CompromisedCluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unify your security with the new AWS Security Hub for risk prioritization and response at scale (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>e19fa07e98e5b8e9021afdf4e6d3f14f45d064b0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/unify-your-security-with-the-new-aws-security-hub-for-risk-prioritization-and-response-at-scale-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Security Hub has been enhanced with new capabilities that integrate multiple AWS security services to automatically discover resources, evaluate risks, analyze attack paths, and provide AI-assisted recommendations, helping security teams prioritize critical issues and respond to threats at scale with improved visualization and remediation guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup adds new Multi-party approval for logically air-gapped vaults]]></title>
        <id>5b49911bc7d41842e56590335b8e7b3615f3ef6c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-adds-new-multi-party-approval-for-logically-air-gapped-vaults/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-party approval for AWS Backup logically air-gapped vaults enables organizations to recover their backup data even when their AWS account is compromised, by creating approval teams of trusted individuals who can authorize vault sharing with a recovery account through a separate authentication path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Shield feature discovers network security issues before they can be exploited (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>5235df10e9121e0b8997ba6595bb1f96974c7419</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-shield-feature-discovers-network-security-issues-before-they-can-be-exploited-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shield network security posture management automatically discovers and analyzes network resources across AWS accounts, prioritizes security risks based on AWS best practices, and provides actionable remediation recommendations to protect applications against threats like SQL injections and DDoS attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront simplifies web application delivery and security with new user-friendly interface]]></title>
        <id>c26dbe5841b16834450965e43bc3fd061d2cf760</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudfront-simplifies-web-application-delivery-and-security-with-new-user-friendly-interface/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try the simplified console experience with Amazon CloudFront to accelerate and secure web applications within a few clicks by automating TLS certificate provisioning, DNS configuration, and security settings through an integrated interface with AWS WAF's enhanced Rule Packs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certificate Manager introduces exportable public SSL/TLS certificates to use anywhere]]></title>
        <id>55aea14f37e97eabeffd376d045f1bb3711feb1b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-certificate-manager-introduces-exportable-public-ssl-tls-certificates-to-use-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use AWS Certificate Manager to issue exportable public certificates for your AWS, hybrid, or multicloud workloads that require secure TLS traffic termination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verify internal access to critical AWS resources with new IAM Access Analyzer capabilities]]></title>
        <id>2bdebfa050d44d96737015f5a4beb4aa5a038a8a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/verify-internal-access-to-critical-aws-resources-with-new-iam-access-analyzer-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new capability in IAM Access Analyzer helps security teams verify which principals within their AWS organization have access to critical resources like S3 buckets, DynamoDB tables, and RDS snapshots by using automated reasoning to evaluate multiple policies and provide findings through a unified dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;Culmination&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/culmination</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/culmination"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T09:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel attacks Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 16, 2025 (#569)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22932</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/16/daily-reading-list-june-16-2025-568/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T23:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how Netflix does a unified data architecture, the role of the "agent architect", and security strategies for prompts and agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating an academic-industry collaboration to advance vehicle technology]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/celebrating-academic-industry-collaboration-advance-vehicle-technology-0616</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/celebrating-academic-industry-collaboration-advance-vehicle-technology-0616"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIT Advanced Vehicle Technology Consortium marks a decade of developing data that improve understanding of how drivers use and respond to increasingly sophisticated automotive features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mackenzie Berry | MIT AgeLab | MIT Center for Transportation and Logistics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS re:Inforce 2025, AWS WAF, AWS Control Tower, and more (June 16, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>bfdcfd4bce1293e4116e091dbb0771283c97ada6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-reinforce-2025-aws-waf-aws-control-tower-and-more-june-16-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the start of AWS re:Inforce 2025, where security professionals are gathering for three days of technical learning sessions, workshops, and demonstrations. This security-focused conference brings together AWS security specialists who build and maintain the services that organizations rely on for their cloud security needs. AWS Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) Amy Herzog will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Israeli War Update]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtKUgRKU9mY9fEERM4J_G7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtKUgRKU9mY9fEERM4J_G7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T14:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take this in steps.
Air Defense Iranian air defense was not active for the first attack wave. They were online for the second one, about six hours later. It’s unclear why. I have heard two credible claims. The first is that they were hit by a cyber-attack, but came online faster than the Israelis expected.
The second is that the Iranians deliberately played rope-a-dope. The first attack was largely a matter of stand-off munitions, which the Israelis have (had) very limited supplies of. The Iranians tanked that hit, counting on the fact that most military targets were underground and hardened. Then when the second attack happened, which required close in attack, the air defenses were turned on. Because they had not been compromised in the first attack (air defense use makes air defens…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not in our name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/not-in-our-name</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/not-in-our-name"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The real threat to Europe doesn’t come from Moscow — but from Israel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 15, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAzAnFPhbO16HLDoD_XO2aE</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAzAnFPhbO16HLDoD_XO2aE"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T18:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 15, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
 
 
Trump not violating any law
‘He who saves his Country does not violate any Law’
 
Trump Stuns By Saying ‘I Don’t Know’ When Asked Directly NBC’s Kristen Welker ‘Don’t You Need to Uphold the Constitution?’
Joe DePaolo, May 4th, 2025 [mediaite.com]
 
Why is Kristi Noem’s bone-chilling pledge of a “regime change” in Calif not getting media coverage?!  Trump wants to remove Democrats from office
Dean Obeidallah, June 13, 2025
But what has been largely ignored in the reporting was the bone-chilling comment that sparked Padilla to interrupt Noem during her press conference. In prepared remarks, Noem delivered a message from Trump that the military occupation of Los Angeles and beyond will not end until both Governor Gavin Ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCRm0S8IqqIxR-Jwg1rdqYt</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCRm0S8IqqIxR-Jwg1rdqYt"/>
        <updated>2025-06-14T11:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts (no Iran/Israel.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>