<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-21T18:35:58.864Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-21T18:35:58.864Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS CloudFormation Hooks invoked via AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI)]]></title>
        <id>06438beb8b5a369c8d7df0ccec85c17549c361b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-aws-cloudformation-hooks-invoked-via-aws-cloud-control-api-ccapi/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the integration of AWS CloudFormation Hooks with AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI). This integration enables the use of hooks to validate the configuration of resources being provisioned through CCAPI. In this blog post, we will explore the integration between CloudFormation Hooks and CCAPI by configuring an existing hook to work with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin DeJong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacific aid falls due to Ukraine focus + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aid to the Pacific falls 18% as focus shifts to Ukraine; Russia launches its first ICBM in the conflict; ICC issues arrest warrants for Netanyahu and Hamas leaders; Oropouche virus cases in Brazil surge amid new strain investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Dukes: &ldquo;Proliferations&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Kevin Killian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Criminal Court Issues Arrest Warrants for Israel Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and Former Minister of Defense, Yoav Gallant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282580</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/international-criminal-court-issues-arrest-warrants-for-israel-prime-minister-benjamin-netanyahu-and-former-minister-of-defense-yoav-gallant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a long delay, the International Criminal Court issued arrest warrants against the open genociders Benjamin Netanyahu and Yoav Gallant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a visual update to the AWS Management Console (preview)]]></title>
        <id>3c48f4b90c1afccc51d832e1bd239d9a4d036796</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-a-visual-update-to-the-aws-management-console-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new intuitive AWS console design enhances readability, reduces complexity for improved task focus and efficiency while maintaining familiarity across AWS experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? Three Facts About Failing Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32456</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-three-facts-about-failing-banks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do banks fail? In a new working paper, we study more than 5,000 bank failures in the U.S. from 1865 to the present to understand whether failures are primarily caused by bank runs or by deteriorating solvency. In this first of three posts, we document that failing banks are characterized by rising asset losses, deteriorating solvency, and an increasing reliance on expensive noncore funding. Further, we find that problems in failing banks are often the consequence of rapid asset growth in the preceding decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/21/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282570</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-21-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T11:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our overly dynamic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK, Jr. Plans Attack on AMA’s Big Meal Ticket, Licensing Fees for Medical Billing Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282563</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/rfk-jr-plans-attack-on-amas-big-meal-ticket-licensing-fees-for-medical-billing-codes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T11:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK, Jr.'s plan, if confirmed as HHS chair, to end Medicare use of AMA licensed-billing codes somehow will increase, not lower, costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Politics & What Is the Political?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282566</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/what-is-politics-what-is-the-political.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T11:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An effort to get at the root of what politics is meant to achieve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Entropy and Information Control: the Key to Understanding How to Mount the Fightback Against Trump and Other Populists”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282568</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/entropy-and-information-control-the-key-to-understanding-how-to-mount-the-fightback-against-trump-and-other-populists.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T09:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reader critical thinking exercise, in form of yet another attack on populism dressed in the pseudo-science of trying to link it to entropy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions & answers on China as a major creditor power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T08:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has been demonized by several commentators: it is said to be the main creditor of many countries of the South and to get the most of them through ruthless exploitation whereas the World Bank, the IMF, the Paris Club, that bring together traditional creditor powers, are supposed to do their best to help those countries burdened by too much debt. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
China, 
BRICS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Trade’s Legacy of Grief for Families of the Disappeared in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343900</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/free-trades-legacy-of-grief-for-families-of-the-disappeared-in-mexico/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Mexico today, thousands of families are searching for loved ones who have disappeared amid the violence associated with “the war on drugs.” Although disappearances in Mexico trace back to the Cold War and the repression of guerrilla movements in the 1960s and 1970s, they have expanded in scale and taken on new dimensions in the neoliberal era. Trade agreements like NAFTA, intended promote economic growth, have inadvertently fueled drug-trafficking across the U.S.-Mexico border, contributing to a crisis of violence that disproportionately impacts marginalized communities—those already vulnerable due to poverty and limited political power. More
The post Free Trade’s Legacy of Grief for Families of the Disappeared in Mexico appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaylih Muehlmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You for Emitting: The Hypocrisies of COP29]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/thank-you-for-emitting-the-hypocrisies-of-cop29/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COP29 was always going to be memorable, for no other reason than the hosting country, Azerbaijan, is a petrostate indifferent to the issue of emissions and scornful of ecological preachers.  It has seen its natural gas supply grow by 128% between 2000 and 2021.  Between 2006 and 2021, gas exports rose by a monumental 29,290%.  A dizzying 95% of the country’s exports are made up of oil and gas, with much of its wealth failing to trickle down to the rest of the populace. More
The post Thank You for Emitting: The Hypocrisies of COP29 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Precarious Precariat and the Garrison State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344439</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/the-precarious-precariat-the-garrison-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the Garrison State isn’t already here, it’s sure to be here very soon. Wait and watch and observe the arrival of a suped-up American political and economic system buttressed anew by the military. True, all eyes, or at least a great many of them across the US and around the world, have been focused on Washington D.C., the White House and Trump’s controversial appointees to cabinet positions. More
The post The Precarious Precariat and the Garrison State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unplugging the News (and History) in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344414</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/unplugging-the-news-and-history-in-san-francisco/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reporters are tasked with wading into the maelstroms of current events—fires, hurricanes, battle spaces, crime scenes, accidents, political riots—to record what we see, to print, televise, and preserve stories of events in the world as viewed through our professional lensing. Hence the adage, “Journalism is the first rough draft of history.” Flawed, biased, and duplicitous  More
The post Unplugging the News (and History) in San Francisco appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Byrne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Change and the Insurability Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344035</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/climate-change-and-the-insurability-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home insurance rates are rising in the United States, not only in Florida, which saw tens of billions of dollars in losses from hurricanes Helene and Milton, but across the country. According to S&P Global Market Intelligence, homeowners insurance increased an average of 11.3% nationwide in 2023, with some states, including Texas, Arizona and Utah,  More
The post Climate Change and the Insurability Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew J. Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Politics Merge with a Sane Future?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344298</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/can-politics-merge-with-a-sane-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America is for Americans – Americans only!” The words are those of Stephen Miller, speaking last month at the infamous Madison Square Garden rally, but they define Donald Trump. This is the message – the cry from the mountaintop – he brought to the country . . . at least to approximately half of it. It’s  More
The post Can Politics Merge with a Sane Future? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Leigh Sings the Blues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344419</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/mike-leigh-sings-the-blues/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to its mission statement, “AFI FEST… showcase[es] the best films from across the globe to captivated audiences in Los Angeles. With a diverse and innovative slate of programming, the film festival presents a robust lineup of fiction and nonfiction features and shorts… along with panels and conversations featuring both master filmmakers and new cinematic  More
The post Mike Leigh Sings the Blues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU’s Dual Approach: Green Subsidies and Tarriffs on Chinese EVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344131</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/the-eus-dual-approach-green-subsidies-and-tarriffs-on-chinese-evs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 29, 2024, the European Commission unveiled new countervailing duties on Chinese electric vehicle (EV) imports, effective the following day. This move is framed as part of a broader aggressive strategy to safeguard European industries, but it overlooks a significant reality. The EU itself has long been an active player in subsidizing its own  More
The post The EU’s Dual Approach: Green Subsidies and Tarriffs on Chinese EVs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Outrageous Disregard for Climate Change Endangers the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344417</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/trumps-outrageous-disregard-for-climate-change-endangers-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T06:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World leaders, negotiators, lobbyists and NGOs are meeting in Baku, the capital of Azerbaijan, for COP29. COP (Conference of Parties) is comprised of approximately 200 countries that ratified the UNFCCC (United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change) in 1992. The representatives of these countries meet every year to negotiate the best approaches to tackling the  More
The post Trump’s Outrageous Disregard for Climate Change Endangers the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chloe Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Possible Justice Department Conversation: a Glyph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344470</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/21/possible-justice-department-conversation-a-glyph/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T05:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Possible Justice Department Conversation: a Glyph appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HP achieved 40% improvement in Kubernetes node utilization on Amazon EKS using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>1cfef501e204d4782ada7fcdd095f8ae11aca063</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-hp-achieved-40-improvement-in-kubernetes-node-utilization-utilization-on-amazon-eks-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post was co-authored by Jon Lewis (SW R&D Director in HP), Gajanan Chandgadkar (Principal Cloud Operations Architect, HP), Rutvij Dave (Sr. Solutions Architect at AWS), Ratnopam Chakrabarti (Sr. Solutions Architect, Containers and Open-Source technologies at AWS), Apeksha Chauhan(Senior Technical Account Manager at AWS) and Chance Lee (Sr. Container Specialist Solutions Architect at AWS) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vannevar Labs cut ML inference costs by 45% using Ray on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>881522d823c2683572eded22898d1b5c5549f643</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-vannevar-labs-cut-ml-inference-costs-by-45-using-ray-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is authored by Colin Putney (ML Engineer at Vannevar Labs), Shivam Dubey (Specialist SA Containers at AWS), Apoorva Kulkarni (Sr.Specialist SA, Containers at AWS), and Rama Ponnuswami (Principal Container Specialist at AWS). Vannevar Labs is a defense tech startup, successfully cut machine learning (ML) inference costs by 45% using Ray and Karpenter on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon CloudFront VPC origins: Enhanced security and streamlined operations for your applications]]></title>
        <id>e9cf7abc977d40ac1bb9255061c1a08c6959b403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-cloudfront-vpc-origins-enhanced-security-and-streamlined-operations-for-your-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securely deliver high-performance web apps with CloudFront VPC origins; serve content directly from private subnets, eliminating undifferentiated work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront now accepts your applications’ gRPC calls]]></title>
        <id>5d526139e265f2b1f97ea808cbe69afe4337f6ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudfront-now-accepts-your-applications-grpc-calls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock high-performance APIs with gRPC on Amazon CloudFront. Reduce latency via a global CDN, secure traffic at the edge, and benefit from DDoS protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger and badder: how DDoS attack sizes have evolved over the last decade]]></title>
        <id>5JhHzAWP0tvrl8ZolsnvyE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/bigger-and-badder-how-ddos-attack-sizes-have-evolved-over-the-last-decade"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we plot the metrics associated with large DDoS attacks observed in the last 10 years, does it show a straight, steady increase in an exponential curve that keeps becoming steeper, or is it closer to a linear growth? Our analysis found the growth is not linear but rather is exponential, with the slope varying depending on the metric (rps, pps or bps).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>José Salvador</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAIRU — a harmful fairy tale]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45841</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/20/nairu-a-harmful-fairy-tale-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The NAIRU story has always had a very clear policy implication — attempts to promote full employment are doomed to fail since governments and central banks can’t push unemployment below the critical NAIRU threshold without causing harmful runaway inflation. Although a lot of mainstream economists and politicians have a touching faith in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient Internet connectivity in Europe mitigates impact from multiple cable cuts]]></title>
        <id>5DP2F9GATeUBYyfl6pQMej</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/resilient-internet-connectivity-baltic-cable-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two recent cable cuts that occurred in the Baltic Sea resulted in little-to-no observable impact to the affected countries, in large part because of the significant redundancy and resilience of Internet infrastructure in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the grass greener on the Bluesky side of the fence?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8870</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/grass-greener-bluesky-side-fence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T20:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter-like microblogging social network Bluesky is having its moment in the sun. We’ve all seen the multiple headlines of late heralding the arrival of another several million new members, most of whom have migrated from Twitter. The buzz is similar to that surrounding Mastodon about two years ago. Even if Mastodon’s decentralised structure confused many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282528</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T19:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemic; Theories of Trump's nomination nethodology; Treasury rumors continue; RFK Big Mac flap ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344318</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/344318/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactively validate your AWS CloudFormation templates with AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>6e59f7aea8061022674286f8882daa78a3e476a1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/proactively-validate-your-aws-cloudformation-templates-with-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CloudFormation is a service that allows you to define, manage, and provision your AWS cloud infrastructure using code. To enhance this process and ensure your infrastructure meets your organization’s standards, AWS offers CloudFormation Hooks. These Hooks are extension points that allow you to invoke custom logic at specific points during CloudFormation stack operations, enabling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a managed hook for Guard]]></title>
        <id>544d1304f85c9b526be6493d28a5fdfad360e121</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-a-managed-hook-for-guard/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s cloud-driven world, maintaining compliance and enforcing organizational policies across your infrastructure is more critical than ever. AWS CloudFormation, a service that enables you to model, provision, and manage AWS and third-party resources through Infrastructure as Code (IaC), has been a cornerstone for automating cloud deployments. While CloudFormation simplifies resource management, ensuring compliance with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Terry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by OutOfHere in "FireDucks: Pandas but Faster"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42195321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42195321"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T16:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't use it:
> By providing the beta version of FireDucks free of charge and enabling data scientists to actually use it, NEC will work to improve its functionality while verifying its effectiveness, with the aim of commercializing it within FY2024.
In other words, it's free only to trap you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OutOfHere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Initial thoughts on The Power of Now by Eckhart Tolle]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/initial-thoughts-on-the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/initial-thoughts-on-the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finally started reading The Power of Now by Eckhart Tolle. I've tried to start this book many times before, but I always stopped in the first chapter or so because I felt that the author was being unnecessarily airy and, more importantly, he directly claimed that he ended up in this semi enlightened state but doesn't rightly know how he got there. This point was the point where I always stopped, but this time I decided to power through it, and in doing so I discovered I've been missing an important part: after not knowing what had happened, and just living in a state of present bliss, Eckhart discovered that what had happened to him is what many religions aim as their ultimate goal, so he went on to discover more about that and how a normal person might get to his state, but told from hi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetary developments in the Euro Area, september 2024. Quiet.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45832</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/20/monetary-developments-in-the-euro-area-september-2024-quiet/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T15:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like John Stuart Mill, I´m more interested in credit than in money. Developments in the amount of credit provided are much more instructive to the economist than data on money. Look at the graph below (no. 2 in the ECB press release) , a highly Post-Keynesian graph that originated from the pre-Euro Bundesbank and is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Neuburger: Tulsi Gabbard’s DNI Nomination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282544</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/thomas-neuburger-tulsi-gabbards-dni-nomination.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T15:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Gaetz, Gabbard is a mixed-bag candidate. Should she get your support?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Company lawyers reduce server load by 93% by adding cookie consent banner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theolognion.com/p/company-lawyers-reduce-server-load</id>
        <link href="https://www.theolognion.com/p/company-lawyers-reduce-server-load"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T14:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German e-commerce startup has been battling repeated server downtimes due to increased popularity of their services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Solenya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM stands in solidarity with the Palestinian resistance in the face of apartheid, crimes against humanity and colonisation practised by the extreme right-wing government in Israel.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-stands-in-solidarity-with-the-Palestinian-resistance-in-the-face-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-stands-in-solidarity-with-the-Palestinian-resistance-in-the-face-of"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We express our solidarity with the people of Palestine and oppose the aerial bombardments and indiscriminate and terrorist military actions carried out by the Israeli authorities. We call for the dismantling of the colonialist apartheid state of Israel and for respect for the rights of peoples to exercise their sovereignty. 
English

/ 
Palestine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yanis Varoufakis: &ldquo;Quantity to Quality&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/quantity-to-quality</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/quantity-to-quality"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T12:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Yanis Varoufakis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282510</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T11:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US attacks Russia, more wild Trump cabinet picks, and ground control to Major Biden.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Post-Election Reflection on Stolen Pride: Loss, Shame, and the Rise of the Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282522</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/a-post-election-reflection-on-stolen-pride-loss-shame-and-the-rise-of-the-right.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T11:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On how the shame resulting from the loss of seen-as-meaningful and well-paid work led many to reject the rule of their PMC betters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Wall Street Journal Blew the Story of the Democrats and Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282527</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-the-wall-street-journal-blew-the-story-of-the-democrats-and-inflation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T11:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The firehose of affluent consumption continues to drive inflation, not the stimulus package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for Abolishing and Replacing the IMF and the World Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-Abolishing-and-Replacing-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-Abolishing-and-Replacing-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mrtksn in "Let's Encrypt is 10 years old now"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42191644</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42191644"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T07:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hands down one of the greatest services out there, stopped a racket and made the internet secure.
I remember a time when having an HTTPS connection was for "serious" projects only because the cost of the certificate was much higher than the domain. You go commando and if it sticks then you purchase a certificate for a 100 bucks or something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mrtksn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Democratic War Party and Its Loss of Legitimacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343997</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/the-democratic-war-party-and-its-loss-of-legitimacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T07:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a political party loses its legitimacy, its traditional priorities and moral compass, its candidates lose elections. Opting not to hold an open convention, which would have tested political viability, the DNC (acting on the President's recommendation) invited Kamala Harris to replace Biden on the ticket.  For many Democrats, the lack of a competitive primary undermined the legitimacy of process. More
The post The Democratic War Party and Its Loss of Legitimacy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Out With a Bang? Biden Plays Nuclear Chicken with Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344210</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/going-out-with-a-bang-biden-plays-nuclear-chicken-with-russia/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biden and his ironically-dubbed national security “brain trust” of Secretary of State Antony Blinken and National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan have for most of this year been nixing Kiev’s request for such missiles as well as permission for Ukraine use Britain’s Storm Shadow stand-off air-launched long-range cruise missiles to hit Russian targets. They did this arguing that such attacks on the Russian heartland could lead to a spiraling escalation of that war — an escalation that could quickly go nuclear. More
The post Going Out With a Bang? Biden Plays Nuclear Chicken with Russia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implication for National Security: What If a Top Leader is Willing to Sell His Soul?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343922</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/implication-for-national-security-what-if-a-top-leader-is-willing-to-sell-his-soul/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[J.D, Vance explained in 2020 why he put aside the elitist atheism he picked up in college and law school to become a Catholic (“How I Joined the Resistance,” The Lamp, April 1, 2020). His quest for a meaningful life led Vance to be baptized a Catholic in 2019. The sentiments he so eloquently endorsed in 2020 suggested that in politics he would act as a Pope Francis progressive—the very opposite of a sophist acolyte for Donald J. Trump. Instead, we now see a vice-presidential candidate who lives by what Peter Quinn calls the “Wanton Opportunism” of a “Horatio Hillbilly,” Commonweal, September 8).  Equally problematic, Vance is paired with a presidential candidate who, as Alexander Motyl points out (here, October 20) stops at nothing to boost his own power. More
The post Implication for National Security: What If a Top Leader is Willing to Sell His Soul? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walter Clemens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Requiem for an Empire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344151</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/requiem-for-an-empire/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some 15 years ago, on December 5, 2010, a historian writing for TomDispatch made a prediction that may yet prove prescient. Rejecting the consensus of that moment that U.S. global hegemony would persist to 2040 or 2050, he argued that “the demise of the United States as the global superpower could come… in 2025, just 15 years from now.”  More
The post Requiem for an Empire appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred W. McCoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Legacy: Handing a Resurgent American Empire to Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343899</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/bidens-legacy-handing-a-resurgent-american-empire-to-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the lasting legacies of U.S. President Joe Biden will be that he reinvigorated the American empire despite the risk of an increasingly authoritarian Donald Trump returning to lead it. Over the past four years, President Biden has continually ignored criticisms of U.S. empire and the dangers it poses to the world to direct  More
The post Biden’s Legacy: Handing a Resurgent American Empire to Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Hunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Political and Climate Storms Rolling In: Look Homeward to Make Real Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343908</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/political-and-climate-storms-rolling-in-look-homeward-to-make-real-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Never has it been more important to build strong places capable of weathering the storms barreling down on us, both the physical storms of a disrupted climate and the political, social and economic storms of a nation and world tumbling into increasing conflict. Never has it been more crucial to strengthen and build the community  More
The post Political and Climate Storms Rolling In: Look Homeward to Make Real Change appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Chicago Community Envisions a World Without Prisons and Police]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344216</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/this-chicago-community-envisions-a-world-without-prisons-and-police/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often referred to as the most segregated city in the U.S. by media outlets like WBEZ Chicago and 14East, Chicago, Illinois, is riddled with redlining and racial profiling. A May 2024 report by a team of United Nations experts outlined a history of racist police brutality in the Chicago area, while a 2019 New York University School of Medicine study found that Chicagoans in the predominantly  More
The post This Chicago Community Envisions a World Without Prisons and Police appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Inequality”: The Missing Word in the 2024 Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344215</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/inequality-the-missing-word-in-the-2024-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, the Council on Foreign Relations warned, “Income and wealth inequality in the United States is substantially higher than in almost any other developed nation, and it is on the rise, sparking an intensifying national debate.” The economy was a major issue in the election. A month before the election, a Gallup survey found: “The economy  More
The post “Inequality”: The Missing Word in the 2024 Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Aroma Round]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344212</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/the-aroma-round/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a couple of years since I’ve been back to my hometown of Lake Placid, New York. On a recent FaceTime conversation with my mother, she was telling me about some of the changes in town. Apparently, the Gap store has been replaced by an arcade. She believed the long-time empty shop, advertising ‘Gifts  More
The post The Aroma Round  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Propaganda Exposed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344153</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/nuclear-propaganda-exposed/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a physicist and concerned citizen, I find myself outraged every time I scroll through social media and encounter tweets from the Department of Energy (DOE) and the Office of Nuclear Energy (ONE) touting nuclear power as “clean, safe, and carbon-free.” This narrative not only misrepresents the dirty reality of nuclear power but also obscures  More
The post Nuclear Propaganda Exposed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lynda Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Floor Speech on Joint Resolutions of Disapproval to Block Sale of Certain Offensive Weapons to Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344400</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/floor-speech-on-joint-resolutions-of-disapproval-to-block-sale-of-certain-offensive-weapons-to-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[M. President, Let me thank the leadership for their cooperation in setting up this debate. Today, we will be voting on three Joint Resolutions of Disapproval, or JRDs, to block the sale of certain offensive weapons systems to Israel. These resolutions are S.J.Res.111 to block the sale of 120mm tank rounds. S.J.Res.113 to block the  More
The post Floor Speech on Joint Resolutions of Disapproval to Block Sale of Certain Offensive Weapons to Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernie Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: You Don’t Get Me, I’m Part of the Union]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343907</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/letter-from-london-you-dont-get-me-im-part-of-the-union/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting out afresh on a journey through UK unions, I have more questions to ask than answers. However, the questions feel real and I suspect will not go away without real change. In the recent budget, the Labour government managed to park a huge amount of money back into the NHS—a staggering £23 billion—yet received  More
The post Letter from London: You Don’t Get Me, I’m Part of the Union appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of Empathy: Did the Gaza Genocide Render the UN Irrelevant?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344028</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/end-of-empathy-did-the-gaza-genocide-render-the-un-irrelevant/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Francesca Albanese did not mince her words. In a strongly worded speech at the United Nations General Assembly Third Committee on October 29, the UN Special Rapporteur deviated from the typical line of other UN officials. She directed her statements to those in attendance. “Is it possible that after 42,000 people killed, you cannot empathize  More
The post End of Empathy: Did the Gaza Genocide Render the UN Irrelevant?  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lula’s Toughest Battle?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344072</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/lulas-toughest-battle/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lawfare is a relatively new term. In essence, it is the weaponization of bourgeois law, usually by the right wing. Various US supporters of Donald Trump would argue that his prosecutions also fall under this mantle, despite the fact that he has skated out of almost every attempt to prosecute him so far. However, this  More
The post Lula’s Toughest Battle? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Tariff Fantasies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344030</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/20/donald-trumps-tariff-fantasies/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T06:23:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tariff Man Donald Trump thinks the world of tariffs. “Tariffs are the greatest thing ever invented,” Trump said in September at a town hall event in Michigan. On another occasion he said “tariff” is the most beautiful word in the English language. Hmm. And he really has had a love affair with tariffs. After all,  More
The post Donald Trump’s Tariff Fantasies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C + Raylib: snake game]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/c-raylib-snake-game/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/c-raylib-snake-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T01:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Continuation of the snake game series. This one is using C + Raylib and there will be another version with Zig + Raylib. You might wonder why did I wrote multiple versions of this snake games? My gamedev session is usually done in Godot 4, but I have always been curious how it differs when doing gamedev in Raylib.
What's Raylib?

Taken from the website: a programming library to enjoy videogames programming; no fancy interface, no visual helpers, no gui tools or editors... just coding in pure spartan-programmers way.
Key point: "pure spartan-programmers way".
Yes compared to using Godot 4, I do feel like a Spartan warrior when using Raylib! Gamedev in Godot is a walk in the park comparatively.
NOTE: you'll see a super similar code compared to the ASCII snake code.
#1 Libraries
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by redleggedfrog in "When did estimates turn into deadlines?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42188611</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42188611"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've gone through times when management would treat estimates as deadlines, and were deaf to any sort of reason about why it could be otherwise, like the usual thing of them changing the specification repeatedly.
So when those times have occurred I've (we've more accurately) adopted what I refer to the "deer in the headlights" response to just about anything non-trivial.  "Hoo boy, that could be doozy.  I think someone on the team needs to take an hour or so and figure out what this is really going to take."  Then you'll get asked to "ballpark it" because that's what managers do, and they get a number that makes them rise up in their chair, and yes, that is the number they remember.  And then you do your hour of due diligence, and try your best not to actually give any other number than the ballpark at any time, and then you get it done "ahead of time" and look good.
Now, I've had good managers who totally didn't need this strategy, and I loved 'em to death.  But for the other numbnuts who can't be bothered to learn their career skills, they get the whites of my eyes.
Also, just made meetings a lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>redleggedfrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded resource awareness in Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>a0a4939548a04cba5f81d0300776c90f4ad22036</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/expanded-resource-awareness-in-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Amazon Q Developer announced expanded support for account resource awareness with Amazon Q in the AWS Management Console along with the general availability of Amazon Q Developer in AWS Chatbot, enabling you to ask questions from Microsoft Teams or Slack. Additionally, Amazon Q will now provide context-aware assistance for your questions about resources in your account […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DO it again: how we used Durable Objects to add WebSockets support and authentication to AI Gateway]]></title>
        <id>2b8uznXSknoVGwTIcxxmKp</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/do-it-again"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Cloudflare’s Developer Platform and Durable Objects to build authentication and a WebSockets API that developers can use to call AI Gateway, enabling continuous communication over a single, persistent connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catarina Pires Mota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fbartos in "Fair coins tend to land on the side they started (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42187911</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42187911"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm the first author of the manuscript, so I thought I could answer some of the questions and clarify some issues (all details are in the manuscript, but who has the time to read it ;)
Low RPM tosses: Most of the recordings are on crapy webcams with ~ 30FPS. The coin spin usually much faster than the sensor can record which results in often non-spinning-looking flips. Why did we take the videos in the first place? To check that everyone collected the data and to audit the results.
Building a flipping matching: The study is concerned with human coin flips. Diaconis, Holmes, and Montgomery's (DHM, 2007) paper theorize that the imperfection of human flips causes the same-side bias. Building a machine completely defeats the purpose of the experiment.
Many authors and wasted public funding:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fbartos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The W3C launches the Sustainable Web Interest Group]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8861</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/w3c-launches-sustainable-web-interest-group/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Wide Consortium (W3C) has the emissions created by the internet in its sights… who knew just high web caused emissions were? The mission of the Sustainable Web Interest Group is to improve digital sustainability so that the Web works better for all people and the planet. The digital industry is responsible for 2-5% […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Katie Cunningham: write badly to write well]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8858</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/katie-cunningham-write-badly-write-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian author and journalist Katie Cunningham: My high school English teacher told me that good writing is the tenth draft of bad writing. I saw this in The Booklist, a weekly newsletter by the Sydney Morning Herald, the other day. Sometimes I feel as if I rewrite everything I post here ten times before publishing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unification, a short Star Trek film, in memory of Leonard Nimoy]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8863</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/unification-short-star-trek-film-memory-leonard-nimoy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To mark the thirtieth anniversary of the 1994 release of Star Trek Generations, comes Unification, which kind of picks ups after the conclusion of Generations. But it’s also a whirlwind jaunt through The Original Series (TOS) universe. There’s a cameo by Gary Lockwood, of 2001: A Space Odyssey, who featured in Where No Man Has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China boosts support for Global South + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-boosts-support-for-global-south-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-boosts-support-for-global-south-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T17:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese President Xi Jinping announces eight development measures for the Global South; President Biden visits the Amazon rainforest to boost climate efforts; Biden pledges record $4 billion to World Bank fund for poorest nations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequence learning: A paradigm shift for personalized ads recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21954</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/11/19/data-infrastructure/sequence-learning-personalized-ads-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI plays a fundamental role in creating valuable connections between people and advertisers within Meta’s family of apps. Meta’s ad recommendation engine, powered by deep learning recommendation models (DLRMs), has been instrumental in delivering personalized ads to people. Key to this success was incorporating thousands of human-engineered signals or features in the DLRM-based recommendation system. [...]
Read More...
The post Sequence learning: A paradigm shift for personalized ads recommendations appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stranger I Know]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/the-stranger-i-know/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/the-stranger-i-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMA - What's one of the hardest things you have ever done?
My Dad woke up this morning and didn't know what day it was. Panicked, he sent a text message to almost everyone in the family asking for help. At this point, that means my siblings and his. We are a close family and several of us sprang into action. His brother-in-law lives a couple of miles away and was the first to arrive. My aunt, a nurse with more than 40 years experience was there within the hour. They got him to the doctor and then the hospital where the doctors are running tests to rule out a stroke. His thinking seems to have cleared up since he sent the original text but he still couldn't figure out how to set an alarm on his phone. That kind of thing is starting to happen with more frequency.
Dad is the sole care-giver f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring and automating recovery from AZ impairments in Amazon EKS with Istio and ARC Zonal Shift]]></title>
        <id>db09bb00bec3054fc452195e8064aa26f8c5eec4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/monitoring-and-automating-recovery-from-az-impairments-in-amazon-eks-with-istio-and-arc-zonal-shift/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Running microservice-style architectures in the cloud can quickly become a complex operation. Teams must account for a growing number of moving pieces such as multiple instances of independent workloads, along with their infrastructure dependencies. These components can then be distributed across different topology domains, such as multiple Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lukonde Mwila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How China Could Re-Dollarize The World]]></title>
        <id>673c3f761a75f60001d16cb4</id>
        <link href="https://indi.ca/how-china-starts-printing-usd/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China just issued a USD bond in Saudi Arabia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>indi.ca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[are we repeating the cycle?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/repeating-the-cycle/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/repeating-the-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These past days, I was very busy with playing Magic the Gathering and Pokemon TCG. Oops.
But when I wasn't busy with that, I was reading about Bluesky.
It's everywhere right now - Bearblog, the news, other online spaces talking about the great eXodus. It ranged from singing praises to it just being the new thing or "at least it's not X". I have to say, some things about it are really enticing and cool; aside from it being a new shiny thing to try out, I love the idea of the starter packs, the import tools, the custom domains (and those also serving as a kind of verification system), algorithmic feeds, thread and feed preferences, labeling and more.
But what keeps me critical is wondering if we aren't just repeating the cycle?
People have spoken about the fact that it feels like old Twitter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["abzug" theme for bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/abzug-theme-for-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/abzug-theme-for-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.marquee-container{width:100%;overflow:hidden;padding:10px 0}.marquee{white-space:nowrap;font-family:monospace;font-size:1rem;color:color-mix(in srgb,var(--text-color) 20%,transparent)}.scroll-right{animation:scrollRight 20s linear infinite}.scroll-left{animation:scrollLeft 20s linear infinite}@keyframes scrollRight{0%{transform:translateX(-50%)}100%{transform:translateX(0%)}}@keyframes scrollLeft{0%{transform:translateX(0%)}100%{transform:translateX(-50%)}}.marquee-top{position:fixed;top:0;left:0}@media (max-width:0){.marquee-container{display:none}}




            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 

-->


Abzug is a simple typography-focused theme that emphasizes readability. Born from a moment of inspiration in a cafe, accompanied by the sounds of Kraftwerk.
Preview: Visit bear.css.observer and select the Abzug preset. 
https://static.mgx.me/bear/themes/abzug.css.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rkharsan64 in "DOJ will push Google to sell off Chrome"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181921</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181921"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T10:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People here seem to be underestimating the advantages that Google gets just because of Chrome:
- When you sign in to Google, you sign in browser-wide. Google now gets all of your browsing data, perfect for advertising. (If you ever doubt it, go check out Google Takeout. You'll be shocked at the amount of data you see there.)
- They have special APIs and features that they get to use, and nobody else. Only because they own Chrome. [1]
- They get to move forward with enabling and pushing features that allow for more advertising: see Manifest v3, FLoC.
- Google specifically serves a worse version of Search on Firefox for Mobile. You have to get an extension to get the full experience.
This isn't an isolated attempt. You can see more of the same thing with Android.
- AOSP (the open source counterpart of Android) is now unusable. It doesn't ship with most essential apps, including a Phone app. In previous versions of Android, all of these were a part of AOSP.
- Most third party launchers/stores struggle to implement features because they are only available for Google themselves.
- The signing in with Google thing from above continues here too: you sign in to Google system-wide.
[1]: https://x.com/lcasdev/status/1810696257137959018]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rkharsan64</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wesselbindt in "DOJ will push Google to sell off Chrome"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181001</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181001"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T08:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm very surprised by the number of people in this thread who don't seem to understand that monopolies are _very_ bad for consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wesselbindt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinians, Both Civilian and Military, are Transcending the Horror We’ve Unleashed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344014</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/19/palestinians-both-civilian-and-military-are-transcending-the-horror-weve-unleashed/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T07:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In February, the public health specialist Muna Abed Alah published a paper in the journal Current Psychology titled “Shattered Hierarchy: How the Gaza Conflict Demolished Maslow’s Pyramid of Needs.” The idea of a hierarchy of needs—first published by the psychologist Abraham Maslow in 1943 and subsequently modified in various ways by Maslow and others—has long been pervasive in the world of pop psychology, while some in academia have poked holes in Maslow’s logic. Now, Alah suggests that the Palestinians of Gaza have rendered the hierarchy of needs wholly obsolete. More
The post Palestinians, Both Civilian and Military, are Transcending the Horror We’ve Unleashed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Media: Whitewashing Israeli Genocide and Manufacturing Consent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344026</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/19/western-media-whitewashing-israeli-genocide-and-manufacturing-consent/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T07:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A UN Special Committee has characterized Israel’s war in Gaza as genocide, while Western "free" media has abandoned its ethical responsibility to cover and or report objectively on the conduct of Israel’s wars in Gaza and Lebanon. Western corporate media outlets, without exception, acquiesced to Israeli directives barring reporters from entering Gaza. Journalists embedded with the Israeli army report only what Israel permits them to observe, creating a one-sided, heavily filtered narrative. More
The post Western Media: Whitewashing Israeli Genocide and Manufacturing Consent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Baku, at the Latest Global Confab on Climate, Hand-Wringing Abounds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343876</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/19/in-baku-at-the-latest-global-confab-on-climate-hand-wringing-abounds/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world desperately needs to pull the plug on fossil fuels. So agree most of the official delegates from nearly 200 nations who have gathered this month by the Caspian Sea for the 29th annual global “Conference of the Parties” on climate change — COP29 for short — in Azerbaijan’s capital city Baku. More
The post In Baku, at the Latest Global Confab on Climate, Hand-Wringing Abounds appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We Will Smoke Them Out!” Escalating Xenophobia in South Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343897</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/19/we-will-smoke-them-out-escalating-xenophobia-in-south-africa/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T06:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2002, the state of Gujarat in India erupted in horrific violence that would shape and define Narendra Modi’s political career. The pogrom, which left thousands of Muslims dead and displaced tens of thousands more, demonstrated the ease with which fear and hatred can be weaponised in pursuit of political power. Modi’s right-wing populism, rooted in Hindu fascism, enabled and cemented his rise to national prominence. Today, South Africa risks following a similarly destructive trajectory as political elites increasingly try to incite xenophobia against African and Asian migrants to redirect anger over a devastating economic and social crisis onto vulnerable scapegoats. More
The post “We Will Smoke Them Out!” Escalating Xenophobia in South Africa appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imraan Buccus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I love blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://jakobusbrahms.com/i-love-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://jakobusbrahms.com/i-love-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T01:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is going to be sort of a meta post, but I just felt such an  sense of joy after publishing my last post that I felt I had to write more.
I’ve long wanted to have a blog. Practically ever since I learned HTML programming with my dad when I was 10, I’ve wanted to have a web presence of some sort. And so I coded various websites to try to fulfill that desire. I found out about free hosting on GitHub Pages, and set up a static site generator to publish to it. But I never had anything to say, and so never used my shiny new website. Then I learned about Wordpress and paid for hosting so I could set up a pretty slick website with a hip theme. But again, I didn’t know what to say.
I think whenever I set up a new site I always got caught in the trap of feeling like I needed to write in a niche…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s dictatorship is a fait accompli]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53405</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/19/trumps-dictatorship-is-a-fait-accompli/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T00:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I drew up a flowchart to estimate the probability that Trump would establish a dictatorship in the US, which looked, at the time, like an even money bet. We don’t need to speculate any more. Trump has announced the dictatorship, and there is no sign of effective resistance. The key elements […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know before you go – AWS re:Invent 2024 cloud resilience]]></title>
        <id>21322524039287ae311396c3c1ba05aedce35ee8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/know-before-you-go-aws-reinvent-2024-cloud-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T23:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent 2024 with the goal of improving your organization’s cloud resilience operations, we will be offering valuable insights, best practices, and fun activities to improve your cloud resilience expertise. This year, we’re offering more than 100 resilience breakout sessions, workshops, chalk talks, builders’ sessions, and code talks. Find the complete list in the re:Invent 2024 session catalog and filter by “Resilience” in the area of interest field. In this post, we highlight must-see sessions for those building resilient applications and architectures on AWS. Reserved seating is now open, so act quickly to claim your seat. Be sure to also check out the vertical-specific re:Invent guides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shllomi Ezra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS enhances Kubernetes control plane observability]]></title>
        <id>28bc1106056a70a93b5b24d9119e9e7a806241bd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-enhances-kubernetes-control-plane-observability/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T23:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) is a managed Kubernetes service to run Kubernetes in the AWS cloud and on-premises data centers. In the cloud, Amazon EKS automatically manages the availability and scalability of the Kubernetes control plane nodes responsible for scheduling containers, managing application availability, storing cluster data, and other key tasks. However, maintaining […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashok Srirama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astra Dynamic Chunks: How We Saved by Redesigning a Key Part of Astra]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17285</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/astra-dynamic-chunks-how-we-saved-by-redesigning-a-key-part-of-astra/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T22:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Slack handles a lot of log data. In fact, we consume over 6 million log messages per second. That equates to over 10 GB of data per second! And it’s all stored using Astra, our in-house, open-source log search engine. To make this data searchable, Astra groups it by time and splits the data…
The post Astra Dynamic Chunks: How We Saved by Redesigning a Key Part of Astra appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Luong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline container application networking with built-in Amazon ECS support in Amazon VPC Lattice]]></title>
        <id>67d7d0b2d520590609cc528db5a2d3e6af8285e0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/streamline-container-application-networking-with-native-amazon-ecs-support-in-amazon-vpc-lattice/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify networking for containerized apps with native VPC Lattice-ECS integration, boosting productivity and flexibility across services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do i use websites again...?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/how-do-i-use-websites-again/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/how-do-i-use-websites-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:13:26.788Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[normally, i avoid "metaposting" about social media. discussions about the pros and cons of social media end up being very insular and kind of repetitive, and it's pretty tiring to me. but i need a place to process my thoughts, and well, that's what this blog is for.
i stopped using twitter sometime in 2022, before Musk took over. the psychic damage that the wretched bird site was doing to me was unbearable, and it was impacting my physical health in a very tangible way. i couldn't do it. if it meant dropping off the surface of the earth to anyone who primarily used twitter, then so be it.
tumblr was also driving me insane, so i hid away on cohost for the entirety of that site's lifespan. i've written enough about mourning cohost; so to put it succinctly, it was a website that i really need…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda SnapStart for Python and .NET functions is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>1efe6355721882348179128f93749c102250b8f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-snapstart-for-python-and-net-functions-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda SnapStart boosts Python and .NET functions' startup times to sub-second levels, often with minimal code changes, enabling highly responsive and scalable serverless apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by teruakohatu in "20 years of Google Scholar"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42176959</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42176959"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T20:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best thing, by a long way, that Google Scholar has achieved is denying Elsevier & co a monopoly on academic search.
In most universities here in New Zealand, articles have to be published in a journal indexed by Elsevier's Scopus. Not in a Scopus-indexed journal, it does not count anymore than a reddit comment. This gives Elsevier tremendous power. But in CS/ML/AI most academics and students turn to Google Scholar first when doing searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teruakohatu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dumbing down Notepad by giving it artificial intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8853</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dumbing-down-notepad-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T20:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having barely touched their simple text editor, Notepad, in years, Microsoft has been laying on the modifications in recent times. A few months ago, they fitted out Notepad with an autocorrect and spell-checker feature. That’s fine for people wishing to use Notepad as a word processor (in preference to paying out for a subscription to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merchant Ivory, a James Ivory, Ismail Merchant documentary, by Stephen Soucy]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8849</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-merchant-ivory-james-ivory-ismail-merchant-documentary-stephen-soucy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T19:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filmmakers James Ivory, the late Ismail Merchant, and Ruth Prawer Jhabvala, who collaborated as Merchant Ivory, made over forty features between 1963 and 2009. I think you’d be hard pressed to find any well-known actor of recent decades who did not work with them. My favourite is A Room with a View, which I’ve written […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and modify apps using natural language with AWS App Studio, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>ca7af76d4e0c5efc867c78848fb0cbd33937942b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-and-modify-apps-using-natural-language-with-aws-app-studio-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash your inner developer with AWS App Studio, the generative AI-powered application builder. Turn your idea into fully-fledged, intelligent, custom, secure, and scalable software in minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda turns ten – looking back and looking ahead]]></title>
        <id>1392cf1e2098d7939ad92ac27e8c9ceb3c6e131b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-turns-ten-the-first-decade-of-serverless-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the journey of AWS Lambda, the pioneering serverless computing service, from its 2013 inception to powering over two million users and tens of trillions of function invocations monthly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS BuilderCards at re:Invent 2024, AWS Community Day, Amazon Bedrock, vector databases, and more (Nov 18, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>2bf6f8f4243881c44ffaa2a8d0dc0785ceb1bc65</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-buildercards-at-reinvent-2024-aws-community-day-amazon-bedrock-vector-databases-and-more-nov-18-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we wrapped up the final 2024 Latin America Amazon Web Services (AWS) Community Days of the year in Brazil, with multiple parallel events taking place. In Goiânia, we had Marcelo Palladino, senior developer advocate, and Marcelo Paiva, AWS Community Builder, as keynote speakers. Florianópolis feature Ana Cunha, senior developer advocate, and in Santiago […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jp57 in "Air traffic failure caused by two locations 3600nm apart sharing 3-letter code"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42174194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42174194"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T16:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FYI: nm = nautical miles, not nanometers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jp57</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superinflation in Milei´s Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45821</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/18/superinflation-in-mileis-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T13:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperinflation is defined as over 50% inflation per month. Let´s define ´normal´ inflation as anything between 0 and 1% per month and anything between 1 and 50% per month as superinflation (1% a month is still a lot, yearly!). Before President Milei, Argentina already knew superinflation. After Milei, inflation accelerated, and the country almost entered […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a Little Friction to My Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T03:20:03.086Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like the peak internet for me was some time around 2004. The internet felt balanced, and I was happy with my relationship with it. Sure, I probably spent more time than I should have on the internet, but at least I wasn't carrying it around with me. I wasn't surfing the web on my bathroom breaks or while standing in line at the grocery store. The internet was a tool, not a conqueror of my attention.
For years, I've talked about wanting to set up a desktop or a designated computer space. Some place where I have go and sit down in order to log on. A place where I'll keep my computer off and give myself a few seconds to decide whether looking up an actress in some random sitcom episode is truly worth the effort. I want to add a little friction to my computing and just see how my mental health responds. Will I feel better? Will my attention improve? These are the questions I'm curious about.
Being that I have a little free time on my hands, I thought now is as good of a time as ever to give this a shot. So, starting tonight at midnight, I'm disconnecting. For the next week, my MacBook will live on my dining room table. I'm uninstalling most of the apps that I use on my phone to make it as bare-bones as possible. My iPad will remain on, but with the Wi-Fi turned off. I have a lot of magazines downloaded courtesy of Archive.org and some books I plan to read with my free time.
I wonder how my browsing habits will change if I don't have a piece of technology at my fingertips. Will I feel compelled to keep up with as much, or will I just find other mindless activities to fill my time? Heck, I even wonder if I'll make it the whole week. But these are the questions I will hopefully have an answer to around this time next week. With that being said, if anyone needs to contact me e-mail is going to be your best bet, because I'm sure I'll check that, but I'm probably going to miss a lot elsewhere.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Moleskine to Hobonici Notebook Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-moleskine-to-hobonici-notebook-switch/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-moleskine-to-hobonici-notebook-switch/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T22:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spoiler Alert: I indeed was not patient enough.
For the past few days, I’ve been contemplating abandoning my Moleskine journal for my newly acquired Hobonici notebook1. One main reason is that ever since I started writing with fountain pens, I’ve discovered that the bleed through on my Moleskine is just something I can no longer stand. I’ve been diligently writing with my favorite Kaco pen, but now that my Pilot Vanishing Point fountain pen has arrived, I really want to start journaling with it. Being absolutely impatient, and accepting that life is short and I should use a journal that sparks joy2, I made the switch today. I only had 14 pages left, so I don't actually feel AS guilty.
I have new notebook anxiety. I love buying journals, and stationery in general, but writing on that first …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blitz, a movie by Steve McQueen, with Saoirse Ronan]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8840</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-blitz-steve-mcqueen-saoirse-ronan/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T20:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve ended up seeing a stack of movies featuring Irish-American actor Saoirse Ronan, over the years. Tracking all the way back to Atonement in 2007, I think. Maybe I’m not so much of a Ronan fan, as I am the movies she’s in. But it’s an impressive list of titles. The Lovely Bones, The Way […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My blog theme and my mini, theme-editing dev environment]]></title>
        <id>https://noat.blog/my-blog-theme-and-my-mini-theme-editing-dev-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://noat.blog/my-blog-theme-and-my-mini-theme-editing-dev-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've gotten really nice comments about the theme I've put together for this blog! It's actually really nice to hear 'cause it's a bit more involved than simple CSS, so I'm glad it sticks out well!
Digging the look of your page, and this guestbook! Just dropping by to say hello 👋
whoa, i love your blog theme. super cute, sleek, while still very functional... i love it! definitely adding your blog to my rss feeds, i've liked your posts so far!
love the look of the blog.
I wanted to make it reminiscent to some elements from my art archive, but keep it pretty simple, both because Bear is pretty minimal by nature & I didn't want to let my perfectionist side take over. But! There are a few things that I think would be fun to point out since they were neat to implement, as well as the tool I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leetrout in "Good Software Development Habits"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42165704</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42165704"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T18:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> It's better to have some wonky parameterization than it is to have multiple implementations of nearly the same thing. Improving the parameters will be easier than to consolidate four different implementations if this situation comes up again.
Hard disagree. If you cant decompose to avoid "wonky parameters" then keep them separate. Big smell is boolean flags (avoid altogether when you can) and more than one enum parameter.
IME "heavy" function signatures are always making things harder to maintain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leetrout</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election: Take Four]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45807</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/17/election-take-four/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T17:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Take four. I continue to listen in on the conversation. The election reverberates loudly around leftish circles. Recriminations mount. Criticisms fly. Finger pointing and over-analysis have become all too common. And this is after just a week. Imagine what a month can produce. So far the central narrative seems to be that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Forest Lawn Memorial Park, Glendale]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53402</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/17/sunday-photoblogging-forest-lawn-memorial-park-glendale/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T17:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitchy and quasi-totalitarian ghastliness, USA (from 2008)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by null0pointer in "The Bluesky firehose viewed in the style of a Windows XP screensaver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42163194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42163194"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T10:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of commenters here are having their minds blown by this. And while I also love this I get the sense that many others here are maybe too young to remember that this kind of open access to data used to exist for lots websites. It inspired companion sites and loads of creativity. I find it tragic really, what the internet has become. I hope federated, and even more-so p2p, protocols take significant foothold on the internet and help revive this spirit of the web. The corpo-web is so fucking boring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null0pointer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by langsoul-com in "CSS gets a new logo and it uses the color `rebeccapurple`"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42162264</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42162264"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T05:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The color was originally going to be called beccapurple, but Meyer asked that it instead be named rebeccapurple, as his daughter had wanted to be called Rebecca once she had turned six. She had said that Becca was a "baby name," and that once she had turned six, she wanted to be called Rebecca. As Eric Meyer put it, "She made it to six. For almost twelve hours, she was six. So Rebecca it is and must be."
Wasn't expecting tears over a colour]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>langsoul-com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Tired, Boss]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/i-m-tired-boss/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/i-m-tired-boss/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }

In the 1999 movie adaption of Steven King's The Green Mile, the guards go into the condemned man's cell to ask about the arrangements for his execution. They want to know his last meal request and if he wants a preacher to be with him. Ultimately, they even ask if he wants a chance to escape. The prisoner, named John Coffey, tells them he's ready to go, starting his speech with a resigned "I'm tired boss." Brother, I can relate.
Most of my working life hasn't been spent in a physically demanding job. Occasionally in educational tech we have …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASCII snake in C]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/ascii-snake-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/ascii-snake-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T04:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
I've got some small/tiny gamedev projects on my pocket that I haven't documented here in my Bearblog account. The first one is an ASCII Snake game only using the curses library. There will be another similar post on making Snake game using Raylib.
#1 Libraries
#include <curses.h>
#include <stdbool.h>
#include <stdlib.h>
#include <time.h>
#include <unistd.h>
#include <string.h>

#2 Consts, structs and global vars
#define MAX_SCORE 256
#define FRAME_TIME 180000

typedef struct {
    int x;
    int y;
} Vec2;

int score = 0;
char score_message[32];

bool skip = false;
bool is_running = true;

int screen_width = 25;
int screen_height = 20;

// initialize screen
WINDOW *win;

// snake
Vec2 head = {0, 0};
Vec2 segments[MAX_SCORE + 1];
Vec2 dir = {1, 0};

// berry
Vec2 berry;

#3 Fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by LakesAndTrees in "Show HN: I built a(nother) house optimized for LAN parties"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160767</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160767"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T00:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think the thing that I’m most amazed by - and this setup is truly amazing - is the fact that you’ve got a group of friends to enjoy this with. Good for you; this looks like a blast, and I can only imagine how fun that’d be, compared to years of purely solo gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LakesAndTrees</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shermantanktop in "Netflix buffering issues: Boxing fans complain about Jake Paul vs. Mike Tyson"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160502</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160502"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T23:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time a big company screws up, there are two highly informed sets of people who are guaranteed to be lurking, but rarely post, in a thread like this:
1) those directly involved with the incident, or employees of the same company.  They have too much to lose by circumventing the PR machine.
2) people at similar companies who operate similar systems with similar scale and risks.  Those people know how hard this is and aren’t likely to publicly flog someone doing their same job based on uninformed speculation. They know their own systems are Byzantine and don’t look like what random onlookers think it would look like.
So that leaves the rest, who offer insights based on how stuff works at a small scale, or better yet, pronouncements rooted in “first principles.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shermantanktop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by softwaredoug in "Netflix buffering issues: Boxing fans complain about Jake Paul vs. Mike Tyson"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42157774</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42157774"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T17:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way to deal with this is to constantly do live events, and actually build organizational muscle. Not these massive one off events in an area the tech team has no experience in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>softwaredoug</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zen of Coding]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/zen-coding/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/zen-coding/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For me, it takes a long time to create something like the Bear Micro Blog. An "unnecessarily" long time.
Partly, it's because I'm an amateur. But that's not the main reason. Nor is it a matter of perfection.
It's because I find it relaxing.
Coding is like meditation for me. A perfect blend of focus and relaxation—a kind of timeless void. I'm often surprised when I look at the clock and realize how much time has passed.
They say time is money. Considering how rewarding these precious moments are to me, it’s a bargain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adi Callai - The Gaza Ghetto Uprising]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adi-callai-the-gaza-ghetto-uprising?v=1731753405</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adi-callai-the-gaza-ghetto-uprising?v=1731753405"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T10:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Adi Callai
Title: The Gaza Ghetto Uprising
Date: May 2024
Source: <brooklynrail.org/2024/05/field-notes/The-Gaza-Ghetto-Uprising>

 TO THE HEART OF IT: Gaza has been a free kill zone and a “concentration camp” (to quote Israel’s National Security Director Giora Eiland in 2004), long before October 7. 
 In light of this, the most radical position comes directly from the simplest question: are Palestinians human beings? If your answer is emphatically yes, unambiguously and without reservations, then you are a lost cause to Zionism. Because if Palestinians are human beings, then their self-defense is legitimate, and the defense of their continued existence is necessary. 
 Gaza, this black box, this holding pen for refugees from the 1948 ethnic cleansing of Palestine—can we think of it…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS and Kubernetes sessions at AWS re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>4bfc30d46cbd01dd4b3f1b6232bff7417450f6fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-and-kubernetes-sessions-at-aws-reinvent-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T03:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction AWS re:Invent 2024, the annual Amazon Web Services conference, is fast approaching. This year’s event will feature a full track of sessions focused on Kubernetes and other cloud-native technologies. To help you navigate the extensive session catalog, we’ve compiled a list of sessions around Kubernetes and cloud-native related topics. They have been grouped by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dumlu Timuralp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "Half-Life 2: 20th Anniversary Update"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42152345</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42152345"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T23:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't seem to be mentioned here, but HL2 (which now includes the sequel episodes) is completely free to claim on Steam until the 18th, if you're new to the series.
https://store.steampowered.com/app/220/HalfLife_2/
Also try clicking on the gravity gun at the end of the anniversary page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[maia arson crimew - anarchism starts in the now: hope for a better future]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/maia-arson-crimew-anarchism-starts-in-the-now-hope-for-a-better-future-1?v=1731710895</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/maia-arson-crimew-anarchism-starts-in-the-now-hope-for-a-better-future-1?v=1731710895"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T22:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: maia arson crimew
Title: anarchism starts in the now: hope for a better future
Subtitle: there is still time
Date: 2024-11-14
Source: Retrieved on 2024-11-14 from https://maia.crimew.gay/posts/anarchism-in-the-now/

one: doom
 "All my siblings wanna swim but it's infested with great whites Tell me if shit changed since Leelah and Blake died Tell me if my best friend's about to be next in line Tell me that I'm brave motherfucker, do you wanna die?" Rural Internet - i am not brave
 the world is looking dire right now. it seems like everything is worse than it has ever been, or maybe just like things suddenly flipped back to "bad" after a brief period where it seemed to be getting better. but no matter what happened or how, one thing is clear: the number of socially acceptable targets…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by galkk in "First Impressions: Lenovo T14s with Qualcomm Snapdragon ARM64 CPU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42151363</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42151363"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T21:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love it(in context of FreeBSD):
—————
What does not work: Keyboard, mouse, TB & USB-C ports, thermal/freq mgt.
Conclusion: Highly recommended]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>galkk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Koala_ice in "Tesla has the highest fatal accident rate of all auto brands, study finds"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42150928</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42150928"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T20:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I thoroughyl expect the Deparment of Government Efficiency to recommend U.S. Fatality Analysis Reporting System (FARS) be shut down to save previous taxpayer dollars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Koala_ice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replicate changes from databases to Apache Iceberg tables using Amazon Data Firehose (in preview)]]></title>
        <id>a4d618fdd2160e263046448cd0db011d82c567f1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/replicate-changes-from-databases-to-apache-iceberg-tables-using-amazon-data-firehose/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T19:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Data Firehose introduces a new capability that captures database changes and streams updates to a data lake or warehouse, supporting PostgreSQL, MySQL, Oracle, SQL Server, and MongoDB, with automatic scaling and minimal impact on transaction performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by agentultra in "Please stop the coding challenges"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42149111</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42149111"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T17:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> When was the last time you had to debug an ancient codebase without documentation or help from a team?
All the time. 300-400k SLOC in C++. Legacy in the sense that there were no tests of any kind. Little-to-no documentation. Solo developer at the tiny company. Fix bugs and add features while keeping the system available to the tens of thousands of users.
A more recent example: here’s a patch for a critical feature we need. It was written over a year ago. The original author isn’t available anymore. You can write the code from scratch or try to resurrect the patch against master.
Being able to jump into a project and lead people towards some goal is definitely a skill for senior developer positions. Yes, you generally have a team you can lean on and have the ability to do research and all that. But how do you show that you can do all that in an interview?
Agree with the conclusion that a good thing to test for is for problem-solving.
The tech side depends a lot on what you’re doing. Although it gets ridiculous and organizations get lazy with this part. You don’t need to be white boarding graph algorithms for a junior web developer role. If your application is a social networking role and you’re interviewing a senior developer or architect? Definitely. They’re going to be teaching this stuff and need to understand it at a deep level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>agentultra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple to launch new AI home screen + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/apple-to-launch-new-ai-home-screen-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/apple-to-launch-new-ai-home-screen-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T17:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google expands AI flood forecasting to 700 million people; Apple plans to launch a new AI smart home hub; EU allocates €300 million for joint defense projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centrally managing root access for customers using AWS Organizations]]></title>
        <id>6cde4418308f8445718533784ecdb35490475db1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/centrally-managing-root-access-for-customers-using-aws-organizations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T16:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliminate long-term root credentials, perform privileged tasks via short-lived sessions, and centrally manage root access - aligning with security best practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Micro Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-micro-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-micro-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Sylvia and mgx, I decided to create a Bear Micro Blog, or status log, or shorts page – whatever you want to call it.
It's quite a simple solution, using tags and the Bear class_name snippet. Having it all in the post template also makes it pretty easy to publish posts. To make posting even easier, I'm planning to create an Apple Shortcut.
I've also ”created” separate feeds for status and posts:
RSS Feed for All Content
RSS Feed for Blog Posts
RSS feed for Status Updates
Let me know if you're interested in getting your own Bear status log and I will post a tutorial.
Wishing you a great weekend!
Update: Here's a tutorial.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please, Stop the Absurd Coding Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://blackentropy.com/please-stop-the-absurd-coding-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://blackentropy.com/please-stop-the-absurd-coding-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about tech interviews – specifically, the ones that go overboard with unrealistic coding assignments. If you’re a developer who’s been asked to debug legacy PHP or build a mini-app from scratch in just a few hours, you know what I’m talking about. It’s becoming a trend, and it’s not helping anyone.
Unrealistic Tests That Don’t Measure Real Skills
These high-stress, solo coding assignments don’t reflect the actual job. Instead, they put developers in situations they’d never face in the workplace, where collaboration and support are standard. When was the last time you had to debug an ancient codebase without documentation or help from a team? Yet companies claim this somehow measures “problem-solving” skills.
The Hidden Time Sink
What companies often ignore is the extra time cand…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Whom It May Concern: Demographic Differences in Letters of Recommendation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32509</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/to-whom-it-may-concern-demographic-differences-in-letters-of-recommendation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letters of recommendation from faculty advisors play a critical role in the job market for Ph.D. economists. At their best, they can convey important qualitative information about a candidate, including the candidate’s potential to generate impactful research. But at their worst, these letters offer a subjective view of the candidate that can be susceptible to conscious or unconscious bias. There may also be similarity or affinity bias, a particularly difficult issue for the economics profession, where most faculty members are white men. In this post, we draw on our recent working paper to describe how recommendation letters differ by the gender, race, or ethnicity of the job candidate and how these differences are related to early career outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beverly Hirtle and Anna Kovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlín Doherty: &ldquo;Interface&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/interface</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/interface"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T11:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Rachel Cusk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Employment growth in Europe. Stark differences.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45789</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/15/employment-growth-in-europe-stark-differences/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T09:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eurostat published new data on employment in Europe. Average employment growth is +0,9%. The average hides stark differences. A Germany-centered core consisting of Germany, Austria, Sweden, Estonia, Finland, and Hungary shows declines. Surprisingly, it excludes Denmark, Belgium and the Netherlands. The South does better. Countries like Portugal, France, Greece, and, especially, Spain post above-average increases. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by swiftcoder in "Something weird is happening with LLMs and chess"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42144784</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42144784"/>
        <updated>2024-11-15T07:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like the article neglects one obvious possibility: that OpenAI decided that chess was a benchmark worth "winning", special-cases chess within gpt-3.5-turbo-instruct, and then neglected to add that special-case to follow-up models since it wasn't generating sustained press coverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>swiftcoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>