<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-03T18:28:22.470Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-03T18:28:22.470Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/3/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274388</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-3-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemis; Jill Biden, Vogue cover girl; Stevie Nicks and Taylor Swift; Great Barrington grifters.~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Social Media Cause Anything?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52847</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/03/does-social-media-cause-anything/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 18 months since I quit Twitter, I can feel the atrophy of my vibe detector. I’m reading more than ever, on Substack and the FT, Discord and group chats — much of the same “content” I would’ve encountered on Twitter, in fact, but without the ever-present spiderweb of the social graph, the network […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code June 2024 Release (1.91)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Celebrating the Wrong Day For 25 years]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-celebrating-the-wrong-day-for-25-years/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-celebrating-the-wrong-day-for-25-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I found out that I have been celebrating the wrong day for a quarter of a century.
Let me back up a little bit…
I’m pretty good at remembering dates. If a date was at some point important to me, or I make a conscious effort to remember a date, it typically sticks with me. This can be a good, bad or absolutely useless talent depending on how you look at it. I even remember the date of when my first “serious” boyfriend asked me to be his girlfriend the summer before high school. I frequently remind my parents about my grandparents’ upcoming death anniversaries because they never seem to remember. I am basically a (niche) walking calendar.
So of course, I have deemed myself in charge of reminding my family on when we first set foot on US soil. Every year on July 3rd, I remind them of the date, and they just accept it as truth.
Except this year.
This year, my dad beat me to the punch. He texts the family group chat on July 2nd (yesterday) to let me know that it’s been 26 years since we first touched down in Newark International Airport in New Jersey. Of course, I countered and said that he was a day early (because I have literally been reminding them for the past 25 years). My mom jumps in with just a “No. July 2nd” before my dad shows the stamp on our passport that literally said: US IMMIGRATION: JULY 2, 1998 and said “Proof”. I imagined him doing a mic drop after that text.
So for the past 25 (now 26 years), I’ve been celebrating commemorating the wrong day, and no one bothered to correct me until now.
Oops.
Anyways, here’s to 26 years (+a day) of living here (I guess).
3/100
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First round of French election: party attacks and a modest traffic dip]]></title>
        <id>66853348a4598c000bd709b9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/first-round-of-french-election-2024-party-attacks-and-a-modest-traffic-dip"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare mitigated DDoS attacks targeting French political parties during the 2024 legislative elections, as detailed in our ongoing election coverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Declare your AIndependence: block AI bots, scrapers and crawlers with a single click]]></title>
        <id>668274eea4598c000bd707cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/declaring-your-aindependence-block-ai-bots-scrapers-and-crawlers-with-a-single-click"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help preserve a safe Internet for content creators, we’ve just launched a brand new “easy button” to block all AI bots. It’s available for all customers, including those on our free tier]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distributional Consequences of Responding Aggressively to Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30686</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/on-the-distributional-consequences-of-responding-aggressively-to-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post discusses the distributional consequences of an aggressive policy response to inflation using a Heterogeneous Agent New Keynesian (HANK) model. We find that, when facing demand shocks, stabilizing inflation and real activity go hand in hand, with very large benefits for households at the bottom of the wealth distribution. The converse is true however when facing supply shocks: stabilizing inflation makes real outcomes more volatile, especially for poorer households. We conclude that distributional considerations make it much more important for policy to take into account the tradeoffs between stabilizing inflation and economic activity. This is because the optimal policy response depends very strongly on whether these tradeoffs are present (that is, when the economy is facing supply shocks) or absent (when the economy is facing demand shocks).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Keshav Dogra, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/3/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274348</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-3-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T10:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our rolicking daily links: kidding kidders, deadly slapping cult, bird flu, Covid surges, climate change induced food price increases, EU v. China again, Keyna protests, France far right freakout, Gaza starvation, bar spying, moar Biden tug-of-war, Trump cases postponed, US car sales stall, cheap toilet paper indicator]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anxious Generation: A View of Where We Are and What Should Come Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274407</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/the-anxious-generation-a-view-of-where-we-are-and-what-should-come-next.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T10:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Haidt contends that changes in childrearing practices  have produced adults who on average are more anxious and fragile]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Houthis Turn the Red Sea Redder, Stymieing Israel and the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274349</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/the-houthis-turn-the-red-sea-redder-stymieing-israel-and-the-us.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T10:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the history of Yemen, its place in the region, and the remarkable Houthi campaign against Israel and Red Sea shipping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[July 4 Holiday Schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274403</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/july-4-holiday-schedule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T09:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will be taking a holiday of sorts via a reduced number of posts through next Monday. Hope you can take a break too!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structural Adjustment and the Washington Consensus Are Not Abandoned in 2000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T09:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ossyrial in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863919</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863919"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T08:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author links to the somewhat dystopian blog where the email sender is quite proud of their work. Their words (or perhaps that of an LLM):
> Could an AI agent craft compelling emails that would capture people's attention and drive engagement, all while maintaining a level of personalization that feels human? I decided to find out.
> The real hurdle was ensuring the emails seemed genuinely personalized and not spammy. I knew that if recipients detected even a whiff of a generic, mass-produced message, they'd tune out immediately.
> Incredibly, not a single recipient seemed to detect that the emails were AI-generated.
https://www.wisp.blog/blog/how-i-use-ai-agents-to-send-1000-...
The technical part surprised me: they string together multiple LLMs which do all the work. It's a shame the author's passions are directed towards AI slop-email spam, all for capturing attention and driving engagement.
How much of our societal progress and collective thought and innovation has gone to capturing attention and driving up engagement, I wonder.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ossyrial</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by taylorius in "I Received an AI Email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863586</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40863586"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T07:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future - megawatts of electricity being used, 24/7 as armies of LLMs email and debate each other, and try to sell each other programs at a great discount.
As for the humans, we went fishing instead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>taylorius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden in the Bardo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327037</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/biden-in-the-bardo/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T06:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seymour Hersh said Biden isn’t all there. Thomas Friedman and Jane Fonda were reduced to tears. Rob Reiner, who watched the debate with Fonda in LA in the company of Doug Emhoff, the husband of Biden’s VP Kamala Harris, screamed at the TV: “We’ve lost.” One of the party's top money-bundlers told Politico: "Our only hope is that he bows out, we have a brokered convention or he dies. Otherwise, we are fucking dead.” More
The post Biden in the Bardo appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Declaring Independence From the Declaration of Independence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326956</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/declaring-independence-from-the-declaration-of-independence/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T06:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Declaration is a manifesto. Its purpose was to explain and justify violent opposition to British “occupation.”  By 1776 gendered and racialized violence was already deeply ingrained within the white settlers.  It was the product of what it took from 1619/20 forward to seize and hold territory, to enslave and keep enslaved at least 500,000 Black people and to control deviant white settlers. (For context as to the latter, the Salem Witch trials were in 1692/93.) More
The post Declaring Independence From the Declaration of Independence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Joyce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump Supreme Court’s War on the Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/the-trump-supreme-courts-war-on-the-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In explaining the decisions regarding regulatory powers, Chief Justice John Roberts, the most reactionary chief justice since Roger Taney, argued that “agencies have no special competence in resolving statutory ambiguities.  Courts do.” It should be noted that justices and judges have no special competence in technical and scientific matters.  The regulatory agencies do.  It is up to Congress to introduce legislation to protect the ability of the U.S. government to conduct policy as well as the ability of regulatory agencies to carry out such policy. More
The post The Trump Supreme Court’s War on the Environment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting NATO’s War Summit in Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327074</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/confronting-natos-war-summit-in-washington/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After NATO’s catastrophic, illegal invasions of Yugoslavia, Libya and Afghanistan, on July 9th NATO plans to invade Washington DC. The good news is that it only plans to occupy Washington for three days. The British will not burn down the U.S. Capitol as they did in 1814, and the Germans are still meekly pretending that  More
The post Confronting NATO’s War Summit in Washington appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Benjamin - Nicolas J. S. Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Anti-Nuclear War Vigil Behind Bars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327020</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/our-anti-nuclear-war-vigil-behind-bars/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Susan Crane (left) and Susan van der Hijden at a past peace camp at Büchel air base Here in Rohrbach prison we are awakened by the sounds of doves and other birds, giving the illusion that all is well in the world, until other sounds, keys rattling, doors being shut, and guards doing the morning  More
The post Our Anti-Nuclear War Vigil Behind Bars appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Crane – Susan van der Hijden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Abysmal Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327112</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/bidens-abysmal-debate/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As much as partisan Democrats seek to put lipstick on a pig, Biden’s first and probably last presidential debate was a disaster, if not fatal. Not only did it fail to do what it was supposed to do but it also confirmed public perceptions about Biden and trendlines in the presidential race that had largely been  More
The post Biden’s Abysmal Debate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schultz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another American War in the Middle East?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327099</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/another-american-war-in-the-middle-east/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-June, the Associated Press announced that the U.S. Navy had been engaged in the most intense naval combat since the end of World War II, which surely would come as a surprise to most Americans. This time, the fighting isn’t taking place in the Atlantic or Pacific Oceans but in the Red Sea and the adversary  More
The post Another American War in the Middle East? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genocide is the Election Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327115</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/327115/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As prospective candidates for the next UK parliament enter their final week of electioneering, it is hard to believe that Israel’s relentless slaughter of the Palestinian people has got barely a mention. With the singular exception of the Workers Party, headed by George Galloway, and a number of Independents, the political parties fielding candidates in  More
The post Genocide is the Election Issue appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Cuba Actually Influencing 2024 Elections in Florida?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327109</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/is-cuba-actually-influencing-2024-elections-in-florida/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Miami Herald has flung all concern for journalistic standards to the wind in a fear-mongering piece speculating that Cuba will influence 2024 elections in Florida. The evidence? McClatchy correspondent Michael Wilner and Miami Herald reporter Nora Gámez Torres present none. Instead, they base their piece on an “assessment,” about which almost no details are provided, by anonymous officials with  More
The post Is Cuba Actually Influencing 2024 Elections in Florida? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Lindsay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Attempts at the Apolitical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326869</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/letter-from-london-attempts-at-the-apolitical/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A number of times over the past five years I have woken up in the middle of the night wondering how Julian Assange was getting on in nearby Belmarsh Prison. (I have written about this here before.) I wondered again last week, only to discover — like one of those dramatic slam cuts in a  More
The post Letter from London: Attempts at the Apolitical appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Gazans’ Extreme Hunger Could Leave Its Mark on Subsequent Generations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326868</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/why-gazans-extreme-hunger-could-leave-its-mark-on-subsequent-generations/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T05:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Israel’s offensive in Gaza rages on, people across the entire Gaza Strip find themselves in increasingly dire circumstances, with nearly the entire population experiencing high levels of food insecurity, including malnutrition, hunger and starvation. A famine review analysis from the Integrated Food Security Phase Classification reported on June 25, 2024, that “a high risk  More
The post Why Gazans’ Extreme Hunger Could Leave Its Mark on Subsequent Generations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hasan Khatib</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Holy Day: July 1, 2024 Negated July 4, 1776]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327101</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/03/no-holy-day-july-1-2024-negated-july-4-1776/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T04:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Declaration of Independence (“DOI”) died July 1, 2024. The King lives. God save the King! Yep, the president, or King of the US, now has official, legal immunity! It’s about time. It took 248 years to get rid of that pesky idea that, “in America Law Is King” promulgated by that traitor Tom Paine!  More
The post No Holy Day: July 1, 2024 Negated July 4, 1776 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kary Love</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian bookseller Booktopia in voluntary administration]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7947</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-bookseller-booktopia-voluntary-administration/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T03:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is sad and concerning news. The Melbourne based bookseller had become well ensconced in the Australian literary realm, since being founded about twenty-years ago. The company, which is also listed on the ASX (though trading of shares has been suspended), had been struggling financially in recent years though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Han Ryner - Ethical Individualism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T01:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Han Ryner
Title: Ethical Individualism
Subtitle: Selected Texts
Date: 2019
Notes: Translated from French to English by Kirk Watson.

Translator’s Introduction
 At the dawn of the 20th century, Europe hosted a brief blossoming of individualistic thought. Inspired by the great thinkers of the preceding century such as Stirner, Ibsen, Nietzsche, and Spencer, they offered a free-thinking, non-dogmatic alternative to the increasingly powerful Marxists and syndicalists of the left, and the economists and theologians of the right. Importantly, this generation of thinkers developed the critique of the State into a critique of society as a whole, which immunized them from recruitment by the anarchist movement. As Ryner says in the Handbook, the anarchists are naive: victory by the anarchist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize your Java application with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>405bbc736a74a4576b2623243a568f24e835610b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/modernize-your-java-application-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations have critical legacy Java applications that are increasingly difficult to maintain. Modernizing these applications is a necessary, daunting, and risky task that takes the focus off of creating new value or features. This includes undocumented code, outdated frameworks and libraries, security vulnerabilities, a lack of logging and error handling, and a lack of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chetan Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Shevek - Leave, Or Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Lee Shevek
Title: Leave, Or Else
Subtitle: Giving Ultimatums to Abuse Victims
Date: April 10, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2 July 2024 from butchanarchy.medium.com/leave-or-else-a60b0dbac2a6

 Abuse is ubiquitous in our society, and as a result there are very few among us, if any, who have not been abused themselves or in proximity to someone else being abused. Myths about why and how abuse occurs run rampant and the ones that dominate are ones that ultimately serve in the maintenance of the status quo that keeps victims disempowered and silent. As a result, even those few who do actually believe victims of abuse and see the danger such abuse poses to them still often respond to the conditions the victim is entrapped within in ways that ultimately affirm the abuser’s narrative and fur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I like your old music better than your new music]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7938</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-old-music-better-than-new-music/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might say that of U2, whose music I once really liked, especially the stuff they did in the nineties. Achtung Baby. Zooropa. Pop. Even 2000’s All That You Can’t Leave Behind. These albums mostly represented their electronic music phase. I’d have them on loop for days at a time. I drew the ire of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Slips a Cog: Second Time as Tragedy, Second Time as Farce, or Both?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274329</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/bidens-slips-cog-second-time-as-tragedy-second-time-as-farce-or-both.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aftermath of Biden's debate with Trump critiqued as drama.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Service in Dissent: Joint Statement of U.S. Government Officials Who Have Resigned Over U.S. Policy Towards Gaza, Palestine, and Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327131</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/service-in-dissent-joint-statement-of-u-s-government-officials-who-have-resigned-over-u-s-policy-towards-gaza-palestine-and-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:25:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Administration’s policy in Gaza is a failure and a threat to U.S. national security. America’s diplomatic cover for, and continuous flow of arms to, Israel has ensured our undeniable complicity in the killings and forced starvation of a besieged Palestinian population in Gaza. This is not only morally reprehensible and in clear violation of international humanitarian law and U.S. laws, but it has also put a target on America’s back. More
The post Service in Dissent: Joint Statement of U.S. Government Officials Who Have Resigned Over U.S. Policy Towards Gaza, Palestine, and Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Blogroll, or to not?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really love the idea of having a Blogroll. When checking out a new blog, after reading and perusing said blog, I typically check to see if it has one. I think it’s one of the best ways to find new people to subscribe to, new content to read, and/or new perspectives to be exposed to. However, I don’t have one on my blog. Hypocritical? Maybe. Or maybe it’s just really personal preference.
I grew up in the days of MySpace, and this irrational want to be included in everyone’s Top 8. Then when you’re in their Top 8, you watch that list like a hawk in case you drop from Top 2 to Top 5, or even worse, drop off altogether. Granted, blogrolls are a bit different since there’s no hard limit on how many can be included (or specified order), but the idea is similar.
You see, I’m fine and OK with no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274350</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; stay safe, new Covid charts; Trump holds his own, pre-debate; Presidential immunity after Trump v. United States ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a Polaroid summer project]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/a-polaroid-summer-project/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/a-polaroid-summer-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T16:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent the long weekend clearing the cobwebs from my apartment.
The main purge was throwing out YEARS of old diaries and journals—all of them. Not one survived.
I've been thinking about doing this for a long time. Reading them made me feel horrible, and they all seemed to circle the same themes. Lugging those boxes full of journals to each new apartment felt tiresome. It was time to let them go.
I feel good about it. I'm free: to untangle myself from past narratives; from reinforcing and remembering things I don't wish to remember; to change; to reinvent the person I want to be.
Next on the to-get-rid-of list: books, clothes, paper ephemera, apps, expired kitchen things, tucked-away closet articles, + bathroom items.
Sketchbook things: 

Polaroid-inspired pencil and marker drawing
&nbsp

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: Get Bored!]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/re-get-bored/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/re-get-bored/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This text starts with a blank page.
There is a rough idea of what it will be about, but not much more than that. It usually works best this way, I think. As usual, my phone and computer are set to "do not disturb" when I'm writing.
Even the basic idea itself often comes out of some kind of void: when I'm walking, driving, or eating, for example. Poof! Suddenly something appears, like the characteristic light bulb symbol.
Creation requires empty space and time. The more successful you are in creating this, the better your overall output will be. So, get bored.
This is what Nikhil writes in the post Get Bored.
I think it's so well put. That's precisely how it is. Just as a document or canvas needs a blank surface to be used, we, as individuals, need an inner void to make room for creation.
Our lives are full of excellent opportunities to create these spaces. They're there every day: we're waiting for the elevator, we've stopped at a traffic light, or we're in line at the grocery store. Magnificent opportunities for a moment of “boredom” — an invitation to creativity.
Your best blog post ever could appear the next time you're on an escalator doing absolutely nothing.
“Bored to death” is the birth of creativity.
This post joins the July Reply blog challenge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[micro tool to convert bear blog csv exports to markdown files]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/micro-tool-to-convert-bear-blog-csv-exports-to-markdown-files/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/micro-tool-to-convert-bear-blog-csv-exports-to-markdown-files/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#b2md{border:2px dotted var(--border-color);padding:20px}.b2mdcontainer{display:flex;justify-content:space-between;align-items:center}.b2mdcontainer input{order:1}.b2mdcontainer button{order:2}#InfoText{color:#8a2be2;font-size:90%;margin-bottom:0}.image-container{position:relative;display:inline-block}.modal,.toggle-input{display:none}.b2md-img{transition:transform .3s}@media (min-width:700px){.b2md-img:hover{transform:scale(1.05)}}.modal{position:fixed;z-index:1000;left:0;top:0;width:100%;height:100%;overflow:auto;background-color:rgba(0,0,0,.8)}.modal-content{background-color:#fefefe;margin:2% auto;padding:20px;border:1px solid #888;width:80%;max-width:700px;box-shadow:0 4px 8px rgba(0,0,0,.2);color:var(--text-color)}@media (prefers-color-scheme:dark){.modal-content{background-color:#012…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aryanam - Funeral, Theocracy, & Religious Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-funeral-theocracy-religious-capital?v=1719921893</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-funeral-theocracy-religious-capital?v=1719921893"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:04:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aryanam
Title: Funeral, Theocracy, & Religious Capital
Subtitle: Observations & Thoughts After a Comrade’s Death
Date: March 10th, 2024
Source: asranarshism.com/1402/12/20/funeral-theocracy-religious-capital-en

 An accident. An accident tore a family apart. An accident took a brave and kind comrade from us. We will remember the date. It was December 2023. 
 Death will come for us all. But, for now, we must put our shattered hearts back together. We need to organize. We need to fight. We need to grieve. Yet, we are not free to grieve, the same way we are not free to be. Not free to love. Not free to live. Countless surviving families and friends were vultured in one of their most vulnerable times. Countless victims of patriarchal honor killings were buried by their murderers. Count…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sheffield Action Group - What is School?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sheffield-action-group-what-is-school?v=1719921860</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sheffield-action-group-what-is-school?v=1719921860"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sheffield Action Group
Title: What is School?
Date: February 2024
Notes: From Sheffield Action Group’s Troublemakers zine, this important piece stands on its own

 As students at university, we have a lot more to say about the global and national role of our institutions — this will come at another point. For now we will focus on primary and secondary school. Many reading this will have left 13 years of schooling, likely hating most of it, and may not have thought a lot about the scale of its impact on our lives and how things could have been so, so different. 
 School is a class stratifier along eugenic lines. Those deemed more intelligent by their ability to absorb and spit out information in tests are seen as more suited for higher paying jobs and therefore, by this society’s lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Znore - Hermetic Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/znore-hermetic-anarchism?v=1719921672</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/znore-hermetic-anarchism?v=1719921672"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T12:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Znore
Title: Hermetic Anarchism
Subtitle: Othering the Other, Uttering the Otter and Uddering the Author
Date: 2014
Source: groupnameforgrapejuice.blogspot.com

I. Hermetic Anarchism and Othering the Other
 Imagination is a magic carpet 
 Upon which we may soar 
 To distant lands and climes 
 And even go beyond the moon 
 To any planet in the sky 
 If we came from nowhere here 
 Why can’t we go somewhere there? 
 Sun Ra – Imagination 
 I end up spending a lot of time in Jimbocho, the old bookseller’s district in Tokyo. Hours and hours I rifle through piles and stacks of dusty pulp hunting for gems. Usually my luck is good, and occasionally I find just the book that I need. There are two shops in particular, both specializing in used English books, where uncanny things can happen. A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ersilia Cavedagni - The Woman]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ersilia-cavedagni-the-woman?v=1719921475</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ersilia-cavedagni-the-woman?v=1719921475"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ersilia Cavedagni
Title: The Woman
Date: 28 October 1899
Notes: Published in The Unstoppable Anarchist Ersilia Cavedagni & Her Selected Writings (pp. 32-34) at <thetransmetropolitanreview.files.wordpress.com> (PDF).
Source: Retrieved on 18 March 2024 from thetransmetropolitanreview.wordpress.com.

 Generally men, rightly or wrongly, claim to have an intellectual and moral superiority over women, in addition to physical superiority. So be it! I want to grant it. 
 Strangely enough, in the vast majority of cases the man who considers himself superior to the woman takes little or no effort to reduce her inferiority and to raise the woman to his level. 
 This happens more especially among men who have a wife or partner. It would be logical that, if only out of a feeling of pride, the h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Barnsley - If it Was Easy They Wouldn’t Call it ‘Struggle’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-barnsley-if-it-was-easy-they-wouldn-t-call-it-struggle?v=1719921397</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-barnsley-if-it-was-easy-they-wouldn-t-call-it-struggle?v=1719921397"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mark Barnsley
Title: If it Was Easy They Wouldn’t Call it ‘Struggle’
Subtitle: Mark Barnsley Talks About Repression and Resistance in British Prisons
Date: 2005
Source: <zinelibrary.files.wordpress.com/2016/01/barnsley.pdf>

 Mark Barnsley has been involved in the Anarchist movement all his adult life, spending time fighting in Lebanon, editing The Sheffield Anarchist, supporting striking miners, confronting fascists, and spending 10 years in prison. Held in 20 different maximum or high security prisons, and 18 different segregation units, he has always taken the fight to the Enemy in jail. Released from prison in 2002, Mark continues to be as active as ever, speaking all over Europe, and being involved in the Campaign Against Prison Slavery, the Anarchist Black Cross, and many oth…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinian Resistance veteran Mark Barnsley on why he joined up]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/palestinian-resistance-veteran-mark-barnsley-on-why-he-joined-up?v=1719921176</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/palestinian-resistance-veteran-mark-barnsley-on-why-he-joined-up?v=1719921176"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title: Palestinian Resistance veteran Mark Barnsley on why he joined up
Date: 2009
Source: <duncanpickstock.co.uk/index.php/videos/testament>

 And they said, oh, are you the the lads that have come to fight in Lebanon? And we said yeah, that’s us. And we sat in the back of this Peugeot car and I remember Lero nudging me, and there was a handgun underneat the dashboard and there was a butt of what was a Kalashnikov underneath one of the seats. So I was like, well, this is the real deal isn’t it? 
Mark Barnsley fought with The Palestinian Resistance between 1978 and 1980
 Well, before I started school, me and my sister, who’s 18 months younger than me, used to on a Friday, we would go to town with my mum, to meet her mother, our grandma and we’d get dragged around the market for a bit. Then…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antithesi - The Ecological Crisis and the Rise of Post-Fascism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antithesi-the-ecological-crisis-and-the-rise-of-post-fascism?v=1719921075</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antithesi-the-ecological-crisis-and-the-rise-of-post-fascism?v=1719921075"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antithesi
Title: The Ecological Crisis and the Rise of Post-Fascism
Date: January 28, 2024
Notes: Translated into English and posted by Illwill on February 17th, 2024
Source: Retrieved on March 19th, 2024 from https://illwill.com/antithesi.

 The ecological crisis profoundly impacts the material conditions of social reproduction, extending beyond “natural disasters” to encompass a deepening of the contradictions inherent in capitalism. This crisis does not only manifest itself in events like floods, droughts, and pandemics, it also plays a direct role in fueling conflicts, social unrest, and mass displacement. In what follows, we attempt to lay out a comprehensive argument for the connection between the ecological crisis and the rise of what we call the post-fascist current, a poli…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pranay Somayajula - nationhood beyond nationalism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pranay-somayajula-nationhood-beyond-nationalism?v=1719920998</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pranay-somayajula-nationhood-beyond-nationalism?v=1719920998"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pranay Somayajula
Title: nationhood beyond nationalism
Subtitle: towards an anarchist politics of anticolonial liberation
Date: December 29th, 2023
Source: Retrieved on March 25th, 2024 from https://www.culture-shock.xyz/p/nationhood-beyond-nationalism.

 In its Spring 2001 issue, the Oregon-based magazine Green Anarchy ran an anonymous article with the title: “The EZLN is NOT Anarchist: Or Struggles at the Margins and Revolutionary Solidarity.” Writing from an anarchist perspective, the author advanced a fierce critique of the Zapatista National Liberation Army—the militant anticolonial, anticapitalist Indigenous movement which had led an uprising and established autonomous zones in southern Mexico several years before, and which is often cited by anarchists as an example of a suc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imanol - Blind Spot]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/imanol-blind-spot?v=1719920664</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/imanol-blind-spot?v=1719920664"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Imanol
Title: Blind Spot
Subtitle: Manuel Huet and the libertarian underground in France
Date: 2023
Notes: Translated by Paul Sharkey from El Angulo Muerto : Manuel Huet y la clandestinidad libertaria en Francia.
Source: English translation published by the Kate Sharpley Library www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 
 
 The Kate Sharpley Library aims to preserve the history of the anarchist movement and record and commemorate the lives of the people who made up the movement. It’s always good to see other people plugging away at the same task. The first translation of a piece by Imanol that we put up was ‘The Massana Gang’ which went in KSL: Bulletin of the Kate Sharpley Library No. 97–98, February 2019. Since then we’ve been glad to host translations of his studies from El Salto which are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harsha Walia - What Is Border Imperialism?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/harsha-walia-what-is-border-imperialism?v=1719919583</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/harsha-walia-what-is-border-imperialism?v=1719919583"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Harsha Walia
Title: What Is Border Imperialism?
Subtitle: Excerpt from Undoing Border Imperialism
Date: 2013
Source: Undoing Border Imperialism. AK Press / Institute for Anarchist Studies, 2013. Pages 35 to 74.

What Is Border Imperialism?
 The world was born yearning to be a home for everyone. 
 —Eduardo Galeano, “Through the Looking Glass: Q & A with Eduardo Galeano” 
 For the past several years, Indigenous organizations in Australia have been issuing “Original Passports” to asylum seekers who have been detained or denied legal status by the Australian government. Most recently, in May 2012, passports were issued to two detained Tamil asylum seekers. During the ceremony, Ray Jackson of the Indigenous Social Justice Association said, “The Australian Government must stop imprisonin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frott - Bulldoze SCI Rockview]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/frott-bulldoze-sci-rockview?v=1719918854</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/frott-bulldoze-sci-rockview?v=1719918854"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Frott
Title: Bulldoze SCI Rockview
Subtitle: Abolition, Prisoner Support, and Resistance to Genocide in PA-DOC
Date: 4/7/24
Notes: 4/7/24 The Final Straw Radio — Episode Transcription
Source: https://ia600308.us.archive.org/5/items/tfsr-202404072024-SCIRockview/Bulldoze-sci-rockview.pdf

 Intro SCI Rockview is a prison in central Pennsylvania where incarcerated comrades have been facing repression for demanding justice in the face of impunity by racist COs and following a year of prisoner deaths due to institutional toxicity and guard violence. We speak to an outside supporter about the situation at Rockview, the reactions of administration, inside / outside relationships and solidarity that have flared up. We hope that this conversation contributes to increased and thickened ties …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Israel is pioneering new methods of genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-israel-is-pioneering-new-methods-of-genocide?v=1719918743</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-israel-is-pioneering-new-methods-of-genocide?v=1719918743"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Israel is pioneering new methods of genocide
Subtitle: Killing by algorithm
Date: April 16th, 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 18th, 2024 from https://petergelderloos.substack.com/p/israel-is-pioneering-new-methods.

 Israel is making sure it will be remembered in history as a pioneer of genocide. Multiple Israeli military sources have testified that the Israeli military is using AI to guide missile and bomb strikes against Palestinians[1]. If the Israeli military’s Artificial Intelligence determines that a person is a military member of Hamas, the Israeli military will systematically approve of a missile or bomb strike to murder that person and any civilians in the immediate vicinity. 
 The AI program used by the IDF, called ‘Lavender,’ can also determine th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loren Goldner - The Spanish Revolution, Past and Future: Grandeur and Poverty of Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/loren-goldner-the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism?v=1719918699</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/loren-goldner-the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism?v=1719918699"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Loren Goldner
Title: The Spanish Revolution, Past and Future: Grandeur and Poverty of Anarchism
Subtitle: How the Working Class Takes Over (or Doesn’t), Then and Now
Date: 2013
Source: Retrieved on April 19th, 2024 from <breaktheirhaughtypower.org/the-spanish-revolution-past-and-future-grandeur-and-poverty-of-anarchism-how-the-working-class-takes-over-or-doesnt-then-and-now>.

Introduction: Why the Spanish Revolution Today?
 “…anarchism and revolutionary syndicalism in general lacked a vision of the problems of political orientation, without which the most powerful and most heroic revolutionary surge is condemned to failure.” — Helmut Rüdiger, AIT, Ensayo critico sobre la revolucion española (1940)[1]
 For many years, I had held the classical left anti-Stalinist view that after the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Fleischmann - “Red Mutualism” Series at Mutualism Co-Op]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/red-mutualism-series-at-mutualism-co-op?v=1719918555</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/red-mutualism-series-at-mutualism-co-op?v=1719918555"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eric Fleischmann
Title: “Red Mutualism” Series at Mutualism Co-Op
Date: April 23rd, 2024
Source: Retrieved 4/25/2024 from https://c4ss.org/content/59582.

 If there are two contemporary anarchist theorists whose work occupies and influences my thought the most, they are Kevin Carson and Wayne Price. Carson has spent a huge segment of his career not just reconstructing a mutualist political economy as an alternative to the anarchist default to the economics of Karl Marx but also making incredibly original contributions to the fields of decentralized technology/production and spontaneous organization theory. Wayne Price in turn has dedicated his mind to a task that at first seems wholly opposite to Carson’s: working to adapt Marxist economics and political strategy to an anarchist co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, CrimethInc. - Campus Building Occupations, 2008–2010 and Today]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-campus-building-occupations-2008-2010-and-today?v=1719918476</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-campus-building-occupations-2008-2010-and-today?v=1719918476"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, CrimethInc.
Title: Campus Building Occupations, 2008–2010 and Today
Date: April 22 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 25th 2024 from <crimethinc.com/2024/04/22/campus-building-occupations-from-2008-2010-to-today>

 A wave of campus building occupations took place in response to austerity measures following the recession of 2008. As today’s Gaza solidarity movement begins to experiment with encampments and building occupations, it could be instructive to learn from the previous generation of student activists. 
 On April 22, 2024, inspired by the resilience of the Gaza solidarity encampment at Columbia University and other demonstrators around the country, students at Cal Poly Humboldt in Arcata, California occupied Siemens Hall. This represented the first confrontational bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, CrimethInc. - “It Is an Honor to Be Suspended for Palestine”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine?v=1719918373</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-crimethinc-it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine?v=1719918373"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, CrimethInc.
Title: “It Is an Honor to Be Suspended for Palestine”
Subtitle: Dispatches from the Solidarity Encampment at Columbia University
Date: April 21 2024
Source: Retrieved on April 25th 2024 from https://crimethinc.com/2024/04/21/it-is-an-honor-to-be-suspended-for-palestine-dispatches-from-the-solidarity-encampment-at-columbia-university

 On April 17, students at Columbia University and Barnard College set up an encampment in solidarity with Palestinians facing genocide at the hands of the Israeli military. On April 18, the university administration brought in massive numbers of police to arrest the demonstrators and crush the encampment; yet in response, students established a new encampment, bigger than the first, inspiring copycat actions from Yale to St. Loui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supreme Court Rules Hitler Immune from Prosecution for Burning Down Reichstag, Seizing Absolute Power]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52835</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/02/supreme-court-rules-hitler-immune-from-prosecution-for-burning-down-reichstag-seizing-absolute-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the current Supreme Court had held comparable office in Weimar Germany, that is, its opinion in Trump v. United States would have rendered the judgment in this post’s headline. Never mind that the Weimar Constitution was different from the U.S. Constitution (importantly, in granting emergency powers to the President to rule by decree under […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liz Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distributional Effects of Inflation and Inflation Stabilization]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30644</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/on-the-distributional-effects-of-inflation-and-inflation-stabilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post and the next discuss the distributional effects of inflation and inflation stabilization through the lenses of a theoretical model—a Heterogeneous Agent New Keynesian (HANK) model. This model combines the features of New Keynesian models that have been the workhorse for monetary policy analysis since the work of Woodford (2003) with inequality in wealth and income at the household level following the seminal contribution of Kaplan, Moll, and Violante (2018). We find that while inflation hurts everyone, it hurts the poor in particular. When the source of inflation is a supply shock, fighting inflation aggressively hurts the poor even more, however, while the opposite is true for demand shocks, as discussed in the companion post.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Keshav Dogra, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angie Barbosa - Marginal Ontologies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies?v=1719917880</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies?v=1719917880"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Angie Barbosa
Title: Marginal Ontologies
Subtitle: Challenges of a Transfeminist Anarchism
Date: 08.03.2023
Notes: Translation by Cello Latini Pfeil [mltpfeil@gmail.com]
Source: Original translation of “Ontologias Marginais: Desafios de um Anarquismo Transfeminista”. Retrieved on 04.28.2024 from https://revistatapuia.com.br/ojs/index.php/revista/article/view/29/19

Abstract
 In this text, written as a speech for the 1st Anarchist Fair in Rio de Janeiro, contradictions of the historically predatory relationship of brazilian democracy with brazilian travestis and transsexuals are presented, paying attention to the ontological marginality of the travesti body under the capitalist patriarchy of white supremacy. Based on this reflection, transfeminist challenges to radical and anarchist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274238</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our foxy daily links: Moth fans, lithium secrets? Covid cognitive impairment in kids, China space setback, France first round freakout, Tory rebound? Hamas still in control, Iran elections Fedex spying, European deportation, moar Biden not budging, Supremes on prez immunity, AI, EU v. Meta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mother Earth - If We Must Fight, Let It Be For The Social Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-if-we-must-fight-let-it-be-for-the-social-revolution?v=1719917731</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-if-we-must-fight-let-it-be-for-the-social-revolution?v=1719917731"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mother Earth
Title: If We Must Fight, Let It Be For The Social Revolution
Date: 1914
Notes: From “Mother Earth”, October 1914, New York City, published by Emma Goldman, edited by Alexander Berkman

 Society has plunged into a world-wide war, but we Anarchists, we cannot shed tears over its horrors, as do the Socialists and other so-called philanthropists. WE KNOW how industriously those same weepers have been piling up the fuel which made this conflagration certain. 
 Governments have made this war. The Austrian government ordered its slaves to sweep Servia with fire and sword. The German government snapped its fingers at the four million and odd Socialist voters, and ordered its slaves to invade Belgium. The American government with hypocritical sobs and sighs, ordered its slaves …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico Scores Major Victory Against Bayer-Owned Monsanto As Corn War With US Reaches Pivotal Moment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274262</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/mexico-scores-major-victory-against-bayer-owned-monsanto-as-corn-war-with-us-reaches-decisive-moment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T10:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Reason has ultimately prevailed in favour of life, health, nature, biodiversity and food sovereignty.” After a four-year legal battle on multiple fronts with Mexico’s AMLO government, Monsanto has finally thrown in the towel. Last Tuesday, Mexico’s National Council of Humanities, Sciences and Technologies (Conahcyt) announced that two Mexican divisions of Monsanto — now subsidiaries of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by awesomekling in "Ladybird Web Browser becomes a non-profit with $1M from GitHub Founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40854904</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40854904"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T09:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello friends, Ladybird founder here!
Here's a short video from Chris Wanstrath announcing our non-profit yesterday, and kicking things off with a $1M donation: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k9edTqPMX_k
Happy to answer questions :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>awesomekling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Efficiency and Performance: Navigating the Spark 3 and EMR 6 Upgrade Journey at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16763</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/unlocking-efficiency-and-performance-navigating-the-spark-3-and-emr-6-upgrade-journey-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slack Data Engineering recently underwent data workload migration from AWS EMR 5 (Spark 2/Hive 2 processing engine) to EMR 6 (Spark 3 processing engine). In this blog, we will share our migration journey, challenges, and the performance gains we observed in the process. This blog aims to assist Data Engineers, Data Infrastructure Engineers, and Product […]
The post Unlocking Efficiency and Performance: Navigating the Spark 3 and EMR 6 Upgrade Journey at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilanjana Mukherjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Finland, the Left Alliance Just Trounced the Far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/In-Finland-the-Left-Alliance-Just-Trounced-the-Far-Right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/In-Finland-the-Left-Alliance-Just-Trounced-the-Far-Right"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T08:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's elections saw gains for anti-immigration parties — but the breakthrough act in Finland was the Left Alliance, with 17% support. Its leader, Li Andersson, told Jacobin about why it did so well and how it defeated the far right. 
English

/ 
Antifascism, 
North, 
Finland]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Dite, Li Andersson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s De Facto EV Mandate at Risk After Supreme Court ‘Chevron’ Ruling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274336</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/bidens-de-facto-ev-mandate-at-risk-after-supreme-court-chevron-ruling.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T08:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at just one implication of the fresh Chevron Supreme Court ruling demonstrates how far-reaching it is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin shortlist for Australian fiction]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7935</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-shortlist-australian-fiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shortlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for works of Australian fiction, was announced earlier today. Of the ten novels named on the longlist in May, the following six titles have been included today: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen Craig Anam, by André Dao The Bell of the World, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advice on faculty job application letters]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52810</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/02/advice-on-faculty-job-application-letters/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T07:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m hosting a couple of professionalization discussions for our PhD candidates and postdocs this summer, informal conversations to help them navigate the crazy academic job market. A few weeks ago we discussed job talks as the department had just had a bunch of candidates visit (very different schedule here in Europe than the US) and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eszter Hargittai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel in Gaza: The Jewish Break with Zionism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326843</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/israel-in-gaza-the-jewish-break-with-zionism/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T06:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something has happened in connection with Israel’s savage war in Gaza that no one expected and that few even now want to discuss. It cannot be summarized numerically – not even when the number of dead and missing Palestinians now exceeds 38,000 and when the total number of casualties is well over 120,000 – the equivalent, in population terms, of 14 million Americans. Nor can it be expressed by describing the effects of starvation, disease, and psychological damage on the surviving two million-plus Gazans, 85% of whom have been displaced from their homes, and who now face continued air and ground strikes aimed at the remaining forces of Hamas.  More
The post Israel in Gaza: The Jewish Break with Zionism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Rubenstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Prescription for Taxing Our World’s Richest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326863</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/a-practical-prescription-for-taxing-our-worlds-richest/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wonder why the divide between the world’s richest and everybody else keeps getting wider? Gabriel Zucman, one of the world’s finest young economists, has just produced a report that riffs on one key reason: Our super rich pay next to nothing in taxes. Just how close to nothing? This close: Over the past four  More
The post A Practical Prescription for Taxing Our World’s Richest appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa’s ‘Government of Neoliberal Unity’ is Constructed on Shaky Ground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327067</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/south-africas-government-of-neoliberal-unity-is-constructed-on-shaky-ground/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 30, South Africa’s leader Cyril Ramaphosa announced his new Government of National Unity (GNU), including 31 ministers in his Cabinet. In the national and provincial elections that had taken place a month earlier, Ramaphosa’s African National Congress won 40% of the vote and the white-led Democratic Alliance won 22%, following which a variety  More
The post South Africa’s ‘Government of Neoliberal Unity’ is Constructed on Shaky Ground appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump/Biden Debate Immigration: US Foreign Policy as a Driver Is Ignored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326862</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/trump-biden-debate-immigration-us-foreign-policy-as-a-driver-is-ignored/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The immigration issue dominated the debate. The challenger claimed that the country was being menaced by immigrants – marauding hordes of rapists, murders, and mentally ill. They were the ruination of the nation. Social Security and Medicare were jeopardized by the alien element. Immigrants endangered the jobs of blacks and Hispanics. There was nothing good and a lot bad about the threat of the foreign-born, who should be deported in large numbers according to Mr. Trump. More
The post Trump/Biden Debate Immigration: US Foreign Policy as a Driver Is Ignored appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Aid and War – How Israel has Used Starvation to Subdue the Palestinians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327072</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/on-aid-and-war-how-israel-has-used-starvation-to-subdue-the-palestinians/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humanitarian aid should never be politicized though, quite often, the very survival of nations is used as political bargaining chips. Sadly, Gaza remains a prime example. Even before the current war, the Gaza Strip suffered under a 17-year hermetic blockade, which has rendered the impoverished area virtually ‘unlivable’. That very term, ‘unlivable’ was used by  More
The post On Aid and War – How Israel has Used Starvation to Subdue the Palestinians  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mystery of the Missing Apes Who Came Before Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327050</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/the-mystery-of-the-missing-apes-who-came-before-humans/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fossil record of our ape ancestors in Africa is almost nonexistent for a period of about 8 or 9 million years. This long gap lasted from about 16.5 million to 7 to 9 million years ago, during the Miocene geological epoch. Yet fossil remains in Europe and Asia show an abundance of ape species  More
The post The Mystery of the Missing Apes Who Came Before Humans appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marjorie Hecht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Nearly One Trillion Dollar Military Budget Won’t Make Us Safer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327052</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/our-nearly-one-trillion-dollar-military-budget-wont-make-us-safer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you looked at the U.S. military budget without knowing otherwise, you’d probably guess we were in World War III. Our military spending is now the highest it’s been at any point since World War II — and Congress keeps adding more. The House of Representatives just passed legislation that will take military spending to $895  More
The post Our Nearly One Trillion Dollar Military Budget Won’t Make Us Safer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsay Koshgarian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Abysmal Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327065</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/bidens-abysmal-debate-denial-aint-just-a-river-in-egypt/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even before this debate there were growing concerns about Joe Biden's age and cognitive capacities. Four years ago the public was concerned about Biden's age and that has only grown since he was president. Biden has held the fewest number of press conferences since Ronald Reagan was president, and his public appearances have mostly been canned and scripted. For many, he looks like their aging grandfather who has good and bad days, with many wondering that while we see Biden on his good days, what is he like on those days which are not so good? More
The post Biden’s Abysmal Debate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schultz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany in Decline: How Political Illusions Have Fostered the Extreme Right in Europe’s Powerhouse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326790</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/germany-in-decline-how-political-illusions-have-fostered-the-extreme-right-in-europes-powerhouse/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The elections for the European Parliament saw a shift to the far right across the EU member states. In Germany, the neo-fascist Alternative for Germans (AfD) party increased its share of the vote by almost a third to around 16%. How did it come to this? To understand the rise of the extreme right, it  More
The post Germany in Decline: How Political Illusions Have Fostered the Extreme Right in Europe’s Powerhouse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Goeßmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who You Gonna Believe, Biden Loyalists or Your Own Eyes and Ears?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327018</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/who-you-gonna-believe-biden-loyalists-or-your-own-eyes-and-ears/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost as appalling as President Biden’s debate performance are the efforts of his loyalists to pretend that what 50 million viewers saw and heard didn’t happen or didn’t really matter. What has unfolded in the last few days amounts to a political gaslighting operation by the Biden campaign and supportive pretenders who’ve been trying to  More
The post Who You Gonna Believe, Biden Loyalists or Your Own Eyes and Ears? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lies and Damned Lies About Venezuela’s Presidential Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326839</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/lies-and-damned-lies-about-venezuelas-presidential-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are continuous lies being said about Venezuela by media and politicians. As the next Venezuelan presidential elections draws near in late July there has been a plethora of unsubstantiated accusations of fraud, with nary any evidence.[1]  Steve Ellner, Professor Emeritus at the University of Oriente, Venezuela, comments on the media barrage against Venezuela: “True  More
The post Lies and Damned Lies About Venezuela’s Presidential Elections appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Paez Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get Bored!]]></title>
        <id>https://nikhil.bearblog.dev/get-bored/</id>
        <link href="https://nikhil.bearblog.dev/get-bored/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T05:21:57.176Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity gurus and hacks have killed the essence of getting bored. Do you think Da Vinci was obsessed with utilising every minute of the day? Do you think Tolstoy wrote with discipline? I am not suggesting you go ahead and waste your time, but if you are a creative person, productivity will only get you so far.
But what do I mean by getting bored? Getting bored implies your brain is free of pressing thoughts. There’s no sense of urgency in your mind. It could be for any reason. When there’s no sense of urgency in your mind, there’s calmness. People suffering from anxiety do not get bored; their thoughts and fears keep them occupied.
When your mind is free from pressing tasks, fear, and worries, it tends to get lost. It wanders. In these wanderings, you dwell upon the thoughts buried deep in the subconscious. Every writer would swear by the benefits of walking. When you go out to walk, your mind is tranquil. It is in sync with nature. That’s when your body digs deeper into the subconscious and helps you find the pearl.
Productivity hacks are excellent when you are focused on a singular task. They are excellent in improving your efficiency by inculcating discipline, like writing a book or a bunch of essays. That’s when you need productivity hacks to stay motivated and meet the deadline. The Pomodoro technique is good for helping you finish tasks. It does not invoke creativity, though.
When you want to create something, you need to get bored. You need to let your thoughts mingle with each other and discover a new perspective on the problem. Creation requires empty space and time. The more successful you are in creating this, the better your overall output will be. So, get bored.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping Up the Good Fight in India]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326978</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/02/keeping-up-the-good-fight-in-india/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T04:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping up the Good Fight: From the Emergency to the Present Day Purkayastha, Prabir New Delhi: LeftWord Books Is it possible to talk of Prabir Purkayastha’s life up to now, as outlined in this memoir, without reference to his two spells in jail, one during the Emergency declared by Prime Minister Indira Gandhi and the  More
The post Keeping Up the Good Fight in India appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nivedita Menon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teleportation: the superpower of choice of superheroes]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7933</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/teleportation-superpower-choice-superheroes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the choice, a regular person, like you or me, who decides they’d like to become a superhero, will choose teleportation as their superhero superpower. In preference to three other choices they could have made: mind-control, flight, or supernatural physical strength. This is the long-story-short conclusion of some recent research into the subject, by Julian […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JumpCrisscross in "Supreme Court rules ex-presidents have immunity for official acts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40850459</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40850459"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T20:46:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article III of the U.S. Constitution is incredibly brief [1].
I propose the Supreme Court be reconstituted such that for each case a panel of judges from the appellate courts is chosen by lot. They hear that case, write their opinion, and then go back to that work. New case, new lot.
Having a permanent bench of judicial oligarchs made sense before telecommunication. It doesn’t anymore. Every ancient democracy used randomness to control corruption. I think it’s time we took a lesson from them.
(Note: this could be done by statute. How the supreme Court is constituted is entirely left to Congress.)
[1] https://constitution.congress.gov/constitution/article-3/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JumpCrisscross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leotravis10 in "Supreme Court rules ex-presidents have immunity for official acts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848647</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848647"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T18:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Folks, the blueprint for a American dictatorship has been created and you'll be a fool and a idiot to think otherwise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leotravis10</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/happy-canada-day/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/happy-canada-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a relatively new arrival to these shores having landed here to visit, but not stay and then, on meeting my partner, I began to visit more often till it was decided. I would stay, stay and pursue first, permanent residency and then, citizenship.
Well, after living here, in Quebec, long enough to apply, and sponsored by my partner, I applied to be a permanent resident. A lot of money later after being vetted like I was about to work at Los Alamos in New Mexico, on some Top Secret weapons program or with Aliens, I was finally cleared as being a desirable alien and given residency. Which afforded me certain rights and privileges.
From this point I had to be a resident for at least 3 years before I could then apply to become a citizen. Again, this is not an easy path or a cheap venture let me tell you. And, without the support of a sponsor—in my case, my partner—near on impossible to do. The financial requirement alone, is prohibitive to so many. But, me and mine persisted and finally, in August 2018, I passed the last hurdle in a very long and meticulous process to achieve citizenship. I presented myself to the relevant authorities, made a declaration signed my paperwork and was told I was at that point, barring any further complications, a citizen of Canada.
The finishing touch to make it all wholly official came later when, online, with about 100+ other participants, I swore the oath of allegiance to Her Majesty the Queen, and sang O Canada in Canada's two official languages in front of a judge, online, with my fellow compatriots.
I was then officially a Canadian citizen. And I have never been more proud of myself, and my partner, at realising a dream.
And here I am, a few years later, on Canada Day, celebrating the fact I am a Canadian.
Happy Canada Day everyone! 🇨🇦
1/100]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by treeFall in "Supreme Court rules ex-presidents have immunity for official acts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848542</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848542"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T18:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>The President of the United States is the most powerful person in the country, and possibly the world. When he uses his official powers in any way, under the majority's reasoning, he now will be insulated from criminal prosecution. Orders the Navy's Seal Team 6 to assassinate a political rival? Immune.
I would consider this an extreme knee jerk take, but it's Sotomayor saying it.
https://x.com/mikedebonis/status/1807787300375445993]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>treeFall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lapcat in "Supreme Court rules ex-presidents have immunity for official acts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848414</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40848414"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T17:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Could Obama be prosecuted for ordering drone strikes that unintentionally killed two Americans? It seems like that world would hamstring the president far too much.
The President shouldn't have the legal authority to conduct any drone strikes without a declaration of war from Congress. We've been ignoring the Constitution for a very long time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lapcat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warzone Distro - Anti-Social Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-anti-social-anarchy?v=1719855971</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-anti-social-anarchy?v=1719855971"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T17:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Warzone Distro
Title: Anti-Social Anarchy
Subtitle: A Short Response to Ausonia Calabrese’s “Against Individualism”
Date: Mar 20, 2020
Source: anarchistnews.org

 Marxism shares one thing in common with other authoritarian ideologies: they are against the individual. Even when Marxists claim to be anarchists or “anti-state communists,” they make sure that masses and classes are always more important than actual people. This is as obvious in Tiqqun or Theory of Bloom as it is in Stalin’s “Anarchism” or “Socialism”, and now, in Ausonia Calabrese’s Against Individualism. The fact that someone identifying themselves as an anarchist or a Stirnite could ever claim to be against individualism is beyond me, but I digress. 
 The main gist of the essay is that individuals are not a real mate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been living inside my head too much]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/ive-been-living-inside-my-head-too-much/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/ive-been-living-inside-my-head-too-much/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T17:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since WeblogPoMo ended in May, I've been stuck in some sort of writing rut. I'm still posting a few times a week so it may not be as obvious, but I've noticed myself living inside my head too much lately. And I think I need to get myself out.
As I always do, I've been overthinking about what I write and create. Rarely are things perfect enough for me to post, so they just kind of hang out in my drafts, or just stay written inside my head. Because of that, my head is now full of these nonsensical words, and I need to find a way to get them out.
I've been considering starting 100 days to offload, and I keep giving myself reasons to delay. I've told myself I'd start it in August for my birthday month, or maybe in November of NaBloPoMo (National Blog Posting Month in November), but honestly why wait? There's no better day than today to start, right? (But also because it’s a brand new month.)
So I guess here's my official 1st day post. 100 posts in a year. Check back with me in 364 days. I'll let you know how I did (or you can follow along!).
I'll be tracking my post here, or in my #100daystooffload tag. Come along for the ride — I would love to have you around to (secretly or not so secretly) nudge me and keep me accountable.
Ready, set, go!
1/100
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AI21 Labs’ Jamba-Instruct in Amazon Bedrock, Amazon WorkSpaces Pools, and more (July 1, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>f2b2f1eca783c03eca935bbe7a8b88226b14d5e3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-ai21-labs-jamba-instruct-in-amazon-bedrock-amazon-workspaces-pools-and-more-july-1-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit New York is 10 days away, and I am very excited about the new announcements and more than 170 sessions. There will be A Night Out with AWS event after the summit for professionals from the media and entertainment, gaming, and sports industries who are existing Amazon Web Services (AWS) customers or have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the TIPS‑Treasury Valuation Puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30548</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/exploring-the-tips-treasury-valuation-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the late 1990s, the U.S. Treasury has issued debt in two main forms: nominal bonds, which provide fixed-cash scheduled payments, and Treasury Inflation Protected Securities—or TIPS—which provide the holder with inflation-protected payments that rise with U.S. inflation. At the heart of their relative valuation lie market participants’ expectations of future inflation, an object of interest for academics, policymakers, and investors alike. After briefly reviewing the theoretical and empirical links between TIPS and Treasury yields, this post, based on a recent research paper, explores whether market perceptions of U.S. sovereign credit risk can help explain the relative valuation of these financial instruments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guillaume Roussellet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities need more trees]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/cities-need-more-trees/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up just outside of Johannesburg, which is touted to be "the greenest city in the world". During the summer, when seen from above, it's a verdant, green landscape, with the tops of buildings popping through the canopy.

Yes, there's a full city beneath those trees.
However, this is not what the land originally looked like.
To cut a long story short, Johannesburg was established following the discovery of gold in 1886. It's known colloquially as eGoli, or "The City of Gold". Gold extraction here is vastly different to other parts of the world. We don't have gold veins running through the rock like in old Western movies. Instead it's mineralised into the rock itself which requires significant processing to extract.
This form of extraction leads to the crushing of millions of tons of ro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving A Country]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/leaving-a-country/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/leaving-a-country/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always tried to optimise for the right environments. I feel like that is the most powerful thing to do. You meet the right people. You generate ideas. You vibe. You get shit done. It's amazing.
The close environments of family, friends, and colleagues indeed have the most impact. So I never thought about the overarching environment I was part of, the city, the country. It is only over the past month I have been thinking about it.
It started with that famous hit-and-run case in Pune. Not the hit-and-run itself. But the coverup. The systemic failure. The corruption. The stories of this happening often and without any consequence all over the country, all the time.
Then it was the roof at the airport collapsing and killing a man. It is the traffic here in Bangalore. How no one cares about traffic rules. How the streets just fill up with water every time it rains. The power cuts. There is nothing new to all this. I grew up in India. It was all around me. I just ignored it.
I feel like I can't ignore it anymore. So the choice is to fix it or to leave. I have tried to fix things in my own way. It made me realise I live in a bubble and the majority of the country is much different from what I am. Or from where I want things to be. It needs a massive culture change.
To change it I will need to get political and dedicate my life. I am not willing to get into the shitshow that is politics nor want to dedicate my life to this. I want to do cool things in my life with cool people. And if I feel like the city or the country I live in blocks it. I will move.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The True Catastrophe of Our Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326974</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/the-true-catastrophe-of-our-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:39:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been writing about climate change for so many years now but, in truth, it was always something I read about and took in globally. It was happening out there, often in horrific ways, but not what I felt I was living through myself. (It’s true that, in past winters, Manhattan’s Central Park went 653 days without producing an inch of snow, almost double any previous record, but if you’re not a kid with a sled in the closet, that’s the sort of thing you don’t really feel.) More
The post The True Catastrophe of Our Times appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Debate: a Victory for Pathological Liars Everywhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326830</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/trumps-debate-a-victory-for-pathological-liars-everywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald J. Trump is a pathological liar and a political predator, and once he realized on the debate stage that neither President Joe Biden nor the feckless CNN moderators would  offer any challenges to his lies or falsities, he went for the kill.  Biden’s tired voice and overall pathetic performance undoubtedly earned him no support from fence sitters or independents, but it is unlikely that Trump’s braggadocio won him any new adherents. More
The post Trump’s Debate: a Victory for Pathological Liars Everywhere appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunted Biden: The First Presidential Debate Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326982</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/hunted-biden-the-first-presidential-debate-disaster/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was cruel.  Sinister cruel.  While Donald Trump was always going to relish the chance to be not only economical with the truth but simply inventive about it, Joe Biden, current Commander in Chief of the United States, leader of the self-described Free World, seemed a vanishing shadow, longing for soft slippers and the fireplace with cocoa, a case of comfort rather than the battling rage of politics. More
The post Hunted Biden: The First Presidential Debate Disaster appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Down With Dirty Dirt and ‘Waste in Place’ in Butte]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326987</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/down-with-dirty-dirt-and-waste-in-place-in-butte/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time to tip one to a rare victory in the never-ending battle to achieve an actual clean up, not a cover up, of Butte’s toxic mining wastes since it was listed as a Superfund site more than 40 years ago.   Thanks to the ferocious efforts of a very determined band of citizens who want their inalienable  More
The post Down With Dirty Dirt and ‘Waste in Place’ in Butte appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the Roots of Religion in Human Prehistory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326979</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/01/finding-the-roots-of-religion-in-human-prehistory/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A glance at recorded history shows us that humans have “always” felt a need to explain phenomena perceived to exist beyond our comprehension. Today, we turn to science to seek answers to our questions about the universe. But in the past, preliterate people developed spirituality to deal with their deepest metaphysical queries. But when exactly  More
The post Finding the Roots of Religion in Human Prehistory appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Barsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaming the Bear Blog Discovery Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://jbrr.dev/gaming-bear-blog-discovery-feed/</id>
        <link href="https://jbrr.dev/gaming-bear-blog-discovery-feed/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T05:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I decided to switch to Bear Blog about 7 months ago from a static site setup. It's been a good experience so far. Pre-Bear, I endlessly tweaked and updated the site, probably to avoid actually writing. Even more user friendly platforms like Wordpress and Ghost require a significant amount of operational work. The beauty of Bear Blog is the constraints. Taking away the option of migrating from Jekyll to Hugo to Astro on a whim, for example, has dramatically increased the amount of time I spend writing.
I also really liked the discover feed. It's much more difficult to attract readers and find new, interesting blogs than it was in the blogging heyday.
Recently though, the discover feed looks increasingly similar to the type of engagement farming you'd see on Twitter or Reddit. I find myself …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez - Up Against the Firewall]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alejandro-ruizesparza-freddy-martinez-up-against-the-firewall?v=1719807284"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T04:14:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alejandro Ruizesparza, Freddy Martinez
Title: Up Against the Firewall
Date: June 2024
Source: XRDS: Crossroads, The ACM Magazine for Students, Volume 30, Issue 4 Pages 26–30, DOI: 10.1145/3665595

In a revolt against techno-optimism and the real-world violence it upholds, members of radical research collective Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL) call for an empiricism rooted in technopolitical critique. Drawing from their own years of labor in the struggles against racial and surveillance capitalism, current work in HCI, and radical theorists like Alfredo M. Bonanano and Modibo Kadalie, LPL invites us to incorporate an ethics of rebellion and progress our tech practices into principled, anti-authoritarian praxis.
 Our organization, Lucy Parsons Labs (LPL), is a collective of researchers, journ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignatius - No Such Thing as Neutral]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-no-such-thing-as-neutral?v=1719787300</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-no-such-thing-as-neutral?v=1719787300"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T22:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignatius
Title: No Such Thing as Neutral
Subtitle: On the Tools We Use
Date: June 2023
Source: Retrieved on 30 June 2024 from ia800301.us.archive.org/4/items/zines-anarchism/Fist_Full_of_Concrete-screen.pdf

While I had already conceptualized and begun writing this piece prior to the publication of “An Anarchist Anti-Gun Manifesto,” the final form of “No Such Thing as Neutral” has been largely influenced by the response to the former. In particular, I was inspired by the common response of guns being “a tool” and “therefore neutral,” of the assumption that my critique of guns, and their world of relations, was of a moral character, and as such the concept of “neutrality” would hold some rhetorical weight. This piece is an attempt to break out of the confinement of moral frameworks …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Honeyeater, the new novel by Australian author Jessie Tu]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7927</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-honeyeater-new-novel-australian-author-jessie-tu/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Honeyeater is the second novel by Sydney based Australian writer Jessie Tu, and will be in bookshops on Tuesday 2 July 2024. That’s tomorrow. I read Tu’s 2020 debut A Lonely Girl is a Dangerous Thing almost four years ago. It was the story of a once child prodigy musician, who wasn’t always successfully […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eschaton in "Writing GUI apps for Windows is painful"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839937</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839937"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T20:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If instead of insisting on custom UI styling the author just used the system UI, they could probably build a pretty straightforward Windows application. It’s the scourge of “brand identity” that has people thinking graphical applications are hard.
Same on the Mac: If you want to build a Mac application, your best bet will be AppKit or SwiftUI and using system controls. And when the OS updates your application will either update with it, or need only minor tweaks and a rebuild to look good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eschaton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by userbinator in "Writing GUI apps for Windows is painful"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839926</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839926"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T20:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Problem: It is extremely hard to stylize native Win32 controls.
That's not a problem, it's a feature. I am absolutely bloody sick of apps that go out of their way to reinvent the standard UI controls in perplexing ways and behave unexpectedly. Following the system UI preferences is what you should do, and it irritates your users if you don't.
There is a “hidden” dark mode for Win32 controls used by Windows File Explorer that you can activate, but it covers only some of the controls and still doesn’t look good.
Don't do that. If you use the regular Win32 controls then they will automatically get the styling the user has set.
I've been writing Win32 apps for close to 30 years now. It's sad to see the regression in UIs over the years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>userbinator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aurornis in "Writing GUI apps for Windows is painful"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839536</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839536"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T19:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a good overview of some of the options, but the author’s specific requirements push it in a specific direction that eliminates a lot of options.
Specifically, the requirement for completely custom GUI styling without writing his own render functions means it’s really a task of selecting easy, customizable GUI libraries rather than generic GUI work.
The requirements to be self-contained executables and under a 40MB limit also rule out a lot of options. The author admits that Qt could have met these requirements but the open-source licensing part wasn’t compatible with his goals and he didn’t want to pay for a license.
If you relax the requirements to tolerate some dependencies, allow larger download sizes, or to simply use built-in Windows GUI controls the situation is very different.
For writing a lightweight, completely custom GUI with no external dependencies and permissive licensing I could have guessed ImGui would be the answer before I started reading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurornis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whazor in "Butterflies flew 2,600 miles across the Atlantic without stopping"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839364</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839364"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T19:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I certainly hope the butterfly has more energy after eating through one apple, two pears, three plums, four strawberries, five oranges, a chocolate cake, an ice-cream, a pickle, a cheese, a salami, a lollipop, a cherry pie, a sausage, a cupcake, a watermelon, and finally a green leaf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whazor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snakeyjake in "Pattern of brain damage is pervasive in Navy SEALs who died by suicide"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839297</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40839297"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T19:03:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was an infantryman in the Army for ten years, from 1998 to 2008, and deployed three times, twice to Iraq,
Encounters with IEDs were common, especially during the surge.
So many of my friends have died to suicide or have killed themselves due to drugs and/or alcohol that it is hard to keep track.
Now that primadonna seals are dying maybe someone will pay attention.
Thankfully the only lasting effects of my deployments seem to be a bad back and distaste for authority.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snakeyjake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indymedia - Interview with Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/indymedia-interview-with-pedro-bautista-rojas-of-cipo-rfm?v=1719773220</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/indymedia-interview-with-pedro-bautista-rojas-of-cipo-rfm?v=1719773220"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Indymedia
Title: Interview with Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM
Subtitle: Cipo-RFM activist Pedro Bautista-Rojas explains the history of the indigenous struggle in Oaxaca and also the implications of the forest dispute for both the people of San Isidro Aloapam and their children.
Date: December 4th, 2008
Notes: Translated by Bea Lopez.
Source: Retrieved on June 30 2024 from https://www.indymedia.org.uk/en/2008/04/396318.html


Pedro Bautista Rojas of CIPO-RFM.

He explains the consequences of deforestation for the village of San Isidro.

For its people...

...and their children.
 Q.- What’s your name and position? 
 A.- My name’s Pedro Bautista Rojas, member of the organising committee of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca. 
 Q.- First, what’s thehistory of this struggle and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - A Letter of Resistance from the Magónista Women’s Commission of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-letter-of-resistance-from-the-magonista-women-s-commission-of-the-popular-indigenou?v=1719772685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-letter-of-resistance-from-the-magonista-women-s-commission-of-the-popular-indigenou?v=1719772685"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: A Letter of Resistance from the Magónista Women’s Commission of the Popular Indigenous Council of Oaxaca
Subtitle: A report from Magónistas on the impact of COVID-19 in Mexico.
Date: May 13 2020
Source: Retrieved on June 30th 2024 from https://itsgoingdown.org/a-letter-of-resistance-ricardo-flores-magon-cipo-rfm/

 We must bear in mind that no government, honest as it is, can decree the abolition of misery. It is the people themselves, the hungry, the disinherited, who have to abolish misery. – Ricardo Flores Magón (Regeneration, Nov. 19, 1910) 
 Once again, the indigenous peoples are forgotten in the oblivion; There is not a single security measure by governments to protect us, and the indigenous women are triple violated. 
 Both before COVID-19 and now, our battl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Becker - CIPO: Oaxaca and Chiapas]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-becker-cipo-oaxaca-and-chiapas?v=1719771759</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mark-becker-cipo-oaxaca-and-chiapas?v=1719771759"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mark Becker
Title: CIPO: Oaxaca and Chiapas
Date: July 9, 2007
Source: Retrieved on June 30 2024 from https://www.yachana.org/reports/mex07/2007/07/cipo-rfm.html

 This afternoon we met with Dolores Villalobo from the Consejo Indígena Popular de Oaxaca “Ricardo Flores Magón” (CIPO-RFM). She began the discussion with an explanation of who was Ricardo Flores Magón–an Indigenous person from Oaxaca who rose up against Porfirio Diáz in the Mexican Revolution. He was persecuted so fled into exile into the United States, but was imprisoned at Levenworth where he was executed. Franciso Madero offered him the vice presidency, but Flores Magón said he preferred jail to his government that was not of the people and who did not represent the change for which they had fought. Dolores said that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janice1999 in "Canada 'sleepwalking' into cashless society, consumer advocates warn"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40838754</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40838754"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T17:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments really need to break the Visa and Mastercard Duopoly.
Not mentioned in this article, but certainly related, was the Canadian governments unprecedented step to freeze hundreds of bank accounts of protestors during COVID protests using their Emergencies Act. While I couldn't be more politically removed from the protestors, using a legislative power envisioned for war like conditions to personally ruin protestors financially is more than worrying.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emergencies_Act]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janice1999</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am asking y'all for help: write me emails.]]></title>
        <id>https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/i-am-asking-yall-for-help-write-me-emails/</id>
        <link href="https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/i-am-asking-yall-for-help-write-me-emails/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, here goes.
Being in a long distance relationship is hard. It is especially hard when I live alone, well, sort of. I don’t talk much with my mom. Maybe I should, but I don’t intend to talk to her for the moment. That means, despite living with her under the same roof, I feel very lonely. And my mental health starts to deteriorate when I am alone and bored.
Thoughts could drive someone crazy when that is all they have being the single person in the room.
I am turning to y’all for support, so please write me emails at corneliuswastaken@proton.me. I would love anything. Book /music/video games recommendations, memes, photos of your pet, tell me about yourself. Heck, send me a string of random letters and numbers if you want. It is just nice to know that there is someone out there listening to my rambling, and that I am not alone. Expect the reply to happen in a while though. Replying to messages becomes a chore when self-care is in dire need.
Thank you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elias Manzanera - The Iron Column]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-manzanera-the-iron-column?v=1719756506</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-manzanera-the-iron-column?v=1719756506"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T14:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Elias Manzanera
Title: The Iron Column
Subtitle: Testament of A Revolutionary
Date: 2006
Source: Booklet from the Kate Sharpley Library - https://www.katesharpleylibrary.net/w6mb2w

What is Anarchism?
 Anarchism is a political theory which opposes the State and capitalism. It says that people with economic power (capitalists) and those with political power (politicians of all stripes left, right or centre) use that power for their own benefit, and not (like they claim) for the benefit of society. Anarchism says that neither exploitation nor government is natural or necessary, and that a society based on freedom, mutual aid and equal shares of the good things in life would work better than this one. 
 Anarchism is also a political movement. Anarchists take part in day-to-day struggl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sean Swain - The FBI Can Go Fuck Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-fbi-can-go-fuck-itself?v=1719751091</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-fbi-can-go-fuck-itself?v=1719751091"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T12:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sean Swain
Title: The FBI Can Go Fuck Itself
Subtitle: A History of the State Terror Organization and An Analysis of Its Political Repression of Me, Based on Its Own Declassified Documents
Date: 11/09/2022
Notes: Prepared For: The Labadie Collection, University of Michigan To Accompany the 223 Disclosed Pages of My FBI File For Posting, Dissemination, and Publication
Source: Retrieved on 5/30/2024 from: <seanswain.noblogs.org/2022/11/the-fbi-can-go-fk-itself>

INTRODUCTION.
 I have been through a lot. For more than a decade now, the Federal Bureau of Investigation has waged a state terror program designed to drive down me to suicide in order to permanently silence me and, in the process, amassed over four thousand pages of files on me, less than three hundred pages of which they ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Bloom and Russell Maroon Shoatz - Dragon and Hydra Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steve-bloom-and-russell-maroon-shoatz-dragon-and-hydra-revisited?v=1719750440</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steve-bloom-and-russell-maroon-shoatz-dragon-and-hydra-revisited?v=1719750440"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T12:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Steve Bloom and Russell Maroon Shoatz
Title: Dragon and Hydra Revisited
Subtitle: A Dialogue
Date: 2016
Source: <www.oldandnewproject.net/Essays/Maroon_D%20and%20H%20Revisited.html>

Special introductory note by the editors
 In the “Policies of this Website” we explain that we are seeking to promote discussions “where participants are engaged in active listening and a search for commonalities or convergences—giving at least as much emphasis to this as we do to ‘clarifying differences.’ The overall goal of our project is not just to recapitulate well-established views but to transcend them if/when we can in order to create a stronger collective synthesis of revolutionary thought.” 
 We believe that the exchange below is an excellent case study in this process and how it can work eff…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrewism - How Anarchy Works]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrewism-how-anarchy-works?v=1719739207</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrewism-how-anarchy-works?v=1719739207"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Andrewism
Title: How Anarchy Works
Subtitle: A Guide To Organising Anarchy
Date: 1 May 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2 May 2024 from https://youtu.be/lrTzjaXskUU

Introduction
 What if we didn’t need bosses, politicians, borders, landlords, police, or prisons? 
 There was a time when each of these things did not exist, and whatever you may believe now about their absolute necessity, have you considered that there can be a time again when we can do much better without them? 
 Anarchists dare to desire a world without rule. 
 Neither the rule of the minority nor the rule of the majority. Neither the rule of the capitalists nor the rule of the bureaucrats. Neither the rule of men nor the rule of royalty nor the rule of the elderly nor the rule of warlords. An-archy. Without rule. 
 The wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pikante - Opposing the massacre in Gaza!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pikante-opposing-the-massacre-in-gaza-an-anarchist-perspective?v=1719738560</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pikante-opposing-the-massacre-in-gaza-an-anarchist-perspective?v=1719738560"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pikante
Title: Opposing the massacre in Gaza!
Subtitle: An anarchist perspective
Date: April 2024
Notes: This is a translation of a text that had been published in the paper “Pikante”, in Toulouse (fRance), in the beginning of April 2024. Contact : pikante(a)riseup.net
Source: Original in French: <mars-infos.org/s-opposer-au-massacre-a-gaza-un-7502>

 To write from here an article about this situation is something that will inevitably be limited, but the silence appears worst to us. We feel the need to write about what is going on, in order to take the emotions out. Also, to try to take ourself out of the media and state propaganda. Even if words won’t ever be enough against this incredibly unfair violence that is falling on an entire population. More than 2 millions of people, gui…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henri Sulku - The Budapest Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascis?v=1719738079</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascis?v=1719738079"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T09:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Henri Sulku
Title: The Budapest Trial
Subtitle: How Hungary Exploits a Dubious EU Mechanism to Chase Anti-Fascists Across the Continent
Date: 22.05.2024
Source: Retrieved on 28.5.2024 from https://turningpointmag.org/2024/05/22/the-budapest-trial-how-hungary-exploits-a-dubious-eu-mechanism-to-chase-anti-fascists-across-the-continent/

 On March 28, 2024, the streets surrounding Milan’s main courthouse, the Palace of Justice, are swarmed with different branches of Italian law enforcement. The municipal police have brought one patrol car, casually parked next to a newspaper kiosk. State police and military police (the Carabinieri) can be seen on the side streets, sporting riot gear in their trademark armored vans, light and dark blue respectively. The scenery does not yet make a stri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metrius - The Simian Redemption]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/metrius-the-simian-redemption?v=1719737957</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/metrius-the-simian-redemption?v=1719737957"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Metrius
Title: The Simian Redemption
Subtitle: Bridging the divide between humanity and nature
Date: April 2, 2014

The simian redemption
 “You don’t know nothing, but you don’t need to know. The wisdom’s in the trees, not the glass windows”. – Jack Johnson[1]
 A lot of theories have surfaced in the relatively new millennium concerning the human species’ relationship to the planet it calls home. Historically, the mechanized view on nature advocated in the 17th century Scientific Revolution is criticized by ecological movements as alienating humanity from its origins. With the advent of the clock for example, man started measuring time according to its own inventions, exempting the sun of this function. Likewise, the clock became a metaphor for the machinery of nature, and “God” bec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur and Barbara Gelb - O’Neill]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-and-barbara-gelb-o-neill?v=1719737733</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-and-barbara-gelb-o-neill?v=1719737733"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arthur and Barbara Gelb
Title: O’Neill
Date: 1960
Notes: The photo gallery broke up paragraphs in 3 places in the source book, so it has been moved to the back matter here.
Source: <archive.org/details/oneill0000gelb_u1k6>

Acknowledgments
 A great many persons, libraries, institutions, organizations and publications have given their help and cooperation in the preparation of this book. We will never be able to thank all of them adequately, and can only try to outline the extent of their assistance and indicate the measure of our gratitude. 
 We acknowledge, first, our debt to Carlotta Monterey O’Neill. With the understanding that we were to have the freedom of complete objectivity, she graciously allowed herself to be interviewed on many occasions, put documents and photographs at…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen - From Revolution to Destitution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikkel-bolt-rasmussen-from-revolution-to-destitution?v=1719737327</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikkel-bolt-rasmussen-from-revolution-to-destitution?v=1719737327"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen
Title: From Revolution to Destitution
Date: May 29th, 2024
Source: https://illwill.com/from-revolution-to-destitution

 What happened to the notion of revolution? In his companion piece to “The Movement of Refusal,” Mikkel Bolt Rasmussen retraces the rise and fall of revolutionary theory from its earliest systematic expression during the First International to the first proletarian offensive of 1917–1921, and onwards to the crisis at the hands of a bourgeois “anti-fascism” that instrumentalized the specter of fascism as a means to save capitalism, before ditching it, after 1945, in order to integrate the laboring class into the nation state. Although the post-war welfare state was the great achievement of the workers’ movement, the price paid for it was the ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brynn Emond - Scenes from the pro-Palestine encampment at OttawaU]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brynn-emond-scenes-from-the-pro-palestine-encampment-at-ottawau?v=1719737130</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brynn-emond-scenes-from-the-pro-palestine-encampment-at-ottawau?v=1719737130"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Brynn Emond
Title: Scenes from the pro-Palestine encampment at OttawaU
Source: https://mutualrage.wordpress.com/2024/05/03/what-the-student-pro-palestine-encampments-are-actually-like/

 The other day my friend and I decided we wanted to visit the student-led pro-Palestine encampment that has recently sprung up on the lawn of OttawaU. On one of the organizing group’s social media pages, they had recently sent out a message informing people they were accepting donations, specifically of certain types of things (like hot water, garbage bags, blue tarps, yoga mats, etc.). I felt driven by the urge to donate whatever I could – so, during my shift, I furtively searched the back storeroom, digging through years’ worth of defunct paper cups, lids, and out-of-season teas. There was enough …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowers & Lawler - Anarchism as a Methodological Foundation in Mathematics Education]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bowers-lawler-anarchism-as-a-methodological-foundation-in-mathematics-education?v=1719737002</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bowers-lawler-anarchism-as-a-methodological-foundation-in-mathematics-education?v=1719737002"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Bowers & Lawler
Title: Anarchism as a Methodological Foundation in Mathematics Education
Subtitle: A Portrait of Resistance
Date: 2021/2022
Source: https://www.exeter.ac.uk/research/groups/education/pmej/pome39/index.html

 
 
A large swath of research in mathematics education claims to serve an equity agenda. However, too often this research is conducted atheoretically, failing to disrupt the worldviews that produce injustice and oppression, for both the researcher and the reader. Responding to this commonplace divergence of intent and impact, we propose a methodological approach that anchors research and praxis in a sociopolitical foundation of anarchism. We seek cohesion of theory and practice by consciously demanding that values common to the equity agenda—cooperation, mutual a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angie Barbosa - Marginal Ontologies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies-1?v=1719736373</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marginal-ontologies-1?v=1719736373"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Angie Barbosa
Title: Marginal Ontologies
Subtitle: Challenges of a Transfeminist Anarchism
Date: 08.03.2023
Notes: Translation: Cello L. Pfeil
Source: Original translation of “Ontologias Marginais: Desafios de um Anarquismo Transfeminista”. Retrieved on 04.28.2024 from https://revistatapuia.com.br/ojs/index.php/revista/article/view/29/19

Abstract[1] [2]
 In this text, written as a speech for the 1st Anarchist Fair in Rio de Janeiro, contradictions of the historically predatory relationship of brazilian democracy with brazilian travestis and transsexuals are presented, paying attention to the ontological marginality of the travesti body under the capitalist patriarchy of white supremacy. Based on this reflection, transfeminist challenges to radical and anarchist politics are presen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Creaghe - “No Rent” in Sheffield]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-no-rent-in-sheffield?v=1719736177</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-no-rent-in-sheffield?v=1719736177"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Creaghe
Title: “No Rent” in Sheffield
Date: July 1891
Source: Retrieved on 6 June 2024 from https://www.marxists.org/history/international/social-democracy/commonweal/1891/index.htm

We refer elsewhere to Comrade Creaghe’s plucky assault upon the landlord robbers. As some of our readers may like to know what he has to say for himself, we quote the following from the first issue of our bright little contemporary, the Sheffield Anarchist, to which we wish all success.
 Comrades, 
 As I find we are now boycotted by the Sheffield Telegraph, which, no doubt, while it silences us, will continue, with its usual sense of fair play, to attack us in its columns, I write to you for the satisfaction of the only public we respect, namely, the workers. 
 I have been held up to the reprobati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Azoulay - We need a plethora of tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/matthew-azoulay-we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics?v=1719735889</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/matthew-azoulay-we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics?v=1719735889"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T08:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Azoulay
Title: We need a plethora of tactics
Subtitle: Considering “metacrisis” and the ever greater need to re-embrace Bookchin’s social ecology.
Date: Mar 10th
Notes: This article first appeared in the Winter 2023-4 issue of Freedom Anarchist Journal
Source: Retrieved on 2024-06-30 from <freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/10/we-need-a-plethora-of-tactics>

 ‘Metacrisis’ is my chosen umbrella term for the escalation of multiple global crises of climate, ecology, and political economy, which have reached such a point now that all radical organising is a form of crisis response. And I know for folk on the sacrificial frontlines of capitalism, the terms ‘radical organising’ and ‘crisis response’ belie that they have to fight just to survive. The metacrisis is hidden from many of us a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: good morning!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52804</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/30/sunday-photoblogging-good-morning/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:57:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to go looking for photos, but this is what greeted me when I got up to make the coffee the other morning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: Macron's gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-Macron-s-gamble</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-Macron-s-gamble"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T05:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France votes over two rounds on June 30 and July 7 in a snap [parliamentary election->https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/frances-snap-election-how-does-it-work-whats-next-2024-06-18 called by President Macron after his party suffered a heavy defeat in the June EU Assembly elections. France has two rounds of voting: if a candidate gets 50% of more in the first round, he or she is elected. If not, then in the second round, the top two candidates fight it out. A survey released by pollster (...)
English

/ 
France, 
Crisis, 
Recession]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To All the Cameras I've Loved Before]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-all-the-cameras-ive-loved-before/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-all-the-cameras-ive-loved-before/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T02:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is apparently National Camera Day. I have no idea who comes up with these seemingly random National holidays, but I’m here for it.
And so today got me thinking of some of the digital cameras I’ve owned in the past. I’ve owned quite a few that I regrettably no longer own, or have forgotten so we’ll start the with the ones I do remember.
A handful of Canon Coolpix: loved these things, and I feel like they’re making a comeback. I think I owned 2-3 of these in the early days. At one point, my university gave me one to document my “life as a student” as a part of their marketing campaign.
Nikon D40: my very first DSLR. I remember working endless amounts of hours at Staples over the summer to save up enough money to buy this on my own. This was around when it first came out, and was roughl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[George Barrett - The Last War]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/george-barrett-the-last-war?v=1719711090</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/george-barrett-the-last-war?v=1719711090"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T01:31:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: George Barrett
Title: The Last War
Date: 1915
Source: Our Masters Are Helpless (ISBN 978-1-904491-32-3) pp. 31-50

 The great European war has come. The truth has almost staggered our imagination, we do not know what to do and the one only definite thought is that we must win. To this end all our efforts are bent. We fight, with the men and women of France, of Russia, of Belgium. It is exactly the same, alas! with the men and women of Germany and Austria. We are all prompted by the same strong feelings of patriotism. We and they rejoice to give our lives that our country may be victorious, and more than all do we each rejoice if we may take the life of another. 
 Such is war. It is strange, is it not? Almost to a man we, in the countries concerned, have thrown aside what belief we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 999900000999 in "A bunch of programming advice I'd give to myself 15 years ago"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40832107</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40832107"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T17:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'll add one point. You are not your job. Don't take things personally at work. And never be afraid to leave if you're not fitting in with your company .
I've left jobs over a few reasons, primarily bad managers, increased compensation, and bad code .
If people are writing bad code at your company, to the point where you know it's going to come back to haunt you later, it's okay to just walk away .
Don't embarrass anybody, don't escalate to a manager and explain how horrible the code is. I was in a situation where someone our team was effectively writing code that pretended to do things it really didn't. I got into a really nasty argument with half my team about this. I ended up putting in my two weeks, and then my manager was like oh you were right the entire time .
Life is too short to deal with incompetent people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>999900000999</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patterns for TargetGroupBinding with AWS Load Balancer Controller]]></title>
        <id>d710f7ae96ae535d56b495119bc31892821121ef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/patterns-for-targetgroupbinding-with-aws-load-balancer-controller/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T16:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although provisioning load balancers directly from clusters has been the Kubernetes native method for exposing services, in some cases this creates a provisioning process that doesn’t align with the architecture of the applications. Therefore, there’s a need to have another mechanism for it. For those use-cases, which we describe in this post, provides the functionality […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tsahi Duek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Azoulay of Epic Tomorrows - A plethora of tactics does not preclude a strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strategic-literacy-metacrisis-matthew-azoulay-of-epic-tomorrows-a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not?v=1719663129</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strategic-literacy-metacrisis-matthew-azoulay-of-epic-tomorrows-a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not?v=1719663129"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Matthew Azoulay of Epic Tomorrows
Title: A plethora of tactics does not preclude a strategy
Subtitle: A call for strategic literacy in the Metacrisis
Date: May 10th 2024
Source: Retrieved on 21/06/24 from https://epictomorrows.com/2024/05/10/a-plethora-of-tactics-does-not-preclude-a-strategy-a-call-for-strategic-literacy-in-the-metacrisis/

Introduction
 For the winter 23–24 issue of the paper version of the Freedom journal (UK) I wrote a piece titled 'Social Ecology vs The Metacrisis.' On the 10th of March 2024 it was republished online by Freedom as 'We Need A Plethora of Tactics' with the subtitle: 'Considering “metacrisis” and the ever greater need to re-embrace Bookchin’s social ecology.' AnarchyNouveau then wrote a response piece titled 'We don`t need a plethora of tactics: w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaku Shin Gi - Buddhist Anarchism in the Dharma-Ending Age]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age?v=1719662749</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age?v=1719662749"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Shaku Shin Gi
Title: Buddhist Anarchism in the Dharma-Ending Age
Subtitle: Commentary on the Cakkavatti-Sihanada Sutta
Date: 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2024 from https://contra.net.br/buddhist-anarchism-in-the-dharma-ending-age/

1. Introduction
 Mahayana Buddhism divides human history into three ages: the Age of the Right Dharma (shōbō), which occurred in the first 500 years after the birth of Buddha Shakyamuni, where enlightenment was fully possible and the Buddha’s teachings were maintained; the Era of Semblance Dharma (zōhō), the 500 years following the shōbō era, where the Buddhist teachings and practice still existed but were deteriorated and lacked confirmed enlightenment; and finally, the Dharma-Ending Age (mappō), in which gradually all teachings bequeathed by the Buddha wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Consensus]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-consensus?v=1719662606</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-consensus?v=1719662606"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Consensus
Subtitle: A New Handbook for Grassroots Social, Political and Environmental Groups
Date: 2006

Introduction
 Making the shift to the consensus decision-making process might be the most important thing that we can do to build a democratic society. Consensus can give us the power we need to focus our society’s attention on improving education, making peace, providing universal healthcare and creating the world we desire. 
 Consensus creates true democracy—not the democracy in name only that sickens any aware person. Consensus empowers all who participate in it. In-name-only democracy disempowers all who participate in it (who dutifully trudge to the polls every few years to select new masters). True democracy might be a large part of the solution to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tiro - Relationship Anarchy and its Discontents]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/relationship-anarchy-and-its-discontents?v=1719662543</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/relationship-anarchy-and-its-discontents?v=1719662543"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T12:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: tiro
Title: Relationship Anarchy and its Discontents
Date: 2/10/2020
Notes: originally written by tiro on his personal blog (now deactivated). republished on queertopia's webpage and also as a print copy from 2022.
Source: Retrieved via the Wayback Machine on 6/23/24 from https://web.archive.org/web/20200218151651/https://kalasutra.wordpress.com/

 Once considered the cool, edgy version of polyamory, a sort of polyam++, relationship anarchy is increasingly coming under scrutiny because it is being used to justify a specific kind of harmful behavior in relationships. 
 This behavior is probably best described in blunt terms: (mostly) cis guys are fucking around with (mostly) femmes, and disconnecting from them the moment there’s any mention of romantic feelings, hopes for a more ent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federico Ferretti - For an Anarchist Decolonial Agenda]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/federico-ferretti-for-an-anarchist-decolonial-agenda?v=1719661124</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/federico-ferretti-for-an-anarchist-decolonial-agenda?v=1719661124"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T11:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Federico Ferretti
Title: For an Anarchist Decolonial Agenda
Subtitle: New Perspectives on Anarchism, Marronage, and Indigeneity from Brazil/Pindorama
Date: 18 June 2024
Source: DOI: 10.1111/anti.13068

Abstract
 This paper proposes new perspectives on anarchism, indigeneity, and Afro-descendent struggles, by discussing the case of Brazilian anarchists’ commitment to luta afroindígena. They mean by this term the intersection of indigenous and Afro-descendant resistances for the recognition of land, against the violence of states, agribusiness, and extractivism. I argue that this case offers key insights to radical geographies, and to the broader field of decolonial scholarship, to challenge cultural and racial essentialisms by connecting different militant traditions. I also argue t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[june notes]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/june-notes/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/june-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am writing this sprawled on bed, laptop on my lap, listening to Stray Kids's Ex. Next to me is Murakami's Wind-up Bird Chronicles, which I recently started. On the table next to my bed, I have my journal open, where I was reflecting on my June. I am drinking a hot cup of Americano and having dark chocolate - my favorite. I spontaneously thought of sharing some notes from June with you.
I think of June as the month where I decided to take my life more seriously. Not to say I was ever a careless, unserious person. I always worked hard, but it was more like if you aim to stay alive for the long run, you need to get it together.
Thinking about it though, June was the first month I felt proud of myself since a long time. During the start of the month, I set a long list of goals for myself: ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kstenerud in "I'm terrified of old people"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40828705</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40828705"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T08:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every 10 years or so I'll look back on my life and cringe at all the stupid stuff I said and believed over the past 10 years and how I naively thought that I knew everything. And then I'd breathe a sigh of relief now that I finally do know everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kstenerud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tw04 in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40827429</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40827429"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T02:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>Fundamentally there’s nothing wrong with the position of supreme court to push the responsibility of lawmaking back on congress.
It would literally be impossible for congress to make a law covering every single nuance agencies are tasked with. This Supreme Court knows it. This is nothing more than deregulation on a scale not seen in modern American history.  When you can’t find clean drinking water in 30 years, this will be why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tw04</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ericsink in "The story, as best I can remember, of the origin of Mosaic and Netscape [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40826214</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40826214"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T22:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on my understanding, some of the details he gave about the Spyglass/Microsoft situation are not quite right, but I don't think it would appropriate for me to provide specific corrections.
However, since I was the Project Lead for the Spyglass browser team, there is one correction I can offer:  We licensed the Mosaic code, but we never used any of it.  Spyglass Mosaic was written from scratch.
In big picture terms, Marc's recollections look essentially correct, and he even shared a couple of credible-looking tidbits that I didn't know.
It was a crazy time.  Netscape beat us, but I remember my boss observing that we beat everyone who didn't outspend us by a favor of five.  I didn't get mega-rich or mega-famous like Marc (deservedly) did, but I learned a lot, and I remain thankful to have been involved in the story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ericsink</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vundercind in "It's getting harder to die"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825584</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825584"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T21:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently watched someone close die over a couple days, after a long decline.
The last 24 hours were monstrous to inflict on anyone. Torture. Evil.
Hours and hours of faltering breathing, often restarting with what was plainly a panicked adrenaline-pumping response. It looked like they felt like they were about to drown every few minutes, hour, after hour, no relief. No IV fluids (terminal anyway, so no trying to keep them alive with techniques like that) and unable to drink, so certainly terribly thirsty the whole time. Unable to communicate or really engage with surroundings, and quite high on pain meds anyway (the closest thing to a mercy in all this). It’s fucked up that that’s a fairly normal way for dying people to make their exit. I’m sure there are all kinds of problems with trying to provide a way out when someone can’t make the choice for themselves, without opening it up to abuse, but damn, I hope this isn’t the best we can do because it’s terrible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vundercind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VincentEvans in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825091</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40825091"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T20:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congress can actually legislate the right of agencies to interpret the gaps in the laws back into effect - by passing a law that explicitly gives agencies this power.
Just like congress can legislate abortion laws rather than leaving it to judicial precedence.
Fundamentally there’s nothing wrong with the position of supreme court to push the responsibility of lawmaking back on congress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VincentEvans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mosh pit rules applied to social media]]></title>
        <id>https://pcalv.es/mosh-pit-rules-applied-to-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://pcalv.es/mosh-pit-rules-applied-to-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T20:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t jump straight in. Observe and see how people are moving before you get involved.
Look out for each other. If someone falls over, help them get up. You are there to have fun together.
Start at the sides and work your way in for a more intense experience. Stay on the outside until you get your bearings. Then, when you’re ready, venture further into the center to get really wild.
Never try and intentionally hurt someone. If you get hit by accident or intentionally do not retaliate.
Treat everyone with respect and stay safe!
⁂
✍️ Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lanstin in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40824075</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40824075"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T19:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AOL's server code was excellent. It was written by some people that had done similar things for BITNET and had a deep understanding of Unix programming and how to use event loops for scalability.
It was in C, but the process was expected to run for months without crashing or running out of memory; if it had an abnormal exit, you'd (the owner as set in some code thing) get an email with the core backtrace. If it had a memory leak, ops would be on you quickly. Ops was considered a primary driver of requirements to dev, and absolutely everything could be reloaded into a running server without restarting it. There was a TCP control port where a TCL interpreter inside the service was exposed and generally you wrote the (very simple, CS 101 style) TCL commands to manage the server.  It was a "No…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lanstin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823777</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823777"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T18:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One that was written from scratch, by me. All others are terrible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pradn in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823142</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40823142"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T17:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's monorepo, and it's not even close - primarily for the tooling:
* Creating a mutable snapshot of the entire codebase takes a second or two.
* Builds are perfectly reproducible, and happen on build clusters. Entire C++ servers with hundreds of thousands of lines of code can be built from scratch in a minute or two tops.
* The build config language is really simple and concise.
* Code search across the entire codebase is instant.
* File history loads in an instant.
* Line-by-line blame loads in a few seconds.
* Nearly all files in supported languages have instant symbol lookup.
* There's a consistent style enforced by a shared culture, auto-linters, and presubmits.
* Shortcuts for deep-linking to a file/version/line make sharing code easy-peasy.
* A ton of presubmit checks ensure uniform code/test quality.
* Code reviews are required, and so is pairing tests with code changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pradn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Milind Naphade, Capital One’s SVP of AI Foundations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/86df019ebf76</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/meet-milind-naphade-capital-ones-svp-of-ai-foundations-86df019ebf76?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T17:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Milind Naphade, Ph.D., about his tech background, vision for AI in finance and approaches shaping our AI future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rswail in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821356</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821356"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T15:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm impressed that they can so easily dispose of 40 years of law making by Congress that assumed that agencies would interpret the statutes and make rules for regulating their area of authority.
Now Congress is going to have to specify every possible consequence of laws in the statutes, otherwise a judge will decide.
So agencies will not have any power to actually regulate.
Awesome logic work, but terrible legal thinking without considering the side effects of the decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rswail</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by brettcvz in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821274</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821274"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems like the judicial branch just voted to give itself substantially more power.
Are there any checks against this? Or can justices just keep granting themselves more powers and invalidating any restraints?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>brettcvz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the first 2024 US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic and security trends]]></title>
        <id>667eb7fea4598c000bd70735</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-first-2024-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic-and-security-trends"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Biden and Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns, email trends, and heightened cybersecurity concerns across digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by consumer451 in "Supreme Court overturns 40-year-old "Chevron deference" doctrine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821187</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40821187"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From Justice Kagan's dissent on page 82:
> This Court has long understood Chevron deference to reflect what Congress would want, and so to be rooted in a presumption of legislative intent. Congress knows that it does not—in fact cannot—write perfectly complete regulatory statutes...
> It knows that those statutes will inevitably contain ambiguities that some other actor will have to resolve, and gaps that some other actor will have to fill. And it would usually prefer that actor to be the responsible agency, not a court...
> Put all that together and deference to the agency is the almost obvious choice, based on an implicit congressional delegation of interpretive authority. We defer, the Court has explained, “because of a presumption that Congress” would have “desired the agency (rather than the courts)” to exercise “whatever degree of discretion” the statute allows. Smiley v. Citibank (South Dakota), N. A., 517
U. S. 735, 740–741 (1996).
> Today, the Court flips the script: It is now “the courts (rather than the agency)” that will wield power when Congress has left an area of interpretive discretion. A rule of judicial humility gives way to a rule of judicial hubris. In recent years, this Court has too often taken for itself decision-making authority Congress assigned to agencies. The Court has substituted its own judgment on workplace health for that of the Occupational Safety and Health Administration; its own judgment on climate change for that of the Environmental Protection Agency; and its own judgment on student loans for that of the Department of Education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>consumer451</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Postgres Named Prepared Statements in Hyperdrive]]></title>
        <id>667c105ba4598c000bd70518</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/postgres-named-prepared-statements-supported-hyperdrive"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperdrive (Cloudflare’s globally distributed SQL connection pooler and cache) recently added support for Postgres protocol-level named prepared statements across pooled connections. We dive deep on what it took to add this feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Repp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 23, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racial and Ethnic Inequalities in Household Wealth Persist]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30411</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/racial-and-ethnic-inequalities-in-household-wealth-persist/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disparities in wealth are pronounced across racial and ethnic groups in the United States. As part of an ongoing series on inequality and equitable growth, we have been documenting the evolution of these gaps between Black, Hispanic, and white households, in this case from the first quarter of 2019 to the fourth quarter of 2023 for a variety of assets and liabilities for a pandemic-era picture. We find that real wealth grew and that the pace of growth for Black, Hispanic, and white households was very similar across this timeframe—yet gaps across groups persist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Natalia Emanuel, and Ben Lahey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by prinny_ in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819222</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819222"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The one in my previous job, which was an admin board for a market intelligence application. Ultimately, the reason it was good was because the engineers had zero ego on top of having excellent skills. The team that set the codebase were basically 4 seniors and 3 principals (the client actually did pay for top talent in this case) so not only everything was based on industry standards, written elegantly and organized perfectly, but every time some new requirement came up, these senior / principal engineers would discuss it in the most civilized matter I have ever seen.
E.g, "we need to come up with a way to implement X". Person A gives their idea, person B gives another idea and so on until everybody shared their thoughts. Then someone would say "I think what person C said makes the most sense" and everybody would agree and that was it. 30 minutes to hear everybody out, 3 minutes to discuss who will do it and when and the meeting was over.
I think the biggest testament to this code base was that when junior members joined the team, they were able to follow the existing code for adding new features. It was that easy to navigate and understand the big picture of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>prinny_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tlarkworthy in "Ask HN: What is the best code base you ever worked on?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819157</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40819157"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google3 codebase. It's just so vast and it works. It's a miracle. I feel lucky to have seen it. Everytime you change it, it reruns the dependencies. Everyone has different view concurrently. Commits are efficient immutable snapshots. It's just incredible multiplayer. So massively beyond what can be done with GitHub. Really I feel it's peak codebase. I've not seen what the other big techs do but it blew my mind]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tlarkworthy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16717</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/proactive-measures-against-password-breaches-and-cookie-hijacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, we’re committed to security that goes beyond the ordinary. We continuously strive to earn and maintain user trust by safeguarding critical components integral to every user’s experience. From passwords to session cookies, and tokens to webhooks, we prioritize protecting everything essential to how users log into the platform and remain authenticated. Through proactive […]
The post Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Lehotsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper: On the curious diet of the Speckled Mousebird]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52787</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/28/occasional-paper-on-the-curious-diet-of-the-speckled-mousebird/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So my wife took this picture in our garden yesterday, here in Kigali, Rwanda: Take a close look.  This little bird — about the size of an American cardinal, or a European robin — is facing us.  It’s also facing the sun, though you can’t see that.  It is holding two twigs with its little […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is turning black and brown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How should we interpret the results of the EU parliamentary elections? 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lpolovets in "FDA warns top U.S. bakery not to claim foods contain allergens when they don't"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T23:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My understanding is this allergen over-labeling was inspired by the FDA in the first place. https://www.fastcompany.com/90830854/sesame-seed-allergen-fd...
From the linked article (from Jan 2023):
  But sesame does differ in one distinct way from eggs, peanuts, shellfish, milk, and soy: The seeds are teeny tiny and hard to keep track of. This means they’re prone to “cross-contamination,” in food-allergy terms. If you operate a bakery that makes sesame bagels, the odds are decent that rogue seeds will end up in your other products, too. Bad news for people with severe sesame allergies. But it’s also expensive and frustrating for food manufacturers to ensure the seeds are kept away from other foods, if they’re on the FDA’s major allergens list.
  
  Advocates have therefore been warning since December that the FASTER Act is poised to have a counter effect. Rather than minimize cross-contamination, as they argue the law requires, many big food brands have opted to add sesame to their bread products, then simply declare it as an ingredient. They are intentionally adding sesame flour to “avoid complying with the spirit and intent of the FASTER Act,” FARE tells Fast Company. That is cheaper than certifying that their facilities are 100% sesame-free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lpolovets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Pools: Cost-effective, non-persistent virtual desktops]]></title>
        <id>984d71ca0c0d724236063c172b55b47f247b8d96</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-pools-cost-effective-non-persistent-virtual-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T22:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline virtual desktop management: provision non-persistent desktops, configure apps and resources, and automatically scale capacity based on demand, all from a centralized platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janalsncm in "Supreme Court blocks controversial Purdue Pharma opioid settlement"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pound for pound, the Sacklers probably did more damage to America than any other drug dealers in history. More damage than any serial killer or mass shooter. In my mind they should be considered public enemies 1 through N. I sincerely hope they face civil and criminal liabilities for what they’ve done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janalsncm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tetris font, fun and games with typography]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7921</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tetris-font-fun-games-with-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a version of Tetris that requires the player to try and spell words with the Tetris pieces, as they fall from the sky? If there is, I’ve not heard of it. But, that’s not saying much, as I don’t know a whole lot about gaming. Anyway, Tetris Font, developed by Erik Demaine and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing end-to-end data lineage (preview) visualization in Amazon DataZone]]></title>
        <id>879d02790e78c3e2de51ba7702fc1da289789fe1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-end-to-end-data-lineage-preview-visualization-in-amazon-datazone/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trace data from origin to insights with an intuitive visual graph, empowering engineers, analysts, and admins to validate provenance, troubleshoot pipelines, and ensure governance with ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>95dac704f4314c4f6db2eca43810d24e08e0c1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of an enhanced AWS Well-Architected Framework. In this update, you’ll find expanded guidance across all six pillars of the Framework: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability. In this release, we updated the implementation guidance for the new and existing best practices to be more prescriptive. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doublet00th in "Supreme Court blocks controversial Purdue Pharma opioid settlement"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40814431</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40814431"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T19:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think there's a misunderstanding in what the settlement is about. As part of Purdue's bankruptcy, the Sackler family is voluntarily providing 6 billion dollars to help settle claims opioid victims have brought against Purdue Pharma.
As a condition to provide the 6 billion dollars, the Sackler family has asked the bankruptcy judge to not even allow any new suits against the Sacklers related to the Opioid epidemic. This is something bankruptcy courts do regular for the company Purdue Pharma, but it is irregular when it comes to the Sackler family (this is not the entity going bankrupt!)
This is the issue that went up to the Supreme Court, and the Supreme Court ruled that the protection given to the Sackler family is not something that can be given  by a bankruptcy judge during the bankruptcy of Purdue Pharma.
Matt Levine has a much better explanation here: https://www.bloomberg.com/opinion/articles/2024-06-27/purdue...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doublet00th</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst now supports GitLab and Bitbucket repositories, with blueprints and Amazon Q feature development]]></title>
        <id>66767bb7893b7246f1f08f78664b23f8a53f9820</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codecatalyst-now-supports-gitlab-and-bitbucket-repositories-with-blueprints-and-amazon-q-feature-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your code across popular git repositories with Amazon CodeCatalyst's new integration with GitLab.com and Bitbucket Cloud. Use blueprints and Amazon Q feature development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded function calling in Workers AI: easier, smarter, faster]]></title>
        <id>667d8733a4598c000bd705cd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/embedded-function-calling"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new way to do function calling in Workers AI by running function code alongside your inference. Plus, a new @cloudflare/ai-utils package to make getting started as simple as possible]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harley Turan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - Anarchist solidarity with the people of Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-anarchist-solidarity-with-the-people-of-ukraine?v=1719492063</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-anarchist-solidarity-with-the-people-of-ukraine?v=1719492063"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: Anarchist solidarity with the people of Ukraine
Date: 25 February 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 On February 24, hundreds of anarchists in several cities across Europe took to the streets in solidarity with the people of Ukraine on the second anniversary of the start of full-scale Russian invasion. The Anarchist Bloc was at actions in Warsaw, Vilnius, Berlin, Tbilisi, Vienna and Zurich. It was important for us to express words of support to people from Ukraine, whose country has been tormented by the Kremlin’s aggression for two years, to applaud the steadfastness of all those who oppose this aggression with weapons in their hands, especially our comrades. 
 At the actions we included audio messages from anarchists, who right now are holding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - 6 activists of the anarchist group “Black Nightingales” were arrested in Belarus]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/prame-6-activists-of-the-anarchist-group-black-nightingales-were-arrested-in-belarus?v=1719490222</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/prame-6-activists-of-the-anarchist-group-black-nightingales-were-arrested-in-belarus?v=1719490222"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: 6 activists of the anarchist group “Black Nightingales” were arrested in Belarus
Date: 30 April 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 As it became known from a propaganda video on youtube published by the state media, anarchists from the group “Black Nightingales” were detained in Belarus several months ago. According to the regime’s version, they were planning to attack the state infrastructure and sabotage the support of the Russian military in Belarus. The list of the group members includes Maria Misyuk, Trofim Barysau, Sergey Zhigalyou, Dmitry Zahoroshko, Anastasia Klimenka, and Aleksandra Pulinovich. Based on the attitude of the Belarusian regime towards anarchists, we believe that any recorded testimony was obtained under torture until the co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prameń - Putin’s reelection victory in the Russian Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-putin-s-reelection-victory-in-the-russian-federation?v=1719490126</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/pramen-putin-s-reelection-victory-in-the-russian-federation?v=1719490126"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Prameń
Title: Putin’s reelection victory in the Russian Federation
Date: 20 March 2024
Source: Retrieved on 27th June 2024 from pramen.io

 No one doubted the ability of Vladimir Putin and his cohort to draw a 50%+ figure to maintain their own power. It would be naive to believe that any action in the controlled environment of the polling stations could affect the percentages displayed on the screens of the Russian empire and the entire planet. Whether you spoil a ballot, write a message on it, or nuke a polling station, Putin will still consistently win. 
 Smart voting, apps on phones and even prayers will not be able to influence the results of the vote. 
 But that’s not the victory we want to talk about today. Rather, we want to talk about the political victory around mobilizati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>