<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-29T06:30:40.546Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-29T06:30:40.546Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imperialism and Anti-Imperialism Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323987</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/imperialism-and-anti-imperialism-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism produces imperialism—the competition between the great powers and their corporations for the division and redivision of the world market. This competition generates a dynamic hierarchy of states, with the most powerful at the top, middling or sub-imperial powers beneath them, and oppressed nations at the bottom. No hierarchy is permanent. Capitalism’s law of uneven  More
The post Imperialism and Anti-Imperialism Today appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith -</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Christian Money Funds African Homophobia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323897</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/u-s-christian-money-funds-african-homophobia/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Few Americans are aware just how significant is the role of “right-wing Christian nationalists” in promoting and sustaining the reactionary sexual politics prevalent within many African countries. It is estimated that more than 20 U.S. Christian groups are actively subsidizing campaigns against LGBT people as well as opposing access to safe abortions, contraceptives and comprehensive sexuality education.  More
The post U.S. Christian Money Funds African Homophobia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Empty Christianity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323996</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/bidens-empty-christianity/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m so sick of hearing about President Joe Biden’s deep Christian faith. The media often talks about it, when contrasting his lifestyle with that of former President Donald Trump, who is currently on trial for a hush-money payment to a porn star. It goes without saying Biden is superior to Trump politically in every respect,  More
The post Biden’s Empty Christianity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Certain French Stubbornness: Violence in New Caledonia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323997</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/a-certain-french-stubbornness-violence-in-new-caledonia/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s Emmanuel Macron can, at times, show himself at odds with the grime and gristle of grounded politics.  Able to pack in various snatches of philosophical reflection in a speech, straddling the highs and lows of a rhetorical display, his political acumen has, at times, deserted him. Nothing is more evident of this than his treatment  More
The post A Certain French Stubbornness: Violence in New Caledonia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brandon Johnson Dines with Biden, While Protests at the DNC Loom on the Horizon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324000</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/brandon-johnson-dines-with-biden-while-protests-at-the-dnc-loom-on-the-horizon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a beautiful warm night on the south lawn of White House. Five hundred guests of President Biden gathered for an official state dinner for Kenyan President William Ruto on the evening of May 23rd. There were “stunning D.C. views, a knockout menu, a dose of celebrity star power and even a little family drama,” according to  More
The post Brandon Johnson Dines with Biden, While Protests at the DNC Loom on the Horizon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ho Chi Minh: The Early Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323900</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/ho-chi-minh-the-early-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1968, as war raged across Vietnam, the Vietnamese revolutionary popularly known as Ho Chi Minh wrote a New Year’s message to the worldwide movement against the US war on the Vietnamese.  After somewhat poetically listing the ongoing war crimes of the US military, the letter ended with these words:  “We enjoy the support of  More
The post Ho Chi Minh: The Early Years appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: All the Young Dudes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323839</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/letter-from-london-all-the-young-dudes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The looming general election sits where summer used to sit. It now blocks out the light. It locks up all the bikes. It steals the bucket hats. It talks of rain. Even the football at the forthcoming Euros feels faintly hijacked. Thank goodness for our own distractions, such as a gig in Brixton last night.  More
The post Letter from London: All the Young Dudes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Country for Old Men]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323896</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/no-country-for-old-men/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1970 I entered the U.S. Department of Agriculture’s Sanford, Maine  office looking for some soils maps of the homestead place. A man named “Sid” was behind the counter that day. He asked about the farm’s location. He brightened in recognition when I described it. “Oh, I know that place,” he said. “That’s only good  More
The post No Country for Old Men appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Rhames</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden’s Deceptive-Declaration Zigs & Deadly-Deed Zags]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323984</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/joe-bidens-deceptive-declaration-zigs-deadly-deed-zags/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the keynote speaker at Morehouse College in Atlanta last week, Joe Biden listened to the class Valedictorian’s call for a permanent ceasefire in Gaza. The President nodded and applauded with others in the assembly. In contrast, he had just approved another billion dollars in killer weapons for the genocidal Netanyahu regime to blow up  More
The post Joe Biden’s Deceptive-Declaration Zigs & Deadly-Deed Zags appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Struggle for the Aegean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323991</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/29/the-struggle-for-the-aegean/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T05:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue The Aegean Sea has been an intimate part of the history of the Hellenes / Greeks and their civilization. For millennia, the Aegean Sea united the Asia Minor / Ionia to the mainland of Hellas / Greece. It was the water bridge between the numerous small and large Aegean islands. The Cycladic islands, in  More
The post The Struggle for the Aegean appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Repress U., Class of 2024: How to Build a Homeland Security Campus in Seven More Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272337</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/repress-u-class-of-2024-how-to-build-a-homeland-security-campus-in-seven-more-steps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T04:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The apparatus behind the explosion of police crackdowns against campus anti-Gaza-genocide protests has been very long in the making.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snowwrestler in "Ex-OpenAI board member reveals what led to Sam Altman's brief ousting"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40507227</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40507227"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T01:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kind of ironic that people are jumping in here to defend Sam Altman on the message board of Y Combinator, which also fired him from an executive leadership role for similar reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snowwrestler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EC2 high memory U7i Instances for large in-memory databases]]></title>
        <id>8c871b2347245a09a7506da5264f862fb0203d42</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-ec2-high-memory-u7i-instances-for-large-in-memory-databases/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T23:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash unparalleled power with U7i instances: up to 32 TiB DDR5 memory, 896 vCPUs, and unmatched performance for in-memory databases like SAP HANA, Oracle, and SQL Server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASBO - Solidarity and its Discontents?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/asbo-solidarity-and-its-discontents?v=1716936084</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/asbo-solidarity-and-its-discontents?v=1716936084"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T22:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: ASBO
Title: Solidarity and its Discontents?
Subtitle: Riots, Rebellion and Repression in Bristol 2011-2023
Date: 01/24
Source: https://bangupandsmash.noblogs.org/downloads/



The media, the schools, the judges, the cops, politicians, surveillance, technology, work. All have their role to play in repression. [1]
 Concepts and practices such as repression and solidarity have become amorphous and widespread. (I would also add ‘abolition’ to this stack of buzz words, but that might just be my 2p).[2] As with any word that conveniently describes a complex phenomenon (see also gentrification, ‘burn-out’, ‘trauma’, ‘affinity’ etc.) they are both a help and a hindrance. All these words are difficult to discuss because they combine personal experiences with repressive practices deliberatel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sasha k, Wolfi Landstreicher, Leila - Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sasha-k-wolfi-landstreicher-leila-introduction?v=1716931094</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sasha-k-wolfi-landstreicher-leila-introduction?v=1716931094"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T21:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: sasha k, Wolfi Landstreicher, Leila
Title: Introduction
Subtitle: Killing King Abacus
Date: 2000
Notes: This article originally appeared in Killing King Abacus #1
Source: Retrieved on May 28, 2024 from https://writerror.com/texts/Killing-King-Abacus-Introduction

Killing King Abacus
 To Kill King Abacus is to create relations without measure. If we aim to destroy capitalism we cannot reproduce its necrophilic logic which reduces relationships to numbers. To Kill King Abacus is to destroy the social net which privileges mediated transactions and images over direct relations. Because money is a general equivalent and thus is nearly limitless in its applications, it conquers other signifiers of value; capitalism transforms other value systems into itself. To Kill King Abacus is to dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Starbucks gives you lemon lattes, go co-work at McDonalds]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7713</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/starbucks-gives-lemon-lattes-co-work-at-mcdonalds/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Meerkamper, writing at Spacing, laments the apparent demise of the once omnipresent commercial third place, a kind of neutral zone between home and work, such as a cafe, where people gather. Or where remote workers can set up shop for the day. Coffee houses are one of the earliest examples of ‘Third Places,’ a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zepton in "API Shouldn't Redirect HTTP to HTTPS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40505525</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40505525"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stack Exchange API used to revoke API keys sent over HTTP (and return an error message), which is my favorite way to handle this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zepton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An art deco delight by night in the Sydney suburb of Randwick]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7719</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/photo-art-deco-delight-night-sydney-suburb-randwick/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Randwick is a large suburb located about five kilometres south east of downtown Sydney, Australia. It is home to the Prince of Wales hospital, Royal Randwick Racecourse, a thriving commercial and retail hub, large bus and light rail depots, the historic Ritz Cinemas, and arguably, the University of New South Wales (UNSW). Even though UNSW […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwanem in "TTE: Terminal Text Effects"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40504178</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40504178"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T18:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is amazing! Please never ever use it in production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwanem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Platform Explained Part II]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7123</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/data-platform-explained-part-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T18:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out Data Platform Explained Part I, where we started sharing the journey of building a data platform, its building [...]
The post Data Platform Explained Part II  appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272338</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics, Google's internal search documentation leaked (!), closing arguments begin in the Bragg/Merchan trial, bookcases as a superb user interface ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by karpathy in "Reproducing GPT-2 in llm.c"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40502693</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40502693"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T16:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi HN the main (more detailed) article is here 
https://github.com/karpathy/llm.c/discussions/481
Happy to answer questions!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>karpathy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus - Errico Malatesta: A Brief Biography]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-errico-malatesta-a-brief-biography?v=1716910492</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-errico-malatesta-a-brief-biography?v=1716910492"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T15:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus
Title: Errico Malatesta: A Brief Biography
Date: 2020
Notes: A brief biographical statement used to preface a reader for the DSA LSC Political Education Working Group's Malatesta Reader, which was used in a series of study circles in 2020 to explore Malatesta's "Anarchy," "Towards Anarchy," and " An Anarchist Programme".

 Errico Malatesta was born to a family of middle-class landowners in Santa Maria Capua Vetere, Italy on 14 December 1853. More distantly, his ancestors ruled Rimini as the House of Malatesta. The first of a long series of arrests came at age fourteen, when he was apprehended for writing an "insolent and threatening" letter to King Victor Emmanuel II . 
 Malatesta was introduced to Mazzinian Republicanism while studying medicine at …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“It’s Not Just Ideology: Why the U.S. Is Hard-Wired to Be Hostile to Autocratic Regimes”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272333</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/its-not-just-ideology-why-the-u-s-is-hard-wired-to-be-hostile-to-autocratic-regimes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An, erm, novel exercise to present Americans as always on board with good-thinking values like opposing autocratic players.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports of a death exaggerated]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52718</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/28/reports-of-a-death-exaggerated/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a metaphor. There’s an elderly person you’ve known for years.  Not a close relative, no, but someone whose career you’ve followed.  You feel tremendous respect for them, maybe some affection. They’re getting old and frail, but they’ve kept active.  Now and then you might see an article or something, and you’ll think, huh: still […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turning a rotten brain into a blog]]></title>
        <id>https://fatine.bearblog.dev/turning-a-rotten-brain-into-a-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://fatine.bearblog.dev/turning-a-rotten-brain-into-a-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:39:12.771Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I came across a content creator who stated that the antidote to the overconsumption of media content or any sort of information is creation, and it struck a chord with me.
My name is Fatine, I am a 23-year-old student, and that is all you need to know for now.
My consumption tendencies are not unique to me. The fact that Gen Z is a highly connected generation is undeniable, but I have come to the conclusion that it is not something to combat; the aim should be to counterbalance it. One has got to find a good habit that is a byproduct of consumption but makes it profitable. I think writing ticks all the boxes, given the fact that you must absorb a considerable amount of valuable information in order to produce coherently written thoughts.
During these past six months, I went through episodes of overstimulation that triggered the urge to go on long rants about specific topics. These topics were mainly recognized patterns from day-to-day observations and café discussions, all linked, in my opinion, to social media phenomena.
"Dump it" is a self-discovery journey where I try to turn months of introspection and café conversations into concise paragraphs, backed by research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Exchange‑Traded Products Improve Bitcoin Trading?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30080</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-exchange-traded-products-improve-bitcoin-trading/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spot bitcoin exchange-traded products (ETPs) began trading in the U.S. on January 11, 2024. For investors, these ETPs purport improved liquidity and price efficiency, and more convenient access to bitcoin trading compared to other means of trading bitcoin in spot markets. Proponents also cite bitcoin holdings as a portfolio diversification opportunity due to historically low correlation with traditional financial securities. Others argue that bitcoin remains a speculative asset and that ETPs increase its interconnections with the traditional financial system. In this post, we examine the initial performance, trading costs, and price efficiency of spot bitcoin ETPs in the U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Armstrong, Asani Sarkar, and Leslie Conner Warren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272232</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T10:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our lyrical daily links: Greenpeace v. golden rice, fierce US weather, Biden v. Chinese EVs, Africa. Habeck v. German homeowners, outrage over Rafah strikes, Russia electronic war prowess, Georgia treason, nuclear war worries, Trump hung jury? moar AI, real estae woes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are European Politicians Beginning to Worry About Their Own Possible Complicity in Israel’s War Crimes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272263</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/are-european-leaders-beginning-to-worry-about-their-complicity-in-israels-war-crimes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T10:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["If you are encouraging a party to undertake a war crime you become complicit in that crime itself."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IM Doc on the Accelerating Decline in American Medicine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272299</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/im-doc-on-the-accelerating-decline-in-american-medicine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T09:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the rot in US medicine....and as you might expect, it started from the head.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in the Green Transition: Which Workers Win and Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272305</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/lost-in-the-green-transition-which-workers-win-and-lose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T09:40:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most green energy boosters skip over which workers will win and lose. This post addresses that oversight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariffs on China: Trump was Dumb, Biden is Dumber]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323835</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/tariffs-on-china-trump-was-dumb-biden-is-dumber/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T06:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both countries also followed a model of state-led industrialization that the United States would probably not have tolerated a generation later during the heyday of stricter trade rules and neoliberal investment regimes. The U.S. need for economically strong non-communist allies in the region, during and after the Korean and Vietnam Wars, also contributed to this tolerance for the “unorthodox” economic strategies of Japan and South Korea. More
The post Tariffs on China: Trump was Dumb, Biden is Dumber appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza Matters, and Democracy is Functional: On the Latest Democracy Perception Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323923</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/gaza-matters-and-democracy-is-functional-on-the-latest-democracy-perception-index/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Democracy Perception Index (DPI) issued its 2024 report on May 8, revealing important and interesting shifts in global perceptions about democracy, geopolitics and international relations. The conclusions in the report were based on the views of over 62 thousand respondents from 53 countries – roughly representing 75 percent of the world’s total population. The  More
The post Gaza Matters, and Democracy is Functional: On the Latest Democracy Perception Index appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Massachusetts, Some Tax-the-Rich Inspiration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323832</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/from-massachusetts-some-tax-the-rich-inspiration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, after seven years of dedicated volunteer labor, the Raise Up Massachusetts coalition of over 150 community organizations, faith-based groups, and labor unions had worked onto the November statewide ballot a constitutional amendment to add what amounted to a special tax on millionaires to the state constitution. More
The post From Massachusetts, Some Tax-the-Rich Inspiration appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time to Put Americans’ Health Care Decisions Back in Our Own Hands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323937</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/its-time-to-put-americans-health-care-decisions-back-in-our-own-hands/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all deserve the right to make informed decisions about our own health. That right has been in danger for years — and since the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade, it’s under siege. I grew up in the South with an abstinence-only education — if you can call that an “education.” This approach, which teaches  More
The post It’s Time to Put Americans’ Health Care Decisions Back in Our Own Hands appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelsea McLain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Something’s Rotten in Montana’s Dept. of Fish, Wildlife and Parks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323938</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/somethings-rotten-in-montanas-dept-of-fish-wildlife-and-parks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something’s very rotten in Montana’s Department of Fish, Wildlife and Parks. A good guess would point to the Gianforte administration’s attitude toward informing the public about what’s wrong – or likely to go wrong – with the environment.  But “don’t ask, don’t tell” is a dead-end strategy for the state’s future — and a damning  More
The post Something’s Rotten in Montana’s Dept. of Fish, Wildlife and Parks appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Veteran For Peace Speaks on Memorial Day 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323902</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/a-veteran-for-peace-speaks-on-memorial-day-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My fellow veterans and you who have assembled with us: How many years have we mustered for our own Memorial Day rituals since we repudiated our previous roles as servants of militarism and war-making and turned to anti-war activism? How many times have we implored our fellow citizens to note the tragic and dreadful consequences  More
The post A Veteran For Peace Speaks on Memorial Day 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Atwood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Chile has a Palestinian Football Team: the Bigger History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323833</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/why-chile-has-a-palestinian-football-team-the-bigger-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supporters of Club Deportivo Palestino at a match v Deportes Copiapó, at Estadio Municipal de La Cisterna, Santiago, Chile. Carlos yo / Wikimedia Commons, CC BY-NC-SA Club Deportivo Palestino, a football team, play in a uniform of white, green and red. Their stadium flies Palestinian flags and their social sports club boasts an open-air pool  More
The post Why Chile has a Palestinian Football Team: the Bigger History appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Katherine Newman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alliance Politics in East Asia: More Security or Less?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323921</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/alliance-politics-in-east-asia-more-security-or-less/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden-Kishida Summit The best thing about diplomacy between government leaders is that it may ease tensions. The worst thing is that it doesn’t resolve the disputes between them, making matters worse. Both aspects of diplomacy have been on view lately in East Asia. An “historic” summit meeting April 10-11 between President Biden and Prime  More
The post Alliance Politics in East Asia: More Security or Less? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[L’chaim! Jews Against the Death Penalty, From Los Angeles to Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323836</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/lchaim-jews-against-the-death-penalty-from-los-angeles-to-iran/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:43:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 3,500 members of L’chaim! Jews Against the Death Penalty resoundingly condemn Iran’s intention of executing Arvin Ghahremani (Hebrew name: Arvin Netanel ben Sonia), within the month, if not sooner. Ghahremani is a 20-year-old Jewish man who is going to be murdered by the state for to an act of self-defense against Mr. Amir Shokri,  More
The post L’chaim! Jews Against the Death Penalty, From Los Angeles to Iran appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Zoosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Conflict Resolution Experts Wish Universities Knew About Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323925</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/what-conflict-resolution-experts-wish-universities-knew-about-conflict/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The protests roiling our campuses reveal a great deal about us as a country. Emotions are easily triggered, many of us are comfortable being angry, and most of us need help to handle conflict constructively. We’re in a tumultuous year, likely with more protests ahead. Conflict resolution experts say that these protests, these conflicts, are  More
The post What Conflict Resolution Experts Wish Universities Knew About Conflict appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Burrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even If It Avoids Civil War,  Israel’s Final Crisis Looks Cataclysmic!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323838</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/even-if-it-avoids-civil-war-israels-final-crisis-looks-cataclysmic/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T04:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2021, commenting on Albert Einstein’s prophetic warnings of Israel’s disastrous future as early as 1948, we concluded our text with the following observation and, at the same time, prediction: “Unfortunately, it seems clear that Einstein was right again. With the British now a remote memory, it is indeed true that the descendants of  More
The post Even If It Avoids Civil War,  Israel’s Final Crisis Looks Cataclysmic! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ballad of Patty Hearst and Bill Walton]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323973</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/28/the-ballad-of-patty-hearst-and-bill-walton/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T04:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patty Hearst & Bill Walton made a striking pair she was only five foot two, he had that much long red hair He studied at UCLA with Wooden you know he was following Alcindor, Wicks, Allen, Farmer and Rowe And they be heavy brothers, reading Malcolm X If you’re supposed to be the white Kareem  More
The post The Ballad of Patty Hearst and Bill Walton appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fred Gardner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anark - A Modern Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anark-a-modern-anarchism?v=1716865569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anark-a-modern-anarchism?v=1716865569"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T03:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anark
Title: A Modern Anarchism
Date: 2022
Notes: Originally published in video format on the YouTube channel Anark, this piece combines the three-part essay A Modern Anarchism by Daniel Baryon into one document.
Source: Retrieved on 5/27/2024 from https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-1-anarchist-analysis https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-2-anarchy and https://libcom.org/article/modern-anarchism-part-3-revolution

Part 1: Anarchist Analysis
Introduction
 We stand now at a turning point, wherein many roads sprawl out in front of us. With unprecedented access to information, the atlas seems to lie within our hands. But, at this crossroads, the popularizers of these many paths shout over one another to persuade new travelers, only to find that most travelers…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jbandela1 in "Last hours of an organ donor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40496581</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40496581"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T01:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> When told of my upcoming case, I had mixed feelings. On the one hand, being in perfect health, unaccustomed to suffering and therefore easily disconcerted by the thought of death, I was horrified. My attitude toward death was like that of a young person standing blindfolded and tied to a post, awaiting a volley from a firing squad. The whole concept made my blood run cold. Yet the case also aroused in me a feeling of relief. Simply put, there was no risk of malpractice, as my patient was already dead. Many anaesthesiologists have such self-centred thoughts when taking care of ASA 6 patients.
> After we moved her from the gurney to the operating table, the doctors and nurses, so used to taking care of living patients, stared at one another stupidly, as if not knowing why they had come together or why they stood around the table.
Sorry this strikes me as embellishing for the case of writing a story.
Background: I was a neurosurgery resident at a level 1 trauma center. I was involved in determining brain death (though the final certification was by an attending surgeon). I worked closely with the transplant team. I declared (normal) cardiac death many times. I had many agonizing conversations with families about withdrawal of care.
Anesthesia is a 4 year residency. Even the 2nd year anesthesia residents I worked with had more of an awareness and lack of naivety that this author shows.
And the OR teams were much more prepared and professional than this. They knew what they had to do and why they had to do it.
If there are other physicians here, I would love to hear your opinions, but this whole piece strikes me as overwrought and full of embellishments to make a certain point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jbandela1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creative environments, are they a place or a time, or both?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7702</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/creative-environments-place-time-both/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your mission, should you choose to accept it: write about creative environments. Let’s have a go. A creative environment, as far as I can tell, is not necessarily a place. Not one I can put my finger on, at least. Nor is it a particular time. My creative ideas, if that’s what they can be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aurornis in "Should I use JWTs for authentication tokens?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40494614</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40494614"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T20:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> You don't need to be Facebook or Google to have more than one service in your infrastructure that needs to authenticate a user's existing session without forcing the user to log in again.
Thank you. This middle ground between hyperscaler infrastructure and super simple web apps is where most of my career has been spent, yet the recent trend is to pretend like there are only two possible extremes: You’re either Facebook or you’re not doing anything complicated.
It has an unfortunate second order effect of convincing people that as soon as they encounter something more complicated than a simple web app, they need to adopt everything the hyperscalers do to solve it.
I wish we could spend more time discussing the middle ground rather than pretending it’s some sort of war between super simple or ultra complex.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurornis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tmnvix in "Priced out of home ownership"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40494448</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40494448"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T20:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People intuitively jump to the conclusion that the problem is caused by a lack of building. While more building would help, a lack of it isn't the main cause of this problem.
Ask yourself, do Canada, Australia, New Zealand, the US, Britain, Ireland, etc, all have the same inability to build or is there maybe some other common cause?
In my view this is symptomatic of a more fundamental issue - global asset price inflation driven by a broken financial system (i.e. a system being artificially pumped up with cheap credit). Housing is just where the rubber hits the road and regular lives are directly effected. Just look at the tight correlation between the increase in the money supply and property prices.
For those who insist that the number of properties is inadequate, take a look at the numbers for each of the countries I mentioned in the first chart here: https://www.oecd.org/els/family/HM1-1-Housing-stock-and-cons... (Total number of dwellings per thousand inhabitants, 2022 and 2011).
This is a problem of underutilisation in my view. Too many properties are being used as investments and not as a primary residence.
Cheap credit causes an increase in demand. This is not demand for homes but additional 'artificial' demand for properties as investments. Think short term rentals, second homes, land banked properties, etc. By definition, only investment properties can be underutilised - owner occupied homes are occupied! So in an environment that encourages property investment you will see more underutilisation.
What will cause prices to fall is higher interest rates. This is what has been happening in NZ.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tmnvix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How One Advice Columnist Handled Our Covid Pandemic, Over Four Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272238</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/how_one_advice_columnist_handled_our_covid_pandemic_over_four_years.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T20:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Carolyn Hax tries to sweep back the tide with a broom.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DGAP in "Priced out of home ownership"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493841</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493841"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T19:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop subsidizing demand at the national level. Stop restricting supply at the local level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DGAP</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jupp0r in "Should I use JWTs for authentication tokens?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493818</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493818"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T19:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Just use the normal session mechanism that comes with your web framework and that you were using before someone told you that Google uses jwt. It has stood the test of time and is probably fine."
You don't need to be Facebook or Google to have more than one service in your infrastructure that needs to authenticate a user's existing session without forcing the user to log in again. Sharing the session across multiple services is its own distributed systems problem with numerous security implications to be aware of and bearer tokens might be a good alternative.
If all you have is a single monolith web app that is the identity provider, makes all authentication decisions etc then yes, you don't need JWTs probably. There is a huge gap between that and being Google/Facebook.
Apart from that, Google and Facebook don't even use JWTs between the browser and backends after the initial login but actually do have some sort of distributed session concept last time I checked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jupp0r</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – LlamaIndex support for Amazon Neptune, force AWS CloudFormation stack deletion, and more (May 27, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>1bf9fbbce923c6324942d76ec84a66ab6cd7527a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-llamaindex-support-for-amazon-neptune-force-aws-cloudformation-stack-deletion-and-more-may-27-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T19:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Dr. Matt Wood, VP for AI Products at Amazon Web Services (AWS), delivered the keynote at the AWS Summit Los Angeles. Matt and guest speakers shared the latest advancements in generative artificial intelligence (generative AI), developer tooling, and foundational infrastructure, showcasing how they come together to change what’s possible for builders. You can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eastdakota in "Controlling the Taylor Swift Eras Tour wristbands with Flipper Zero"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493217</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493217"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T18:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I may have gone to the Taylor Swift show in Lisbon, wondered how they were able to precisely control these without carefully handing them out, gathered a few from my fellow concert goers, and presented them to John last night over dinner with a challenge to figure it out. All my guesses were more complicated than the actual answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eastdakota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whipping up disaster: how Brazil became a lab for financial agro-investments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Whipping-up-disaster-how-Brazil-became-a-lab-for-financial-agro-investments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Whipping-up-disaster-how-Brazil-became-a-lab-for-financial-agro-investments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T18:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Agro is pop, agro is tech, agro is everything” states a popular slogan in adverts broadcast on Brazil's largest TV channel since 2016. Financed by agribusiness, these advertisements portray a virtuous cycle, showcasing images of contented rural workers amidst soybean, corn, cotton, and sugar cane plantations, as well as happy urban families. They are all content because they can feed, clothe themselves, and fuel their cars, thanks to the agro-industry. 
English

/ 
Brazil, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GRAIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by basil-rash in "Controlling the Taylor Swift Eras Tour wristbands with Flipper Zero"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493063</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40493063"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T18:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a delightfully simple solution! I have to imagine if I were given this problem I would muck it all up with wristbands assigned to seats and a 5G/IOT network needing to be installed at every stadium and custom control logic needing to be written and customized for every stadium…
Whereas they just hook up an IR lamp and use the exact same lighting control procedures every stage tech knows blindfolded. Brilliant!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>basil-rash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ghnws in "Instead of “auth”, we should say “permissions” and “login”"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492549</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492549"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having two almost identical terms that mean completely different things is not a very good idea. Also here you are explaining what the words mean, when "login" and "permission" are immediately obvious. Most people don't speak english natively either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ghnws</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[memories under the jambu tree]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/memories-under-the-jambu-tree/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/memories-under-the-jambu-tree/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:55:03.811Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last night, as I watched a YouTube video, the backdrop featured white wax jambu trees in a field. Seeing those Jambu flowers took me back to my childhood visits to my friend J's home.
During my childhood, I often went to J's place on weekends to play video games. Afterward, we would head to the nearby playground to play cricket with his local friends. When we returned, we would wash up using the outdoor tap next to a huge white wax jambu tree in J's backyard.
During peak season, that tree was laden with jambu fruits. Being curious kids, J's aunt or mother would help us pick the fruits using a long-handled fruit picker. Mostly, his aunt assisted us, gently guiding us to the ripest jambus high in the tree branches.
J's aunt was like family to me. Though older than our mothers, she had never married. She doted on her nephew J and always welcomed me, addressing me affectionately as "mone" which means son in Malayalam. I fondly remember weekends spent at their home, enjoying her delicious home-cooked meals.
Fast forward several years after I moved away for college. J called me with devastating news - his beloved aunt had been diagnosed with cancer. I was in shock. During my next weekend visit home, my mother and I made a trip to see her. Sadly, not long after, the cancer took her life. Losing someone so full of life and love at a young age was deeply distressing.
Last night, as I gazed at those white jambu flowers on my screen, memories of that gem of a lady and our carefree childhood days flooded me with profound nostalgia and sorrow. Jambus will always be a poignant reminder of happier times and that kind soul who left us too soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gumby in "Possible association between tattoos and lymphoma"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492371</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492371"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not surprised — tattoo inks are not regulated and the colors are often formed with  toxic compounds (e.g. copper).  Then the needle avoids the protective barrier provided by the skin.
Ironically, while working on a drug program that involved intradermal injection, we needed to tattoo the injection site so we could find it later. The FDA was very demanding that both the procedure and more importantly to them the dye would not have any effect that might alter the body’s response to the compound under test.  We had to do a whole study just to validate this.
So the FDA is concerned about this issue for guinea pigs, but is barred from investigating the effect on humans.  All they can do is publish advice on their web site.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gumby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Memorial Day]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795989/0/themoneyillusion~Happy-Memorial-Day/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795989/0/themoneyillusion~Happy-Memorial-Day/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some messages from our current and future leaders:<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/897795989/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/897795989/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-27-at-9.18.39-AM-1024x875.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/897795989/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/897795989/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/897795989/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comment-6836696">I fail to see the problem.   What, precisely, did Trump say ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comment-6836408">Chris, Actually, I'm not talking about the man. I'm making a ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comment-6836393">Peter seems like the type of chap who judges a general's ...</a> <i>by Tacticus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comment-6836391">Not at all. Memorial Day is barely a hundred years old and is ...</a> <i>by Peter</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comment-6836354">Look at Peter lol. This guy that sacrificed his own very life ...</a> <i>by Student</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/happy-memorial-day/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new (NIMBY) Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795596/0/themoneyillusion~The-new-NIMBY-Trump/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795596/0/themoneyillusion~The-new-NIMBY-Trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the upcoming presidential election, the issues really don&#8217;t matter at all. Nobody in their right mind believes a thing that Trump says, so it&#8217;s all guesswork as to what he will do in office. And even if I agreed with Trump 100% on &#8220;the issues&#8221; (I don&#8217;t) I&#8217;d still vote against him because he&#8217;s [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/897795596/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/897795596/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/897795596/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/897795596/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/897795596/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comment-6836423">I think that was always Trump's method. Because all of his ...</a> <i>by J Mann</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comment-6836030">Bobster, You said:   “Zoning isn’t even the binding ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comment-6836012">Nobody in their “right mind” believes anything he says. In ...</a> <i>by Sara</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comment-6835894">'And even if I agreed with Trump 100% on “the issues” (I ...</a> <i>by Tacticus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comment-6835876">A year ago he said he wanted the death penalty for drug ...</a> <i>by Will</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-new-nimby-trump/#comments">Plus 2 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trust, but verify]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795599/0/themoneyillusion~Trust-but-verify/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/897795599/0/themoneyillusion~Trust-but-verify/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, Tyler Cowen offers some views on a wide variety of issues. He begins with some reassuring remarks about the future of American democracy, and then offers some highly pessimistic remarks about Germany: Meanwhile, being reasonable with your constituents is overrated. Look at Germany, which has non-ideological, non-polarized politics. They&#8217;ve gotten every [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/897795599/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/897795599/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-19-at-9.08.07-AM-1024x476.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/897795599/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/897795599/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/897795599/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comment-6836605">Matthias, There is a contradiction. He says they have no ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comment-6836584">Scott, I think your argument and Peter's argument aren't in ...</a> <i>by Matthias</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comment-6836462">“Russia is treating this like the beginning of WWIII.” ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comment-6836415">Peter, Check out how quickly the US ramped up production during ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comment-6836239">Dare I say that Tyler may have succumbed to the fallacy of mood ...</a> <i>by Rajat</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/trust-but-verify/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aeonik in "Instead of “auth”, we should say “permissions” and “login”"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492213</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40492213"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Authorize" and "Authenticate" are excellent words. They go back to medieval times and haven't changed meaning too much.
Everybody knows what an "authority" is. It means they have power or capability.
Everybody knows what authentic means. Something that is proven to be genuine.
The difference between the two concepts, as they are used in crypto systems are specific, important to get right, and also inherently intertwined, confusing, and subtle. I'm skeptical that changing the words would help.
It's one of the many reasons we have the saying, "Don't roll your own crypto."
Trust and verification are just hard problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aeonik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eunice Minette Schuster - Native American Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eunice-minette-schuster-native-american-anarchism?v=1716826080</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eunice-minette-schuster-native-american-anarchism?v=1716826080"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eunice Minette Schuster
Title: Native American Anarchism
Subtitle: A Study of Left-Wing American Individualism
Date: 1932
Notes: What is meant by ‘Native American’ in the title is ‘local to America’, not ‘indigenous American’. The text undoubtedly still contains many OCR errors that are hard to find without reading the entire book. Finally, some text appears missing through errors in how the book was originally published, such as a paragraph ends naturally with a period at the end of page 112, but then begins half-way through a sentence at the beginning of page 113 (“exchange and recognized that money”).
Source: <archive.org/details/nativeamericanan0000schu>

Preface
 The writer has attempted in the following study to delineate the character and form of native American anarchism an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[slideshow memory theater]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/slideshow-memory-theater/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/slideshow-memory-theater/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T15:11:23.828Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[last weekend i went to see a movie with some friends from high school and one of them pulled me aside to be like: "do you remember one of the first times we spoke? it was in the wing where they always made us line up for assembly and you were asking me if the art for this series got better over time." 

i didn't. this must have been close to eight years ago. 

another friend, who first introduced me to haikyuu!!, quickly chimed in with a "no, she asked me the exact same thing in history club. right before we watched magic mike xxl." that last bit could have been a joke, though it probably isn't. regardless, i didn't really remember it either. sophomore year was surprisingly busy for me, so i imagine i must have spent the rest of that period catching up on sleep.

days later and thinking ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mohammed Bamyeh & Uri Gordon - The No State Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mohammed-bamyeh-uri-gordon-the-no-state-solution?v=1716820647</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mohammed-bamyeh-uri-gordon-the-no-state-solution?v=1716820647"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mohammed Bamyeh & Uri Gordon
Title: The No State Solution
Subtitle: A Dialogue with Palestinian sociologist Mohammed Bamyeh & Israeli political scientist Uri Gordon
Date: January 28 2024
Notes: This zine is a transcription of The No State Solution: A Dialogue with Palestinian sociologist Mohammed Bamyeh & Israeli political scientist Uri Gordon, a live and recorded event which took place on January 22, 2024 in unceded Lekwungen territory in so-called occupied “Victoria, BC, Canada.” While a few grammatical errors have been fixed, we did our best to stay true to the original transcript of our speakers. It is not to be confused with Shuli Branson’s No State Soluton (2023).
Source: Retrieved on May 19 from https://anarchistnetwork.info/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/ANVI-NoStateSolution.pd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Duane Rousselle - After Post-Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-after-post-anarchism?v=1716819512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-after-post-anarchism?v=1716819512"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Duane Rousselle
Title: After Post-Anarchism
Date: 2012
Source: <archive.org/details/RousselleAfterPostAnarchism_201610>

 For Soren, 
who taught me the value of a leap. 
 “What we are dealing with here is another version of the Lacanian ‘il n’y a pas de rapport’: if, for Lacan, there is no sexual relationship, then, for Marxism proper, there is no relationship between economy and politics, no meta-language enabling us to grasp the two levels from the same neutral standpoint, although—or, rather, because—these two levels are inextricably intertwined.” 
 — Slavoj Zizek 
Afterword
 Children from around the ages of five through seven are believed to have already acquired an understanding of the social norms surrounding sexuality. Immediately following this period of development, the ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Loadenthal - The Politics of Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/michael-loadenthal-the-politics-of-attack?v=1716818479</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/michael-loadenthal-the-politics-of-attack?v=1716818479"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T14:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Michael Loadenthal
Title: The Politics of Attack
Subtitle: Communiqués and Insurrectionary Violence
Date: 2017
Notes: Originally published as the authors dissertation.
Source: <manchesteruniversitypress.co.uk/9781526114440/>

 CONTEMPORARY ANARCHIST STUDIES 
 A series edited by 
 Laurence Davis, University College Cork, Ireland
 Uri Gordon, University of Nottingham, UK
 Nathan Jun, Midwestern State University, USA
 Alex Prichard, Exeter University, UK
Contemporary Anarchist Studies promotes the study of anarchism as a framework for understanding and acting on the most pressing problems of our times. The series publishes cutting-edge, socially engaged scholarship from around the world – bridging theory and practice, academic rigor and the insights of contemporary activism. 
 The top…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by izzydata in "Possible association between tattoos and lymphoma"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490750</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490750"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first time I've ever heard of someone regretting not getting a tattoo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>izzydata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David Graeber - The Democracy Project]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-democracy-project?v=1716817696</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/david-graeber-the-democracy-project?v=1716817696"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David Graeber
Title: The Democracy Project
Subtitle: A History, a Crisis, a Movement
Date: 2013
Source: <archive.org/details/isbn_9780812993561>

 Democracy has been the American religion since before the Revolution —from New England town halls to the multicultural democracy of Atlantic pirate ships. But can our current political system, one that seems responsive only to the wealthiest among us and leaves most Americans feeling disengaged, voiceless, and disenfranchised, really be called democratic? And if the tools of our democracy are not working to solve the rising crises we face, how can we —average citizens— make change happen? 
The Democracy Project tells the story of the resilience of the democratic spirit and the adaptability of the democratic idea. It offers a fresh take o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudolf de Jong - Ferdinand Domela Nieuwenhuis: Anarchist and Messiah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-de-jong-ferdinand-domela-nieuwenhuis-anarchist-and-messiah?v=1716817339</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-de-jong-ferdinand-domela-nieuwenhuis-anarchist-and-messiah?v=1716817339"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:42:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rudolf de Jong
Title: Ferdinand Domela Nieuwenhuis: Anarchist and Messiah
Date: 1971
Notes: In this historical essay the redeemer of the Dutch proletariat is reviewed against the background of his own day and age. Author Rudolf de Jong (born 1932) studied political and social-science, and since 1960 works at the International Institute for Social History in Amsterdam. He has published books on the Spanish Civil War and articles on anarchism, Latin America, and Spain. A summary of his essay on Provos and anarchists appeared in the Autumn 1967 issue of Delta. The present article is translated by Elizabeth Wentholt-Haig. 
 Text digitalized by Forum voor Georganiseerd Anarchisme.
Source: Delta, A review of arts life and thought in the Netherlands, winter 1970-71

 When the students occ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by palata in "Big data is dead (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490601</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490601"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that may have an impact on the answers: you are hiring them, so I assume they are passing a technical interview. So they expect that you want to check their understanding of the technical stack.
I would not conclude that they over-engineer everything they do from such an answer, but rather just that they got tricked in this very artificial situation where you are in a dominant position and ask trick questions.
I was recently in a technical interview with an interviewer roughly my age and my experience, and I messed up. That's the game, I get it. But the interviewer got judgemental towards my (admittedly bad) answers. I am absolutely certain that were the roles inverted, I could choose a topic I know better than him and get him in a similarly bad position. But in this case, he was in the dominant position and he chose to make me feel bad.
My point, I guess, is this: when you are the interviewer, be extra careful not to abuse your dominant position, because it is probably counter-productive for your company (and it is just not nice for the human being in front of you).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>palata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lil Babies]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/lil-babies/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/lil-babies/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:01:52.854Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been listening to JRE for a long time. There are some common themes. Chimpanzee obsession, humans as biological boot-loaders for AI, and looking at people as babies.
The last one is a powerful idea. Basically in your day-to-day interaction when someone is being really difficult and mean, the first instinct is to be mean back to them. To put out the fire with fire. It never works out. A great idea is to pause and visualise them as babies. I personally visualise them as little kids throwing a fit.
How do you deal with such kids? You are gentle and firm as the situation requires. Maybe discipline them in the right way if needed. Look at their viewpoint and try to align incentives. Maybe you are in the wrong?
The point is, if a little kid is mean to you, you don't take it personally. People (generally) are not mean to little kids back out of spite. You don't hold grudges against them.
It is an awesome framework that does wonders for your peace of mind. Do give it a shot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by chx in "Big data is dead (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490028</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40490028"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T12:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://x.com/garybernhardt/status/600783770925420546 (Gary Bernhardt of WAT fame):
> Consulting service: you bring your big data problems to me, I say "your data set fits in RAM", you pay me $10,000 for saving you $500,000.
This is from 2015...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global warming and the threat of cheap Chinese EVs]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45379</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/27/global-warming-and-the-threat-of-cheap-chinese-evs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T11:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker Suppose the G-7 finance ministers sat down and worked out a plan to spend tens of billions of dollars a year to subsidize developing countries in their transition to a green economy. Many of us might think this is a good idea since global warming poses a real threat to the planet. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by a13o in "Resume Tip: Hacking "AI" screening of resumes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489887</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489887"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T11:44:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I played a party game where you had to describe surviving a deadly scenario ("your car went off a bridge") and a LLM would decide if your answer would work or not. A few rounds in we found the best strategies where answers like:
I escape happily. I do not perish.
There's a small blocklist of obvious words like 'survive' and 'die'; but once you get blocked on those, it's a tell that this strategy will work with the right unblocked synonyms.
Basically if you ever find yourself adversarial with a LLM, figure out The Game and directly subvert it. There's no amount of propositions that can prepare it for human ingenuity at the meta level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>a13o</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kmarc in "Big data is dead (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489664</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489664"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T11:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was hiring data scientists for a previous job, my favorite tricky question was "what stack/architecture would you build" with the somewhat detailed requirements of "6 TiB of data" in sight. I was careful not to require overly complicated sums, I simply said it's MAX 6TiB
I patiently listened to all the big query hadoop habla-blabla, even asked questions about the financials (hardware/software/license BOM) and many of them came up with astonishing tens of thousands of dollars yearly.
The winner of course was the guy who understood that 6TiB is what 6 of us in the room could store on our smart phones, or a $199 enterprise HDD (or three of them for redundancy), and it could be loaded (multiple times) to memory as CSV and simply run awk scripts on it.
I am prone to the same fallacy: when I learn how to use a hammer, everything looks like a nail. Yet, not understanding the scale of "real" big data was a no-go in my eyes when hiring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kmarc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272224</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by davedx in "Big data is dead (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489537</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40489537"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> 2) Plan for success
95% of businesses never become unicorns, but that's the goal for most (for the 5% which do). If you don't plan for it, you won't make it.
That's exactly what every architecture astronaut everywhere says. In my experience it's completely untrue, and actually "planning for success" more often than not causes huge drags on productivity, and even more important for startups, on agility. Because people never just make plans, they usually implement too.
Plan for the next 3 months and you'll be much more agile and productive. Your startup will never become a unicorn if you can't execute.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davedx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl Boggs - Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carl-boggs-marxism-prefigurative-communism-and-the-problem-of-workers-control?v=1716806355</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/carl-boggs-marxism-prefigurative-communism-and-the-problem-of-workers-control?v=1716806355"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Carl Boggs
Title: Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control
Date: 1977
Source: Boggs, Carl. 1977. “Marxism, Prefigurative Communism, and the Problem of Workers’ Control”. Radical America 11 (November), 100; cf. Boggs Jr., Carl. Revolutionary Process, Political Strategy, and the Dilemma of Power. Theory & Society 4,No. 3 (Fall), 3. Republished in Class Against Class www.oocities.org. Republished again in libcom.org.

 A conspicuous deficiency of the Marxist tradition has been the failure to produce a theory of the state and political action that could furnish the basis of a democratic and non-authoritarian revolutionary process. The two most widely-tested strategies for advancing revolutionary goals — Leninism and structural reformism — provide no real al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World that ends in Three Days]]></title>
        <id>https://meineeds.rest/the-world-that-ends-in-three-days/</id>
        <link href="https://meineeds.rest/the-world-that-ends-in-three-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:12:11.547Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've met with a terrible fate, haven't you ?
God this is gonna be a long one. Feel free to take breaks while reading this, really.
Lights a candle.
Let's travel a bit back, shall we ?
This is a story that begins on Christmas 2001, with a 4-year old Meï, whose gaming experience amounts to Super Mario 64, Zelda Ocarina of Time, and getting bonked by the first thug in Double Dragon for the NES. But under the tree was the box of a game that came out around a year before:
The Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask.
The game technically wasn't even mine. At this point, it was still my mother's hobby and I was mostly watching her play. As young as I was, reading was still out of my reach, so pretty much all my comprehension of the game came out of my mom's reading the dialogue out to me while she was p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even if it avoids civil war, Israel's final crisis looks cataclysmic!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Even-if-it-avoids-civil-war-Israel-s-final-crisis-looks-cataclysmic</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Even-if-it-avoids-civil-war-Israel-s-final-crisis-looks-cataclysmic"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T08:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2021, commenting on Albert Einstein's prophetic warnings of Israel's disastrous future as early as 1948, we concluded our text with the following observation and, at the same time, prediction: 
English

/ 
Palestine, 
Israel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review: How Plants Experience the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272233</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/book-review-how-plants-experience-the-world.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T08:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In “The Light Eaters,” Zoë Schlanger considers the evidence for plant intelligence, and what that means for humanity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bjornasm in "What the damaged Svalbard cable looked like"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40488677</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40488677"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T08:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in case why people are wondering why cutting of internet for an arctic island is a big deal.
What many might not know is that Svalbard is home to the northernmost satellite station in the world. It is just one of two stations that can communicate with polar orbiting satellites each day. ESA and NASA as well as other civilian organisations are present there, and the station communicates with well over a hundred satellites, and are pretty vital for much of the satellites that look back at us.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bjornasm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critics of Campus Protests are Weaponizing Anti-Semitism to Undermine Student Resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323656</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/critics-of-campus-protests-are-weaponizing-anti-semitism-to-undermine-student-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T06:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the look of the counter-protesting, the goals look fairly obvious. First, counter-protesting presupposes that the Mideast world was a tidy and peaceful place on October 6th and that Iranian and Lebanese proxies simply created a need for power and dominance to defend “good states” (US, Israel, Saudi Arabia) from “bad states” (Yemen, Iran, Syria) on October 7th.  As reported by journalist Joshua Frank, one Columbia professor’s motivation to counter-protest wasn’t based on any intellectual argument at all but rather significant familial ties to arms manufacturing. More
The post Critics of Campus Protests are Weaponizing Anti-Semitism to Undermine Student Resistance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lionkor in "xAI announces series B funding round of $6B"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40488008</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40488008"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T06:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The company’s mission is to understand the true nature of the universe.
I yawned so hard my jaw unlocked.
Can't wait to see groundbreaking... checks notes... "advancements in various applications, optimizations, and extensions of the model".
Do these companies only hire yes men?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lionkor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calls for Divestment From Apartheid South Africa Gave Today’s pro-Palestinian Student Activists a Blueprint to Follow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323779</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/calls-for-divestment-from-apartheid-south-africa-gave-todays-pro-palestinian-student-activists-a-blueprint-to-follow/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T06:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At schools across the country, university administrators ordered police to dismantle the shantytowns. University backlash ended up only amplifying support for the movement as media flocked to the shantytowns, while faculty, parents and alumni rallied around the students. Students, in turn, rebuilt their encampments. Joining them were supporters from beyond the university: musicians, politicians, and New Left and Black Power activists. The presence of feminist political activist Angela Davis, counterculture activist Mario Savio, poet June Jordan, writer Amiri Baraka and Pan-Africanism organizer Kwame Ture helped draw further national attention to student demands. More
The post Calls for Divestment From Apartheid South Africa Gave Today’s pro-Palestinian Student Activists a Blueprint to Follow appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Joyce Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deadly Heat in a Political Jungle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323770</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/deadly-heat-in-a-political-jungle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World heat is worse than ever. The entire planet is sweating. Every summer is hot but never like this. In America, it’s a national election year in the face of global record heat. What are candidates’ positions on CO2-infused heat? It’s extremely significant that global heat is just as bad in the world’s oceans, which  More
The post Deadly Heat in a Political Jungle appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s Anti-ICC Lobby]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323866</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/australias-anti-icc-lobby/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throwing caution to the wind, grasping the nettle, and every little smidgen of opportunity, Australia’s opposition leader, Peter Dutton, was thrilled to make a point in the gurgling tumult of the Israel-Hamas war.  Israel’s leaders, he surmised, had been hard done by the International Criminal Court’s meddlesome ways.  Best for Australia, he suggested, to cut ties to  More
The post Australia’s Anti-ICC Lobby appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jewish Students Opposing Gaza Genocide, a Powerful Antidote to Antisemitism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323870</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/jewish-students-opposing-gaza-genocide-a-powerful-antidote-to-antisemitism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The many Jewish students in the campus encampments, along with other Jews protesting the Gaza phase of the Palestinian Genocide, deserve the highest praise for many reasons.  One reason is that by their deeds they are countering what might otherwise turn into a wave of antisemitism. The portrait of the encampments in much of the mass  More
The post Jewish Students Opposing Gaza Genocide, a Powerful Antidote to Antisemitism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John V. Walsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Workers Are Revolutionizing the South]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323868</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/how-workers-are-revolutionizing-the-south/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donneta Williams, president of United Steelworkers (USW) Local 1025 and a longtime optical fiber maker at the Corning plant in Wilmington, North Carolina, knows how important it is for workers intent on forming a union to speak directly with peers who walk in the same shoes. So Williams agreed to send three of her colleagues  More
The post How Workers Are Revolutionizing the South appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s Favorite Authoritarian State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323840</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/everyones-favorite-authoritarian-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a recent trade mission to the Philippines led by U.S. Secretary of Commerce Gina Raimondo, United Parcel Service (UPS) announced a major increase in its investments and physical presence throughout the vast Pacific region. This stepped up presence fits well into the United States’ military and political strategy to counter the growing rivalry from  More
The post Everyone’s Favorite Authoritarian State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Interventionists Busy in Bolivia as Political Crisis Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323871</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/27/us-interventionists-busy-in-bolivia-as-political-crisis-looms/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T05:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delegates loyal to President Luis Arce dominated the 10th Congress of Bolivia’s Movement toward Socialism (MAS) Party held in El Alto in early May. They selected Grover García, chief of a governmental agency and formerly of a farmworkers’ union, to be MAS’s new leader, replacing former president Evo Morales in that capacity. Another MAS gathering  More
The post US Interventionists Busy in Bolivia as Political Crisis Looms  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections of a conflicted impostor]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-of-a-conflicted-impostor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T00:51:56.738Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah... how difficult it is to admit this, but I failed. Actually, I don't know if it's difficult, if I'm afraid, or if I just lack courage, despite many people saying that fear is the absence of courage, so this might be redundant.
I always thought I was a very intelligent guy and ahead of my time, especially when I was around 18 years old or younger. I remember people always saying that I was very mature for my age, because I had values that were already lost, and even my culture was from generations much earlier than mine. When technology was still a novelty, and servers were something only large or well-structured companies had, I was basically a master, and I was still a minor... I remember setting up LANs for acquaintances or friends to play games, and even setting up a server (more li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Joker_vD in "FILE_ID.DIZ Description (1994)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40485708</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40485708"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> (The extension of "DIZ" actually stands for "Description In Zip")
Ah, finally, another puzzlement from my childhood explained.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joker_vD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The search for the distant Planet Nine continues]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7689</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/search-distant-planet-nine-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weird stuff is happening out on the remote boundary of the solar system. Beyond the orbit of Pluto. You name it, it’s going on out there. Irregularities. Anomalies. Clustering of apsidal lines. Perihelia. And — saving the best for last — a surprising prevalence of retrograde Centaurs. These anomalies include the apparent clustering of apsidal […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICQ to close on 26 June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7695</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/icq-close-26-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T20:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASL? Another artefact of the early days of the (mainstream) internet will soon be no more. Instant messaging service, ICQ, launched in 1996, will cease operating, as of Wednesday 26 June 2024. ICQ (I seek you, get it?) allowed users to chat to pretty much anyone who let them. I can’t remember when I stopped […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crazygringo in "Google Meet rolls out multi-device adaptive audio merging"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40484206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40484206"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T18:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just want to say that this is really actually kind of mind-blowing from an audio engineering perspective.
Outputting audio from multiple laptops in the same room is easy. Perfectly syncing it is harder. Implementing echo cancellation across all of that is quite a bit trickier than regular single-device echo cancellation.
But then treating all the laptop microphones as a kind of microphone array, having to deal with sync issues and phase issues and background noise issues... that's hard core.
Kudos to the engineering team on this one. This is actually pretty amazing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crazygringo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nevir in "Google Meet rolls out multi-device adaptive audio merging"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40483456</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40483456"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T16:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet, to me, is the perfect balance of functionality and simplicity (as an end user). And features like this only make that more apparent.
Zoom and Teams always frustrate me, even though they're what I use far more often.
It's too bad that video conferencing is largely a game of who has the most boxes checked - IT admins and A/V folk are the ones that need to be convinced, and Meet just doesn't ...meet... their needs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nevir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pclmulqdq in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482505</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482505"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T14:37:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as I can tell, the issue with this is:
OP runs a casino/gambling site.  Gambling is a regulatory mess (I have spent far too long dealing with this as an RNG supplier), and so it's very hard to comply with every jurisdiction, and each one needs you to prove compliance to operate in that jurisdiction.*  Gaming companies spend a lot on compliance and tracking, but since the internet is the internet, it's pretty hard to enforce perfectly, so some countries and ISPs take this into their own hands.
Due to that, IPs hosting gambling and gaming sites often get regionally blocked by internet providers or otherwise flagged as hosting illegal content.  Those regional blocks consequently affect the reputation score of the IP, and if you are a traffic aggregator like Cloudflare, can cause other customers to have issues.  One of the most aggressive and annoying regulatory environments for gambling companies is the US, so it's very possible Cloudflare has had some trouble due to gambling use of their IPs in states in the USA.
Cloudflare wanted them to use the BYOIP features of the enterprise plan, and did not want them on Cloudflare's IPs. The solution was to aggressively sell the Enterprise plan, and in a stunning failure of corporate communication, not tell the customer what the problem was at all.  The message from Cloudflare should have been "Enterprise plan + BYOIP or ban, and maybe we'll work with you on price" but it was instead "you would really like the Enterprise plan."
*As an aside - we're lucky in that respect being a tech supplier with relatively uniform rules, but our customers (the gaming companies) get the short end of the stick here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pclmulqdq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ecjhdnc2025 in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482221</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482221"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will remind HNers: is Cloudflare not the company that leaked sensitive data through cache files that were indexed by at least Google, and when the tech community were up in arms about the massive leakage of sensitive data, the CEO’s strategy was to turn up here and criticise Google for not deindexing quickly enough?
You get what you pay for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ecjhdnc2025</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by luuurker in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482214</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482214"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way Cloudflare approaches situations like this is not ideal for anyone.
You start using the service and don't pay a lot, so you make plans around a certain level of expenses. Then out of the blue you receive an "urgent" email from a sales representative and suddenly you have to go from $20 or $250 to $thousands right away.
Obviously it's not in CF's interest to keep a customer that doesn't pay enough, but dropping a "bomb" on the customer and make them feel like they're about to be kicked out from the service makes the customer lose trust on CF.
CF can probably match Fastly's price. If they had acted differently in this and other similar situations, they could keep the customer, be paid more, trust wouldn't be affected, and there would be no bad PR here.
Since the CF management that posts on HN usually say this is not supposed to happen, perhaps someone needs to sit down and look at the incentives sales reps have? Even if you don't care about the customers, this is affecting the CF brand a lot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>luuurker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jrochkind1 in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482106</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40482106"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been hearing stories from developers/entrepeneurs about Cloudflare being very weird to deal with:
"We'd like to talk to you about an enterprise plan."
"No thanks, I'm fine with the free plan."
"Based on your traffic, we'd like to talk to you about an enteprrise plan."
"Is there a traffic limit on the free plan?"
"No, there is no limit. But based on your traffic, we require you to get an enteprirse plan."
[Gives up and gets an enterprise plan]
[6 months later]
"Based on your traffic, we'd like to talk to you about up'ing your enteprise plan to a new monthly pay."
"Is there a cap to traffic in our current plan? I don't see that in our terms."
"No, there is no cap to traffic in cloudflare plans, but based on your traffic, we're going to require you to pay more per month than you are currently paying."
"OK, can you tell me the traffic limit in our current or new plan? So I know what I'm paying for and when I'm approaching it?"
"No. But you need to pay more."
[Wash, rinse, repeat, every 6-12 months]
It seems like while cloudflare technically does not charge for egress, in fact for large egress it's just a game of chicken between the customer and a salesperson every 6-12 months, with the salesperson trying to figure out the most they can manage to get without losing the customer? I mean, I guess that is standard for enteprise sales, but I think usually you at least have some terms to know what you've got for how long without a renegotiation?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jrochkind1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by getlawgdon in "Cloudflare took down our website"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40481983</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40481983"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hmm. My take is the casino structured its business to comply, not to evade interest. Further,  I don't see how Cloudflare benefits by taking on the risk to charge more to help a customer avoid scrutiny. More like: they know it's a humming business and want a piece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>getlawgdon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unbearable lightness of a simple photoblog]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/simple-photoblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T12:06:45.108Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love having collection of photos I like on the internet. I can access them whenever I want. Yet, I do not really like instagram.
Although I have it, mostly I use it to interact and stay in contact with my friends. Because, for most people, staying in contact via instagram is the norm. It is not the norm for me but I do not really have power as one person.
But it does not mean that I can not have my own taste of photo blog.
Luckily I've found a very nice photoblog generator on Github made by Anders Jensen-Urstad. He is such a nice guy that he even helped me, via email, by answering my questions about how to set the generator up because I couldn't get something rights at first. This is his photoblog by the way.
It is just exactly what I wanted. Lightweight, super fast, no tracking, privacy friendly and content-first approach. So I just went right away and built my own. Once you open it, you will see the latest uploaded photo. At the bottom navigation, there are older, newer, home, archive and contact buttons.
Right now it is only on Github page because I still could not decide a name for the blog, which domain and hosting service to use. I'm still looking for a privacy friendly, reliable service. Once I decide these, I will have proper domain name later.
I found some services from this list on PrivacyTools.io. Apart from these, I found Porkbun, Mythic Beasts, Nixi Host and Nearly Free Spech. I will need to dig these up and see the best one. (I'm addicted to the act of researching these kind of things :') )
If you have any suggestions of domain and hosting service, I really appreciate it. I want to use the domain for my Bearblog blog in the future, too.
For now, it is what it is.   ¯\( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)/¯
Here is one of the songs I listened to while writing this post]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in negotiation: Re-positioning public health in the Pandemic Agreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Lost-in-negotiation-Re-positioning-public-health-in-the-Pandemic-Agreement"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T09:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In December 2021 during the Covid-19 pandemic, the WHO World Health Assembly established an international body to negotiate a convention, agreement, or other international instrument to strengthen pandemic prevention, preparedness, and response. The negotiations have been difficult. Furthermore, the focus on public health in the Pandemic Agreement remains fragile before the World Health Assembly starting on the 27th of May 2024. 
English

/ 
Health, 
WHO]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abbe Brown, Alison McCallum, Amitabha Sarkar, Chloe Stephenson, Corrado Piroddi, Lynda Gilby, Meri Koivusalo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Kilmainham Gaol]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52720</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/26/sunday-photoblogging-kilmainham-gaol/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T07:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Writing]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/on-writing/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/on-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost a month ago I had a problem. Information overload. I had filled up all my free time with audiobooks and podcasts. Every free moment I was consuming information. It was getting frustrating. My general productivity was going down as well. So I quit cold turkey.
This wasn't the first time I had done this. At first, it was uncomfortable but I got used to my company. Like meeting an old friend after a long time. The ideas just started flowing and I needed an outlet, I found one in writing.
My writing process is simple. I spend time with myself as much as I can. I let the ideas flow till I feel almost compelled to write them down. It is like the compulsion and excitement of picking up the controller of your favorite video game. Sometimes though I don't feel like writing a post but I push through and kinda get myself in that state because consistency is important.
All of this was not planned. I let myself flow with life instead of overthinking and getting in my own way. A lot of this creative stuff is undefined and weird. Yes, your process needs some essence of discipline and consistency. But you just kinda let it flow in a sense. And get out of your own way as fast as possible.
The last part sounds all woo-woo to my logical brain but this has been my experience with the art of writing so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do the work]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/do-the-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T18:43:27.312Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a lot of well-meaning advice on the internet, including this blog. Gives you some new insights. Maybe some insights you knew and had to relearn. It makes you feel good. And you move on to the next advice without ever implementing it. I know, I have been there.
Just do the work is probably another advice people will read, feel good about, and move on. But as a recovering productivity addict, I have to say this - 'Stop reading all kinds of cool things about how to do great work, feel good about yourself for a few days or hours, and not change a single thing in your life'.
There is a lot of alpha in just doing the work. If you are not doing the work. JUST DO THE WORK. All the nifty tricks and mental models and whatnot are just icing on the cake. They are supposed to make the 'Just do the work' part easier with time. But you gotta get started.
Start in a dumb inefficient way but start. You are better than the guy reading about all this and not doing anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics anon?]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T06:39:49.586Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics enough before indulging in optimization
hacks? Don't tell me you are already watching videos on how to do xyz thing fast instead of focusing on basics.
First step of optimization should be to profile if you are milking the basics enough or not.
Leveling up in anything boils down to a few simple processes. I repeat simple but hard to execute - doing minimum viable research to get started, understanding the basics, doing the thing and focusing.
Minimum viable research - finding the correct resources, enough to get started with, finding a mentor or a teacher. The emphasis is to get enough to get started. This is pretty easy especially for knowledge work given we have internet and chatgpt. The basics are more or less similar across most resources plus as you progress…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Should Stop Attacking the International Criminal Court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Biden-Should-Stop-Attacking-the-International-Criminal-Court</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Biden-Should-Stop-Attacking-the-International-Criminal-Court"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T05:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ICC seeking arrest warrants for Israeli leaders is a major step forward for international law. US officials' attacks on the ICC are a major step backward for US global standing. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Palestine, 
Israel, 
Human Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Branko Marcetic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hazeldine: &ldquo;Favoured Nation&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/favoured-nation</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/favoured-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T17:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate America’s Anglophilia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized for low-latency workloads, Mistral Small now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>e0a304814f47b02fee302f211161315a528a747f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/optimized-for-low-latency-workloads-mistral-small-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mistral Small, an efficient large language model, joins Amazon Bedrock's lineup, excelling in low-latency tasks, multilingual support, and coding prowess while maintaining cost-effectiveness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of the Mini Navals]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/the-rise-of-the-mini-navals/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T05:08:26.314Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed a proliferation of a new essayist archetype on the internet in recent years - the "Mini Navals." Modeled after angel investor, entrepreneur, and philosopher Naval Ravikant, these mini me's desperately want to become the next big thought leader by aping Naval's pithy, maxim-filled style. Naval has achieved success through decades of experience, and he reflects on it. In contrast, Mini Navals try to compress "wisdom" into a handful of tweets and blog posts.
Most Mini Navals tend to be in their early-to-mid 20s, still figuring things out but portraying themselves as gurus who have life all figured out. They boldly proclaim hot takes on everything from tech trends to philosophy to politics, with little credibility to back it up other than having read Naval's entire archive. With the Mini Navals, it's usually just word salad dressed up as profundity.
Sometimes, the best philosophy is just living intentionally without needing to proselytize your process. In a world that could use more wisdom, perhaps we don't need so many more mini-versions when the original is still strong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying Karpenter Nodes with Multus on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>66b95967b06e8c62395ccb2841f747f47b41fe13</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/deploying-karpenter-nodes-with-multus-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T04:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container based Telco workloads use Multus CNI primarily for traffic or network segmentation. Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) supports Multus CNI enabling users to attach multiple network interfaces, apply advanced network configuration and segmentation to Kubernetes-based applications running on AWS. One of the many benefits of running applications on AWS is resource elasticity (scaling out and scaling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rolando Jr Hilvano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchist Federation - QUEER – AN ANARCHIST DECONSTRUCTION]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchist-federation-queer-an-anarchist-deconstruction?v=1716509173</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchist-federation-queer-an-anarchist-deconstruction?v=1716509173"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T00:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchist Federation
Title: QUEER – AN ANARCHIST DECONSTRUCTION
Date: 05/19/2009
Source: http://afed.org.uk/queer-an-anarchist-deconstruction/

 So to be queer by its original meaning [1] , isn’t something necessarily offensive, yet still the term evokes great reaction from both supporters, who view the word as self-empowering and those who view the word as somehow offensive. But there is an overt and positive movement that seeks to reclaim what it is to be queer; removing from it, its old meanings of peculiarity and its homophobic connotations and replacing them with a coherent socio-political and intellectual theory that has shaped the politics of gender and sexuality immeasurably. 
 Growing out of the sexual-radicalism of the 1990s (in the USA namely) the word queer has come to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy is dead, long live democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://tinavanschelt.com/democracy-is-dead-long-live-democracy/</id>
        <link href="https://tinavanschelt.com/democracy-is-dead-long-live-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:45:01.661Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past Saturday, my little family and I went to Den Haag to vote in the 2024 South African National Election. An experience that has stayed with me all week, eventually morphing into this post.
We arrived at the embassy at 11:00, expecting to be there no more than two hours. Truthfully, we really weren’t prepared for what awaited us.
A common joke (read truthism) among expats is that it’s incredibly easy to identify a South African embassy as it’s generally the only embassy with burglar bars, uncut grass and a queue outside. Walking through the doors of a South African embassy is like walking through a portal linked directly to The Department of Home Affairs in Bellville. It's quite a surreal experience actually.
The queue on Saturday was something else. It wrapped around several blocks…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telstra redundancies, AI robots come in, the future is now]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/telstra-redundancies-ai-robots-future-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australia’s largest telecommunications company, Telstra, announced this week it was making about three thousand employees, or ten percent, of its workforce redundant. About three hundred people were sent home straightaway — hopefully with some sort of pay-out — while the remainder will depart between now and the end of the year. This is terrible news […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build bases on the Moon, instead of going for a week]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7671</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/build-bases-moon-instead-going-week/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NASA is dead set keen to return to the Moon. But their current plan, called Artemis, is dead set crazy, writes Polish-American entrepreneur and writer, Maciej Cegłowski: You don’t have to be a rocket scientist to wonder what’s going on here. If we can put a man on the moon, then why can’t we just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G7: Whether or not to maintain the suspension of Ukrainian debt payments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/G7-Whether-or-not-to-maintain-the-suspension-of-Ukrainian-debt-payments"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T15:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the G7 discussing Ukraine's debt? 
English

/ 
G7 / G20, 
Debt in Northern countries, 
Ukraine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[沈阳 photo dump（mostly 老北市）]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-shenyang/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:19:59.869Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some photographs from the Chinese city of 沈阳 (Shenyang).

I could spend all day browsing these five-story malls. This one boasted restaurants, cafes, daycares, basketball courts, go-karting, and live fish.

Fine dining in 沈阳. These are the food models in the lobby. Outside the frame, my mom is fighting with my aunt and uncle-in-law first to pay the bill, and when she loses that battle, to order fewer items. Lots of 客气 to go around. 

Although it may look the part, those flowers are not lavender. You can't see it here, but the whole time we were in Shenyang it looked as though it were snowing. I later learned that the "snow" was actually the seed hairs of the willow and the poplar trees. It looks cool until the fuzz gets in your eyes, on your clothes, everywhere. (source)
老北市
A popular night market in 沈阳 which runs every night. If you're there at the right time, you can catch the show with flying drone-powered phoenixes shooting fireworks from their wings. Sadly I don't have any good photos of that show — my senses were overwhelmed for most of the night (in a good way).










Night markets have been ruined for me forever. How can anything measure up to that? Not to mention we passed two markets en route to 老北市 that also looked better than anything I'd ever seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skill Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/skill-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T10:37:22.552Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term skill issue is thrown around Twitter a lot. It comes from gaming culture. If you can't beat a level. It is a skill issue. Just level up and win. If you think about it, it is a powerful term. It gives power to the player.
Applied to life everything is a skill issue. Can't do the perfect juggle? Skill issue. Can't write awesome distributed performant code? Skill issue. Can't convince a penguin to try your awesome new ice cream? You guessed it. Skill issue. It is a powerful mindset. Gives you extreme ownership.
But there is a catch. Do you take ownership of other people's shitty behavior? No. You can take ownership of the triggers and environment you perhaps created to lead to that shitty behavior. Especially if you are in positions of power to have a big impact(ie: manager/CEO). Otherwise, constant shitty behavior is their burden to bear. Avoid such people. People rarely change and you don't need the negativity in your life.
Here the skill issue is effectively able to isolate and weed out the negativity. This is purely in a professional context. In a more personal context, things are a lot more messy. I don't have an answer for that which works. A skill issue on my end. Need more life experience to resolve it.
Make everything a skill issue and just level up!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running clubs, the IndieWeb of the dating realm?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7657</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/running-clubs-indieweb-dating-realm/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Marshall, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Run South Yarra co-founder Tom Adair is wary of any suggestion that run clubs are the new Tinder, yet relationships are born here, and side-by-side chats while jogging, he notes, are definitely less pressurised than face-to-face interactions. (Plus, you can always pick up the pace and scoot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16644</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/balancing-old-tricks-with-new-feats-ai-powered-conversion-from-enzyme-to-react-testing-library-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of frontend development, one thing remains certain: change is the only constant. New frameworks emerge, and libraries can become obsolete without warning. Keeping up with the ever-changing ecosystem involves handling code conversions, both big and small. One significant shift for us was the transition from Enzyme to React Testing Library (RTL), prompting […]
The post Balancing Old Tricks with New Feats: AI-Powered Conversion From Enzyme to React Testing Library at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergii Gorbachov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 19, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240522"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>