<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-16T06:32:26.450Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-16T06:32:26.450Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Stop Block Cop City!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-stop-block-cop-city?v=1721110116"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Stop Block Cop City!
Date: 10/25/23
Source: https://berkmananarchy.noblogs.org/post/2023/10/26/stop-block-cop-city/

Tire fire barricade at the AirBnBs!
 Throw a molotov at the PowerPoint Presentations! Dump a smelly bucket of shrimp on the peaceful protest! We’re going to Stop Block Cop City!! 
 Why? 
 Because I’m mad that they wasted my time with their awful presentation/book-report/thinly-veiled-business-management-double-speak that tried to sell me and a bunch of other anarchists a program of non-violent civil disobedience to stop the police training facility from being constructed in the Old Prison Farm. 
I had to sit through:
 Being told about the history of the movement in a few awful slides 
 …know your fucking audience. 
 Being told not only about affinity…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Cancer on the West Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328298</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/a-cancer-on-the-west-bank/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:59:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1979, I made the first of what would turn out to be decades of periodic visits to Israel and the West Bank. I traveled there for the New York alternative publication The Village Voice to investigate Israel’s growing settler movement, Gush Emunim (or the Bloc of the Faithful). The English-language Israeli newspaper, The Jerusalem Post, then reported  More
The post A Cancer on the West Bank appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ellen Cantarow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Selective Outrage” Towards Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328176</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/selective-outrage-towards-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Israel’s selective treatment creates a myth of antisemitism We’ve all heard the baseless claims that criticizing Israel is antisemitic. As simple arguments break down, staunch supporters of Israeli apartheid turn to more nuanced points to try and justify atrocities.  Sam Harris is one of the recent voices speaking about “selective outrage” towards Israel. Like  More
The post “Selective Outrage” Towards Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nim Thorn - Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nim-thorn-traveler-s-guide-to-the-acronym-wasteland?v=1721109436"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nim Thorn
Title: Traveler’s Guide to the Acronym Wasteland
Subtitle: Tankies and Authoritarian Entryist Groups in Philadelphia
Date: July 10, 2024
Notes: From the original post: A general, group-by-group overview of some tankie and authoritarian entryist Left orgs in Philly (though partly relevant to other contexts; many are national groups), to help more autonomous, uncontrollable rebels better understand and defend against their manipulations. Includes some reflections and propositions at the end (‘Anti-Social Social War?’). pdf for reading pdf for printing
Source: Retrieved on July 15, 2024 from Reeking Thickets Press

Freedom from money, jobs, and education!
PSL (Party for Socialism and Liberation) and WWP (Workers World Party) and ANSWER Coalition (Act Now to Stop War and End …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Childcide in the Age of Fascist Theocracies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/childcide-in-the-age-of-fascist-theocracies/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of over five hundred shootings during the July 4th weekend, reports indicate that “a Texas-based company has developed vending machines that sell bullets and installed them at a handful of grocery stores in Texas, Oklahoma, and Alabama, with plans for expansion into other states.”1 Violence has become an organizing and governing principle  More
The post Childcide in the Age of Fascist Theocracies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump on Immigrants: “They’re Not Humans, They’re Animals”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328283</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/trump-on-immigrants-theyre-not-humans-theyre-animals/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The June 28th debate between Joe Biden and Donald Trump was a two-pronged disaster.  Much has been made of Biden’s “senior moments” as well as Trump’s 30-plus false claims.  There is a growing number of “liberal” national media outlets, led by The New York Times, calling for Biden to step aside for a younger and more coherent candidate. Sadly, less attention has been  More
The post Trump on Immigrants: “They’re Not Humans, They’re Animals” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing Pleads Guilty to Criminal Fraud: the Continuing 737 Max Saga]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328277</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/boeing-pleads-guilty-to-criminal-fraud-the-continuing-737-max-saga/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing has agreed to plead guilty to a criminal fraud charge regarding the two crashes of 737 Max airplanes that caused the death of 346 passengers on two flights: a Lion Air flight out of Indonesia in October 2018 and an Ethiopian Airlines flight in March 2019. Though Boeing had tried hard to convince the world that  More
The post Boeing Pleads Guilty to Criminal Fraud: the Continuing 737 Max Saga appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prabir Purkayastha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We Love you Joe, but…”: Hollywood’s Advice to President Biden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328275</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/we-love-you-joe-but-hollywoods-advice-to-president-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something to be said about ignoring actors.  They assume roles, quite literally, camouflage themselves in scripts where personalities are created, and behave accordingly.  Given that they are paid liars, their political promptings should be treated with caution.  It is no accident that much the same thing can be said about the members of Congress. Given that  More
The post “We Love you Joe, but…”: Hollywood’s Advice to President Biden appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sex Workers in Chile Continue to Face the Consequences of COVID-19 Without Government Assistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328280</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/sex-workers-in-chile-continue-to-face-the-consequences-of-covid-19-without-government-assistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little over a year ago, WHO declared the end of the COVID-19 health emergency. The pandemic had disastrous consequences for workers, especially those in the informal sector. According to a World Bank report, the last five years will reflect the lowest figures for economic growth in the last 30 years: 40 percent of low-income countries will remain  More
The post Sex Workers in Chile Continue to Face the Consequences of COVID-19 Without Government Assistance  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taroa Zúñiga Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Trump Sweeps Rhode Island and Southern Mass.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328285</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/how-trump-sweeps-rhode-island-and-southern-mass/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent Supreme Court rulings were pretty shocking. It just goes to show how far “Originalism” goes in defending political parties where subscription to decency, sanity, and the existence of reality itself are optional membership requirements. Sammy “Ding-Dong” Bell and his “People’s Republic of Providence” Pwogwessive Demoquacks have never impressed me, but that prejudice goes  More
The post How Trump Sweeps Rhode Island and Southern Mass. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andie Stewart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Biedermeier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328007</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/american-biedermeier/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we apply Mark Twain’s observation that “history does not repeat itself but it often rhymes,” then at this moment in time we may well be inhabiting the American Biedermeier. The data are coming in. The public is tuning out. Vanity Fair called it The Great Tune-Out of 2024. The PEW Research Center was definitely  More
The post  American Biedermeier appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erika Schelby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This 2024 Election and the Metastatic Entrails of America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328295</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/this-2024-election-and-the-metastatic-entrails-of-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is as if we all synchronized our nightmares—or, rather, in a world of neoliberal austerity, we have run out of night-time horror tales and need to all share the same moth-eaten, unraveling, tedious bad dream. We have a tsunami of infected shit pouring mightily through our paper mache sea wall—a fierce, eternal heat wave,  More
The post This 2024 Election and the Metastatic Entrails of America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Year Later, Vermont Floods Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328290</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/one-year-later-vermont-floods-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year to the day after the devastating floods of July 10, 2023, Vermont was hit hard again. The remnants of Hurricane Beryl, the earliest category 5 hurricane ever recorded, met a stalled warm front to deliver a band of tropical, torrential rain that dumped up to seven inches across parts of the state in  More
The post One Year Later, Vermont Floods Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting Disaster on the Home Front]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328094</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/confronting-disaster-on-the-home-front/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There can be no denying that the U.S. is in trouble. The political party system has tied the country into a sort of Gordian knot. It has done so by allowing two aged men, both deeply flawed in their own ways, to command the two dominant political parties. In an election year that is bound  More
The post Confronting Disaster on the Home Front appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One is Irreplaceable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328148</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/no-one-is-irreplaceable/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m certainly not a political insider, and in times like these, who would want to be? My first vote in a Presidential election was 52 years ago and I haven’t missed one since. My vote went to the losing candidate as it has many times since, but at least back then, I could vote for  More
The post No One is Irreplaceable appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Map Can Tell Us About Greater Yellowstone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328156</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/what-a-map-can-tell-us-about-greater-yellowstone/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I studied geography in grad school. One of the basic premises of geography is that maps can show graphical concepts and ideas that might not be obvious with other forms of communication. The map of roads in Greater Yellowstone serves as a powerful tool, revealing a reality that many fail to grasp. Despite the protection  More
The post What a Map Can Tell Us About Greater Yellowstone appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Factory Tourism is Wrecking Greece]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328292</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/16/factory-tourism-is-wrecking-greece/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T05:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Odious debt and collapse of the state The debt-strapped Greek government is not defending Greece from Turkey or factory tourism. Turkey continues its long-standing manipulation of NATO countries while threatening Greece. Turkish insults and aggressive actions in the Aegean continue. The Turks have the audacity and insolence to advertise to their NATO “allies” and to  More
The post Factory Tourism is Wrecking Greece appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating development feedback loops with AWS CDK hotswap deployments for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>ce26d458d598d4737adde02742504651c450ef09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/accelerating-development-feedback-loops-with-aws-cdk-hotswap-deployments-for-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T04:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Culture Amp is an employee experience platform that provides the insights into employee engagement, performance, and development that organizations need to build a category-defining culture. Culture Amp’s mission is to create a better world of work. Developer feedback loops An efficient developer feedback loop is a critical part of an effective development process – […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Wright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoe Baker - What is the Proletariat?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zoe-baker-what-is-the-proletariat?v=1721098268"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T02:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zoe Baker
Title: What is the Proletariat?
Date: 2024/05/10
Source: Retrieved on 2024-07-16 from <anarchopac.com/2024/05/10/what-is-the-proletariat>

 In 1848 Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels published the Manifesto of the Communist Party. It famously ends by declaring, “let the ruling classes tremble at a communist revolution. Proletarians have nothing to lose in it but their chains. They have a world to win. Proletarians of all countries unite!” (Marx and Engels 1996, 30). The word proletariat continues to be used by socialists and communists today. This does not mean that the word is widely understood. Some people use it as a meaningless adjective whereby their ideas, attitudes, and activities are proletarian. Those of people they dislike are bourgeois. Others equate the proletaria…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On keeping a book past its due date]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-keeping-a-book-past-its-due-date/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-keeping-a-book-past-its-due-date/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T22:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I consider myself a pretty fast reader. I typically get through a book way before it needs to be returned back on Libby1. I get 21 days to finish a book (although my friends have reported 14 days), and that is usually plenty of time. With that said, I’ve never stressed about finishing a book in time.
Until now.
It’s taking me forever to finish A Court of Silver Flames by Sarah J. Maas. It’s not that it’s a terrible book but I haven’t been finding enough energy to read lately. I even switched to listening on Spotify Premium, and I’m still not done.
Anyways.
The return due date has come and gone, but I’m still not done with the book. For those who are familiar with the ACOTAR series, it’s pretty popular right now so the wait time is pretty long. I was on hold for several months for each book in the series… and I’m registered in three libraries. Doing another hold on this book means I’m going to have to wait months again.
💡 Enter the Kindle / Libby workaround.
I read my e-books via my Kindle Oasis and/or Kindle Paperwhite. To avoid the book auto returning on its due date, I just put the Kindle where it’s downloaded on Airplane mode. Voila! The book is there until you connect back to the Internet.
If you have a ton of books you want to get through way past your deadline, this is the way to go.
📙 Bonus hack: did you buy a Kindle with ads? Typically you have to pay $20(?) to get it removed. I just called Customer Service and told them that some of these ads are inappropriate for the minor who also has access to my account. They removed it for free. Now my Kindle screensaver is the cover of the book that I am currently reading.
You’re welcome, and happy reading!
If you have your own tips and tricks, feel free to reach out to me in however way you feel most comfortable!
🖊️ And while you’re at it, please say hello in my Guestbook if you haven’t done so already!
11/100
Reply by email
A service that allows you to borrow e-books (and other media formats) from your public library.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anonymous - Train To Nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-train-to-nowhere?v=1721078644"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anonymous
Title: Train To Nowhere
Subtitle: Call for a week of world wide action and solidarity against the North Bothnia Line, August 11th to 17th, 2024!
Date: 2024
Source: https://de.indymedia.org/node/377193

1. THE NORTH BOTHNIA LINE
Why aiming at this beast?
 This is a call to action against the North Bothnia Line, a railway just beginning to be built along the coast of Swedish-occupied Sápmi. This project is a continuation of several hundred years of brutal colonization of the peoples and lands in Sápmi. Extractive industries are thriving on the increased demand for raw materials following the so-called “green transition”. This makes them continually stress the importance and urgency of the train line. So do the Swedish State and the European Union. 
 The track will be used f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seventy-five of the best sci-fi books, but I only ever read one]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8011</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/seventy-five-best-sci-fi-books-but-only-ever-read-one/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might be a fan of science-fiction stories, 2001: A Space Odyssey, Star Trek, Star Wars, and the like, but of the seventy-five titles listed by Esquire magazine, on their best sci-fi books of all time, I’ve only read one. The Hitchhiker’s Guide to the Galaxy, by Douglas Adams. That’s it. 1984, by George Orwell? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions, great for IndieWeb, and, unfortunately, spammers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8007</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/webmentions-great-indieweb-unfortunately-spammers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T20:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Webmentions allow you to notify the publisher of a website that you’ve mentioned, or linked to, one of their pages, from your website or blog. Webmentions are commonly used in the Indie and Small Web communities, and have existed as a W3C recommendation since 2017. But Webmentions have also come to the attention of spammers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by modeless in "Run CUDA, unmodified, on AMD GPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40970717</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40970717"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T19:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of people think AMD should support these translation layers but I think it's a bad idea. CUDA is not designed to be vendor agnostic and Nvidia can make things arbitrarily difficult both technically and legally. For example I think it would be against the license agreement of cuDNN or cuBLAS to run them on this. So those and other Nvidia libraries would become part of the API boundary that AMD would need to reimplement and support.
Chasing bug-for-bug compatibility is a fool's errand. The important users of CUDA are open source. AMD can implement support directly in the upstream projects like pytorch or llama.cpp. And once support is there it can be maintained by the community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>modeless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Advanced capabilities in Amazon Bedrock and Amazon Q, and more (July 15, 2024).]]></title>
        <id>1fd3ff20bcccaf56da4bc38e70780bfd8ba588bb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-advanced-capabilities-in-amazon-bedrock-and-amazon-q-and-more-july-15-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T18:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As expected, there were lots of exciting launches and updates announced during the AWS Summit New York. You can quickly scan the highlights in Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2024. My colleagues and fellow AWS News Blog writers Veliswa Boya and Sébastien Stormacq were at the AWS Community Day Cameroon last […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275021</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T18:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Judge Cannon throws out Smith's case; Trump's would-be assassin appeared in a Blackrock ad; unelecting Biden: how's that going? Bird flu~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Top 1% now have more wealth than the middle class]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45472</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/15/u-s-top-1-now-have-more-wealth-than-the-middle-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[cruising]]></title>
        <id>https://passerine.bearblog.dev/cruising/</id>
        <link href="https://passerine.bearblog.dev/cruising/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it was hard to write anything at all on the cruise ship last may. i'd spend so much of the day walking that by night time my feet were fast asleep before i was. i also generally found that there was so little for me to say. i could only describe X, Y, and Z as “so cool” &  “so interesting” so many times before it got dull. so i’ll say it just once here! each stop was, in fact, so cool and so interesting. i do love good food, old architecture, and scenic views – europe has these aplenty. i just wish i spent more time birdwatching. (but i knew that that would be particularly difficult to do on such a tight schedule).
honestly, before my trip, i was 100% convinced i’d hate being on the ocean for such long stretches of time. and this is still partially true now that it's over. i’m prone to motion sickness and i’m afraid of a slow death. i ended up partially bedridden for three days, so i was right to worry about the former. i couldn’t eat anything but apples, and i threw up everytime i moved from my bed. it sucked, but at least i'm not dead.
when i recovered, i discovered that it was ironically grounding to stroll the topmost deck and see nothing but blue and horizon. and that it was especially beautiful at night, even if you couldn't really see the stars at all. instead, i’d watch the water long enough for it to look like a fingerprint. then, even longer to find the unicorns in the sea foam. i found myself returning to the same thought each time: in the grand scheme of all things, i am fortunately very small. i will never run out of earth to explore. nothing is never really just nothing, but nothing feels as good as finally being home too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Inertial Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275003</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/israels-inertial-genocide.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An update on Israel's horrific campaign against Palestinians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/operation-scripta-manent-in-italy-2016-2019?v=1721055788"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: “Operation Scripta Manent” in Italy 2016-2019
Subtitle: A collection of news, updates letters, texts and communiques
Date: 2019
Notes: This pamphlet has been put together by Act for freedom now. Check actforfree.nostate.net for updates in English.
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/SCRIPTA-pdf-2019.pdf>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Operation ‘Scripta Manent’ is one repressive operation among the many that have already occurred, and continue to occur, against comrades who dare to oppose the Italian State. The pretext here was of trying to find those who have taken part in Informal Anarchist Federation attacks since 2005, but it is also an attempt to destroy all insurrectional conflict in Italy and to cut off any solidarit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Putting into practice]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/putting-into-practice?v=1721051669"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Putting into practice
Subtitle: Adding to the conversation on anarchist activity in Montreal
Date: March 21, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=26705>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 We’d like to respond with our thoughts to a text “Mise en Commun” (Putting in Common) that has been circulated critiquing insurrectionary projects and perspectives in Montreal. We appreciate that the authors of Mise en Common want to elaborate similarities and clarify differences, and move past bad faith. We’re taking this as an occasion to respond and to clarify ideas that we’ve been reflecting on for a few years now. We’ll try to use points of difference with Mise en Commun as an opportunity to delve further into ideas and how they inform practices, rather than…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investments in Hospital Infrastructure Reduced Mortality in the US South]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275014</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/investments-in-hospital-infrastructure-reduced-mortality-in-the-us-south.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cost-effective investments in healthcare infrastructure disproportionately benefited historically marginalised groups, had long-run benefits, and complemented, rather than substituted, medical innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Rain & Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rain-fire?v=1721051421"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Rain & Fire
Subtitle: Statement from a UK FAI sector
Date: September 13, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=6304>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This text was written during the course of the growing European social war, and our attempts to situate ourselves in the context of that, whilst in the midst of rising fascism, complicity from most of the society and a fractured and divisive anti-capitalist ‘movement’. These scant few pages cannot express the complexity of the various situations being described in any great depth, but we write so that other rebels at the edges can know how it is for us here. As we were putting the final touches to the text, cities in the UK exploded and remain volatile. However this is not an analysis of the riots –…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Fischer - An Essay on Total Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dan-fischer-an-essay-on-total-liberation?v=1721050642"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Dan Fischer
Title: An Essay on Total Liberation
Subtitle: Marcusean Insights for Catalyzing Transformation
Date: 2024
Source: Building Multispecies Resistance Against Exploitation: Stories from the Frontlines of Labor and Animal Rights, edited by Zane McNeill (New York: Peter Lang, 2024)

 A 2021 study found that 56% of young people across ten countries believed “humanity is doomed.” The researchers rightly warned against narratives of “individualizing ‘the problem’ of climate anxiety, with suggestions that the best response is for the individual to ‘take action.’” However, they followed with the equally misguided suggestion that “such action needs to be particularly taken by those in power.”[1] Those of us influenced by Frankfurt School theorist Herbert Marcuse’s analysis consider…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-the-beginnings-and-early-ideology-of-cypriot-anarchism?v=1721050234"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: The Beginnings and Early Ideology of Cypriot Anarchism
Subtitle: 'Federation or Death'
Date: 2022
Notes: Anarchist Studies 30.1
Source: https://archive.org/details/05-anarchist-studies-30.1-pastellopoulos

Abstract:
 The article presents a first overview of the emergence and early development of anarchism in the Republic of Cyprus, utilising archival material. It contextualises Cypriot anarchism within the broader wave of political ideas making their appearance after the island’s de-facto partition in 1974, tracing the formation of the first anarchist groups and the circulation of early Cypriot anarchist publications. It moves on to briefly discuss three key historical moments of anarchist political expression, followed by an examination of early Cypri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1721049994"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T13:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)
Subtitle: “Cyprus Belongs to its Mouflons”
Date: 2017
Source: Retrieved on 23rd March 2022 from www.grin.com

Abstract
 This dissertation examines the structure of Cypriot anarchist ideology and the way it challenges Greek Cypriot ethnic nationalism, as it developed in the first decade following the partition of the island of Cyprus. It aims to contribute to the understanding of grass root political activity in Cyprus, by examining the early expressions of anarchism in the island. Ideology has been argued to function around the use of key discursive signifiers, through which the mediation of a fixed meaning is structured and social reality is experienced. This research…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[it might as well be you]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/it-might-as-well-be-you/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/it-might-as-well-be-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[read through pj's blog entry 'please let me know' recently and wanted to write a quick post in response! 1 

the brief answer would be that i live for other people. 

long one from here: when the future feels bleak, i keep going because i imagine someone could maybe benefit from my sticking it out at some point. 

ignoring the fact that i sound like a walking savior complex — it's more like, there are too many moving parts to write off. 

no matter how average or ordinary you feel, nobody else is going to know what you know the way you know it. nobody is going to do the same things you do, whether you achieve your goals or not. that you spend time reflecting on your place in the world at all means you're probably doing your best at living, and chances are you're gonna move somebody somewhe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275006</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T10:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our unvanquished daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As NATO Bids Farewell to Reality, Moscow and Beijing Pursue Win-Win Deals With Türkiye]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274935</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/sco-and-nato-summits-show-how-turkiyes-interests-increasingly-align-with-moscow-and-beijing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T10:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beijing Promises More Investments, US Threatens More Sanctions. Türkiye starts to buy into Shanghai Cooperation Organization security architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson:  World Shaking Up! Epic Political & Economic Earthquakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275000</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/michael-hudson-world-shaking-up-epic-political-economic-earthquakes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson reviews the commitments made at the recent NATO and SCO gatherings and what they mean for changes in the world order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Myth of the Magic Bullet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328182</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/the-myth-of-the-magic-bullet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While much remains unknown about the motives of the would-be assassin in Butler, Pennsylvania, one thing is certain. The man who attempted to kill Donald Trump believed his bullet would change the course of history for the better. Such thinking is common and is promoted in most school books that exhort young people to be better citizens by featuring the stories of national heroes who have changed the world. The killer’s belief that murdering a political leader could improve the nation was the logical converse of this mistaken principle. More
The post The Myth of the Magic Bullet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Messer-Kruse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning From the Edge of the Abyss]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328146</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/warning-from-the-edge-of-the-abyss/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:01:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two sets of events, which have important echoes today, precipitated the Cuban Missile Crisis.  The US had moved Jupiter medium-range nuclear missile systems into Turkey, prompting the Soviets to take countermeasures, including preparing to station missiles in Cuba and send Ilyushin jet bombers to the island.  Kennedy and the Americans were understandably deeply concerned about this breach of the Monroe Doctrine and the very real threat it posed.  More
The post Warning From the Edge of the Abyss appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gaza Genocide Deepens: The Reckoning Begins for the Perpetrators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328128</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/the-gaza-genocide-deepens-the-reckoning-begins-for-the-perpetrators/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early weeks of Israel’s massive bombardment and invasion of Gaza, the Israeli military was killing anyone who moved and destroying anything that stood.  In response to telephone calls from President Joe Biden and U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken urging Netanyahu to minimize civilian casualties reportedly he would respond:  Don’t lecture me, look  More
The post The Gaza Genocide Deepens: The Reckoning Begins for the Perpetrators appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Boy Biden in His Own Words]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328084</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/big-boy-biden-in-his-own-words/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biden held his first press conference in a year last Thursday. His staff had promoted the event all week as a “Big Boy” press conference that would demonstrate to NATO leaders and the American public that his inept performance during his debate against Trump two weeks ago that so terrified the Democratic donor class was merely an aberration and that the President still had the mojo to run the Empire. More
The post Big Boy Biden in His Own Words appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate and Political Heatwaves Kill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328158</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/climate-and-political-heatwaves-kill/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late July 1987 was a bad time for Athens, Greece. A suffocating heat wave embraced the polis of Athena. Hundreds of Athenians died. The government ordered gravediggers to work overtime days and nights. And to keep bodies chill, hospitals received ice from the fish market. “The Athens summer,” said Alan Cowell, a New York Times  More
The post Climate and Political Heatwaves Kill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Convulsed Republic: The Shooting of Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328190</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/the-convulsed-republic-the-shooting-of-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a nation, the United States, as if we did not already know, is convulsed.  Paranoid and divided, giddy with conspiracy and deranged by a fear of totalitarian seizure, hyper partisan and hostile to debate and any loose definition of facts (this condition afflicts the entire political spectrum), the only thing missing so far was this:  More
The post The Convulsed Republic: The Shooting of Donald Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. War Games in Pacific Seek Global Participation in Imperialist Maneuvers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328193</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/u-s-war-games-in-pacific-seek-global-participation-in-imperialist-maneuvers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every two years, the Indo-Pacific Command Center of the United States convenes the largest maritime war exercises on the planet. With over 35,000 troops participating, 29 nations, 46 naval surface ships, 4 nuclear submarines, and a multitude of air and ground forces, the Rim of the Pacific military exercises, or RIMPAC, is one of the  More
The post U.S. War Games in Pacific Seek Global Participation in Imperialist Maneuvers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kawenaʻulaokalā Kapahua and Joy Lehuanani Enomoto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Empowering Public-Sector Workers Builds Stronger Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328196</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/how-empowering-public-sector-workers-builds-stronger-communities/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wayne Creasy turned the corner in his municipal work truck, saw emergency vehicles idling at the railroad crossing, and instinctively pulled over to help. About 12 feet in the air, a railroad worker writhed in agony, pinned against his seat by a 39-foot-long, 1,500-pound slab of rail that fell from the claws of the crane  More
The post How Empowering Public-Sector Workers Builds Stronger Communities appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malawi’s Farmers Face a Precarious Future From Climate Change-Related Storms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328200</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/malawis-farmers-face-a-precarious-future-from-climate-change-related-storms/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the 2021 Global Climate Risk Index, Malawi is among the five nations worldwide most affected by extreme weather events. The country experiences distinct wet and dry seasons, so climate phenomena like El Niño can disrupt normal rain patterns and lead to periods of drought. The nation’s proximity to the Indian Ocean also makes it  More
The post Malawi’s Farmers Face a Precarious Future From Climate Change-Related Storms appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jenipher Changwanda and Freddie Clayton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Death Grip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328203</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/bidens-death-grip/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden reminds me of Jack Evans, a disgraced former DC councilman I’ve written about more than anyone over the years. Both grew up in working-class families in Pennsylvania. At the outset of their careers, both had a touch of progressive in them, as well as a touch of scandal. And for both, the scandal  More
The post Biden’s Death Grip appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the GOP so Paranoid About Montana Voters?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328197</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/why-is-the-gop-so-paranoid-about-montana-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s truly a mystery right now watching the incredible efforts by Montana’s Secretary of State, Christi Jacobsen, to try and disqualify voters who signed citizen initiatives from being counted.   Their twisted logic and faulty interpretation of the Montana Constitution reflects a deep paranoia on the part of the Republicans toward Montana’s citizens and voters. The  More
The post Why is the GOP so Paranoid About Montana Voters? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give Peace a Chance in Haiti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328096</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/give-peace-a-chance-in-haiti/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At 9:16 a.m. on June 25, a Kenya Airways plane touched down in Port-au-Prince, Haiti. On board were some 200 Kenyan police, the vanguard of the Multinational Security Support (MSS) mission approved by the United Nations Security Council late last year. Eventually, the force is expected to consist of 2,500 officers from at least a  More
The post Give Peace a Chance in Haiti appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelans to Vote on Continuing the Bolivarian Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328167</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/venezuelans-to-vote-on-continuing-the-bolivarian-revolution-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Venezuela’s 25-year-old socialist movement will be decided in the upcoming July 28 election. Venezuelans will go to the polls knowing that a vote for incumbent President Nicolás Maduro means no relief from US unilateral coercive measures. These so-called “sanctions” have been central to Washington’s regime-change campaign explicitly designed to asphyxiate the Venezuelan  More
The post Venezuelans to Vote on Continuing the Bolivarian Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter and the U.S. Left: Lessons for Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328165</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/15/jimmy-carter-and-the-u-s-left-lessons-for-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Response to Mike Johnston I read Mike Johnston’s article Choosing Our Opponent: Why I will work to elect Joe Biden in the Stansbury Forum with a mixture of curiosity and concern. Not because I find it surprising that he is going to campaign for Biden’s reelection, but because he reaches back to the Carter presidency to  More
The post Jimmy Carter and the U.S. Left: Lessons for Today? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ejiblabahaba in "We need visual programming. No, not like that"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40965329</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40965329"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T04:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone with a hardware background, I'll throw in my $0.02. The schematic capture elements to connect up large blocks of HDL with a ton of I/O going everywhere are one of the few applications of visual programming that I like. Once you get past defining the block behaviors in HDL, instantiation can become tedious and error-prone in text, since the tools all kinda suck with very little hinting or argument checking, and the modules can and regularly do have dozens of I/O arguments. Instead, it's often very easy to map the module inputs to schematic-level wires, particularly in situations where large buses can be combined into single fat lines, I/O types can be visually distinguished, etc. IDE keyboard shortcuts also make these signals easy to follow and trace as they pass through hierarch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ejiblabahaba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - The only possible administration]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-only-possible-administration?v=1720991591"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: The only possible administration
Subtitle: The question of cities
Date: October 4, 2018
Notes: “L’unica amministrazione possibile. La questione delle città”, “Vetriolo” #1, 2017
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=31586>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 These are times when it seems there are big discussions about the issue of cities, urban areas, about the possibilities of revolt inside them (even of living), of their reformability. Big discussions frequently focused on various topics relating to struggles carried out by many opponents, antagonists, often reformists, sometimes even by enemies of every order and authority; among these issues there is gentrification, a word not so unusual anymore, a word we now want to express some thoughts about. 
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should right to disconnect laws be scrapped because of lazy workers?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7997</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/should-right-disconnect-laws-scrapped-because-lazy-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne based Workplace Relations lawyer Paul O’Halloran, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald, on Australian “right to disconnect” workplace laws that come into effect on Monday 26 August 2024: Well, laziness is an increasing trend in the cases I defend for employers. Putting aside pandemic lockdowns where all sorts of things other than work were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding peace in settling down more than traveling]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/finding-peace-in-settling-down-more-than-traveling/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/finding-peace-in-settling-down-more-than-traveling/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I guess most of us have been exposed to the promotion of traveling by someone around us at least once in our lives. Like, how traveling around the world, seeing new places, having adventures and visiting museums are important and how life would be so bad without those.
Alright, I know they are not bad activities at all and they might be one of the ways to enrich our inner selves. But traveling is neither holy nor sacred.
In my 20s, I loved exploring new places. I hitchhiked around Eastern Europe, rode my touring bicycle along the coast in western Türkiye and went on numerous camping trips. Back then, these activities gave me a sense of freedom and the joy of meeting interesting people. Nowadays, these activities no longer bring me the same enjoyment.
These days, I do not enjoy traveling an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Assassination Attempt: A Round-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274968</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/trump-assassination-attempt-a-round-up.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iconic photo, the shooter, the venue, the thooting, cui bono, and some of the more humane responses to Trump's attempted assassination]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell - Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/long-live-ilya-romanov-cell-explosive-incendiary-device-against-the-premises-of-an-electoral-co?v=1720988282"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: ‘Long live Ilya Romanov’ Cell
Title: Explosive/incendiary device against the premises of an electoral committee
Subtitle: In solidarity with Monica Caballero and Francisco Solar
Date: November 20, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15603>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

We Are not Spectators but Enemies of all Forms of Dominion
 Today we wanted to give vent to a small anarchist impulse by brandishing the weapons of life and the ideas of rebellion. 
 As we are convinced that the status quo is being maintained not only by those who hold power but also by the servile attitude of those who tacitly support it, toady we decided to attack polling station 98a in the town of La Reina with an explosive/incendiary device. 
 The electoral committee is a piece of the democ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Scarblac in "How to Know When It's Time to Go"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40962886</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40962886"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T20:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started programming at 10 and now I'm 50, and right now it feels like I've reached this point -- it's boring, I have trouble keeping up, I feel the things work lets me work on are not important. Interesting work goes to younger colleagues.
The problem is, I have a family and finding fulfilling work that you have no experience in, in this country, at 50, is close to impossible.
So for now I consider myself lucky and try to rediscover the fun things in programming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scarblac</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-on-socialism-communism-and-anarchism?v=1720973639"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:13:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: On Socialism, Communism, and Anarchism
Subtitle: or: an imprecise definition of terms
Date: July 3, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 4th July 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 One time, maybe ten years back, I was on the DC metro with my family. My brother and I were happily talking about the feminist implications of GI Joe, because my brother is cool as hell, when a stranger looked over at my father (not knowing we were related) to complain about how I spoke. 
 “They really don’t teach people how to speak English anymore,” the stranger complained. 
 I’m not the world’s fighty-est person, but I’ve also never been the world’s least fighty person, so I confronted him immediately. “Oh?!” I asked. “What’s wrong with the way we’re talking?!” 
 He went on a tirade…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anna Beniamino - Right you are… if you think you are]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anna-beniamino-right-you-are-if-you-think-you-are?v=1720972888"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T16:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anna Beniamino
Title: Right you are… if you think you are
Subtitle: Reflections and updates on a trial
Date: March 20, 2018
Source: actforfree.nostate.net>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 There’s not much to be said about an episode of repression, after all it’s the simple cyclical occurrence of action and reaction – or even on how repression plays dirty – another well-known fact. At most these are just a few notes on the development of techniques and strategies. 
 This I’ll try to do. More than a year after the arrests, with the trial already underway, a crack has opened in the censuring bell jar and the court papers been disclosed in all their misery after the short report on the last issue of Croce Nera and the latest developments on the closure of investigatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell - Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ccf-consciousness-gangs-sole-baleno-cell-responsibility-claim-for-explosive-attack-on-vehicle?v=1720971716"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CCF — Consciousness Gangs — Sole–Baleno Cell
Title: Responsibility claim for explosive attack on vehicle of the Koridallos prisons director (Athens)
Date: June 10, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?paged=174>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

PHOENIX PROJECT
Freedom for anarchists of praxis incarcerated in Italy
I ‘Return of the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire from the ashes’
 Only in those moments when our tension for freedom is rejoined with practice do we truly manage to live anarchy, here and now. Unfortunately the dream we carry in our hearts is too great to avoid the risk of finding ourselves up against the monstrous wall of authority raised in defense of the State and Capital. When we really put our life in play, inevitably we end up confronting the hardness t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity - Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cell-of-revolutionary-solidarity-communique-for-the-12-13-january-arson-barrage?v=1720971539"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cell of Revolutionary Solidarity
Title: Communique for the 12–13 January arson barrage
Date: January 27, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3553>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

The War Is on
 Today more than ever, the fortification of Power and it’s attack against the internal enemy becomes an urgent necessity. Under the fear of the oncoming rebellions and the dynamics that have been developed , mainly in the latest years, the Dominance has to protect it’s interests and will do it. 
 So, we ‘r leaving in an unprecedented upsurge of repression and control. Their mechanisms of chasing the enemy are being enforced and enriched in both human and technical level, while their legal arsenal expands and becomes more flexible. The new ‘anti-terror’ law that states thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-declaration-on-the-sixth-day-of-the-first-ccf-trial?v=1720971262"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Declaration on the Sixth Day of the First CCF Trial
Date: 2012
Source: <interarma.info/2012/02/02/dilwsi_xristou_tsakalou_synedriasi6/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 According to your court indictment, Conspiracy of Cells of Fire is a terrorist organization. But words were never, nor are or will ever be neutral. Words acquire the meaning given by the person who uses them. We do not speak the language of the judges and prosecutors. We speak the language of the hunted who have refused the victimʼs role, the wanted who have not handed themselves in to the authorities, the prisoners who have not caged their will for freedom, the anarchists who have never kneeled in front of Power. Solidarity, Dignity, Urban Guerrilla, Anarch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - Letter about persecutory procedures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-letter-about-persecutory-procedures?v=1720971085"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:31:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: Letter about persecutory procedures
Date: May 10, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=4537>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

On the 27th of April, Christos Tsakalos, for the case of C.C.F. with the upgraded charge of the managerial executive, was transported to the prisons of Koridallos, after a call for appearance at the juridical council, where he denies to appear.
 Today therefore, Wednesday the 27th of April, I announce officially to the juridical authorities, to not “bother me again” with their repeated calls for my presence in the interrogative process, because they will receive my total refusal and my factual contempt. 
 There is not even a millimeter of dialogue to be shared with my judges. 
 As I have declared repeatedl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAFE Boulder - Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/safe-boulder-preventing-and-treating-heat-related-illness-while-living-outside?v=1720970438"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T15:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: SAFE Boulder
Title: Preventing and Treating Heat-Related Illness While Living Outside
Date: July 12th, 2024
Notes: We created this zine to hand out alongside ice packs and gatorade as a deadly heatwave swept accross our region. At time of posting, that heatwave is continuing east across North America, and more will certainly follow in the coming months and years as the climate crisis worsens. While this zine contains a couple sentences specific to so-called Boulder Colorado, it should still be broadly applicable, and we encourage people to print and distribute it anywhere that’s affected by extreme heat. We note that the advice contained within is not particularly useful without the supplies needed to follow it, and we recommend accompanying this zine with water, electrolyte powder…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc - Against the Logic of the Guillotine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine?v=1720969174"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc
Title: Against the Logic of the Guillotine
Subtitle: Why the Paris Commune Burned the Guillotine—and We Should Too
Date: April 8, 2019
Source: Retrieved on June 11, 2019 from https://crimethinc.com/2019/04/08/against-the-logic-of-the-guillotine-why-the-paris-commune-burned-the-guillotine-and-we-should-too

 148 years ago this week, on April 6, 1871, armed participants in the revolutionary Paris Commune seized the guillotine that was stored near the prison in Paris. They brought it to the foot of the statue of Voltaire, where they smashed it into pieces and burned it in a bonfire, to the applause of an immense crowd.[1] This was a popular action arising from the grassroots, not a spectacle coordinated by politicians. At the time, the Commune controlled Paris, which was st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Dining with Vultures]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-dining-with-vultures?v=1720968254"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T14:44:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Dining with Vultures
Subtitle: Bristol Anarchists & the UK Media
Date: 2015, February
Source: Retrieved on July 13, 2024 from https://darknights.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/13/dining-with-vultures-bristol-anarchists-the-uk-media/

 The purpose of this piece is to better understanding of mass media’s relationship to rebels (including anarchists of all stripes), in general as well as in the context of a repressive atmosphere in Bristol. As well as raising local specifics, it hopes to encourage stronger awareness around wider issues of representation and counter-insurgency. 
 It will speak critically, even harshly when deemed necessary, of some self-professed radicals’ interactions with the establishment – but not out of an impulse for character-assassination. Contrary t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274942</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T10:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our cool-hearted daily links/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efforts to Build Climate Resilience Do Not Protect Human Health]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274950</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/efforts-to-build-climate-resilience-do-not-protect-human-health.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T10:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Health and Human Services’ resilience policy undermines efforts to prevent climate disaster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: house martins]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52864</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sunday-photoblogging-house-martins/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my issue with online interactions]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/online-interactions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The longer I am off of any social media and not constantly bombarded with the language and digital mannerisms inherent to it, the more I notice how odd it feels to detect that kind of language in others outside of those timelines and feeds.
I am active in very few Discord servers and most of them are small, friends-only groups. However, in the few public ones I am in, I often see groups of people whose choices of words and how to express themselves, how to enter conversations, their tone and views make them feel eerily... unreal. I've thought about it, and the best way I could describe it is as if someone trained AI on the most active Twitter users. There is a specific flavor of overly cool, casually careless, sarcastic, flippant, at times vitriolic undertone to everything that is hard to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the EPA Hiding at the Landfill in Uniontown, Ohio?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328043</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/14/what-is-the-epa-hiding-at-the-landfill-in-uniontown-ohio/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T06:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Koushik Chowdavarapu.
THE TWILIGHT ZONE — Picture if you will the citizens of a small town in Northeast Ohio, facing a daunting toxic threat yet trapped in a maze of regulatory capture at the so-called Environmental Protection Agency. Not the citizens of East Palestine, though they too face a challenging quest for the truth about the environmental health threats they may face. But the citizens in and around Uniontown, Ohio have been trapped in such a quagmire for decades, subjected to a dystopian level of gaslighting from the powers that be in an effort to bury the truth regarding the ultra-hazardous poisons reportedly dumped at the town landfill.
The Industrial Excess Landfill (IEL) in Uniontown closed in 1980 and was designated as an EPA Superfund site in 1984, listed as one of the most contaminated sites in the country. Akron area rubber companies were the biggest known polluters at the IEL, dumping millions of gallons of industrial waste and chemicals in the ‘60s and ‘70s. But local citizen eyewitnesses have long testified that the U.S. military was another covert client in the late ‘60s/early ‘70s. This includes the IEL’s former owner Charles Kittinger, who came forward in 2001 to speak of clandestine dumping of three metal eggs of nuclear weapons waste he was eerily warned not to speak of.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What is the EPA Hiding at the Landfill in Uniontown, Ohio? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greg M. Schwartz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sex, lies and Videotape]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52862</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/14/sex-lies-and-videotape/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T06:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What to do when we can’t trust our own eyes (or at least, the videos we are looking at. I spoke last weekend at a panel discussion on Navigating Lies, Deepfakes & Fake News, organised by McPherson Independent. This a group promoting the idea of an independent community candidate in the electorate of McPherson south of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by williamstein in "After initially rejecting it, Apple has approved the first PC emulator for iOS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40958945</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40958945"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T05:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just ran genuine 64bit Linux on a non jailbroke iPhone!  I have waited so so so long for this.  Finally.  Thank you EU regulators!!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>williamstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wkat4242 in "Jelly Star – The Smallest Android 13 Smartphone"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40957274</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40957274"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T22:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the problem with this brand is that this "Android 13 Smartphone" will probably stay that forever. Updates are very very minimal.
I have their first jelly and it didn't even get the upgrade they promised.
Other than that, it's not so bad. Swype-typing makes a small keyboard still useful. But the updates really are the achilles heel here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wkat4242</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by munificent in "Crafting Interpreters"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40956186</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40956186"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T19:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author here. Seeing all of the positive comments about my book is really warming my heart. I appreciate everyone and I'm glad so many people have enjoyed the book. I put a ton of time and love into it and it's gratifying to see it had the effect I'd hoped for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>munificent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guestbook]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/guestbook/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/guestbook/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guestbook
Write me a poem, a favorite memory, or simply just say hello 👋.
 


    
        

        
Lovingly made with Guestbooks
  

Messages
  

____ 

📖 Guestbook Archive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ramblings and Saturday Musings]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/ramblings-and-saturday-musings/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/ramblings-and-saturday-musings/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It took me a while to get settled into this particular space of mine on the Interwebs. I didn't know what I wanted out of it, but over time (past few months) it just kind of grew into its own thing.
Notes by JCProbably started out as just a place for scrappy thoughts, and scattered notes. Nothing too serious. It was hosted on a different platform, while what I called my "primary" blog (titled: With Love, JCProbably) was hosted in another1. That one included my microposts that I labeled as musings.
When starting this Notes subdomain, I initially said2
I'm hoping to use this page as a more scattered note, a digital post-it of some sort, when I think of things... and possibly just start linking more coherent thoughts when I write my Week Notes to it.
After the May challenge, I started writing more in this space. By June, I transferred it to Bear (where you're reading this now), and I'm in a much more comfortable space when it comes to writing and blogging.
Anyways, all of this to say that I am also looking into (re)adding my short-form thoughts and musings here (to consolidate everything). I've come to accept that I don't need to always have a long-winded post about a specific topic on here.
Sometimes I really just want to write a few sentences about how I'm feeling, or ponder on some thoughts, and calling it a day.
These posts will be tagged #musings — in case you were curious (but probably not). And no, those will (hopefully) not be as long as this ended up to be. I'm also hoping to include just every day photos that are a little bit more casual3 than what I post on my site specifically for photos.
Okay, that's it. Seriously.
10/100
One tenth done with 100DaysToOffload!
Reply by email
It still is, but I haven't been wanting to go on there lately, so I'm not even going to link it on here.↩


Original post did not make it through the migration process.↩


Veronique has been my inspiration on this front, if I'm being honest. I love how she incorporates just daily photos in her posts. Go check out her blog and posts!↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm ditching spotify]]></title>
        <id>https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/im-ditching-spotify/</id>
        <link href="https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/im-ditching-spotify/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T11:17:37.602Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[spotify is legal piracy. you can listen to most of your music by just paying a small amount and most of that doesn't go to the artist. hell with the rise of AI, enshittification got to a level that it never has before. I just don't want to be a part of that anymore.
there is also another reason I'm doing this. having physical files of your collection feels great. you can take your music collection anywhere you want, convert it to any format you wish and use any music player you fancy. it is at times a bit time consuming but I enjoy growing my collection and not having to throw money at a faceless company just to keep listening to my music.

how I manage it
I download most of my music as flacs then convert it to opus at 160kbps. the ones I couldn't get as flacs stay as mp3s. I store them in an SD card and use poweramp as my music app. I am not really settled on it yet, so recommendations are welcome.
I use last.fm and regular old internet browsing for recommendations. I never really used spotifys recommendation algorithm to begin with, because i value a passionate music fans words more than an algorithm.
notes
you can also take a look at kit's post for an artists perspective on why spotify is shitty as a platform. kit puts it into words better than I ever could.
reply via email
liked this post? you can follow my rss feed for more. i'd also appreciate if you toasted this post below.  🍞]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274827</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T10:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our rebellious daily links: Night owls, Covid nasal vax trial, South China Sea confrontation Africa backs Russia, German shoplifting, France chaos, UK credit crisis? Ukraine Patriot batteries destroyed, drone prison deliveries, moar Dem Biden freakout, EU X censorship attempt, suicide capsule funding yanked, consumers rebel v. high food prices]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't think too much]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/dont-think-too-much/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/dont-think-too-much/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday I was watching a Swedish music documentary. In one of the scenes, the artist Errol (aka Eddie Meduza) says:
If you think too much, you go crazy. Take life as it comes.
True words — and all too easy to forget. We put so much emphasis on thinking in our modern society that the gut feeling, the inner vibe, has been overshadowed. We think like crazy, even in moments when thinking brings nothing but confusion and fatigue.
Thinking has an important role, of course. We can make great use of this ability to plan, prepare, and make calculated decisions. But often the best thing we can do is "take life as it comes."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by imroot in "AT&T says criminals stole phone records of 'nearly all' customers in data breach"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40952214</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40952214"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T06:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm no longer under this specific NDA, so, I can talk a bit about this.
It was well known in the wireless industry that ATT collected and kept the most data on all of the carriers:  7 years for text metadata, "7 years" for call history (I put that in quotations because it was rumored that ATT kept them indefinitely, but, there were technical limitations for restoring data that far back), and 7 years for the contents of the text messages themselves.  Verizon was up there as well, but, I don't remember specifics.
The carrier that I worked with kept only 3 days content of the actual messages, 28 days for the text message metadata, and 28 days for the call records for their enforcement database, but, they could get calling records and sms envelope information for billing back 7 years, and at the time, we had to implement sharding at the database layer that maintained the warrant database due to the amount of traffic that we were receiving from the calling systems and the amount of queries/data that we were sending out, in near realtime, to law enforcement users who paid $10,000/month for access to that data.
AT&T wasn't storing this data out of the kindness of their heart, it was a (probably small) revenue stream for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>imroot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rsingel in "AT&T says criminals stole phone records of 'nearly all' customers in data breach"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951402"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T02:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no federal law requiring AT&T to hold onto this data.
There's possibly a FISA court requirement (too secret to reveal), but AT&T has long been an exceedingly willing part of the gov's spying apparatus. It fed these records and Internet data to the feds without any court order, and only escaped legal troubles when Obama, contrary to his campaign promises, gave AT&T, Verizon and more retroactive immunity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rsingel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Sean-Der in "Show HN: 30ms latency screen sharing in Rust"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951316</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951316"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T02:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote this to solve a few things I cared about.
* I want to show people that native WebRTC players can be a thing. I hope this encourages hangouts/discord/$x to implement WHIP and WHEP it would let people do so much more
* I wanted to make low latency sharing easier. I saw the need for this working on adding WebRTC to OBS and Broadcast Box[0]
* I wanted to show devs what a great ecosystem exists for WebRTC. Lots of great implementations in different languages.
* Was a bit of a ‘frustration project’. I saw a company claiming only their proprietary protocol can do latency this low. So I thought ‘screw you I will make an open source version!’
[0] https://github.com/glimesh/broadcast-box]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean-Der</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simpaticoder in "Use a work journal"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951259</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40951259"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T02:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The benefit of journaling is not just reentry, but that you begin to solidify the mental model into a concrete branching of possibilities that is tightly coupled to the specific problem. Your work becomes traversal and mutation of this tree. Several benefits accrue: you begin to see gaps in the tree, and can fill them in. You begin to have confidence in your mental model, recovering the time you used to spend going over the same nodes again and again in a haphazard way. In distributed systems in particular, the work is often detailed, manual, error prone and high latency - with a solid mental model you can get through a checklist of steps with minimum difficulty and high confidence that you didn't miss anything. This ability to take something abstract and make it more concrete on the fly is a critical skill.
Perhaps the greatest barrier to using it is akin to envy. We see others who apparently do this without written materials, in their head. I think we see this as evidence of intellectual superiority and harbor the doubt that using an aid like a journal means we are somehow lacking in skill or ability. This is wrong. Using an aid to map out complex problems isn't a failure, it's essential, especially for problems in systems you've never used before. Over time you may yourself build up your expertise such that you no longer need the aid, but  that doesn't signal anything about your intelligence or ability either, only your experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simpaticoder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by trompetenaccoun in "AT&T says criminals stole phone records of 'nearly all' customers in data breach"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40950716</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40950716"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T00:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It surprises me that there isn't a single comment pointing out that corporations like AT&T don't collect all that data for fun. This actually costs them a lot of money, but they're legally required by the government. While everyone is blaming the company, did you not take a second and contemplate how weird it is that you're fine with the government (and now everyone else es well) getting a record of all your phone activity? I'm old, back in my youth we'd have referred to that as a dystopian surveillance state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>trompetenaccoun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by academia_hack in "CISA broke into a US federal agency, and no one noticed for a full 5 months"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40949629</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40949629"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T21:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until the US federal government pays civilian tech talent competitively, this is always going to be an issue.
Your typical hands-on-keyboard blue team engineer in federal government is a GS-12 getting paid around $68,000 per year (or $99k in very high cost of living areas like DC). They have expensive health benefits, 13 days of PTO a year, put a huge chunk of their paycheck (almost 5%) into a mandatory pension plan that consistently underperforms the market, and can literally go to jail for making mistakes at work depending on the statutory context they work in.
The best people in these jobs burn out fast and quit or they end up having to abandon IC work for GS-14/15 jobs (max pay is around $190 for those) in order to keep up with cost-of-living and justify their careers.
As a result, you have almost zero genuinely capable principal/senior engineers in government who have the authority to architect complex IT systems for security. Instead you get contractors who charge the taxpayers enormous overhead costs and cut corners wherever possible.
If there's one letter to write your congress person to improve government - my vote would be for civil service reform to attract and retain actual top tech talent. They've done it for doctors and lawyers (both of whom can get paid well above the $190k GS pay ceiling), but engineering is still not treated as a comparably skilled professional trade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>academia_hack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whyenot in "AT&T says criminals stole phone records of 'nearly all' customers in data breach"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40949181</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40949181"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T20:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T has 110 million customers. Let's be optimistic and assume that each customer only has to spend one minute of extra time managing their account due to the break-in. That is more than 209 years of lost time.
Laws related to data breaches need to have much sharper teeth. Companies are going to do the bare minimum when it comes to securing data as long as breaches have almost no real consequences. Maybe pierce the corporate veil and criminally prosecute those whose negligence made this possible. Maybe have fines that are so massive that company leadership and stockholders face real consequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whyenot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T20:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In June, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-07-12-github-availability-report-june-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: June 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serge Halimi: &ldquo;Victory Deferred&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/victory-deferred</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/victory-deferred"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T17:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[France’s new Assembly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deaton on labour shortages and wages]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45469</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/12/deaton-on-labour-shortages-and-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T15:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll ZEIT: Today, the debate focuses on the labor shortages facing many industrialized countries. Angus Deaton: I am always cautious when people talk about a scarcity of labor but don’t talk about wages. The argument always is: Americans don’t want to do these jobs, Germans don’t want to do these jobs. So we have to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Techninal Blog/Notes]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/techninal-blognotes/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/techninal-blognotes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, these wont be the traditional notes where you write down your understanding or something. No. Never worked for me. Too boring and I never actually read again. What works is just having a bunch of questions that I can answer again and understand. So thats what it would be. Do it with your favorite llm for additional fun but take the effort to answer yourself first. That is the point.
And for the blog part, I will write if I feel I can add some new value by connecting things or simplify things down in a unique way.
Technical Notes :
Technical Blog :]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Barker: &ldquo;Washingtonology&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/washingtonology</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/washingtonology"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T14:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the debate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jader201 in "AT&T says criminals stole phone records of 'nearly all' customers in data breach"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40945527</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40945527"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never got the impression that the market ever cares about data breaches. It seems most companies are rarely held financially responsible for data breaches anyway.
I would bet any effects you’re seeing in stocks is unrelated to this news.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jader201</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kibwen in "Arm Accuracy Super Resolution"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40944685</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40944685"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T11:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphical fidelity isn't the reason I don't play mobile games. I don't play mobile games because touchscreens are terribly deficient compared to a controller, and because the monetization of mobile games is invariably psychotic.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kibwen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[V. S. Lozovyi - Far-left agrarianist peasant-centric discourse]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/v-s-lozovyi-far-left-agrarianist-peasant-centric-discourse?v=1720782433</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/v-s-lozovyi-far-left-agrarianist-peasant-centric-discourse?v=1720782433"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T11:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: V. S. Lozovyi
Title: Far-left agrarianist peasant-centric discourse
Subtitle: Makhnovist movement
Date: 2021
Notes: Excerpted from Party-Political Peasant-Central Discourse in the Day of the Ukrainian Revolution 1917–1921: Ideological Types and Mobilization Possibilites. doi:10.36059/978-966-397-236-7/53-72.
Source: Retrieved on 12th July 2024 from eprints.cdu.edu.ua

 Left and far-left forces dominated the Ukrainian political space. After the February Revolution of 1917, N. Makhno expanded his activities in the south of Ukraine, which turned into a powerful peasant movement. At first, N. Makhno and his movement did not have their own political program. He was strongly influenced by anarchist ideas, but during the revolution an independent ideological search developed in N. Makhno …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by smusamashah in "WebVM is a server-less virtual Linux environment running client-side"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40940585</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40940585"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T21:03:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a few others
VMs
https://copy.sh/v86/
https://bellard.org/jslinux/
https://jamesfriend.com.au/pce-js/ (https://github.com/jsdf/pce)
https://www.pcjs.org/ (lots of hardware and OSes) (https://github.com/jeffpar/pcjs)
Mac OS
https://infinitemac.org/ (https://blog.persistent.info/2023/03/infinitemac-dot-org.htm...)
https://jamesfriend.com.au/projects/basiliskii/BasiliskII-wo...
https://jamesfriend.com.au/pce-js/pce-js-apps/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smusamashah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meryl Streep, Emily Blunt, return for Devil Wears Prada sequel]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7992</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/meryl-streep-emily-blunt-devil-wears-prada-sequel/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, this will be something. A sequel is in the works for The Devil Wears Prada. By the time it is released, assuming production starts sooner rather than later, the follow-up will pick-up almost twenty-years after events of the original film. That’s a long time in the fashion world. So far, Meryl Streep — as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The torture of being exposed to people who live on a totally different frequency]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/the-torture-of-being-exposed-to-people-who-live-on-a-totally-different-frequency/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/the-torture-of-being-exposed-to-people-who-live-on-a-totally-different-frequency/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T20:08:00.277Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some people around us who live on a totally different frequency, especially in the work environment.
They never shut up.
They always seek a chance to talk to you.
They don't let you have a peaceful and silent moment.
They talk but don't say anything.
They do not understand that we just need peaceful and silent moment.
They do not understand that we don't like them.
They expect attention and response.
It is hell when I see them around. I just cannot escape. I usually try to put my headphones on and listen to music at full volume. But this time, they wave their hand at me to talk to me - and in that moment I want to scream.
It does not matter if you give them very short answers and ignore. They never stop.

Because of this, I developed a habit of looking at the floor so that I won't have eye contact with them. Sometimes I close my eyes and pretend to be sleeping. It's so difficult to be kind sometimes. 

My social battery is already pretty weak and people who live on a different frequency are just torturing my soul. People like me should work at a cave or something like that. I lose my sanity when I want peaceful moment while having no escape.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rasmus Hästbacka - Swedish Unions in Crisis – What Solutions Do Syndicalists Offer?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rasmus-hastbacka-swedish-unions-in-crisis-what-solutions-do-syndicalists-offer?v=1720727902</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rasmus-hastbacka-swedish-unions-in-crisis-what-solutions-do-syndicalists-offer?v=1720727902"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T19:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rasmus Hästbacka
Title: Swedish Unions in Crisis – What Solutions Do Syndicalists Offer?
Date: July 8, 2024
Notes: Article from the websites Znetwork and Counterpunch. Another version of the article was first published in Swedish. Both versions published in 2024. Illustration below from Znetwork.
Source: Retrieved on July 11, 2024: https://znetwork.org/znetarticle/swedish-unions-in-crisis-what-solutions-do-syndicalists-offer/


Swedish unions are governed from the top down and are therefore bad at serving workers' interests. So writes Rasmus Hästbacka of the syndicalist union SAC. Based on his new book, he suggests how worker-led unions can be rebuilt.
 It’s a truism that capitalism is not a democracy; capitalism means economic dictatorship, which is most evident in our workplaces.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing software version consistency for Amazon ECS services]]></title>
        <id>804df1297f07a7ffb6fbd385fd1a1a2bdb03636f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-software-version-consistency-for-amazon-ecs-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Container image tags offer a user-friendly way to manage and keep track of different versions of container images. However, they also present a security risk to organizations due to their mutable nature. Without protections in place, a container image tag can be changed in a container image repository to point to a different container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces workspace context awareness for Amazon Q Developer chat]]></title>
        <id>27c05c55cfcfa7555a9de914dce5f0bcd0e5f0b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/aws-announces-workspace-context-awareness-for-amazon-q-developer-chat/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced the release of workspace context awareness in Amazon Q Developer chat. By including @workspace in your prompt, Amazon Q Developer will automatically ingest and index all code files, configurations, and project structure, giving the chat comprehensive context across your entire application within the integrated development environment (IDE). Throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Matos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chat about your AWS account resources with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>1ebdbeac0365214c30b3bebba744123a5e7c6ad4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/chat-about-your-aws-account-resources-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traditional way customers had to interact with AWS account resources was through the AWS Management Console, SDKs, or command line interface (CLI) calls. However, these methods do not provide a quick way to gather information about AWS resources without writing scripts or navigating thought the AWS Management Console. The ability to use natural language […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security report: 2024 update]]></title>
        <id>668ea1544f58a9000ada525d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/application-security-report-2024-update"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s updated 2024 view on Internet cyber security trends spanning global traffic insights, bot traffic insights, API traffic insights, and client-side risks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tremante</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euro 2024’s impact on Internet traffic: a closer look at finalists Spain and England]]></title>
        <id>6690086858eb3b000a367cdd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/euro-2024s-impact-on-internet-traffic-a-closer-look-at-finalists-spain-and-england"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we examine how UEFA Euro 2024 football matches have influenced Internet traffic patterns in participating countries, with a special focus on the two finalists, Spain and England, on their journey to the final]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[country diary]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/country-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/country-diary/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My apartment doesn't have power.
They're doing some kind of maintenance.
The air is hot and thick, and I'm pining for some AC.
Took the doggo out for our morning walk and stopped at Timmies to get a coffee and breakfast sandwich, then remembered I had to walk up four flights of stairs bc—no power.
K drove me back to the city last night, and as much as I miss being in the country...coming home to my own apartment and bed felt nice.
As I was falling asleep, I saw the tiniest of ants crawling up my arm, and immediately murder, death, kill for that little guy and of course I then googled what would happen if an ant crawled into your ear and nothing good came out of that.
I distracted myself by watching some ASMR and fell asleep in my perfectly temperature-controlled bedroom (K's apartment is a veritable icebox).
** his mom crocheted me a shawl(!!!), and I think my heart imploded. Nothing says i love you more than here...I made you something.
&nbsp
country sunsets & trails






the trail where I got devoured by an army of carnivorous mosquitos

out-the-car-window photographs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dtagames in "The Typeset of Wall·E (2018)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937960</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937960"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T15:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article's title really downplays how much terrific cultural analysis there is here. This write-up has great depth, not only on typography but also architecture, art styles, film, and music! Many links and reference images, too.
A worthwhile read that I thoroughly enjoyed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dtagames</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aroopchandra in "Scientists discover a cause of lupus, possible way to reverse it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937383</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937383"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was diagnosed with lupus a few years ago. My mom also had it and passed away after 10 years due to complications. My initial symptoms were severe joint pains, which made daily activities difficult. This happened during the COVID lockdown, which helped me maintain my job.
I did a lot of research and tried various treatments. Functional medicines and expensive vitamins didn’t help. I read about long-term fasting and tried different routines at home. I did several 1-day, 3-day, and 7-day fasts. During the 7-day fasts, my pain disappeared, but it returned once I resumed eating. This led me to believe that food was causing inflammation.
Previously, I ate a lot of lean meat and occasional red meat. I then cut down to eating meat once a week and ate mostly raw leafy vegetables the rest of the time. My pain would come back after eating meat and decrease over the week. I eventually stopped eating meat entirely and consumed a ton on greens, and within six weeks, I was pain-free.
I also tried Benlysta for months, but it didn’t help much. Vegetables seemed to reduce my inflammation more effectively. I stopped taking Benlysta but continued regular blood tests. After a year, my doctor agreed I could stop the medication. I’ve been in remission for the last two years with no pain or inflammation.
I hope this helps, though it’s just my personal experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aroopchandra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AegirLeet in "Second factor SMS: Worse than its reputation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937274</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40937274"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turns out ads aren't just annoying little acts of psychological terrorism that eat up a lot of bandwidth and computing power, they are also the #1 vector for spreading scams and malware on the web.
In other words: If you're trying to improve your security posture, installing an ad-blocker is one of the best things you can do. If you have less tech-savvy friends and relatives, I would strongly recommend setting up uBlock Origin for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AegirLeet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dools in "Second factor SMS: Worse than its reputation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40936560</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40936560"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A family friend of ours recently fell victim to a phishing attack perpetrated by an attacker who paid for Google Ads for a search term like "BANKNAME login". The site was an immaculate knock off, with a replay attack in the background. She entered her 2fa code from the app on her phone but the interface rejected the code and asked her for another one. In the background, this 2nd code was actually to authorise the addition of a new "pay anyone" payee, and with that her money was gone[0].
I have accounts with 2 banks, one uses SMS 2fa and the other uses an app which generates a token. I had thought that the app was by default a better choice because of the inherent lack of security in SMS as a protcol BUT in the above attack the bank that sends the SMS would have been better because they send a different message when you're doing a transfer to a new payee than when you're logging in.
So really the ideal is not just having an app that generates a token but one that generates a specific type of token depending on what type of transaction you're performing and won't accept, for example, a login token when adding a new payee. I haven't seen any bank with that level of 2fa yet, has anyone else?
I guess perhaps passkeys make this obsolete anyway since it establishes a local physical connection to a piece of hardware.
[0] Ron Howard voice: "she eventually got it back"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dools</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Some Radical Numerology]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-radical-numerology?v=1720703681</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-radical-numerology?v=1720703681"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Some Radical Numerology
Date: 10/18/23
Source: https://berkmananarchy.noblogs.org/post/2023/10/21/the-illegalist-number/

Illegalist Number
 There is some confusion,
 about the magnitude of revolutionary action,
 by individuals who live in civilization,
 and work,
 and pay taxes. 
 These individuals talk a lot about insurrection,
 and about revolution,
 and destitution,
 but seem in every way other than talk,
 to support the capitalist systems of oppression. 
 So in an effort to help all those who,
 by talking so much,
 confuse words with action,
 appraise the extent of their efforts toward their purported ends,
 we introduce the ILLEGALIST NUMBER. 
The Illegalist Number
sum of the damages done to the capitalist system,
through destruction,
expropriation,
fraud,
or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jimnotgym in "Microsoft cutting crucial link to Gaza, Palestinians say"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40936200</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40936200"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T12:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These companies want to become as ubiquitous as a public utility. Therefore they should be regulated like a public utility]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jimnotgym</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mysterious Slowdown in U.S. Manufacturing Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30531</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/the-mysterious-slowdown-in-u-s-manufacturing-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the twentieth century, steady technological and organizational innovations, along with the accumulation of productive capital, increased labor productivity at a steady rate of around 2 percent per year. However, the past two decades have witnessed a slowdown in labor productivity, measured as value added per hour worked. This slowdown has been particularly stark in the manufacturing sector, which historically has been a leading sector in driving the productivity of the aggregate U.S. economy. What makes this slowdown particularly puzzling is the fact that manufacturing accounts for the majority of U.S. research and development (R&D) expenditure. Despite several recent studies (see, for example, Syverson [2016]), much remains to be uncovered about the nature of this slowdown. This post illustrates a key facet of the mystery: the productivity slowdown appears to be pervasive across industries and across firms of various sizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danial Lashkari and Jeremy Pearce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by carom in "GitHub Copilot is not infringing your copyright (2021)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40935075</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40935075"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T10:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is missing the largest argument in my opinion. The weights are the derivative work of the GPL licensed code and should therefore be released under the GPL. I would say these companies release their weights or simply not train on copyleft code.
It is truly amazing how many people will shill for these massive corporations that claim they love open source or that their AI is open while they profit off of the violation of licenses and contribute very little back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>carom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antti Rautiainen - What Does Putin Want?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antti-rautiainen-what-does-putin-want?v=1720691537</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antti-rautiainen-what-does-putin-want?v=1720691537"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T09:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antti Rautiainen
Title: What Does Putin Want?
Subtitle: The Russian autocrat is not crazy, war is simply a necessity for his power and economic system
Date: 11 July 2024
Notes: The original Russian text was published by Autonomous Action. Translated into English for Freedom by Sean Patterson.
Source: Retrieved on 11th July 2024 from freedomnews.org.uk

 Shortly after Russia’s full-scale invasion of Ukraine in February 2022, Putin outlined five goals for his war: Ukraine’s non-alignment with NATO; a change in Ukraine’s government; a severe limitation of Ukraine’s defence capacity; the seizure of Ukrainian territory (with international recognition); and the lifting of Western sanctions on Russia. 
 In the first weeks of the war, Putin also had a maximalist agenda: the quick occupatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by martypitt in "An abundance of Katherines: The game theory of baby naming"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40934379</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40934379"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also good...
> Simon Shindler contributed significantly to the aesthetic
of Figure 7, but could not be named an author for obvious reasons.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>martypitt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dabiged in "An abundance of Katherines: The game theory of baby naming"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40934197</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40934197"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T06:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best bit: They recursively reference the paper to provide proof that too many parents choose the same common names:
> For instance, a parent might anticipate the name “Kate” would be a pleasantly traditional yet unique name with only moderate popularity. They would be wrong [6].
Reference 6 is the paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dabiged</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mos_basik in "Show HN: Dut – a fast Linux disk usage calculator"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40933613</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40933613"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T04:07:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something like that exists for btrfs; it's called bdtu. It has the accuracy/time trade-off you're interested in, but the implementation is quite different. It samples random points on the disk and finds out what file path they belong to. The longer it runs the more accurate it gets. The readme is good at explaining why this approach makes sense for btrfs and what its limitations are.
https://github.com/CyberShadow/btdu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mos_basik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by matthewmcg in "An abundance of Katherines: The game theory of baby naming"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40933462</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40933462"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T03:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author listing: Katy Blumer, Kate Donahue, Katie Fritz, Kate Ivanovich, Katherine Lee, Katie Luo, Cathy Meng, Katie Van Koevering
For people unfamiliar with common English names, all of the authors have first names similar to or derived from Katherine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>matthewmcg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warzone Distro, Susaron 4 - MORE THAN JUST A DIET]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-more-than-just-a-diet?v=1720659191</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-more-than-just-a-diet?v=1720659191"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Warzone Distro, Susaron 4
Title: MORE THAN JUST A DIET
Subtitle: A Conversation Between Warzone Distro & the Susaron 4
Date: July 7 2024
Source: https://warzonedistro.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/04/more-than-just-a-diet-a-conversation-between-warzone-distro-the-susaron-4/

So first and foremost, could you give us and the readers an update? Last many of us heard, one of you was released.
 So for those who don’t already know about our case and a small update: 
 On November 3, 2022 we four comrades were arrested, accused of the arson attack to the meat company Susaron, a national industry that has been supplying the whole country with beef, pork and poultry meat for years. 
 On November 4, we were remanded in custody for the duration of the investigation. Accused of burning six trucks, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics (Continued)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics-continued?v=1720657195</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics-continued?v=1720657195"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics (Continued)
Subtitle: Problem of "Anjin" (安 心, Peace of Mind)
Date: 1965
Source: Retrieved on 07/10/2024 from https://noselvesnomasters.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/hakugen_ethics_2.pdf

 By "Anjin" is meant here spiritual calmness created by Prajna. Prajna is a unique intuition that sees the true nature of things as they are (Yathabhutam). "Zazen-shin" (坐 禅 箴, Instruction in Zazen) by Dogen (1200 -1253) reads: "A bird flies as a bird does; a fish swims likes a fish!" The essence of things seen by Prajna or Yathatathyadarsana (如 実 見, seeing into the truth as it is) is named "Suchness" (tathata) or "Emptiness" (sunyata), because it is beyond our daily expression which is the result of discriminative consciousness …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atombender in "Scientists discover a cause of lupus, possible way to reverse it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40932199</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40932199"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T22:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AhR), which is key to this discovery, appears to be super relevant to psoriasis, another autoimmune disease.
AhR has been known for a long time, but it seems it's been somewhat mysterious until a series of recent breakthroughs. In 2022, an AhR inhibitor called tapinarof, sold as VTAMA, was launched, and has shown itself to be one of the most effective treatments for psoriasis to date. It's also unique in that it appears to have the ability to bring lasting remission. In the main clinical trial, patients who used VTAMA for one year and then stopped had a mean remission duration of 4 months until their psoriasis returned. That is unheard of for any topical medication used on psoriasis.
Blocking AhR has also shown promise in treating MS [1].
I haven't read the lupus paper, but often with papers like these, the "cause" turns out not to be the actual origin, but some cytokine or other protein that is more disease-specific than current drug targets. This lupus discovery appears to identify an imbalance that may be compensated for, but we still don't know what triggers the imbalance in the first place.
In some cases diseases turn out to be a genetic fault, but my money is on pathogens acting as the initial triggering event, which then spins the immune system into a vicious cycle of autoimmunity. In psoriasis we see this with strep bacteria, for example, but the exact mechanisms are not well understood. However, the mechanism that makes psoriasis chronic has been identified, a type of T-cell called a tissue-resident memory (TRM) T-cell. This type of cell acts as a kind of biological memory for infections.
[1] https://newsroom.uvahealth.com/2023/02/15/multiple-sclerosis...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atombender</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 07, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240710</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240710"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spellcheck, autocorrect: the end of Notepad as a simple text editor]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7981</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/spellcheck-autocorrect-end-notepad-simple-text-editor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s go back in time. Way back in time. To about this time in 2000. I had, or was just about, to start my first job as a web designer, at an exciting, multidisciplinary design studio, on Sydney’s trendy urban fringe. Ok: Surry Hills. I’m pleased to say I was headhunted into the role, thanks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taming the tail utilization of ads inference at Meta scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21421</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/10/production-engineering/tail-utilization-ads-inference-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T20:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tail utilization is a significant system issue and a major factor in overload-related failures and low compute utilization. The tail utilization optimizations at Meta have had a profound impact on model serving capacity footprint and reliability.  Failure rates, which are mostly timeout errors, were reduced by two-thirds; the compute footprint delivered 35% more work for [...]
Read More...
The post Taming the tail utilization of ads inference at Meta scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wsay in "AMD to buy Silo AI for $665M"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40931097</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40931097"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T20:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who has designed and taught those courses, my experience (admittedly only one persons) is that you pick what will work with the least hassle - because you'll have plenty of hassle elsewhere and probably no real time to deal with any of it without making more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wsay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by j1elo in "Zed on Linux Is Here"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40930865</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40930865"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on the same camp, but in the end it turns out we were not putting it to the actual, real, hard-world test.
VSCode is very fast for me, when I open it in the morning and just starting my day.
But once I've opened the main project and 7 support library's projects, and I'm in a video-call on Chrome sharing my screen (which is something that eats CPU for breakfast), and I'm live-debugging a difficult to reproduce scenario while changing code on the fly, then the test conditions are really set up where differences between slow/heavy and fast/lightweight software can be noticed.
Things like slowness in syntax highlighting, or jankyness when opening different files. Not to mention what happened when I wanted to show the step-by-step debugging of the software to my colleagues.
In summary: our modern computer's sheer power are camouflaging poor software performance. The difference between using native and Electron apps, is a huge reduction in the upper limit of how many things you can do at the same time in your machine, or having a lower ceiling on how many heavy-load work tasks your system can be doing before it breaks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>j1elo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sfink in "Vision language models are blind"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40930402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40930402"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T19:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A human would need to trace the cable. An LLM may just be responding based on (1) the fact that you're asking about the clip in the first place, and that commonly happens when there's something wrong; and (2) that this is a very common failure mode. This is supported by it bringing up the "never saddle a dead horse" mnemonic, which suggests the issue is common.
After you fix it, you should try asking the same questions!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sfink</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The conjuncture in the crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-conjuncture-in-the-crisis</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-conjuncture-in-the-crisis"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T18:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Aaranchiya Subhai!” (‘Await Good News') read posters plastered across the country recently. It was the build-up to Ranil Wickremesinghe's televised speech on June 26, passing off a bad deal with official creditors on debt servicing as “Sri Lanka has won”. 
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Crisis, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector search for Amazon MemoryDB is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>a2931bd0421d69f5d03ea0b81d6deb2d21e7adfa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/vector-search-for-amazon-memorydb-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Store, index, retrieve, and search vectors with in-memory performance for use cases like retrieval augmentation, semantic caching, and anomaly detection through single-digit millisecond queries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build enterprise-grade applications with natural language using AWS App Studio (preview)]]></title>
        <id>675e924e6be607327f2b94aa9a414b0452cc18b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-custom-business-applications-without-cloud-expertise-using-aws-app-studio-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effortlessly build apps with AI-powered low-code tools, enabling organizations to create secure custom apps in minutes without dev teams - streamlining processes like claims, inventory, and approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Apps, now generally available, enables users to build their own generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>58d223451397f47b42448e9f3d0eb7a68ab67077</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-apps-now-generally-available-enables-users-to-build-their-own-generative-ai-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craft generative AI apps from conversations using natural language and approved data sources. Customize securely shared apps, specifying data sources per card and new APIs for programmatic app management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize Amazon Q Developer (in your IDE) with your private code base]]></title>
        <id>dbb8742329cd1fae053e5dd3ea9c6f968b17483f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/customize-amazon-q-developer-in-your-ide-with-your-private-code-base/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock hyper-relevant code suggestions tailored to your codebase; enhance productivity with Amazon Q Developer's private customization while maintaining robust data privacy and security standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock now support memory retention and code interpretation (preview)]]></title>
        <id>cb2425b75e646718c827c993d8716db44573e98a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/agents-for-amazon-bedrock-now-support-memory-retention-and-code-interpretation-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock now offer Memory to retain user context and Code Interpreter to dynamically execute code snippets—whether for data analysis, visualization, or complex problem-solving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Decision-Making in a Fragmented Space: Spotify In-Car Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7142</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/07/technical-decision-making-in-a-fragmented-space-spotify-in-car-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Car rides have become connected and interactive these days with drivers jamming to music or catching up on podcasts or [...]
The post Technical Decision-Making in a Fragmented Space: Spotify In-Car Case Study appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock can now detect hallucinations and safeguard apps built using custom or third-party FMs]]></title>
        <id>e71f10193867cd708459006c696412bbd9e25212</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/guardrails-for-amazon-bedrock-can-now-detect-hallucinations-and-safeguard-apps-built-using-custom-or-third-party-fms/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock adds hallucination detection and an independent API to fortify generative AI applications with customized guardrails across any model, ensuring responsible and trustworthy outputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports additional data connectors (in preview)]]></title>
        <id>d1ac6c04af654f43a3f18f82c30276aa6defb928</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-additional-data-connectors-in-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance company knowledge bases with new Amazon Bedrock connectors for Confluence, Salesforce, SharePoint, and web domains - empowering RAG models with contextual data for more accurate and relevant responses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Q Developer in SageMaker Studio to streamline ML workflows]]></title>
        <id>2f43e4416aa370a33fa9f2f85b61010b3aa3c5d8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-q-developer-in-sagemaker-studio-to-streamline-ml-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your ML workflows with this generative AI assistant providing tailored guidance, code generation, and error troubleshooting, to build, train, and deploy models efficiently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: Thanks to a massive mobilization of the Left the Far Right cannot control the government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-Thanks-to-a-massive-mobilization-of-the-Left-the-Far-Right-cannot</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-Thanks-to-a-massive-mobilization-of-the-Left-the-Far-Right-cannot"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the results of the parliamentary elections in France on 7 July 2024? 
English

/ 
France, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/life-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/life-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enter your email if you'd like to get inside our overnight momentum trading chat for a free month.
I started writing about Going Infinite about the highly autistic Sam Bankman-Fried, Alameda Research, FTX and its downfall. However, I couldn't do it justice. I recommend picking up the book and reading it for yourself. FWIW, after reading it, your pov should remain the same of "crypto is highly retarded".
Instead of going down that rabbit hole, I decided to go for a feel-good post with a little update since deciding to step away from my former profession...
Okay, so I left on April 3rd, 2024 so it's been a total of 97 days and during that time I have:
Severely reduced the stress and anxiety I was dealing with day to day by no longer making my life revolve solely around work.
Started to enjoy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grammar aggression]]></title>
        <id>https://junejuice.bearblog.dev/grammar-aggression/</id>
        <link href="https://junejuice.bearblog.dev/grammar-aggression/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[you sound so aggressively passionate about grammar. i get it. don't worry. being passionate about something you want everyone to follow through. order.
and then there's these people who are going against that order yuck
oh no ! no ! no ! /stomps three times i'll curse you out! >:(
or
oh no the world will end if i don't use grammar right. /dramatically flops on the ground tongue lolling to the side
come on now, don't get your knickers in a twist
let people write what they want, post what they want and however they want. because guess what?
it's their blog /dramatic gasp
the reader also, also, guess again, have the choice to click away. shocker
also don't cuss people out that's not nice
read original post here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Zaraz adds support for server-side rendering of X and Instagram embeds]]></title>
        <id>667d9546a4598c000bd7062b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/zaraz-supports-server-side-rendering-of-embeds"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce Cloudflare Zaraz support for server-side rendering of embeds from X and Instagram. This allows for secure, privacy-preserving, and performant embedding without third-party JavaScript or cookies, enhancing security, privacy, and performance on your website]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yair Dovrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s approach to machine learning prediction robustness]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21437</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/10/data-infrastructure/machine-learning-ml-prediction-robustness-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s advertising business leverages large-scale machine learning (ML) recommendation models that power millions of ads recommendations per second across Meta’s family of apps. Maintaining reliability of these ML systems helps ensure the highest level of service and uninterrupted benefit delivery to our users and advertisers. To minimize disruptions and ensure our ML systems are intrinsically [...]
Read More...
The post Meta’s approach to machine learning prediction robustness appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Some Zapatista Principles & Practices...]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-zapatista-principles-practices?v=1720605560</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-zapatista-principles-practices?v=1720605560"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Some Zapatista Principles & Practices...
Date: 2009
Source: Scanned from “Sharing Leadership Series Handout 5.6.09”

 The Zapatista indigenous movement in Chiapas, México has summarized many of their principles into short, accessible sayings that convey big ideas about a different way of leading and building power, which contrast greatly with repressive/oppressive methods of holding power and authority. 
Mandar Obedeciendo (Lead by Obeying)
 PRINCIPLE: True leaders follow the will of the people, the desires of the larger community. 
 PRACTICE: This principle challenges authoritarianism in the communities, and representatives who are not accountable to the widespread desires of the community will be ousted from their positions. In many of the communities, an oversig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TheOffer.txt]]></title>
        <id>https://library.xandra.cc/the-offer/</id>
        <link href="https://library.xandra.cc/the-offer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're Buying a House
i am absolutely exploding inside with this news, but i have no way to scream it, so this will have to do.
we've put an offer in on a house on sunday, and they accepted it today! i cannot believe it! i cried all the two hours it took for us to get home; partially because this is a dream that i have worked so hard for and never thought i'd actually get.
the house is deeply within our budget, thank goodness; but it's pushing the limits of commute for my boyfriend, which is unfortunate. i wish it was still affordable to live within reasonable commuting distance of a major city like seattle, but i'm just so thankful that we're staying in the pacific northwest. i'm really loving every second of being here, and it feels as though i was always meant to be here in this moment—i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - A Short and Incomplete Guide For New Activists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-a-short-and-incomplete-guide-for-new-activists?v=1720577930</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-a-short-and-incomplete-guide-for-new-activists?v=1720577930"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: A Short and Incomplete Guide For New Activists
Subtitle: or: how to get started by getting started
Date: May 22, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 4th July 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 A couple weeks ago, I was talking to my friends who run the podcast It Could Happen Here. “Summer is coming, and an awful lot of people are newly radicalized. You all should put out an episode about what the next steps are,” I told them. 
 “Perfect,” someone replied. “Write it and record it by May 20th.” 
 So I wrote a short and incomplete guide for new activists. You can hear me present it in audio format if you’d like. 
 I’m coming with my own biases which I want to get out right up front: I’m an anarchist, and it’s also been decades since I broke into the movement, beca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - The Direct Urgency of Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-the-direct-urgency-of-attack?v=1720577766</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-the-direct-urgency-of-attack?v=1720577766"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: The Direct Urgency of Attack
Date: 2013
Notes: A contribution by the CCF member, Christos Tsakalos, to the Nihilistic March zine and the counter-information blog Parabellum. Continuing the conversation, started by Italian comrade Nicola Gai. 
 Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2014/02/13/ellada-amesh-anagkaiothta-ths-epithsis-chts/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. The miracle workers of social salvation
 We live in a dull, predictable and mechanical age. We live in the dictatorship of numbers of the financial crisis, of unemployment statistics, stock market analysis and of generalized social fear. 
 At the same time, the humanist merchants of “progressive” ideologies are seeking new clients. The wandering…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.), Giorgos Nikolopoulos (C.C.F.) - Text in Relation to the Summons for the Inflammatory Parcel That Was Sent to Berlusconi]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-giorgos-nikolopoulos-c-c-f-text-in-relation-to-the-summons-they-receive?v=1720577098</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-giorgos-nikolopoulos-c-c-f-text-in-relation-to-the-summons-they-receive?v=1720577098"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.), Giorgos Nikolopoulos (C.C.F.)
Title: Text in Relation to the Summons for the Inflammatory Parcel That Was Sent to Berlusconi
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/06/23/keimeno-x-tsakalos-g-nikolopoulos-dema-berlusconi/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

‘Through the sadness of endless mediocrity that suffocates us from everywhere, I console myself that somewhere in a closet several stubborn people struggle to counteract the spoilage.’ [Odysseas Elytis]
 We are summoned to appear before the Prosecutor’s Office of Bologna, Italy, on June 28th in order to participate in a preliminary investigation in regard to the ‘punishable offense under Articles 110, 280 of the Criminal Code (attempt with terrorist and subversive purposes)’ of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - A Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-a-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics?v=1720575200</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-a-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics?v=1720575200"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T01:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: A Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics
Date: 1963
Source: Retrieved on 7/4/2024 from <jstage.jst.go.jp/article/ibk1952/11/1/11_1_359/_pdf/-char/ja>

 A short poem “Adoring Naivety” by a Christian poet Jukichi Yagi (1827–1927) runs as follows: 
 Rice bread, 
 Whole-rice bread, 
 Fresh and steaming! 
 Whole-rice bread! 
 A bread seller goes about a “Non-acting” (Mu-i 無 爲 akarma) path singing cries of wares, as if in ecstacy over his singing.[1]
 This verse seems to suggest the aesthetic character of the Japanese folks. In the early days, Japanese peddlers, such as gold-fish vendors, beancurd dealers and seedling-peddlers used to peddle by crying in rythmical voices. Mood, relish, flavour and atmosphere carry great weight in a Japanese life. “Japanese ph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gerasimos Tsakalos (C.C.F) - Individuality and the Anarchist Group]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gerasimos-tsakalos-c-c-f-individuality-and-the-anarchist-group?v=1720573604</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gerasimos-tsakalos-c-c-f-individuality-and-the-anarchist-group?v=1720573604"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T01:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gerasimos Tsakalos (C.C.F)
Title: Individuality and the Anarchist Group
Date: December 2015
Source: Web archive capture on 13 Sep 2016 from <web.archive.org/.../325.nostate.net/.../>

Instead of a Prologue
 About the subject of “Individuality and the anarchist group”, one could say that it’s a timeless issue within the anarchist milieu… Is an anarchist individuality subjugated or liberated within a group? How does the individual encounter the collective? Can disagreements between comrades of the same collective be creative or do they inevitably lead to disputes, rivalries, intrigues, competitions and end up in rupture? 
 How are friendships and cliques able to bring about a cancellation of an anarchist group? 
 What is the relationship of an anarchist organization to the expulsions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kostas Sakkas - Political statement at the terror-trial of Koridallos prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kostas-sakkas-political-statement-at-the-terror-trial-of-koridallos-prison?v=1720569724</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kostas-sakkas-political-statement-at-the-terror-trial-of-koridallos-prison?v=1720569724"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T00:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kostas Sakkas
Title: Political statement at the terror-trial of Koridallos prison
Date: January 14, 2015, anarchists in trouble
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=18709>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 I am sending the following text to Athens lawyer Dimitrios Katsaris in order for him to deliver it to his client and my co-accused Giorgos Karagiannidis, in order to read it out in the courtroom during the testimony procedure. 
 I realize absolutely that what a relative of mine testified during the witnesses’ testimonies was done with the best of intentions. However I must clarify that a large part of it does not reflect reality and does not express me as an individual. Unfortunately the conditions in which I find myself in, my inability to communicate and the restr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clarence Lee Swartz, in collaboration with The Mutualist Associates - What Is Mutualism?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/clarence-lee-swartz-in-collaboration-with-the-mutualist-associates-what-is-mutualism?v=1720568727</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/clarence-lee-swartz-in-collaboration-with-the-mutualist-associates-what-is-mutualism?v=1720568727"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T23:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Clarence Lee Swartz, in collaboration with The Mutualist Associates
Title: What Is Mutualism?
Date: 1927
Notes: This is a very interesting and valuable text on Mutualism. It is slightly dated in some points and a bit off the target when dealing with monetary matters. Nevertheless it remains a powerful exposition of the main tenets of Mutualism and a sincere plea in favour of the freedom and autonomy of the individual.
Source: <c4ss.org/wp-content/uploads/2009/06/what-is-mutualism.pdf>

MUTUALISM — A Social System Based on Equal Freedom, Reciprocity, and the Sovereignty of the Individual Over Himself, His Affairs, and His Products; Realized Through Individual Initiative, Free Contract, Cooperation, Competition, and Voluntary Association for Defense Against the Invasive and for the P…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor data events in Amazon S3 Express One Zone with AWS CloudTrail]]></title>
        <id>08f8205391b4f54c420072e762445c6a8d490a15</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/monitor-data-events-in-amazon-s3-express-one-zone-with-aws-cloudtrail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T22:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudTrail data event logging enables auditing for governance and compliance of object operations like PutObject and GetObject. Leverage high performance and low cost for latency-sensitive workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2024]]></title>
        <id>8ed151291b1f97b46f2655d37b994f085e5bd6eb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/top-announcements-of-the-aws-summit-in-new-york-2024-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Along with a plethora of new launches, read about the latest models in Amazon Bedrock and new features for Amazon Q.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate your data and collaborate using data preparation in AWS Glue Studio]]></title>
        <id>3dbcc75ef8554e17d4ce640b34987f60e1ed5ea5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/integrate-your-data-and-collaborate-using-data-preparation-in-aws-glue-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Glue's new visual interface, data teams can collaboratively build ETL pipelines, bridging the gap between analysts and engineers through an intuitive, shareable canvas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19: third most lethal cause of death in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7977</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/covid-19-third-most-lethal-cause-death-australia-2022/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From The Daily Aus. Aside from being linked to a slight decrease in life expectancy, COVID-19 was the third highest cause of death in Australia in 2022, claiming almost ten-thousand lives: COVID-19 was the third leading cause of death in Australia in 2022, according to AIHW. It was the first time in more than 50 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Graviton4-based Amazon EC2 R8g instances: best price performance in Amazon EC2]]></title>
        <id>07a71bd7ce6b0c97862edd3bdcb3b2e5005fcf1c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-graviton4-based-amazon-ec2-r8g-instances-best-price-performance-in-amazon-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the price performance and sustainability benefits of Graviton4 with Amazon EC2 R8g instances, ideal for memory-intensive workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reminder to Take a Walk and Breathe]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-reminder-to-take-a-walk-and-breathe/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-reminder-to-take-a-walk-and-breathe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A non-stressful day at work is hard to come by. I am constantly straddling the fine line between being burnt out, and just flipping a table and walking away. At the end of the day, those two feelings are basically the same side of a coin.
I work remotely full-time, for the most part. Sometimes I travel for workshops, but that’s mostly just at the beginning of kicking off a new product that I’ve been asked to build. Any other time, I’m mostly working in my home office, which has become my favorite place in the house, yet the place where I stress out the most.
I spend a lot of time in front of a computer. I’m in meetings probably 5-6 hours a day. With a majority of my current team in Central and Eastern time zones (2-3 hours ahead of me), sometimes I also forget to take a break and eat. It’s easy to lose track of time when I’m focused on solving this problem or that.
I also forget to breathe.
The weather finally cooled down yesterday, and a little bit today before we hit another heat wave. LSC constantly encourages me, and at times pushes me to go for a walk. Take a walk around the block, and just breathe. We practice breathing together, inhaling and exhaling. Inhale the fresh air slowly, keep it in for a few seconds, exhale slowly. Then we go back in the house, and I feel a tiny bit better.
Sometimes we get into what we’re doing so deeply that we forget the essentials. We forget to breathe. We don’t notice it until we’re drowning, and it’s even harder to get back to the surface. Sometimes all it takes is a reminder to stop what you’re doing, take a walk if you can, and breathe.
So hey, let this be a reminder.
Go for a walk. Inhale that fresh air. Hold it in. Exhale.
7/100
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the challenges in creating an accessible sortable list (drag-and-drop)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Drag-and-drop is a highly interactive and visual interface. We often use drag-and-drop to perform tasks like uploading files, reordering browser bookmarks, or even moving a card in solitaire.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/">Exploring the challenges in creating an accessible sortable list (drag-and-drop)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>