<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-28T18:29:41.919Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-28T18:29:41.919Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/28/2024: Biden v. Trump Post-Match Analysis and Commentary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274152</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-28-2024-biden-v-trump-post-match-analysis-and-commentary.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T18:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's Water Cooler: Biden v. Trump and the Democrat succession crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Milind Naphade, Capital One’s SVP of AI Foundations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/86df019ebf76</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/meet-milind-naphade-capital-ones-svp-of-ai-foundations-86df019ebf76?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T17:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Milind Naphade, Ph.D., about his tech background, vision for AI in finance and approaches shaping our AI future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the first 2024 US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic and security trends]]></title>
        <id>667eb7fea4598c000bd70735</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-first-2024-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic-and-security-trends"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Biden and Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns, email trends, and heightened cybersecurity concerns across digital platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Crashes, Trump Lies: A Campaign-Defining Presidential Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274141</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/biden-crashes-trump-lies-a-campaign-defining-presidential-debate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yves here. The presidential debate last night is likely to go down as being of historical importance, in the same league as the Kennedy-Nixon debate. But here, instead of demonstrating how the then-young medium rewarded good looks and a confident affect, here it showed two men, which as often happens with the aged, having become […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Postgres Named Prepared Statements in Hyperdrive]]></title>
        <id>667c105ba4598c000bd70518</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/postgres-named-prepared-statements-supported-hyperdrive"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperdrive (Cloudflare’s globally distributed SQL connection pooler and cache) recently added support for Postgres protocol-level named prepared statements across pooled connections. We dive deep on what it took to add this feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Repp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 23, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240628"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racial and Ethnic Inequalities in Household Wealth Persist]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30411</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/racial-and-ethnic-inequalities-in-household-wealth-persist/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disparities in wealth are pronounced across racial and ethnic groups in the United States. As part of an ongoing series on inequality and equitable growth, we have been documenting the evolution of these gaps between Black, Hispanic, and white households, in this case from the first quarter of 2019 to the fourth quarter of 2023 for a variety of assets and liabilities for a pandemic-era picture. We find that real wealth grew and that the pace of growth for Black, Hispanic, and white households was very similar across this timeframe—yet gaps across groups persist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajashri Chakrabarti, Natalia Emanuel, and Ben Lahey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274107</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our sweetened, condensed daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sifting Through the Debris of Another Failed Coup in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274045</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/sifting-through-the-debris-of-another-failed-coup-in-bolivia.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T10:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was probably the shortest lived coup in Bolivia's history. But who was behind it?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After the European Elections: Fiscal Policy is the Elephant in the Room]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274132</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/after-the-european-elections-fiscal-policy-is-the-elephant-in-the-room.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fiscal pressures are set to intensify battles among shifting European leadership groups as to how much to spend and on what.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Layoffs, Retirement, and Post-Pandemic Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274105</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/layoffs-retirement-and-post-pandemic-inflation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:35:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finally, a look at how Covid-related early retirement has contributed to our recent inflation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16717</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/proactive-measures-against-password-breaches-and-cookie-hijacking/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, we’re committed to security that goes beyond the ordinary. We continuously strive to earn and maintain user trust by safeguarding critical components integral to every user’s experience. From passwords to session cookies, and tokens to webhooks, we prioritize protecting everything essential to how users log into the platform and remain authenticated. Through proactive […]
The post Proactive Measures Against Password Breaches and Cookie Hijacking appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Lehotsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper: On the curious diet of the Speckled Mousebird]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52787</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/28/occasional-paper-on-the-curious-diet-of-the-speckled-mousebird/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T08:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So my wife took this picture in our garden yesterday, here in Kigali, Rwanda: Take a close look.  This little bird — about the size of an American cardinal, or a European robin — is facing us.  It’s also facing the sun, though you can’t see that.  It is holding two twigs with its little […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europe is turning black and brown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Europe-is-turning-black-and-brown"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How should we interpret the results of the EU parliamentary elections? 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of the Innocence: Railroading Marcellus Williams to Death Row]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326677</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-end-of-the-innocence-railroading-marcellus-williams-to-death-row/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T06:01:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was, as prosecutors often say, an evidence-rich crime scene. Felicia Gayle’s murderer left behind footprints in her blood, fingerprints, hair, and, most crucially, DNA on the knife used to kill her. The problem was: none of the evidence implicated the person the DA charged, tried, convicted, and sentenced to death for the crime. More
The post The End of the Innocence: Railroading Marcellus Williams to Death Row appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Combats Climate Change. The U.S., Not So Much]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326599</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/china-combats-climate-change-the-u-s-not-so-much/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The two leading U.S. presidential candidates offer a dismal future for the earth ecosystem. That’s because it’s time for a real climate president, not a phony one, like Joe “More Oil Leases” Biden or a climate wrecker like Donald “Let the World Burn” Trump. The earth is warming, and we all know how to apply the brakes: stop burning oil, gas and coal. But both Biden and Trump refuse such a so-called radical step, thus condemning our species to a hotter, less human-friendly planet, at best. More
The post China Combats Climate Change. The U.S., Not So Much appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antarctic Ice Melt – New Sobering Studies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/antarctic-ice-melt-new-sobering-studies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was only two years ago that studies of the infamous Thwaites Glacier, aka: the Doomsday Glacier located in West Antarctica, found rapid melting. At the time, scientists said it was “hanging on by its fingernails.” (Source: ‘Doomsday Glacier’ Which Could Raise Sea Level by Several Feet, is ‘Hanging by its Fingernails,’ Scientists Say, CNN,  More
The post Antarctic Ice Melt – New Sobering Studies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Altalena Affair: Is Israel Heading Towards a Civil War?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326762</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-altalena-affair-is-israel-heading-towards-a-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“There will be no civil war” in Israel, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said on June 18. But he might be wrong. Netanyahu’s statement was made in the context of the growing popular protests in Israel, especially following the long-anticipated resignations of several Israeli War Cabinet Ministers, including Benny Gantz and Gadi Eisenkot – both  More
The post The Altalena Affair: Is Israel Heading Towards a Civil War? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assange is Finally Free as America, Britain, Sweden and Australia are Shamed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/assange-is-finally-free-as-america-britain-sweden-and-australia-are-shamed/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Assange, the founder of the whistleblower organization Wikileaks, after being hounded by the US with the help of its sycophantic allies in the governments of the UK, Sweden, Ecuador and, most shamefully, his native Australia, for 14 years since his Wikileaks organization obtained and released  documents proving systemic war crimes by the US in Iraq and Afghanistan, has been freed. He spent the last 14 years fighting efforts by the US to lock him up oar execute 9or even to assassinate him ,spending 12 of those years in the hell of confinement in a British maximum security prison and earlier seven years as an asylum seeker trapped in the Ecuadoran Embassy in London. More
The post Assange is Finally Free as America, Britain, Sweden and Australia are Shamed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Not-So-Great Debates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326744</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-not-so-great-debates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based upon their published programs and utterances last night, Trump and Biden largely agree. They aim to send asylum seekers and economic migrants alike to concentration camps in the Southwest, or holding areas in southern Mexico. In the U.K., Sunak wants to ship an annual 50,000 U.K. migrants to Rwanda in contravention of both U.K, and international law. Starmer wants to unleash MI5 on them, and smash “the cartels” that supposedly enable small boats with migrants to cross the channel. I half expected him to announce, a la Churchill, “we shall fight them on the beaches…” More
The post The Not-So-Great Debates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assange’s Release: Exposing the Craven Media Stable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326771</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/assanges-release-exposing-the-craven-media-stable/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WikiLeaks project was always going to put various noses out of joint in the journalistic profession. Soaked and blighted by sloth, easily bought, perennially envious, a good number of the Fourth Estate have always preferred to remain uncritical of power and sympathetic to its brutal exercise. For those reasons, the views of Thomas Carlyle,  More
The post Assange’s Release: Exposing the Craven Media Stable appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bribery Case Touches SCOTUS In A Tender Spot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326758</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/bribery-case-touches-scotus-in-a-tender-spot/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a former mayor of Portage, Indiana, James Snyder will forever remain known for three things: First, steering $1.1 million in city business to Great Lakes Peterbilt for the purchase of five garbage trucks in 2013. Second, receiving a $13,000 “consulting fee” from Great Lakes Peterbilt in 2014. Third, getting the Supreme Court to pretend  More
The post Bribery Case Touches SCOTUS In A Tender Spot appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowman Was Defeated by a Toxic Blend of Zionism and Militarism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326559</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/bowman-was-defeated-by-a-toxic-blend-of-zionism-and-militarism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Congressman Jamaal Bowman lost a primary election Tuesday because of unprecedented spending against him by powerful forces that insist Israel does no wrong. By last week, AIPAC had already devoted more than $14 million to defeating Bowman, in retaliation for his outspoken support of human rights for all — including Palestinian — people. Since last fall, most Democratic voters  More
The post Bowman Was Defeated by a Toxic Blend of Zionism and Militarism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liberal Zionism: Gatekeeping Criticism of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326707</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/liberal-zionism-gatekeeping-criticism-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s ongoing genocide is part of a downward spiral for the Zionist project. In the words of acclaimed historian Professor Ilan Pappe: “We are witnessing a historical process – or, more accurately, the beginnings of one – that is likely to culminate in the downfall of Zionism.” Yet Zionism’s long-standing settler goals have not only thrived through genocidal  More
The post Liberal Zionism: Gatekeeping Criticism of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Years After Dobbs, Women are Still Fighting to Reclaim Their Rights]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326740</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/two-years-after-dobbs-women-are-still-fighting-to-reclaim-their-rights/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its Dobbs ruling two years ago this June, the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade. Since then, abortion restrictions have had devastating effects not only on pregnant people but on our society more generally. Abortion restrictions force poor women to travel out of state to seek care. This requires not only the funds to pay for the procedure, which  More
The post Two Years After Dobbs, Women are Still Fighting to Reclaim Their Rights appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Georgia Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old Mole Comes Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326729</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/old-mole-comes-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reds— the title of Warren Beatty’s Bohemian/Bolshevik love story that features John Reed and Louise Bryant— is also the title of Maurice Isserman’s new book subtitled, “The Tragedy of American Communism.” Issermam is the author of three other books about communism with a big letter C and a small letter c: If I had a Hammer:  More
The post Old Mole Comes Back appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Earth Farms Is Proof That Intentional Communities Can Succeed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326745</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/red-earth-farms-is-proof-that-intentional-communities-can-succeed/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperative living might look idyllic on paper, but intentional communities aren’t easy to sustain. It takes a hardy soul to weather all the monetary struggles, power imbalances, compromises with neighbors, and other complications that come with choosing this lifestyle. According to Diana Leafe Christian’s book, Creating a Life Together: Practical Tools to Grow Ecovillages and Intentional Communities, 90 percent of all ecovillages  More
The post Red Earth Farms Is Proof That Intentional Communities Can Succeed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Election in Danger?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326679</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/an-election-in-danger/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Officials and election experts are now struggling in a big-time way. How, they wonder, can they effectively address mounting threats — of violence, election denialism, foreign influence, and voter discrimination? Do they run the risk of alarming the public to the point of reducing voter turnout? Are there reasons to assuage fears about either election disinformation  More
The post An Election in Danger? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JULIAN ZELIZER - KAREN J. GREENBERG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Venezuela Is Overcoming the US Blockade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326717</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/how-venezuela-is-overcoming-the-us-blockade-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of Venezuela’s Bolivarian Revolution, a target of US imperial power since its inception in 1998, may be decided on July 28, the date of their presidential election. Incumbent President Nicolás Maduro and seven other presidential candidates pledged to abide by the choice of the electorate. Edmundo González, promoted by the US, and another  More
The post How Venezuela Is Overcoming the US Blockade appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merle Haggard and the Lost “Free Life”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326614</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/merle-haggard-and-the-lost-free-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Is the best of the free life behind us now?” Merle Haggard asked in a haunting 1982 country music hit song. Nine years earlier, Haggard had scoffed at potheads and draft dodgers in a White House performance of his song “Okie from Muskogee” for President Richard Nixon. But reflecting widespread loss of faith in the  More
The post Merle Haggard and the Lost “Free Life” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Wants to Make Coal Mining Jobs a Big Election Issue and the Washington Post is Ready to Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326674</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/trump-wants-to-make-coal-mining-jobs-a-big-election-issue-and-the-washington-post-is-ready-to-help/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a major proponent of global warming, Donald Trump apparently thinks it benefits him to be perceived as a savior of jobs in the coal industry. This is likely not because he can do much to protect the country’s remaining coal jobs, but it gives him an opportunity to appear to be supporting workers. The  More
The post Trump Wants to Make Coal Mining Jobs a Big Election Issue and the Washington Post is Ready to Help appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kenya Protests: Why Ruto Pulling the Finance Bill is Unlikely to Satisfy Angry Young Protesters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326673</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/kenya-protests-why-ruto-pulling-the-finance-bill-is-unlikely-to-satisfy-angry-young-protesters/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a move that shocked observers, Kenya’s President William Ruto announced on 26 June he was withdrawing his government’s highly controversial finance bill. This followed two days in which tens of thousands of mostly young protesters took to the streets in nationwide rallies against the proposals contained in the country’s 2024 budget. Kathleen Klaus, who  More
The post Kenya Protests: Why Ruto Pulling the Finance Bill is Unlikely to Satisfy Angry Young Protesters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Klaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Racial Wealth Gap is Persistent…and Growing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326686</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-racial-wealth-gap-is-persistent-and-growing/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The data is clear – the racial wealth gap in the United States is persistent and growing. Why, sixty years after the formal end of Jim Crow, is the gap between Black and white families still widening? And what can we do to narrow it? Researchers from the Samuel DuBois Cook Center on Social Equity  More
The post The Racial Wealth Gap is Persistent…and Growing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amber Holland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Kenyan Forces Arrive in Haiti as Part of Latest Foreign Intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326631</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/first-kenyan-forces-arrive-in-haiti-as-part-of-latest-foreign-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Tuesday, June 25, the first contingent of Kenyan security forces, the initial deployment of the much-discussed and long-delayed Multinational Security Support mission (MSS), touched down on the tarmac in Port-au-Prince. Its arrival comes 20 months after former prime minister Ariel Henry first requested a foreign security intervention amid nationwide protests calling for his resignation.  More
The post First Kenyan Forces Arrive in Haiti as Part of Latest Foreign Intervention appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jake Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Debate Was About Theatrics, Not Public Policies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326779</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/the-debate-was-about-theatrics-not-public-policies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good morning from Chicago, where I am attending a family reunion. My family arrived yesterday evening and enjoyed greeting other relatives, so I did not view last night’s televised “debate” between Joe Biden and Donald Trump as it happened. Based on all media analysts and political pundits I have considered since then, Biden and Trump  More
The post The Debate Was About Theatrics, Not Public Policies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wendell Griffen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Take Trump’s Threat to Deport Millions of Migrants Seriously]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326736</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/we-need-to-take-trumps-threat-to-deport-millions-of-migrants-seriously/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often trivialize former U.S. President Donald Trump’s racism—we consider his bigotry in passing while ruminating at length on his legal woes and alleged cognitive deterioration. Social media pundit David Pakman has been showing clips of Trump slurring his words or rambling chaotically on a daily basis—as if the primary threat posed by another MAGA presidency would  More
The post We Need to Take Trump’s Threat to Deport Millions of Migrants Seriously appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zeus Filled the Streets, Markets, Seas, and the Heavens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326691</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/zeus-filled-the-streets-markets-seas-and-the-heavens/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue I was born and brought up in a Greek village. Like the vast majority of Greeks, I was Christian. Not that I understood what Christianity was all about. I simply followed the rest. But my college education and work in the United States convinced me to abandon Christianity and return to the gods of  More
The post Zeus Filled the Streets, Markets, Seas, and the Heavens appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journalists Shouldn’t Just Repeat What Politicians Say. They Should Investigate It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326742</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/journalists-shouldnt-just-repeat-what-politicians-say-they-should-investigate-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:40:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my time as a student journalist and editor, I’ve picked up a few lessons about integrity. It’s surprisingly easy to let objectivity slip on some subjects. But as my editor-in-chief continuously reminded me, responsible journalism means we need to properly investigate all sides of a story — before publishing things like “the cafeteria food here sucks.”  More
The post Journalists Shouldn’t Just Repeat What Politicians Say. They Should Investigate It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chisom Okorafur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partenope by the Bay: Handel in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326775</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/partenope-by-the-bay-handel-in-san-francisco/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Flaubert was Madame Bovary, then Handel was Partenope. She is the title character of his 1730 opera, a big hit in its time, but then spurned for supposed tawdriness over the ensuing 250 years. Partenope is a woman who thrives on adoration and the theatricality of life and love. Handel may himself never have  More
The post Partenope by the Bay: Handel in San Francisco appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandy Koufax and the Lost Legacy of Brooklyn’s Lafayette High School]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326753</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/sandy-koufax-and-the-lost-legacy-of-brooklyns-lafayette-high-school/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City real estate developers care little for preserving the City’s history and our memories. And educators are surprisingly reticent as well. I walked by Lafayette High School, where students had painted magnificent mural tributes to their fellow students who’d died. They updated them every year, utilizing the handball court walls as their canvasses.  More
The post Sandy Koufax and the Lost Legacy of Brooklyn’s Lafayette High School appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mitchel Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture of Cities: Birds of Prey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326728</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/architecture-of-cities-birds-of-prey/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on a true story: I once chased after a red tail hawk: I ran down a mountain: the sloping valley appeared near: I was a photographer about to make a capture: nearly out of breath, I abruptly stopped: I reached two more steps. I looked down: the abyss reigned. I roamed inclusive in the  More
The post Architecture of Cities: Birds of Prey appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Schulman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Balm in Gilead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326507</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/no-balm-in-gilead/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just finished, with my breakfast, reading the latest essay in the New York Review of Books by Marilyn Robinson who, I fear, is writing less and less clearly. She feels entangled in her own rhetoric, and I found myself terribly impatient with her convoluted and often disconnected reasoning. I even went back to re-read the  More
The post No Balm in Gilead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Gubernat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Stonewall to Blair Mountain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326714</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/28/from-stonewall-to-blair-mountain/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time, in a village called Greenwich, there was a dingey little bar called Stonewall where several shades of queens and dykes used to hang out, get lit, and get their rocks off. It wasn’t much to look at, just a punchy little hole in the wall run by the Genovese Crime Family  More
The post From Stonewall to Blair Mountain appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicky Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rumble in the Jungle: Biden v. Trump Presidential Debate Live Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274062</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/rumble-in-the-jungle-biden-v-trump-presidential-debate-live-blog.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T00:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Lambert Strether of Corrente. With “Rumble in the Jungle” in the headline, I had hoped to present the terrific When We Were Kings: It’s 1974, Muhammad Ali is 32 and thought by many to be past his prime. George Foreman is ten years younger and the Heavyweight champion of the world. Promoter Don King […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lpolovets in "FDA warns top U.S. bakery not to claim foods contain allergens when they don't"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40816392"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T23:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My understanding is this allergen over-labeling was inspired by the FDA in the first place. https://www.fastcompany.com/90830854/sesame-seed-allergen-fd...
From the linked article (from Jan 2023):
  But sesame does differ in one distinct way from eggs, peanuts, shellfish, milk, and soy: The seeds are teeny tiny and hard to keep track of. This means they’re prone to “cross-contamination,” in food-allergy terms. If you operate a bakery that makes sesame bagels, the odds are decent that rogue seeds will end up in your other products, too. Bad news for people with severe sesame allergies. But it’s also expensive and frustrating for food manufacturers to ensure the seeds are kept away from other foods, if they’re on the FDA’s major allergens list.
  
  Advocates have therefore been warning since December that the FASTER Act is poised to have a counter effect. Rather than minimize cross-contamination, as they argue the law requires, many big food brands have opted to add sesame to their bread products, then simply declare it as an ingredient. They are intentionally adding sesame flour to “avoid complying with the spirit and intent of the FASTER Act,” FARE tells Fast Company. That is cheaper than certifying that their facilities are 100% sesame-free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lpolovets</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon WorkSpaces Pools: Cost-effective, non-persistent virtual desktops]]></title>
        <id>984d71ca0c0d724236063c172b55b47f247b8d96</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-workspaces-pools-cost-effective-non-persistent-virtual-desktops/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T22:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline virtual desktop management: provision non-persistent desktops, configure apps and resources, and automatically scale capacity based on demand, all from a centralized platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janalsncm in "Supreme Court blocks controversial Purdue Pharma opioid settlement"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40815272"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pound for pound, the Sacklers probably did more damage to America than any other drug dealers in history. More damage than any serial killer or mass shooter. In my mind they should be considered public enemies 1 through N. I sincerely hope they face civil and criminal liabilities for what they’ve done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janalsncm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tetris font, fun and games with typography]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7921</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tetris-font-fun-games-with-typography/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there a version of Tetris that requires the player to try and spell words with the Tetris pieces, as they fall from the sky? If there is, I’ve not heard of it. But, that’s not saying much, as I don’t know a whole lot about gaming. Anyway, Tetris Font, developed by Erik Demaine and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing end-to-end data lineage (preview) visualization in Amazon DataZone]]></title>
        <id>879d02790e78c3e2de51ba7702fc1da289789fe1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-end-to-end-data-lineage-preview-visualization-in-amazon-datazone/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trace data from origin to insights with an intuitive visual graph, empowering engineers, analysts, and admins to validate provenance, troubleshoot pipelines, and ensure governance with ease.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>95dac704f4314c4f6db2eca43810d24e08e0c1ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of an enhanced AWS Well-Architected Framework. In this update, you’ll find expanded guidance across all six pillars of the Framework: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability. In this release, we updated the implementation guidance for the new and existing best practices to be more prescriptive. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274060</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T18:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics; The Debates, pre-game analysis; Murthy v. Missouri; Digital ID exposure  debacle; CDK auto dealer outage and consumer spending ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by freedomben in "Remembering Larry Finger, who made Linux wireless work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40813002</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40813002"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow, this is sad news indeed for the world at large, but also me personally.  I'm suddenly in deep regret for having procrastinated reaching out the thank him.  He doesn't know this, but he was somewhat of a mentor for me.
In the early 00s I bought a laptop that had an RTL 8188 CE card in it that ran awful under Linux.  I forked his driver and made a number of changes to it and eventually got my wifi working really well (by doing things that could never be upstreamed due to legal/regulatory restrictions).  Over the years I rebased often and reviewed the changes, and learned a lot from watching his code.  It took a bit of getting used to, but a certain amount of beauty and appreciation emerged.  One thing was very clear:  This man was doing a lot of the work to keep the ship together.  Even just keeping the driver compilable with each kernel release often took some non-trivial refactoring, which he did reliably and well.
Larry, you will be missed my friend.  RIP.
If you are waiting to reach out to somebody, don't wait too long or it may suddenly be too late.  The years can slip by in a flash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freedomben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst now supports GitLab and Bitbucket repositories, with blueprints and Amazon Q feature development]]></title>
        <id>66767bb7893b7246f1f08f78664b23f8a53f9820</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-codecatalyst-now-supports-gitlab-and-bitbucket-repositories-with-blueprints-and-amazon-q-feature-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your code across popular git repositories with Amazon CodeCatalyst's new integration with GitLab.com and Bitbucket Cloud. Use blueprints and Amazon Q feature development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded function calling in Workers AI: easier, smarter, faster]]></title>
        <id>667d8733a4598c000bd705cd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/embedded-function-calling"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new way to do function calling in Workers AI by running function code alongside your inference. Plus, a new @cloudflare/ai-utils package to make getting started as simple as possible]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harley Turan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fear & Loathing on The Economist Subscription Trail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274011</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/fear-loathing-on-the-economist-subscription-trail.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T14:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satayjit Das' penetrating and witty look at The Economist reveals a great deal not to like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finance Healthcare, Not Insurance Premia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274055</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/finance-healthcare-not-insurance-premia.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T13:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study finds that revenue-funded healthcare is cost-effective, efficient, and fair, while all health insurance has avoidable excess cost]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up in Nuseirat – Where Massacres Become Routine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/27/growing-up-in-nuseirat-where-massacres-become-routine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I clearly remember my first day at an UNRWA school in a refugee camp in Gaza. I was five years of age. It felt like my life was over. The distance from Block 5 of the Nuseirat Refugee Camp to the New Camp – located within the municipal boundaries of Nuseirat – was long, exhausting  More
The post Growing up in Nuseirat – Where Massacres Become Routine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "6 months ago, I left the bullshit industrial complex"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40807299</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40807299"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T04:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While this author is of a younger generation, this really resonated with me as a Gen Xer. I feel there is so much disillusionment among folks that came of age during the 90s because there was so much techno optimism then, and it didn't quite turn out like we envisioned. Two things made me think about this recently:
1. I saw a Reddit post that was titled something like "The 90s were peak humanity. Enough tech to make life comfortable, but not so much that it had totally taken over the focus." It was a video of a packed mall around the holidays filled with generally happy people socializing in public.
2. That viral quote that was making the rounds, "I want AI to do my laundry and dishes so that I can do art and writing, not for AI to do my art and writing so that I can do my laundry and dishes."
I just feel there has been a growing chasm over the past 25 years where tech is no longer solving pressing human problems (generally, obviously not true in all areas e.g. decarbonization tech) but is more concerned with just rent-seeking value extraction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by changexd in "Show HN: I built an indie, browser-based MMORPG"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40806835</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40806835"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T03:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logged in, saw a guy spitting out racist words, attacked the shit out of him with two other strangers, we've beat racism, 10/10 game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>changexd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[this love is strong, why do i feel weak?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/whitney/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/whitney/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been in a writing slump lately. I've been going out (a little bit) and doing things and even posting some pictures to keep the Publish button warm. But the voice in my head has been awfully quiet, so today I'm going to sit here and coax him out.
Last week my dad flew to New Jersey for a business trip and did me a favor by bringing a bag of my clothes with him, so I took the train over to Newark (EWR) to meet him and pick up my stuff. While waiting for him I killed some time riding in the airport Airtrain that whisks you from one terminal to another. The Airtrain is so strange. The train cars are absurdly small — I'm used to them being subway sized — and fit probably no more than 10 people each. I spent a few minutes alone in my tiny metal capsule and did not pass up the opportunity to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Migrating to the cloud with AWS]]></title>
        <id>59dc679b0c05157308218c9126cc3375da8e04e1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-migrating-to-the-cloud-with-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, businesses are increasingly turning to the cloud for its scalability, agility, and cost-effectiveness. Migrating your data center to the cloud can be a daunting task, but with the right approach and tools, it can be a successful journey. This Let’s Architect! blog post will guide you through the process of migrating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Federica Ciuffo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aerroon in "South Korean telecom company attacks torrent users with malware"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805471</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40805471"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T22:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, terrible Korean internet strikes again. ISPs try to charge companies insane fees because customers want to connect to their servers. Company decides to use peer-ro-peer instead so the ISP starts installing spyware on customer computers.
Makes me wonder where this myth of "good Korean internet" even came from if everything ends up so bandwidth constrained. Is it because all the customers and services are in the same city so it appears low latency?
I hope everyone involved in this catches criminal charges, all the way up the chain. Completely unacceptable behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aerroon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/about/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/about/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi 👋  I’m JC (Probably)
But you can call me Jedda.
🚧 This page is a work in progress, but I too, am always a work in progress, so I think it all works out.
Based in the Bay Area (CA), but originally from the East Coast. I’m a Product Manager by profession, photography hobbyist, avid reader, and a creative by nature. I have a 12-year old dachshund named Cocoa (Chanel), who pretty much runs my life.
I’m not great at writing (or talking) about myself. If you stick around, little bits and pieces of my life do surface itself in the things I create and write.
This blog doesn’t have a specific theme. It’s mostly anything and everything that pops into my head. It was initially started as a place for quick notes, that turned into long form thoughts, but now is just an overall place for my primarily text-based everything.
I’d love to hear from you, even if it’s just to say hello. I’m typically available on socials such as 🐘Mastodon but can easily be reached via email through my Letterbird (or the email embedded in my posts). If you’d like to subscribe via RSS, you can do so 📡 here.
Welcome to my Notes. I am so glad you're here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did the universe exist before the Big Bang? Maybe…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7915</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/did-the-universe-exist-before-the-big-bang-maybe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happened, or was there, before the Big Bang that is said to have brought the universe into being? Was there nothing, to which something came? It is the question of the ages. In his recent documentary series, Universe, British physicist Brian Cox posits that the universe existed before the Big Bang. How long this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically replacing polyfill.io links with Cloudflare’s mirror for a safer Internet]]></title>
        <id>667c60c6a4598c000bd7056a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/automatically-replacing-polyfill-io-links-with-cloudflares-mirror-for-a-safer-internet"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T20:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[polyfill.io, a popular JavaScript library service, can no longer be trusted and should be removed from websites]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese Diaspora]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/the-chinese-diaspora/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/the-chinese-diaspora/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City's cultural and demographic landscape is wide and deep; today we focus on the narrative of the Chinese Diaspora in New York which offers a compelling study in migration, community dynamics, and urban development.
At the heart of this narrative lies the transformation of Manhattan's Chinatown, a neighborhood once bustling with the vibrant intricacies of Chinese culture, now a shadow of its former self, restaurants dwindling, residents leaving, and culture evaporating. The assertion that Manhattan's Chinatown has succumbed to the relentless march of urban evolution is not just an observation; it's a stark reality. The exodus, driven by the prohibitive costs of Manhattan living, has rerouted the lifeblood of this community to Flushing, at the end of the Queens-bound 7 line, marki…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ai safety]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/ai-safety/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/ai-safety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T18:15:59.737Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the author thought of the next word
him and autocomplete concurred
the artist put up a blank canvas
the generative ai left it spotless
the woman applied for a loan
two bytes, “no”
the people yelled in defiance
the drone left only silence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nomel in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802490</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802490"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think there's a severe problem with this implementation. By using wrapping, I can't write "boobs" and have everyone else read my graffiti without them having having the same zoom wrapping point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ssalka in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802377</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40802377"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[tried doing:
```
$$('input[type=checkbox]').forEach(elt => elt.click());
```
and got an alert that said "CHILL LOL". fun site]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ssalka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eieio in "One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801815</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40801815"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T16:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(developer here)
this is....more popular than i expected. the server's gonna be having some problems for a while]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eieio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methodological fetishism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45459</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/26/methodological-fetishism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Beyond the significant financial expenses required to conduct RCTs … critics have raised concerns about considerable opportunity costs associated with their privileged status in programme and policy assessment. These costs result from how an over-emphasis on experimental evaluations in evidence generation systematically undermines alternative research methods potentially better equipped to answer questions about causal mechanisms (or the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Book From an MIT Whiz Kid]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/mit-whiz-kid/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/mit-whiz-kid/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*** For the first 500 people that input their email, I will email you access to a FREE MONTH of our Trading chat.
It's May 8th, 2022 and the market has officially left "easy-mode" and entered into a straight grind down. Gone are the days of just buying $NIO at the end of the day because it closed up at least 1 ATR on elevated rvol and you'll wake up with it a couple points higher, just cause!
Now, we are seeing the high flyers that are up in the air getting hit on earnings and selling off aggressively. The r*tarded trade that Tim and I are taking in our joint account is shorting earnings day 1 under premarket lows and it's working! We aren't crushing it, but it's working. We are covering everything at 1:1, often reshorting into vwap vs high of day and taking them overnight. Additionally, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Amazon Simple Queue Service (SQS) for speed and scale]]></title>
        <id>d4565ed778c5a0e98b15e9b099d374724e2830bf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/optimizing-amazon-simple-queue-service-sqs-for-speed-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SQS boosts performance, scaling capabilities, and energy efficiency without impacting existing behavior - a behind-the-scenes look at AWS's continuous improvement journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare incident on June 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>667b4709a4598c000bd7048c</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-june-20-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new DDoS rule resulted in an increase in error responses and latency for Cloudflare customers. Here’s how it went wrong, and what we’ve learned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lloyd Wallis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate and environmental crisis: Sorcerer's apprentices at the World Bank and the IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Climate-and-environmental-crisis-Sorcerer-s-apprentices-at-the-World-Bank-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Ecology/Climate, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libertarian Communist Group - Towards a Programme]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/libertarian-communist-group-towards-a-programme?v=1719384278"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T06:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Libertarian Communist Group
Title: Towards a Programme
Date: 1977
Notes: Another, earlier TOWARDS A PROGRAMME text can be found on <www.thesparrowsnest.org.uk/collections/public_archive/15788.pdf>

Preface (2004)
 This document was originally drafted by members of the Anarchist Workers’ Association, (A.W.A.) following a resolution passed at the 1976 [?] A.W.A. conference, which called for the A.W.A. to agree a clearer definition of its theory and strategy. At that time the A.W.A. had groups and members in England and Scotland, and a sympathiser or two in Ireland, and published the monthly newspaper ‘Anarchist Worker’. The text below was adopted as a ‘provisional’ rather than as a definitive text by the tendency whose members went on to publish ‘Libertarian Communist’, and renamed t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you! I’m trying to read your blog post so don’t stop.]]></title>
        <id>https://thecombine.bearblog.dev/thank-you-im-trying-to-read-your-blog-post-so-dont-stop/</id>
        <link href="https://thecombine.bearblog.dev/thank-you-im-trying-to-read-your-blog-post-so-dont-stop/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T02:35:34.071Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found this blog site a few weeks back. I have a very hectic schedule at the moment and don’t have too much time for writing.
But I do seem to have time for browsing what others write while I wait on the mundane waits in life, which normally translates to waiting in a line, waiting in a waiting room (probably the most obviously named room in the english language)  or waiting for the dog to stop sniffing around and pee.
In these little moments, the phone comes out and I look at the recent posts. I’m fascinated by what you write. The honesty, the freeform, the choice of blog styles, the navigation tabs (I’m really happy with the “nope” and will be adding one soon), all of it.
I’m just really glad to be here. And I want to thank you all for your contributions. You make my world brighter.
And for those of you that think “no one will see this”. You are wrong. Someone will.
So keep writing please!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Street]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/cmu-export/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T01:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is intended to be the most basic of rundowns in getting a top job offer for Carnegie Mellon SCS freshman.
While the following may sound annoyingly prestige-oriented, and compensation-driven, it is bluntly intended to reflect the realities of an increasingly competitive professional landscape. There is a lot of yapping, beware. Get some Tsaocaa boba and settle in.
About me, for context, I grew up low-income in a suburban town with immigrant parents that never attended high school. I took up to Calc AB in high school, and I only knew basic web development coming into CMU. I graduated from Carnegie Mellon University this semester. My highest offer this year included a total compensation of $550k. I had offers from trading firms, two FAANGs, tiktok.
CMU's Greatest Export is Jane Stre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by farhadhf in "Microsoft breached antitrust rules by bundling Teams and Office, EU says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794676</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794676"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T23:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This essentially killed my (EU-based) startup in the project management and collaborate space. Before MSFT bundled Teams with O365 we were rapidly growing and closing enterprise customers in the automotive, energy and education industries with high retention rates. Right around the time the Teams bundling started our retention dropped, churn went through the roof, growth slowed down, we failed to raise our next round because of it and had to drastically downsize the company, causing even more churn (about 80% net churn in 2 years). This move by the EU is good, but too little too late - 99% of the companies that were hurt by this have already shut down, and the ones still running will take years to recover...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>farhadhf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Netflix Reliability with Service-Level Prioritized Load Shedding]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e735e6ce8f7d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/enhancing-netflix-reliability-with-service-level-prioritized-load-shedding-e735e6ce8f7d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Quality of Service techniques at the application level]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by itsoktocry in "Waymo One is now open to everyone in San Francisco"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794263</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40794263"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love how we've gone from "Taxis are gross and dirty, that's why I love Uber!" to"Ubers are gross and dirty, that's why I love Waymo!" in the span of 5 years.
What do you think comes next? These cars are literally unsupervised.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>itsoktocry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ye Old Blogroll, a trove of links to blogs, personal websites]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7911</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ye-old-blogroll-trove-links-blogs-personal-websites/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My thanks to Ray for recently adding disassociated to Ye Old Blogroll, a directory of small and independent websites and blogs. Directory websites like Ray’s are invaluable when it comes to promoting the work of Indie and Small Web writers and bloggers, which is often overshadowed by all sorts of things, including some of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[about me]]></title>
        <id>https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/</id>
        <link href="https://iamyourboon.com/about-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm boon.
appreciate you for being here.
i've always wanted to be an astronaut but i found myself making bits fly instead. i love that which is aesthetic and i take great pride in designing beautiful distributed systems. i enjoy dota, strawberries, and software (in that order).
i like to think reasonably, objectively, creatively, simply, and always with the future in mind. i'm very strongly opinionated, but i love nothing more than being corrected correctly. i love learning experiences.
the majority of my posts will probably be irrelevant to you, especially since i enjoy yapping, but peruse at your leisure.
always happy to chat on twitter.
see you sometime,
boon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse, an IndieWeb arts community by Chris Shaw]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7899</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-artocalypse-indieweb-arts-community-chris-shaw/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Artocalypse is a subscription based community for artists on IndieWeb, created by Chris Shaw at uncountable thoughts. This a great cross-promotional idea, showcasing the work of artists, while also spreading the word about IndieWeb. I dare say some of the participating artists will already have followings elsewhere, and their membership of Artocalypse will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 forces data backup to OneDrive, possible workaround]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7893</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/windows-11-forces-data-backup-onedrive-possible-workaround/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T20:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe it’s time to start a Windows 11 is going just great website, similar to Molly White’s Web3 is Going Just Great. I say this after reading about another instance of heavy-handedness on Microsoft’s part, at Neowin: Quietly and without any announcement, the company changed Windows 11’s initial setup so that it could turn on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pimterry in "Polyfill supply chain attack hits 100K+ sites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40792222</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40792222"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T19:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> this domain was caught injecting malware on mobile devices via any site that embeds cdn.polyfill.io
I've said it before, and I'll say it again: https://httptoolkit.com/blog/public-cdn-risks/
You can reduce issues like this using subresource intergrity (SRI) but there are still tradeoffs (around privacy & reliability - see article above) and there is a better solution: self-host your dependencies behind a CDN service you control (just bunny/cloudflare/akamai/whatever is fine and cheap).
In a tiny prototyping project, a public CDN is convenient to get started fast, sure, but if you're deploying major websites I would really strong recommend not using public CDNs, never ever ever ever (the World Economic Forum website is affected here, for example! Absolutely ridiculous).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pimterry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by program_whiz in "Polyfill supply chain attack hits 100K+ sites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40792199</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40792199"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T18:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Game theory at work?  Someone needs to maintain legacy code for free that hosts thousands of sites and gets nothing but trouble (pride?) in return.  Meanwhile the forces of the world present riches and power in return to turn to the dark side (or maybe just letting your domain lapse and doing something else).
If security means every maintainer of every OSS package you use has to be scrupulous, tireless, and not screw up for life, not sure what to say when this kind of thing happens other than "isn't that the only possible outcome given the system and incentives on a long enough timeline?"
Kind of like the "why is my favorite company monetizing now and using dark patterns?"  Well, on an infinite timeline did you think service would remain high quality, free, well supported, and run by tireless, unselfish, unambitious benevolent dictators for the rest of your life? Or was it a foregone question that was only a matter of "when" not "if"?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>program_whiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by drojas in "Julian Assange has reached a plea deal with the U.S., allowing him to go free"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40791219</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40791219"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T17:36:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is almost bringing me to tears today. I am happy he's finally going to be free but I am still in deep sadness because this is not the world we are supposed to living in. With all of our knowledge and technology we are still doing horrible things as a civilization and we have lost control of our leadership. This scares me a lot because it is a growing problem and every day it seems like humanity is losing more and more of itself to evil and greedy powers that be. Assange did a great thing by exposing corrupt and criminal behavior at the highest levels and got such a inhumane treatment from the most powerful organizations on earth. He should not have been punished, he should have been protected and praised and his case should be a matter of study on every school on earth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>drojas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by w-m in "Testing AMD's Giant MI300X"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40791010</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40791010"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T17:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Impressions from last week’s CVPR, a conference with 12k attendees on computer vision - Pretty much everyone is using NVIDIA GPUs, and pretty much everyone isn’t happy with the prices, and would like some competition in the space:
NVIDIA was there with 57 papers, a website dedicated to their research presented at the conference, a full day tutorial on accelerating deep learning, and ever present with shirts and backpacks in the corridors and at poster presentations.
AMD had a booth at the expo part, where they were raffling off some GPUs. I went up to them to ask what framework I should look into, when writing kernels (ideally from Python) for GPGPU. They referred me to the “technical guy”, who it turns out had a demo on inference on an LLM. Which he couldn’t show me, as the laptop with the APU had crashed and wouldn’t reboot. He didn’t know about writing kernels, but told me there was a compiler guy who might be able to help, but he wasn’t to be found at that moment, and I couldn’t find him when returning to the booth later.
I’m not at all happy with this situation. As long as AMDs investment into software and evangelism remains at ~$0, I don’t see how any hardware they put out will make a difference. And you’ll continue to hear people walking away from their booth, saying “oh when I win it I’m going to sell it to buy myself an NVIDIA GPU”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>w-m</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21409</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/25/developer-tools/the-key-to-a-happy-rust-c-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The history of Rust at Meta goes all the way back to 2016, when we first started using it for source control. Today, it has been widely embraced at Meta and is one of our primary supported server-side languages (along with C++, Python, and Hack). But that doesn’t mean there weren’t any growing pains. Aida [...]
Read More...
The post The key to a happy Rust/C++ relationship appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by prasoonds in "Waymo One is now open to everyone in San Francisco"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40789666</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40789666"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I highly recommend everyone try it out if you're in SF. It's an incredibly smooth and sure ride. The cars are really nice too (Jaguar I-Pace electric cars), clean and spacious.
The first time you ride in one, it feels truly sci-fi. But within 5 minutes, you're almost bored of it - that's how good it is. If I had to choose between an Uber of questionable cleanliness and driver temperament and a Waymo with a slightly longer wait and slightly more fare, I'd choose the Waymo every time.
(I have no affiliation with Waymo, Google or any related industry - it's just an amazing service!)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>prasoonds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Nosferatu" theme for bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/nosferatu-theme-for-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/nosferatu-theme-for-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to share a new Bear Blog theme paying homage to the classic vampire film, Nosferatu. I was inspired to create this one after watching the trailer for the upcoming 2024 remake. The theme has an atmospheric aesthetic that evokes the haunting tone of the original movie. I've designed this theme to be ideal for blogs focused on horror, Gothic literature, or film reviews. The font treatment is also ideal for long-form book reviews or essays. I hope you enjoy exploring the CSS and customizing it to your liking. Now, if you'll excuse me, I think I hear rats scratching in the walls...
Demo: nosferatu.bearblog.dev 
static.mgx.me/css/nosferatu-v1.0.0.css]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Equally different]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/equally-different/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/equally-different/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I launched the July Reply blog challenge. I like the idea and hoped there would be a lot of interest, but so far, it's been lukewarm.
For the past few weeks, I have posted something new every day. Many of the texts that I've been proud of have barely gotten any attention at all.
“Why am I even doing this for?”
I heard myself thinking that today. It's so incredibly stupid and ridiculous that it's embarrassing to even mention it.
I'm doing this because I love it. If others like it too, great, but that's not the main purpose.
No one likes everything we do, whether we're a small blogger or the biggest artist in the world. On the other hand, we will always think that our latest creations are our best. Why else would we continue?
We are all different—equally different.
You're sitting on the world's best joke, looking forward to the laughter, but you're met with the reaction: “Is that all?”
Different.
You tell someone about the greatest movie ever made and then ask what they thought: “It wasn't to my taste, so I turned it off after half an hour."
Different.
You like watching football. I hate sports.
Different.
What a wonderful diversity!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices working with self-hosted GitHub Action runners at scale on AWS]]></title>
        <id>c54a5e17bad2934e3e0477995d7d86a4bf854ecd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-working-with-self-hosted-github-action-runners-at-scale-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview GitHub Actions is a continuous integration and continuous deployment platform that enables the automation of build, test and deployment activities for your workload. GitHub Self-Hosted Runners provide a flexible and customizable option to run your GitHub Action pipelines. These runners allow you to run your builds on your own infrastructure, giving you control over the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shilpa Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Neil44 in "Microsoft breached antitrust rules by bundling Teams and Office, EU says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40788021</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40788021"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They don't just bundle it, they make it auto-start on screen on Windows machines whether you've got an account or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil44</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by superultra in "Microsoft removes documentation for switching to a local account in Windows 11"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40787998</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40787998"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long long time ago as a poor college student, I signed up to get a “free PC.” You got a shitty packard bell tower for signing away your privacy and allowing a bunch of ads annd telemetry exist in the OS. It really wasn’t that intrusive and eventually the company folded and I got a free (shitty) ad-free pc out of it.
I’m a Mac user now but when I pull up windows 11 on my kid’s or wife’s laptop, it feels like that free-pc dot com again, only it’s in every person’s PC. I’m genuinely shocked at the amount of trash that barrages a common user in windows, and shocked that Microsoft gets away with it.
My 14 year old gets barraged with not just co-pilot but a bunch of news and trash clickbait that is straight inappropriate for kids to see.
I’ve had to remove it all twice but with every significant update, somehow my settings get reversed and we’re back at square one.
I tried even using local accounts but it causes significant issues in the OS.
If you’d told me in 1999 that free-pc.com was the dystopian digital future we’d all be living in, I’d have laughed you out of the room - but that’s exactly what we have. The only difference is that the PC isn’t free. We are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>superultra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oblio in "From 0/10 to 8/10: Microsoft Puts Repair Front and Center"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40785180</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40785180"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T06:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker news: the place where Americans find out about current and future EU legislation through the lens of propaganda from American corporations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oblio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Julian Assange has reached a plea deal with the U.S., allowing him to go free"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40783505</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40783505"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T01:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That is the text of https://twitter.com/wikileaks/status/1805388007475732646, for those keeping track. (We merged that thread hither from https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40782571.)
Other URLs from threads we merged:
https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-06-25/julian-assange-releas...
https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/24/us/politics/assange-plea....
https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/crgggyvp0j9o]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scarmig in "Denver gave homeless people $1k/mth. Year later, nearly half had housing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40783341</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40783341"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T01:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interestingly:
People who received $1k/month: 44% housed
People who received a $6500 lump sum followed by $500/month: 48% housed
The control group who received $50/month: 43% housed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scarmig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by esnard in "Julian Assange has reached a plea deal with the U.S., allowing him to go free"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40782572</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40782572"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T23:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JULIAN ASSANGE IS FREE
Julian Assange is free. He left Belmarsh maximum security prison on the morning of 24 June, after having spent 1901 days there. He was granted bail by the High Court in London and was released at Stanstead airport during the afternoon, where he boarded a plane and departed the UK.
This is the result of a  global campaign that spanned grass-roots organisers, press freedom  campaigners, legislators and leaders from across the political spectrum,  all the way to the United Nations. This created the space for a long period of negotiations with the US Department of Justice, leading to a deal that has not yet been formally finalised. We will provide more information as soon as possible.
After more than five years in a 2x3 metre cell, isolated 23 hours a day, he will soon reunite with his wife Stella Assange, and their children, who have only known their father from behind bars.
WikiLeaks published groundbreaking stories of government corruption and human rights abuses, holding the powerful accountable for their actions. As editor-in-chief, Julian paid severely for these principles,and for the people's right to know.
As he returns to Australia, we thank all who stood by us, fought for us, and remained utterly committed in the fight for his freedom.
Julian's freedom is our freedom.
[More details to follow]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>esnard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jaas in "More Memory Safety for Let's Encrypt: Deploying ntpd-rs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781863"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T22:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the person driving this.
NTP is worth moving to a memory safe language but of course it's not the single most critical thing in our entire stack to make memory safe. I don't think anyone is claiming that. It's simply the first component that got to production status, a good place to start.
NTP is a component worth moving to a memory safe language because it's a widely used critical service on a network boundary. A quick Google for NTP vulnerabilities will show you that there are plenty of memory safety vulnerabilities lurking in C NTP implementations:
https://www.cvedetails.com/vulnerability-list/vendor_id-2153...
Some of these are severe, some aren't. It's only a matter of time though until another severe one pops up.
I don't think any critical service on a network boundary should be written in C/C++, we know too much at this point to think that's a good idea. It will take a while to change that across the board though.
If I had to pick the most important thing in the context of Let's Encrypt to move to a memory safe language it would be DNS. We have been investing heavily in Hickory DNS but it's not ready for production at Let's Encrypt yet (our usage of DNS is a bit more complex than the average use case).
https://github.com/hickory-dns/hickory-dns
Work is proceeding at a rapid pace and I expect Hickory DNS to be deployed at Let's Encrypt in 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jaas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by suby in "Windows 11 is now enabling OneDrive folder backup without asking permission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781691</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781691"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T22:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened to me. I was wondering why my internet speeds were slow when I discovered that Microsoft was in the process of uploading my users directory, they had already uploaded almost two gigs when I realized. They also changed the path to these directories to something like C:\Users\name\OneDrive\Desktop\. Another poster in this thread claimed it's easy to reverse -- I disagree, it's a pain in the ass to track down the setting, and I shouldn't have to do this. When I did, it gave me an error for one of the directories and refuses to revert (documents?).
I don't like leaving negative or hyperbolic comments on HN, but this was enraging and unacceptable to me. It's hard to convey without coming off as unhinged. I only ever boot into Windows nowadays when I need to compile and test a Windows build of software. I understand Microsoft has built up good will through efforts like VS Code, but it's all undone because of things like this. I avoid MS products, they cannot be trusted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put your Palace Cinema wine glass in the cup-holder carefully]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7882</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/put-palace-cinema-wine-glass-cup-holder-carefully/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether they are a part of an on-going series of light-hearted clips by Australian cinema group Palace Cinemas, remains to be seen, but the two I’ve caught to date, on their Instagram page, have been pretty witty. The first is in response to the apparent problem of patrons nicking the cinema’s wine glasses. Why would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i gave my depression one month]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/i-gave-my-depression-one-month/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/i-gave-my-depression-one-month/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:28:45.709Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Towards the end of May, I promised myself I would give this life my all for one month. Just for one month, I told myself. If I still can't find myself gaining control of depression, then I can give up, but at least I would have given up contently knowing I tried.
Last night, I was unable to sleep (unfortunately, insomnia seems to be a common side effect in antidepressants). I stared up the ceiling aimlessly, and pondered, A month has passed. Even more. I am still the same. What changed?
I was clearly anxious and upset throughout the day, because I skipped work too. I told myself I deserved a break, but deep down I knew I was lying to myself. The break was an excuse. I actually wanted to run from work and people and from existing in general. Because, after a month, I felt like nothing chang…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping keep customers safe with leaked password notification]]></title>
        <id>6675c883a4598c000bd703c6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/helping-keep-customers-safe-with-leaked-password-notification"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help protect against account compromise via credential stuffing attacks, Cloudflare will notify dashboard users when we detect that a password was found in an external data breach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Galow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive scaling of Amazon ECS services using Amazon ECS Service Connect Metrics]]></title>
        <id>dddca191d6a2df5df6c28c233a33652b924833c9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/proactive-scaling-of-amazon-ecs-services-using-amazon-ecs-service-connect-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post discusses Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) Service Connect, a capability that provides a secure and scalable way to connect different Amazon ECS service deployments. This enables seamless communication between micro-services while reducing the operational overhead. It provides features such as service discovery, load balancing, and network traffic metrics. This post primarily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Nalpet Ramakrishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging AI for efficient incident response]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21393</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/24/data-infrastructure/leveraging-ai-for-efficient-incident-response/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing how we streamline system reliability investigations using a new AI-assisted root cause analysis system. The system uses a combination of heuristic-based retrieval and large language model-based ranking to speed up root cause identification during investigations. Our testing has shown this new system achieves 42% accuracy in identifying root causes for investigations at their [...]
Read More...
The post Leveraging AI for efficient incident response appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Claude 3.5 Sonnet in Amazon Bedrock, CodeCatalyst updates, SageMaker with MLflow, and more (June 24, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>7dacc08a7aef106cc0797e9788dead147aa616ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-5-sonnet-in-amazon-bedrock-codecatalyst-updates-sagemaker-with-mlflow-and-more-june-24-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I had the opportunity to try the new Anthropic Claude 3.5 Sonnet model in Amazon Bedrock just before it launched, and I was really impressed by its speed and accuracy! It was also the week of AWS Summit Japan. JAWS-UG, a Japanese AWS user group, held various sessions with AWS Heroes and Community Builders at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fanf2 in "Microfeatures I love in blogs and personal websites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40776533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40776533"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T14:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of these suggestions are good. (I should make my subheds clickable!) But a couple of them, oh dear…
I really hate progress bars, they are incredibly distracting. One of the worst examples of front end programmers wasting their time reimplementing browser functions badly. I already have scroll bars! I do not need more scroll bars!
Also, link decoration: my browser already has a nice discreet indicator to tell me where a link goes, I don’t need or want mysterious dingbats in the running text. (It reminds me of websites that are so scared of hyperlinks that they send them via interstitial warning pages “YOU ARE LEAVING THE SITE!!!!1!1!”, or in a recent case via a $yber$ecurity box that broke the link completely.) And preview popups? Get in the sea, hostile obnoxious interruption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fanf2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using machine learning to detect bot attacks that leverage residential proxies]]></title>
        <id>66722bd6a4598c000bd700f0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/residential-proxy-bot-detection-using-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare's Bot Management team has released a new Machine Learning model for bot detection (v8), focusing on bots and abuse from residential proxies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob AminAzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciphering the Disinflation Process]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30281</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/deciphering-the-disinflation-process/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. inflation surged in the early post-COVID period, driven by several economic shocks such as supply chain disruptions and labor supply constraints. Following its peak at 6.6 percent in September 2022, core consumer price index (CPI) inflation has come down rapidly over the last two years, falling to 3.6 percent recently. What explains the rapid shifts in U.S. inflation dynamics? In a recent paper, we show that the interaction between supply chain pressures and labor market tightness amplified the inflation surge in 2021. In this post, we argue that these same forces that drove the nonlinear rise in inflation have worked in reverse since late 2022, accelerating the disinflationary process. The current episode contrasts with periods where the economy was hit by shocks to either imported inputs or to labor alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Heise and Ayşegül Şahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JumpCrisscross in "US prosecutors recommend Justice Department criminally charge Boeing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774272</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774272"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> This will go nowhere
As will this comment thread. We saw the same rhetoric on Holmes and Bankman-Fried. Once they were charged it was obvious they’d get off. Once convicted that they’d get a light sentence. Once sentenced that they’d have their sentences shortened, et cetera.
It’s a lazy learned helplessness that’s always potentially right because it feeds into a type of cynicism that has always been part of human nature in every culture since the beginning of history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JumpCrisscross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by madeofpalk in "Apple found in breach of EU competition rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774176</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774176"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can feel however you want about Apple's rules and EU regulation, but I think it's pretty indispuitable how wrong it is that Apple prevents developers from explaining these rules to their users. Apple prevents developers from saying that Apple takes a % cut of the sale. Apple prevents developers from saying its available cheaper elsewhere. If Apple feels these rules are so just and fair and indispuitably correct, why does it go to such measures to hide them from its consumers?
Consistently these anti-steering rules are what gets Apple in trouble all around the world. It's the one part Apple lost in the US Epic case, and it's the EUs first point on their breach. Apple has done this to themselves by being so stubborn and refusing to budge an inch on how they run their platforms. The tiniest concession years ago could have avoided all this regulation on them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madeofpalk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Compromised Cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16687</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/catching-compromised-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slack uses cookies to track session states for users on slack.com and the Slack Desktop app. The ever-present cookie banners have made cookies mainstream, but as a quick refresher, cookies are a little piece of client-side state associated with a website that is sent up to the web server on every request. Websites use this […]
The post Catching Compromised Cookies appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Slama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DebtDeflation in "US prosecutors recommend Justice Department criminally charge Boeing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773948</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773948"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T09:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem for Boeing is that this wasn't a one time thing.  Two weeks ago it came out that they were using counterfeit titanium, then a few days later the CEO testifies that they had in fact retaliated against whistleblowers, then a few days later it comes out that they actually hid faulty parts from FAA regulators and then lost them.  Every apple that gets pulled from the bushel is rotten and there are a lot of apples left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DebtDeflation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sim7c00 in "I am using AI to drop hats outside my window onto New Yorkers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773600</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773600"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T08:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems to only support windows :(]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sim7c00</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The economic crisis and unfolding disaster in Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45445</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/24/the-economic-crisis-and-unfolding-disaster-in-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The population of Argentina is suffering. The purchasing power of people who still have a job is down (a lot), and unemployment must have doubled (it was 5,7% in the last quarter of 2023) if it has not tripled. Less government spending, less consumer spending, and, no doubt, less private investment means that Argentina is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the trap of good memories]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I struggle with this thing, of remembering certain people in such a golden light. Before this seems like a post talking about not-so-good people, it's not. It's about perfectly nice people.
The thing is, the way I tend to remember people is by how they made me feel. Few people in my life have made me feel like a real, raw person when talking to them. But some have. Some of these people are miles away, and have maybe always been miles away, both geographically and otherwise.
It's a really painful thing, because as these memories I hold go further and further back in my memory, I don't know what I want anymore. All I really want is to feel the way they made me feel again. Not so easy though, is it?
We've both grown in separate ways, and I'm grateful for where I am in my life, I think I've done pretty alright for myself so far. No matter what I do though, it does feel like there's a certain hole in my life, somewhere I'm lacking greatly. The remedy is so far though. Maybe it doesn't even exist, not anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Extensions are all you need]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to extend GitHub Copilot by using the Chat and Language Model APIs in your Visual Studio Code extension. Get inspired by early adopters and their extensions.
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A book about ferns: the truth of the three-hour Gilligan’s Island cruise]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7876</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/book-ferns-truth-three-hour-gilligans-island-cruise/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gilligan’s Island was a slapstick American TV series which ran from 1964 to 1967. Despite its popularity, the show was cancelled shortly before filming of a fourth series commenced. I first saw reruns of Gilligan’s quite some time later. A number of movies, featuring most of the original cast, were made between 1978 and 1982. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We can’t have a new paradigm as long as people think the old one was free-market fundamentalism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45437</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/23/we-cant-have-a-new-paradigm-as-long-as-people-think-the-old-one-was-free-market-fundamentalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The belief in free-market fundamentalism runs very deep. When I say that, I don’t mean that support for the concept runs deep, I mean the belief that we had been pursuing free-market policies in the years before the Trump and Biden presidency runs very deep. I was reminded of this fact in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Selfish Woes About Dark Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a fan of having dark mode on my site because I have a hard time choosing colors that speak to me. I like to keep things minimalistic with my colors, and for me, it’s just much easier to do with a white background. However, I know (and acknowledge) the importance of having one, and so I pushed myself to do some tinkering on the blog this morning. Besides, my eyeballs also hate me when I look at my site at night, and so I’m sure it’s the case for other people too.
I subscribe to a lot of blogs via RSS reader, but I do take the extra step to launch their site to read the post. I have a deep appreciation for those who take the time to design their site the way they want, and so I want to read their posts the way it was meant to be read. It’s kind of like: listening to an album in order because I know that the artist ordered it a specific way for people to listen to. At the same time, it’s OK if you want to shuffle the playlist if you as the consumer want to, just like it’s OK for those who read my posts to do so via an RSS feed.
Anyways, this is just a quick post to say that, if your preference is dark mode, it is now available on here. I’ll revisit my site again at night time to test out the color contrasts (since I worked on this during daytime) to see if it makes sense, or if my eyeballs are still straining to read things.
Due to this, I’ve also gone ahead and created a Changelog for my site, so I can keep track of the little (and big) changes I make on here.
Side note:
I typically do have my screens on dark mode, and so if the sites/blog I read have dark mode, I read those in dark mode. It’s a weird thing for me to want my site in a lighter background, but I do struggle with it sometimes. Thanks to those who have put up with probably burning your retinas reading my posts if you weren’t doing so in an RSS reader. I appreciate you.
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TrianguloY in "Start all of your commands with a comma (2009)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769974</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769974"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T19:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those can really be called comma_nds!
Ahem. Nice idea though, I think I'll start using it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TrianguloY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Anthropic's Claude 3.5 Sonnet  All You Need -  Vibe check]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro
Source
    
I have been subbed to Claude Opus for a few months (yes, I am an earlier believer than you people). Couple of days back, I was working on a project and opened Anthropic chat. Then I realised it was showing "Sonnet 3.5 - Our most intelligent model" and it was seriously a major surprise.
I have been playing with with it for a couple of days now. Wrote some code ranging from Python, HTML, CSS, JSS to Pytorch and Jax. Made it do some editing and proof-reading. So far it's been smooth sailing. Maybe we haven't hit a wall yet (Ok I am not important enough to comment on this but you gotta remember it's my blog).
But why vibe-check, aren't benchmarks enough? Oversimplifying here but I think you cannot trust benchmarks blindly. There can be benchmark data leakage/overfitting to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Narbonne Cathedral (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52793</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/23/sunday-photoblogging-narbonne-cathedral-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T06:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Rooum - Anarchism is about individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T14:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Donald Rooum
Title: Anarchism is about individuals
Date: 1986
Notes: From the 1986 centenary issue of Freedom, pp. 56–57
Source: Retrieved on 2024-06-21 from https://files.libcom.org/files/freedom-centenary.pdf

 There is no such thing as human society. 
 A lot of muddled thinking rests on the error that because ‘society’ is a useful noun, it must refer to a thing. It is one of those nouns like ‘journey’ and ‘tennis’, which refers not to a thing but to a relationship between things. The statement ‘human society exists’ is simply a less cumbersome way of saying ‘human individuals relate to each other in certain complicated ways’. The question, ‘what is the purpose of human society?’ means the same as, ‘why do human individuals associate in the way they do?’. 
 Human craving for soci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The day I talked to my crush.]]></title>
        <id>https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/</id>
        <link href="https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T13:44:53.532Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was exciting, to say the least. I had an exam that day, and people usually finish their exams and go on their way. The problem was I had never talked to my crush before, so I couldn't exactly call her up to meet me. I finished my exam really early—about an hour and a half early—so that I wouldn't miss her.
Let's cut back to the morning of that day. I had already prepared what I wanted to say to her. But since I might talk non-stop, I decided to go with a letter (yeah, I'm old school that way—don't judge me). I woke up and did my morning routine (yes, I do have a routine). Then I wrote what I wanted to say, put it in an envelope, and went to the gym because I was too excited and nervous.
Now back to the scene where I'm waiting in the corridor for her to come out of the exam hall. Man, I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fault-isolated, zonal deployments with AWS CodeDeploy]]></title>
        <id>6bdb1a94f1d30c014904a2d39161cd2f38f4fcfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/fault-isolated-zonal-deployments-with-aws-codedeploy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post you’ll learn how to use a new feature in AWS CodeDeploy to deploy your application one Availability Zone (AZ) at a time to help increase the operational resilience or your services through improved fault isolation. Introducing change to a system can be a time of risk. Even the most advanced CI/CD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Haken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways Amazon Q simplifies AWS CloudFormation development]]></title>
        <id>325586d795e23aaa06a2c511ac9f946c1213c70b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-ways-amazon-q-simplifies-aws-cloudformation-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the full potential of AWS CloudFormation development with Amazon Q. Generate templates, understand resources, explain code, troubleshoot issues, and query documentation seamlessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>