<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-17T12:50:08.693Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-17T12:50:08.693Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/17/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280468</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-17-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Conflicts in the Middle East Spill Over Into the Caucasus (Part 2): What Are the US and Türkiye Up To?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280498</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/will-the-conflicts-in-the-middle-east-spill-over-into-the-caucasus-part-2-what-are-the-us-and-turkiye-up-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US tutors Armenia on the ins and outs of being non-agreement-capable. Türkiye up to no good? Russia remains patient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Disruptive Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-disruptive-elements?v=1729159011</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-disruptive-elements?v=1729159011"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Disruptive Elements
Subtitle: The Extremes of French Anarchism
Date: 2014
Notes: A dense compendium of old and brand-new translations of a dizzying array of names from the individualist anarchist tendency, mostly from early 20th Century France. New translations from Wolfi Landstreicher, Shawn Wilbur, and Vincent Stone. Anyone who is interested in this tendency, fans of My Own, Enemies of Society, Stirner’s works, etc., will find much to enjoy and fodder for future research in this book.
Source: <opendistro.net/pdf-library/disruptive-elements>

If Pierre Chardon overflowed with ardor, enthusiasm, activity, he was intransigent. Verbosity inspired pity in him; the verbosity of rhetoricians as well as that of revolutionaries. He wanted to “practice” in the field …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das: Interrogating Russian History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280450</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/satyajit-das-interrogating-russian-history.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das discusses three new books on Russian history that profess to offer new insights, with predictably mixed results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firm Behind £4M Labour Party Donation Invested in Weapons for Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280494</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/firm-behind-4m-labour-party-donation-invested-in-weapons-for-israel.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T08:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quadrature Capital, which gave the Labour Party’s largest-ever donation, held shares in arms companies that make Israeli fighter jets and bombs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Children Are Murdered, What is There to Celebrate?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337990</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/when-children-are-murdered-what-is-there-to-celebrate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After news broke that Han Kang—the South Korean author—had won the Nobel Prize for Literature, her father—the novelist Han Seung-won—asked her where she wanted to hold a press conference to talk about the award. She published her fiction with Changbi and her poetry with Munhakdongne, both of which hoped to host her. Initially, Han Kang, the 53-year-old author of the 2016 Booker Prize-winning The Vegetarian, thought that she would talk to the press. But then, after reflection, she told her father that he should make a statement in her place. “With the war intensifying and people being carried out dead every day,” she told the press through her father, “How can we have a celebration or a press conference?” More
The post When Children Are Murdered, What is There to Celebrate? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Her Father’s Footsteps: an Interview With Che’s Daughter, Aleida Guevara]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337961</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/in-her-fathers-footsteps-an-interview-with-ches-daughter-aleida-guevara/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was 1967. In La Higuera, a small village in the Vallegrande region of the Santa Cruz Department in Bolivia, there was a man leading a small guerrilla group that had been fighting for months to transform the Bolivian state. He had arrived in Bolivia from Cuba in November 1966 under the pseudonym “Fernando.” Initially,  More
The post In Her Father’s Footsteps: an Interview With Che’s Daughter, Aleida Guevara appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilantha Ilangamuwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Threat of Christofascism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337834</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/the-threat-of-christofascism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. is struggling through a profound socio-political crisis reflecting the deeper global economic and environmental realignments now taking place.  The presidential campaigns of Kamala Harris and Donald Trump signify a unique expression of the crisis: Harris, moderation and accommodation; Trump, radicalism and selfishness.   The election outcome will shape the nation for a decade to  More
The post The Threat of Christofascism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Florida’s Abortion Measure: DeSantis Angles for a Mistrial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338203</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/floridas-abortion-measure-desantis-angles-for-a-mistrial/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Florida’s proposed Amendment 4 would add the following language to the state constitution’s Declaration of Rights: “… no law shall prohibit, penalize, delay, or restrict abortion before viability or when necessary to protect the patient’s health, as determined by the patient’s healthcare provider,” except for requiring parental notification when a minor seeks an abortion. I  More
The post Florida’s Abortion Measure: DeSantis Angles for a Mistrial appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[34 Million Seniors in Medicare Advantage Plans Face Rude Awakening]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337941</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/34-million-seniors-in-medicare-advantage-plans-face-rude-awakening/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[October 15 marks the first day of open enrollment in Medicare Advantage (MA) plans – a time that will deliver chaos and confusion for many of the 34 million seniors who depend on these plans to pay their healthcare bills. It’s yet another reminder that Medicare wastes billions of dollars funneling public money to private  More
The post 34 Million Seniors in Medicare Advantage Plans Face Rude Awakening appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma Curchin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CA’s New Law: ADL Genocide Deniers to Train Teachers on Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338132</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/cas-new-law-adl-genocide-deniers-to-train-teachers-on-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not long after Wikipedia’s volunteer editors rejected the Anti-Defamation League (ADL) as a credible source on Israel/Palestine and antisemitism, California Governor Gavin Newsom signed SB 1277 into law to empower the ADL and their allies to actively suppress discussion of Palestinians as victims of genocide and occupation. The law–promoted by the California Legislative Jewish Caucus–establishes  More
The post CA’s New Law: ADL Genocide Deniers to Train Teachers on Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcy Winograd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Godzilla at 70: The Monster’s Warning to Humanity Remains urgent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337823</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/godzilla-at-70-the-monsters-warning-to-humanity-remains-urgent/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Nobel Peace Prize has been awarded to Nihon Hidankyo, the Japan Confederation of A- and H-bomb Sufferers Organizations. Many of these witnesses have spent their lives warning of the dangers of nuclear war – but initially, much of the world didn’t want to hear it. “The fates of those who survived the infernos  More
The post Godzilla at 70: The Monster’s Warning to Humanity Remains urgent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Kennell – Jessica McManus Warnell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 economic sciences laureates]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45678</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/17/the-2024-economic-sciences-laureates/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The Sveriges Riksbank Prize in Economic Sciences in Memory of Alfred Nobel 2024 is awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson “for studies of how institutions are formed and affect prosperity.”  Daron Acemoglu and James Robinson’s work, particularly in Why Nations Fail (2012), is widely recognized within new institutional economics for its […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Threat of ‘Robotic’ Warfare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338121</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/17/the-growing-threat-of-robotic-warfare/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 7th, 2001, the first reported use of a weaponized unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) (or drone) occurred in Kandahar, Afghanistan. In what appeared to be a mistake that would become all too common in the years to come, the CIA’s target, Taliban leader Mullah Omar, was nowhere near the scene of the strike. At the time,  More
The post The Growing Threat of ‘Robotic’ Warfare appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Royden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Neuburger: Carbon Sinks Are Failing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280452</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/thomas-neuburger-carbon-sinks-are-failing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T04:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On carbon sinks becoming inoperative: 'Nature has so far balanced our abuse. This is coming to an end']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Macaulay Library, Bird Songs, and Citizen Science]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280483</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/the-macaulay-library-bird-songs-and-citizen-science.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:25:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tiny singing dinosaur friends, and the assets they create....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to reduce bad screen time, while needing good screen time?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8691</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/how-reduce-bad-screen-time-while-needing-good-screen-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mary Grace Descourouez, writing for Stanford Lifestyle Medicine: Additional studies found that adults who engage in excessive screen time or have a diagnosed smartphone addiction had lower gray matter volume. Gray matter is brain tissue essential for daily human functioning and is responsible for everything from movement to memory to emotions. Gray matter volume naturally […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexandrB in "AI PCs Aren't Good at AI: The CPU Beats the NPU"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863552</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41863552"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Also, people often mistake the reason for an NPU is "speed". That's not correct. The whole point of the NPU is rather to focus on low power consumption.
I have a sneaking suspicion that the real real reason for an NPU is marketing. "Oh look, NVDA is worth $3.3T - let's make sure we stick some AI stuff in our products too."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexandrB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives and progressives have different brain structures]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8687</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/conservatives-progressives-different-brain-structures/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to political leanings, I’m probably centre/left. But I have a number of family and acquaintances who definitely lean more to the right. Of course, everyone is different, but certain of the mannerisms of the more conservative people I know are particularly distinct. To me, these seemed to go beyond regular personal preference. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating multi-AZ high availability for WebLogic administration server with DNS: Part 2]]></title>
        <id>4b7294a6fcaa6819d859ea467faf2491ebb12ac2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/automating-multi-az-high-availability-for-weblogic-administration-server-with-dns-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T20:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, we used a floating virtual IP (VIP) to achieve hands-off high availability (HA) of WebLogic Admin Server. In Part 2, we’ll achieve an arguably superior solution using Domain Name System (DNS) resolution. Using a DNS to resolve the address for WebLogic admin server Let’s look at the reference WebLogic […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Geddes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS optimized Amazon Linux 2023 accelerated AMIs now available]]></title>
        <id>593079c1e25d7535b97de1bcd70da92cb64657a3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-optimized-amazon-linux-2023-accelerated-amis-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Earlier this year we announced support for Amazon EKS optimized AL2023 AMIs that provided many enhancements in terms of security and performance. Amazon Linux 2023 (AL2023) is the next generation of Amazon Linux from Amazon Web Services (AWS) and is designed to provide a secure, stable, and high-performance environment to develop and run your […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse Butler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Believe nothing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338141</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/believe-nothing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post Believe nothing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stclair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280458</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T18:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Michelle stays home; Trump to work the grill at McDonald's in Philly; Trump's "fascism"; Boeing borrows $10 billion, fights off junk status for now, faces break-up ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling a Large Language Model with NVIDIA NIM on Amazon EKS with Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>959b0cd8030d1d8de276b6f0cd400ca1059430a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/scaling-a-large-language-model-with-nvidia-nim-on-amazon-eks-with-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T17:17:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations are building artificial intelligence (AI) applications using Large Language Models (LLMs) to deliver new experiences to their customers, from content creation to customer service and data analysis. However, the substantial size and intensive computational requirements of these models may have challenges in configuring, deploying, and scaling them effectively on graphic processing units (GPUs). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shawn Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Calavar in "Winamp deletes entire GitHub source code repo after a rocky few weeks"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861254</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861254"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've lost a lot with the deletion of this repo. Not the code - that's already out in the ether - but the absurdist comedy of the issues, pull requests, and commit history of trying to piecemeal delete third party non-FOSS software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Calavar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance release control with AWS CodePipeline stage-level conditions]]></title>
        <id>65f440ccd69151ae494d678b6627abe59b90c9e0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/enhance-release-control-with-aws-codepipeline-stage-level-conditions/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an established practice for development teams to build deployment pipelines, with services such as AWS CodePipeline, to increase the quality of application and infrastructure releases through reliable, repeatable and consistent automation. Automating the deployment process helps build quality into our products by introducing continuous integration to build and test code, however enterprises may sometimes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Bachman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by justinpombrio in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861129</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41861129"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:43:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsubscribe links are a fantastic regulation, but there is a workaround. I must have received at least a dozen emails from Brown after graduating despite unsubscribing to every email they sent.
The trouble is they're endlessly creative about the lists they put you on. I'd get one email from "Alumni Connections" and then another from "Faculty Spotlight" and then another from "Global Outreach" and then another from "Event Invitations, 2023 series". I'm making those names up because I forget exactly what they were called, but you get the idea. I hope this was in violation of the regulation: surely you can't invent a new mailing list that didn't used to exist, add me to it, and require me to unsubscribe from it individually.
They finally stopped after I sent them an angry email.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justinpombrio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Issues in Economic Analysis in an Increasingly Turbulent Security Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280456</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/key-issues-in-economic-analysis-in-an-increasingly-turbulent-security-environment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a period of rapid growth, recent trends in world trade reveal a phase of stagnation. Rising geopolitical tensions have been accompanied by trade restrictions in the name of national and economic security. Analysis of economic security measures should consider multiple dimensions, including the effect on global supply chains, efficiency, costs, foreign direct investment, trade in services, and international competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Uehreka in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41860626</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41860626"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T15:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people try and say that regulating stuff like this is impossible, I often think about how unreasonably great the regulations around “Unsubscribe” links in emails are.
There really seems to be no loophole or workaround despite there being huge incentive for there to be one. Every time I click an “Unsubscribe” link in an email (it seems like they’re forced to say “Unsubscribe” and not use weasel words to hide the link) I’m either immediately unsubscribed from the person who sent me the email, or I’m taken to a page which seemingly MUST have a “remove me from all emails” option.
The level of compliance (and they can’t even do malicious compliance!) with this is absurd. If these new rules work anything like that, they’ll be awesome. Clearly regulating behavior like this is indeed possible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uehreka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ajkjk in "FTC announces "click-to-cancel" rule making it easier to cancel subscriptions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41859541</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41859541"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T14:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are so many things like this that have needed fixing for such a long time. The fact that something is happening, even slowly, is so heartening.
If your reaction is wondering if this is legal then you should be interested in the passing of new laws that make it unequivocally legal. Society should be able to govern itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ajkjk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instant Well-Architected CDK Resources with Solutions Constructs Factories]]></title>
        <id>7008c6ada575bca57e3ce795352aa4475347ca7d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/instant-well-architected-cdk-resources-with-solutions-constructs-factories/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For several years, AWS Solutions Constructs have helped thousands of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) users accelerate their creation of well-architected workloads by providing small, composable patterns linking two or more AWS services, such as an Amazon S3 bucket triggering an AWS Lambda function. Over this time, customers with use cases that don’t match an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Biff Gaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways to optimize code with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>b9326e05e2ea846501a662f4c405f59150fe3959</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-ways-to-optimize-code-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical improvement and optimization of software quality requires expert-level knowledge across various subjects. As such, in this blog we shall look at how Amazon Q Developer can help improve your development team productivity and application stability by enabling automation around code optimization by improving your code’s quality, performance, application infrastructure specifications. The blog will also look […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karthik Chemudupati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code security scanning with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>6d44f9c81cc19acd510afee10e3ea6effb8cc074</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/code-security-scanning-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A primary objective of software developers is to develop products that uphold the highest standards of data privacy and security, fostering trust and confidence among their users and customers. Developers seek to secure their software by identifying and mitigating security vulnerabilities in their codebase, thereby enhancing its resilience against cyber threats. Amazon Q Developer, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surabhi Tandon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs Are Not Commodities]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/blogs-are-not-commodities/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/blogs-are-not-commodities/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somehow, when I first investigated starting a blog, I managed to avoid the many websites devoted to creating a money-making machine USING THESE 10 SIMPLE TRICKS!!! The blogs I was familiar with weren't covered in ads, and I didn't have to pay to read them. There was an occasional invitation to buy the writer a coffee, but nothing high-pressure or gross.
A couple of weeks ago, Keenan, the creator of A Very Good Blog, wrote a long, heartfelt post about his lifelong relationship with his much-loved cousin and how the American political divide affected their relationship. It's the kind of work that deserves to be included in an anthology and everyone's Best of 2024 collections. It wasn't surrounded by banner advertisements or cut off in the middle with a place for paying customers to log in. N…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280424</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our five star-rated daily links.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Conflicts in the Middle East Spill Over Into the Caucasus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280428</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/will-the-conflicts-in-the-middle-east-spill-over-into-the-caucasus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The standoff between Armenia and Azerbaijan is being used to apply more pressure on Iran and has all the signs of a neocon divide and conquer scheme.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Exciting Year for CounterPunch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338125</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/an-exciting-year-for-counterpunch/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please consider donating to our annual fund drive.
The post An Exciting Year for CounterPunch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Your Feminism Include Palestine?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337972</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/does-your-feminism-include-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Women's Marches are being planned across the country ahead of Election Day to "show the strength of our feminist movement." However, curiously missing from the talking points around the strength of the feminist movement is the women of Palestine - who have endured the brutality of anti-feminist policies for decades under the illegal occupation by Israel. More
The post Does Your Feminism Include Palestine? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nour Jaghama - Grace Siegelman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Han Kang’s Nobel Prize Award is a Cry for Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337746</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/han-kangs-nobel-prize-award-is-a-cry-for-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean novelist Han Kang has won the Nobel Prize for Literature, beating short-listed literary heavyweights like Thomas Pynchon, Haruki Murakami, Salman Rushdie, Gerald Murnane, and the all-odds-favorite, Chinese author Can Xue.  Han Kang was as shocked as anyone else after receiving the call notifying her that she had won. When asked what she would do next, she said she would quietly "have tea with her son".  More
The post Han Kang’s Nobel Prize Award is a Cry for Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KJ Noh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powder Keg in the Pacific]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337979</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/powder-keg-in-the-pacific/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the world looks on with trepidation at regional wars in Israel and Ukraine, a far more dangerous global crisis is quietly building at the other end of Eurasia, along an island chain that has served as the front line for America’s national defense for endless decades. Just as Russia’s invasion of Ukraine has revitalized  More
The post Powder Keg in the Pacific appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred W. McCoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy Dies in Crude Oil]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337975</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/democracy-dies-in-crude-oil/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental activists rarely get to celebrate a major win for the planet, but that’s what happened in Ecuador in August last year. After a decade-long struggle between activists and the government, a referendum was held on whether to continue drilling for oil in a protected part of the Amazon. The people voted to kick the  More
The post Democracy Dies in Crude Oil appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adem Ay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s War on the United Nations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338066</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/israels-war-on-the-united-nations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Nations is an easy body to hate.  At times, it seems to be effusion without substance, body with no backbone.  It was conceived in a fit of post-war idealism, when egos were humbled and hatred briefly stemmed.  Over the ruins of the Second World War, the builders were favored over the destroyers and mischief makers –  More
The post Israel’s War on the United Nations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: I Read the News Today, Oh Boy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337582</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/letter-from-london-i-read-the-news-today-oh-boy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[London, 4.44am. I used to catch minicabs to airports around this time. To Kabul, via Dubai, or a plane direct to New York. Back then, a quick blast of Bob Marley’s Three Little Birds or Public Image’s Rise. Golden Slumbers by The Beatles at nightfall. Nowadays, how about Adrianne Lenker’s song Anything? On this morning  More
The post Letter from London: I Read the News Today, Oh Boy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Words Matter: “Scratching” the Surface of American Racism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=338063</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/words-matter-scratching-the-surface-of-american-racism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When I use a word,” Humpty Dumpty said in rather a scornful tone, “it means just what I choose it to mean – neither more nor less.” “The question is,” said Alice, “whether you can make words mean so many different things.” “The question is,” said Humpty Dumpty, “which is to be master – that’s  More
The post Words Matter: “Scratching” the Surface of American Racism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John G. Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toward an Economy Not Dependent on Endless Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337585</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/toward-an-economy-not-dependent-on-endless-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part of a scenario for how a city comes together to address the multiple economic, social and environmental crises facing our world. The first part of the scenario is here. It covers how the city creates basic frameworks of life. How it gains control of its own finances and local economy  More
The post Toward an Economy Not Dependent on Endless Growth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNN Tells Harris Not to Talk About the Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337870</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/16/cnn-tells-harris-not-to-talk-about-the-economy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CNN has been at the forefront in pushing the Biden bad economy story in defiance of the data. It had two of my six favorite untruths about the Biden economy. In one case, it told people about a “retirement crisis” even though the real wealth of near retirees is more than 45 percent higher than  More
The post CNN Tells Harris Not to Talk About the Economy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Pinterest’s Custom Spark Job logging and monitoring on Amazon EKS: Using AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and ADOT]]></title>
        <id>bdee5c2591496eec52dbc266a230659e41d9f831</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/inside-pinterests-custom-spark-job-logging-and-monitoring-on-amazon-eks-using-aws-for-fluent-bit-amazon-s3-and-adot-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1, we explored Moka’s high-level design and logging infrastructure, showcasing how AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and a robust logging framework make sure of operational visibility and facilitate issue resolution. For more details, read part 1 here. Introduction As we transition to the second part of our series, our focus shifts to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vara Bonthu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Pinterest’s Custom Spark Job logging and monitoring on Amazon EKS: Using AWS for Fluent Bit, Amazon S3, and ADOT]]></title>
        <id>2906849e01c03228ff10bcb7b325af81d37d5136</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/inside-pinterests-custom-spark-job-logging-and-monitoring-on-amazon-eks-using-aws-for-fluent-bit-amazon-s3-and-adot/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Part 1 of the blog post. Introduction Pinterest is a visual search and curation platform focused on inspiring users to create a life they love. Critical to the service are data insights, recommendations and machine learning (ML) models that are produced by synthesizing insights provided by the over 500 million monthly active users […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vara Bonthu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On enjoying my work]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/on-enjoying-my-work/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/on-enjoying-my-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So over on Aura's blog, an anonymous asker asks:
Hello! A Youtube video essayist I follow on Bluesky (Big Joel if you know of him) posted this:
“How do you become a person who just really likes doing work? I thought having a very interesting job would do it but this has not paid off as you might expect”
The first two people I thought of who give me the impression they enjoy their jobs are you and Bruno Dias, so I was wondering if you had an answer for this (because I sure don’t!)
I was slightly taken aback by this, as one often is when one sees one's name in print unexpectedly, and I had to pick apart a little this idea that I give the impression that I enjoy my job.
I certainly have talked very positively about my work in public; I believe most readers should be familiar with the old (but…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 19]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-19?v=1729044044</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-19?v=1729044044"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T02:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 19
Date: 31/05/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/05/31/no-issue-19/

Bullying Health
Elena Hagopyan
 As soon as you got any “bigger” health problem, you’re basically in trouble, not only by the things you’re facing by your condition, but actually the opinion is far harder. Today it is better to be some picture perfect child, young person or adult, as otherwise, you will be looked down upon by others. The silly of it is the fact no one is picture perfect, everyone who seems this way, it is just an act. 
 Myself, I have epilepsy, it always has been a problem, basically because I have to hide it every single day. If you have epilepsy, you better have the version of seizures most k…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 20]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-20?v=1729043075</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-no-against-adult-supremacy-vol-20?v=1729043075"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T01:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: NO! Against Adult Supremacy Vol. 20
Date: 21/06/2016
Source: Retrieved on May 9, 2022 from https://stinneydistro.wordpress.com/2016/06/21/no-issue-20/

Condemned and Hated
Isis Nelson
 Adults have consistently ignored young opinions and voices forever. It’s taught to us that we should respect our elders, because they’re old, and not speak unless spoken to by an adults. They constantly fail to protect and help us. The history of our world is filled with young people and children being failed by adults and losing their rights. From birth, we’re told that we are inherently inferior. Year after year, young people’s ideas are shot down by older relatives, older siblings, teachers, professors, leaders, bosses, etc. Our ambitious, often progressive, ideals and value…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexErrant in "Why don't we use awnings anymore (2022)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854344</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41854344"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T00:06:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "Technology Connections" youtube channel recently discussed awnings too. (And it had more or less the same message as this blog.)
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uhbDfi7Ee7k]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexErrant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a website is easy: a guide to the first steps]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8674</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/building-website-easy-guide-first-steps/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T21:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML for people, by American software developer Blake Watson, is a helpful resource for people wishing to build their first website, with a simple text editor. HTML for people guides first time web designers through the process of creating webpages, to uploading them, to produce a live website. You, my friend, are about to go […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://absoluteblank.bearblog.dev/why-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://absoluteblank.bearblog.dev/why-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:38:08.781Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is my belief that we all have something interesting to say. Whether you are an average Joe or a high status individual, your thoughts and opinions matter. If they didn't then why do they have the urge to socialize with friends or family? Okay so we chat with the people we love, so what? Why would I need to blog? For those that tell me that their journal is their blog I do not disagree that it isn't important. The only difference is that your written word now has an audience. Gasp! Being perceived?! This can be scary to some but let's look at the positive aspects of blogging.
First, there are no rules to blogging. Blogs serve different purposes depending on the person. For example, this blog you are reading is a personal blog that doesn't have a specific focus or target audience. I just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean author Han Kang wins 2024 literature Nobel Prize]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8679</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/south-korean-author-han-kang-wins-2024-literature-nobel-prize/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T20:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Seoul based author is the first South Korean to be named a Nobel Prize literature laurate. Han Kang has written over a dozen novels since 1995, so if you’re a book reader, chances are you’ve seen at least one. The Vegetarian, published in 2016, won the International Booker Prize in the same year. In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Amazon DynamoDB zero-ETL integrations with Amazon Redshift now generally available]]></title>
        <id>5718e2ab1acb3131b5cb8e4c41f4e24e864f2f93</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-postgresql-and-amazon-dynamodb-zero-etl-integrations-with-amazon-redshift-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T19:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock insights instantly with Amazon Redshift's new zero-ETL integrations for Aurora PostgreSQL and DynamoDB, eliminating complex ETL pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OCP Summit 2024: The open future of networking hardware for AI]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21834</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/15/data-infrastructure/open-future-networking-hardware-ai-ocp-2024-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Open Compute Project Summit (OCP) 2024, we’re sharing details about our next-generation network fabric for our AI training clusters. We’ve expanded our network hardware portfolio and are contributing two new disaggregated network fabrics and a new NIC to OCP. We look forward to continued collaboration with OCP to open designs for racks, servers, storage [...]
Read More...
The post OCP Summit 2024: The open future of networking hardware for AI appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s open AI hardware vision]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21832</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/15/data-infrastructure/metas-open-ai-hardware-vision/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the Open Compute Project (OCP) Global Summit 2024, we’re showcasing our latest open AI hardware designs with the OCP community. These innovations include a new AI platform, cutting-edge open rack designs, and advanced network fabrics and components.  By sharing our designs, we hope to inspire collaboration and foster innovation. If you’re passionate about building [...]
Read More...
The post Meta’s open AI hardware vision appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO-to-worker compensation ratio, 1965-2023]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45655</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/15/ceo-to-worker-compensation-ratio-1965-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T16:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All In Its Own Time]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/all-in-its-own-time/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/all-in-its-own-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to be obsessed with timelines.
When I was young and naive, I had a list of things I wanted to accomplish by specific points in my life. Some of those goals included:
Five years after earning my degree, I should be making a certain amount of money.
By 25, I should be engaged, and shortly after, should be married.
By a certain age, I should have a specific number of children.
Before that, I should own a particular kind of house in a specific location.
And so on, and so on.
Life is a fickle thing. I was young and didn’t fully grasp that wanting to achieve something by a certain time didn’t guarantee I would actually do it then.
Having a goal was good for me. During those 5 years, I worked really hard to reach a specific point in my career to hit that number. What was not helpful was be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of the EPYC 145% performance gain in Cloudflare Gen 12 servers]]></title>
        <id>1Sj8x3oCQRSZqU8oNgMmkE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/analysis-of-the-epyc-145-performance-gain-in-cloudflare-gen-12-servers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s Gen 12 server is the most powerful and power efficient server that we have deployed to date. Through sensitivity analysis, we found that Cloudflare workloads continue to scale with higher core count and higher CPU frequency, as well as achieving a significant boost in performance with larger L3 cache per core.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JQ Lau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing the Bigger Picture]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bigger-picture/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bigger-picture/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other day, someone pointed out that I had lost weight.
I said that it's a matter of perspective – and I didn't mean that I look extra slim from a certain angle.
It's true I've lost weight compared to six months ago. However, someone who hasn't seen me in two years might say I've gained weight, which is also true from that perspective. The bigger picture, literally.
Opposites, yet both true.
We often overlook this paradox when judging ourselves, don't we? We look back six months and see setbacks rather than successes. But if we widen our perspective and look back a couple of years, we'll likely discover we've made significant progress.
Every setback holds considerably more successes.
Let's not forget that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP O’ Malley - Interview: David Graeber, leading figure of Occupy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-interview-david-graeber-leading-figure-of-occupy?v=1728997340</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-interview-david-graeber-leading-figure-of-occupy?v=1728997340"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: JP O’ Malley
Title: Interview: David Graeber, leading figure of Occupy
Date: 3 May 2013
Notes: davidgraeber.org & davidgraeber.institute
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.spectator.co.uk

 The anarchist movement in the United States has had the support of leading libertarian intellectuals, such as Noam Chomsky; but it has lacked a figure who could transform its guiding principles into something resembling a political movement. In the autumn of 2011, David Graeber seemed to be the man who could drag anarchism into mainstream politics. 
 Graeber, along with other leading figures in the Occupy movement, coined the term ‘we are the 99 percent’. The catchphrase caught on, and within weeks — with the assistance of social media — Occupy transformed a small group of idealists…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta]]></title>
        <id>7LZCXzvQgHwLVGoT4O4Pj6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protect-against-identity-based-attacks-by-sharing-cloudflare-user-risk-with-okta"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uphold Zero Trust principles and protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta. Learn how this new integration allows your organization to mitigate risk in real time, make informed access decisions, and free up security resources with automation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Kagan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qalandar Bux Memon and Zaki Abbas - Prefiguration of a Common Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/qalandar-bux-memon-and-zaki-abbas-prefiguration-of-a-common-dream?v=1728996194</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/qalandar-bux-memon-and-zaki-abbas-prefiguration-of-a-common-dream?v=1728996194"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Qalandar Bux Memon and Zaki Abbas
Title: Prefiguration of a Common Dream
Subtitle: An Interview with David Graeber
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from nakedpunch.com

Qalandar Bux Memon: Can you explain why you support horizontal organisation, collective assemblies and a dialogical method for organising for social change as opposed to the vertical left party?
 David Gaeber: I like to make the distinction between forms of organization that could exist outside structures of coercion – that is, in the absence of any ability to call up men armed with weapons to threaten anyone who refuses to go along with a decision – and those which could not. It seems to me it’s the responsibility of those who are trying to create a free society to do so through forms of organization that cou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur De Grave - The era of predatory bureaucratization]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-de-grave-the-era-of-predatory-bureaucratization?v=1728995026</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/arthur-de-grave-the-era-of-predatory-bureaucratization?v=1728995026"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Arthur De Grave
Title: The era of predatory bureaucratization
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: 27 January 2016
Notes: This interview was originally published in Socialter n°14.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from legacy.ouishare.net

 David Graeber is an anthropologist and a well-known anarchist figure. He was one of the initiators of the Occupy movement in 2011. He is the author of a major essay, Debt, the First 5,000 Years. I met him in Paris for the release of his latest book, The Utopia of Rules: On Technology, Stupidity, and the Secret Joys of Bureaucracy.
Back in 2011, you were among the initiators of the Occupy movement. Several similar social movements have happened ever since, but it seems none of them managed to stay alive long enough to reach their…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Steven Durel - Teach Me if You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steven-durel-teach-me-if-you-can?v=1728994563</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/steven-durel-teach-me-if-you-can?v=1728994563"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Steven Durel
Title: Teach Me if You Can
Subtitle: An Interview with David Graeber
Date: November 21, 2005
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from towardfreedom.org

 David Graeber: It’s not really Yale’s leadership so much as the Department of Anthropology and senior faculty who decided to cut me off. For a long time I really tried to avoid getting involved in campus politics. I thought that I had come up with a nice formula, that I would be an activist in New York and simply a scholar here in New Haven. 
 Generally speaking, the academy really doesn’t care what you say and think or what you write, so long as you don’t do anything. If you’re willing to be a hypocrite, they’re fine with you, whatever you espouse. On the other hand, if there’s any sign that you might actually liv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ross Wolfe - The movement as an end-in-itself?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ross-wolfe-the-movement-as-an-end-in-itself?v=1728994191</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ross-wolfe-the-movement-as-an-end-in-itself?v=1728994191"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T12:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ross Wolfe
Title: The movement as an end-in-itself?
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: February 2012
Notes: Published in Platypus Review 43.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from platypus1917.org

On December 16, 2011, Ross Wolfe interviewed David Graeber, Reader at Goldsmiths College in London, author of Fragments of an Anarchist Anthropology (2004), and central figure in the early stages of the #Occupy Wall Street Movement. What follows is an edited transcript of the interview.
Ross Wolfe: There are striking similarities between the #Occupy movement and the 1999 anti-WTO protests in Seattle. Both began in the last year of a Democratic presidency, were spearheaded by anarchists, motivated by discontents with neo-liberalism, and received the support of organized …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suzi Weissman - The Rise of Bullshit Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/suzi-weissman-the-rise-of-bullshit-jobs?v=1728988945</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/suzi-weissman-the-rise-of-bullshit-jobs?v=1728988945"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Suzi Weissman
Title: The Rise of Bullshit Jobs
Subtitle: An interview with David Graeber
Date: June 30, 2018
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from jacobin.com

 In his latest book, David Graeber, the best-selling author of Debt: The First 5000 Years, argues that many jobs today are essentially pointless — or, as the book’s title calls them, Bullshit Jobs. 
 Jacobin Radio’s Suzi Weissman sat down with Graeber to find out what bullshit jobs are and why they’ve proliferated in recent years. 
A Taxonomy
Suzi Weissman: Let’s just get right down to it. What is the definition of a bullshit job? 
David Graeber: A bullshit job is a job which is so pointless, or even pernicious, that even the person doing the job secretly believes that it shouldn’t exist. Of course, you have to pretend…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP O’ Malley - The Utopia of Rules, David Graeber Interview]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-the-utopia-of-rules-david-graeber-interview?v=1728988786</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jp-o-malley-the-utopia-of-rules-david-graeber-interview?v=1728988786"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: JP O’ Malley
Title: The Utopia of Rules, David Graeber Interview
Date: 1st April 2015
Notes: JP O’ Malley interviews anthropologist, activist, anarchist and author, David Graeber, who was one of the early organisers of Occupy Wall Street.
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from bellacaledonia.org.uk

 In a compelling new book of essays entitled The Utopia of Rules: On Technology, Stupidity, and the Secret Joys of Bureaucracy, the American anarchist, and anthropologist, David Graeber argues that in all western countries today bureaucracy—whether it comes from multinational corporations or government offices— informs almost every single aspect of both public and private life. 
 Graeber is a radical thinker who is not afraid to dream big and envision a society that is profoundly d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sen$e - Why America’s favorite anarchist thinks most American workers are slaves]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/making-sen-e-why-america-s-favorite-anarchist-thinks-most-american-workers-are-slaves?v=1728988512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/making-sen-e-why-america-s-favorite-anarchist-thinks-most-american-workers-are-slaves?v=1728988512"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Making Sen$e
Title: Why America’s favorite anarchist thinks most American workers are slaves
Date: April 17, 2014
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.pbs.org

Editor’s Note: Conservative proponents of the guaranteed income want a lump sum payment (Charles Murray suggests about $11,000 to all adults) to replace existing social welfare programs and downsize American bureaucracy. But some leftists oppose those government welfare agencies, too, London School of Economics professor David Graeber says. The leftist critique of private and public bureaucracies, Graeber explains, is that they “employ thousands of people to make us feel bad about ourselves.” 
 Bureaucrats pushing paper decide what we and our work are worth. But somewhat ironically, Graeber suggests, it’s those bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elias Isquith - “I found myself turning into an idiot!”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-isquith-i-found-myself-turning-into-an-idiot?v=1728988254</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elias-isquith-i-found-myself-turning-into-an-idiot?v=1728988254"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Elias Isquith
Title: “I found myself turning into an idiot!”
Subtitle: David Graeber explains the life-sapping reality of bureaucratic life
Date: March 5, 2015
Source: Retrieved on 15th October 2024 from www.salon.com

 David Graeber, a professor of anthropology at the London School of Economics, is a man who wears many hats. He’s an academic, of course — and a respected one at that. But he’s also an author, an activist and political anarchist. But his most unique attribute may be this: He’s an honest-to-God public intellectual in an era when such figures are few and far between. 
 Graeber proved as much with “Debt: The First 5000 Years,” his ambitious tour de force overview of the role debt has played throughout the history of civilization and into the present day. And while it ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Agnes Callard, on the Art of Governing Teaching & Learning and student protests]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53272</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/15/on-agnes-callard-on-the-art-of-governing-teaching-learning-and-student-protests/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T10:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really liked and admired Agnes Callard’s essay, “Beyond Neutrality: The university’s responsibility to lead” in The Point (September 29, 2024) [HT Dailynous]. My post is, despite some quibbles, primarily about amplifying a point Callard (Chicago) makes. I do so not just because there is considerable overlap between our positions (recall here and here), but also because she advances the discussion on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Words That Haunt So Many Hurricane Victims: “Claim Denied”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337457</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/two-words-that-haunt-so-many-hurricane-victims-claim-denied/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know that you’re in good hands with Allstate? Or how about State Farm? Do you know that, like a good neighbor, State Farm is there? Of course you do. Insurance companies have been blasting slogans like these at us for years now. In 2022 alone, Allstate spent $617 million on advertising. State Farm spent an even more whopping $1.05 billion. More
The post Two Words That Haunt So Many Hurricane Victims: “Claim Denied” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionist ‘Safety Patrols’ on Campus Have Little Concern for Jewish Safety]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337862</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/zionist-safety-patrols-on-campus-have-little-concern-for-jewish-safety/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although last year's campus protests were overwhelmingly peaceful and included many anti-Zionist Jewish students and faculty, Israel’s supporters in media, politics and academia itself responded to the demonstrations by accusing protesters of peddling anti-Semitism and intimidating Jewish students. Towards the end of the academic year, police dismantled most of these campus protests, arresting hundreds of students in the process and charging them with crimes ranging from third-degree trespass to felony burglary. More
The post Zionist ‘Safety Patrols’ on Campus Have Little Concern for Jewish Safety appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poetry for a World on Fire: an Interview With Aja Monet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337549</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/poetry-for-a-world-on-fire-an-interview-with-aja-monet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Who’s got time for poems when the world’s on fire?” asks Aja Monet in the heart-achingly beautiful and gut-wrenchingly honest ‘For Sonia.’ Her answer, it becomes clear, is that it is precisely when the world’s on fire that the movement, such as it is, needs the nourishment and meaning and soul that poetry provides more than ever. But Monet will not offer words to comfort and soothe at the expense of truth. “These days it hurts to write,” the track continues, “Every sentence is a false promise.”  More
The post Poetry for a World on Fire: an Interview With Aja Monet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Glazebrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Montana is Not “a Product” and Government is Not “a Business”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337840</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/montana-is-not-a-product-and-government-is-not-a-business/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montana Gov. Greg Gianforte has boasted that “Montana is an easy product to sell” and recently referred to himself as our state’s CEO. He’s dead wrong on both counts. Montana is a state, not a product — and government is not a business. We have elected officials whose duty it is to serve the people  More
The post Montana is Not “a Product” and Government is Not “a Business” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Badly Tarnished Nobel Peace Prize is Finally Awarded to a Group that Truly Deserves It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337852</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/the-badly-tarnished-nobel-peace-prize-is-finally-awarded-to-a-group-that-truly-deserves-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pity the Biden and Harris speechwriters tasked with composing a congratulatory comment for the head of state and the vice-head of state to offer to Toshiyuki Mimaki recipient of the 2024 Nobel Peace Prize along with Nihon Hidankyo, the organization of Hibakusha. (Hibakusha are the victims of the US atomic bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.)   More
The post The Badly Tarnished Nobel Peace Prize is Finally Awarded to a Group that Truly Deserves It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Tenth Depraved Presidential Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337572</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/my-tenth-depraved-presidential-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presidential season is a time for Americans to restore their faith in democracy. How can folks not be filled with gratitude for being permitted a perfunctory choice of who will seize their paychecks and tyrannize them in the following four years? Actually, I’ve had a bad attitude on presidential elections going back to the end  More
The post My Tenth Depraved Presidential Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gun Violence Lowers Academic Achievement Especially for Black Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337458</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/gun-violence-lowers-academic-achievement-especially-for-black-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early September, the United States experienced its 24th school shooting of the year. Since that incident at Apalachee High School in Georgia, there have been several additional school shootings. Gun violence in schools has increased in recent years (Figure 1), but sadly that is only a small slice of the gun violence that children  More
The post Gun Violence Lowers Academic Achievement Especially for Black Children appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is 2024, 1968 All Over Again?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337864</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/is-2024-1968-all-over-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing recently in the LA Progressive, Stephen Rhode lamented: I learned an important lesson in 1968. My conscience could not allow me to vote for [Democratic Party nominee and serving Vice-President] Humphrey because of his unflinching support of President Lyndon Johnson’s dangerous escalation of that illegal war. So I voted for Dick Gregory, the Freedom and  More
The post Is 2024, 1968 All Over Again? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We the People Conduct Our Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337865</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/how-we-the-people-conduct-our-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I love working the polls!” a friend told me recently. “It strengthens my trust in the whole process. And it’s fun getting to help eligible voters flex their civic muscles.” I think about my friend’s experience as I hear stories about mistrust in our elections. National and state laws set some guardrails for our elections,  More
The post How We the People Conduct Our Elections appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Burrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cultivated-Meat Nationalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337856</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/cultivated-meat-nationalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eleven Republican members of Congress recently sent a letter to the director of national intelligence and the USDA’s director of homeland security, expressing their concern China was pulling away from the United States in the field of biotechnology, specifically as it relates to cultivated meat. For those who don’t know, cultivated meat is grown from  More
The post Cultivated-Meat Nationalism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Virtues of Selfies-ness Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337580</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/15/the-virtues-of-selfies-ness-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past, I’ve written on (my friend and heroine) Caryn Ann Harlos’s challenge to Colorado’s law commanding that “[no] election official, watcher, or person shall reveal to any other person the name of any candidate for whom a voter has voted or communicate to another his opinion, belief, or impression as to how or  More
The post The Virtues of Selfies-ness Revisited appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by umanwizard in "World conker champion found with steel chestnut, cleared of cheating"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41844648</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41844648"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T03:33:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this game well-known enough in Britain and Ireland that readers will know what on earth is being alleged just from reading this article? Or are you expected to have to google it?
Apparently it’s a game where you take turns swinging a chestnut on a string and trying to hit the opponent’s chestnut and break it. Yes, I can see how a steel fake chestnut would be an advantage here, though I’m amazed it wouldn’t be instantly obvious to even a casual observer that the look and sound were wrong. So maybe I’m still missing something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>umanwizard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by londons_explore in "Turn your Android phone into a modern ham radio transceiver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842346</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41842346"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T21:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The radio simply plugs into the USB C port on your Android smartphone and transforms it into a fully-fledged handheld radio transceiver.
When I saw the headline I was hoping someone had hacked the qualcomm modem and turned it into a software defined radio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>londons_explore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One personal website is enough for me]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8669</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/one-personal-website-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T21:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure disassociated always rates as a personal website, with its informational content style. But it’s owned personally by me, and I personally write the content, so on that basis it’s a personal website. A lot of what I post are my thoughts on the many and various things happening online and in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigation of a Workbench UI Latency Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/faa017b4653d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/investigation-of-a-workbench-ui-latency-issue-faa017b4653d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T20:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Hechao Li and Marcelo Mayworm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I hate my degree]]></title>
        <id>https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/i-hate-my-degree/</id>
        <link href="https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/i-hate-my-degree/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:10:54.371Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year I started my magister degree in programming, and it fucking sucked from the very beginning of the bachelors, to be honest. I constantly regret "my" choice (my dad is a programmer, and I sorta wanted to make him proud, but there was no pressure from him or anybody else) to start all this. I long for history, literature, philosophy, languages and human psychology constantly. I try to self-study some of this, but university studying takes most of my time and mental capacity. IT just feels like it is not for me. I want to understand our situation as humans on this tiny planet. I feel this void inside of me every day. I feel like this year I will eventually fail my studies due to numerous mental breakdowns. Fuck it, I will be someone else in the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automating custom Amazon EKS worker node builds using EC2 Image Builder]]></title>
        <id>0f6921caef075cd4bf67b783cc1704da9240aca9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/automating-custom-amazon-eks-worker-node-builds-using-ec2-image-builder/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T18:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers who are building their “Golden Image” Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) using EC2 Image Builder may wish to extend their Image Builder pipelines to build out their Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) worker nodes as well. In this blog, we will show you how to do this and provide you with AWS CloudFormation templates […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brad Watson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zhovner in "Busy Status Bar"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41839748</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41839748"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T17:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, Pavel Zhovner here, Flipper Devices CEO. 
Yes it's our product, but it's not ready for announcement yet, so we keep it secret.
Right now, we are working on implementing Matter smart home protocol and will slightly change the product concept.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zhovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: What’s App, AWS Lambda, Load Balancers, AWS Console, and more (Oct 14, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>802232dd71f635b36fd40d9d7a982433d951aad6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-whats-app-aws-lambda-load-balancers-aws-console-and-more-oct-14-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T16:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, AWS hosted free half-day conferences in London and Paris. My colleagues and I demonstrated how developers can use generative AI tools to speed up their design, analysis, code writing, debugging, and deployment workflows. These events were held at the GenAI Lofts. These lofts are open until October 25 (London) and November 5 (Paris). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On being a great gift-giver]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/on-being-a-great-gift-giver/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/on-being-a-great-gift-giver/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people are great at giving gifts. The kinds of gifts that squeeze your heart make you feel seen. I'm trying to become one of those people, but my friend Simon already is.
If you're reading this you're probably aware that I run a blogging platform that I care for deeply. And it's the main thing I speak about when someone asks after my day. I rattle on about a challenging bug I'm trying to squash, complain about cheeky script-kiddies rattling the latches on all the doors and windows looking for an exploit, or mention an email I received from a blogger letting me know they see the love and effort I put into my work.
Simon hears all of this, and on my 32nd birthday gave me a gift that really hit home.
I keep a mostly-up-to-date list of nice messages about Bear that I've received from users over the past few years. It helps me remember why I do what I do, and makes me feel all warm and fuzzy whenever I need some extra motivation.
Knowing this, Simon conspired with a friend who owns a 3D printer and designed and created a little desktop bear that can hold a message board. He then wrote each of these messages out by hand (suffering only minor carpel tunnel) on sticky notes which the bear now carries like a human bear directional.

It now sits on my desk, next to my computer where I get to see it every work day, right when and where I need a shot of good vibes.
These are the kinds of gifts I want to learn how to give. Ones that make the receiver feel like they've been listened to and understood. That don't cost much money but are priceless at the same time.
I'm grateful and inspired. Thanks Simon (I know you're subscribed to my blog). And thanks to everyone who has sent me a kind email over the past few years. I appreciate you all.
Enjoyed the article? I write about 1-2 a month. Subscribe via email or RSS feed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The European Central Bank and the return of history]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45647</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/14/the-european-central-bank-and-the-return-of-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T09:42:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of the post-World War II ´Pax Americana, an almost eighty-year period of peace for European countries allied with the USA, will soon lead the EU to end the prohibition of monetary financing of governments by the European Central Bank (ECB). This might take the shape of the ECB providing credit to an entity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US just lost a war and nobody noticed]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53266</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/14/the-us-just-lost-a-war-and-nobody-noticed/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T07:09:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the eight decades following the end of World War II, the US has taken part in dozens of land wars, large and small. The outcomes have ranged from comprehensive victory to humiliating defeat, but all have received extensive coverage. By contrast, the US Navy’s admission of defeat in its longest and most significant campaign […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy is Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/privacy-is-politics/</id>
        <link href="https://caffeinated.bearblog.dev/privacy-is-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to having an opinion, every cornerstone of a community becomes a droughtless wellspring. No matter where you go, opposing arguments will follow. That is the nature of opinions—there will always be one slightly different from another. Amazingly, even in areas where opinions shouldn’t take precedence over fact, people will still hold their personal beliefs over them. I think that’s just plain ignorance.
One of these communities is the Land of OPSEC. The world of information security, simply put. An area of knowledge that should, without a doubt, be centered around the obvious fact of the matter. Easily. Want to be secured? Don’t use that—use this. Is this thing compromised? Update to this.
Right? Sort of. The world of digital security is probably one of the most politically mot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by matrix2003 in "Why does FM sound better than AM?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41832921</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41832921"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T00:15:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Someone gave me an analogy some time ago that made a lot of sense.
If you shine a flashlight through a tree blowing in the wind and vary the brightness to convey information, the signal can get distorted pretty easily.
However, if you have a constant brightness source and vary the color, it’s a lot easier to figure out what the source is trying to convey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>matrix2003</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ProRata: an AI chatbot that pays for the knowledge it disseminate]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8664</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/prorata-ai-chatbot-pays-knowledge-idisseminate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ProRata is an AI chatbot that pays the content producers whose work is used to format answers to questions put to it. Yes, you read that correctly. The technology is being backed by American investor and entrepreneur Bill Gross, writes Fred Vogelstein, for Crazy Stupid Tech: But it will do something none of the others […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michaelmior in "CRLF is obsolete and should be abolished"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41831072</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41831072"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T20:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> various protocols (HTTP, SMTP, CSV) still "require" CRLF at the end of each line
What would be the benefit to updating legacy protocols to just use NL? You save a handful of bits at the expense of a lot of potential bugs. HTTP/1(.1) is mostly replaced by HTTP/2 and later by now anyway.
Sure, it makes sense not to require CRLF with any new protocols, but it doesn't seem worth updating legacy things.
> Even if an established protocol (HTTP, SMTP, CSV, FTP) technically requires CRLF as a line ending, do not comply.
I'm hoping this is satire. Why intentionally introduce potential bugs for the sake of making a point?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaelmior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation is called “Productivity Growth”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45643</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/13/automation-is-called-productivity-growth-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker It is more than a bit bizarre reading pieces that talk about automation or job-killing AI as something new and alien. These are forms of productivity growth. They allow more goods and services to be produced for each hour of human labor. Productivity growth is usually thought of as a good thing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[unwanted dead or alive]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/unwanted-dead-or-alive/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/unwanted-dead-or-alive/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T19:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MICROFEELINGS:
records on my walls as art
sometimes it feels like a battle to exist and be who you are.
These days, I feel criminally uncool. I open the Substack app, read a plethora of girlhood essays, and realize they no longer feel relatable.
After watching ​His Three Daughters (a brilliant movie), I thought about my dad and the dynamics within my own family as he was dying. We all grew up with a different dad and experienced a different relationship with him, which seems so bizarre. I also thought about his clothes. Did his wife throw them all out? What about his deathbed pajamas? Are they hanging up at the Goodwill? He'd probably be very disappointed in me for not having a job right now. He'd call me lazy.
started watching the new Marilyn Manson doc series. I don't know why I'm so surprised by what was revealed. Disappointed, disgusted, and pissed off to lose yet another musician/actor I like to the pits of shitty behavior.
I wish there were more indie-print literary magazines.
I've been watching a lot of Mina Le vids while eating dinner on my living room coffee table. (My kitchen table is overrun by my unfinished jigsaw puzzle atm)
Life has felt a little shaky lately. I feel like I'm on the precipice of so much change: moving in with my boyfriend (?), finding/starting a new job, and living out of the city (can I be a country girl?)
ROLL.DIARY:

sketchbook peek

making marks

morning light

pretty fall foliage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ChuckMcM in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41830516</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41830516"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T18:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty impressive. The engineering team at SpaceX is really something. Some thoughts;
The 'chopsticks catch' was amazing to watch. Seems like it adds a lot of risk and clearly the booster needs additional fire suppression systems :-) perhaps the tower could mount something that sprays the booster like the barges have for the F9 boosters.
The heatshield held out for a much longer time, the asymmetric heating on the flaps was interesting. I had guessed that all four flaps would have equivalent heating based on an approach that was basically that side of the rocket perpendicular to the flow but it seems like that isn't the case. Still it seems like they are close to having something workable here.
The detonation at the end was pretty spectacular too, but I suspect that structurally the tanks failed as the rocket hit the water vs anything that was an engineering failure. Engineering it to be strong enough to land on water would presumably compromise the cargo to orbit number.
The use of Starlink was really interesting. The ability to get live video for the entire re-entry is pretty game changing for engineering. I'd guess there are even more 'views' than they showed (there would be if I were running things :-)) but overall that capability is something that really helps evaluate the changes made.
I can easily imagine that flight 6 will be nominal end to end without any unintended damage. That would enable, perhaps, one of their 'massive' Starlink missions to test cargo delivery. It will also start to give us some better numbers on exactly how much cargo Starship can put in orbit in 'full reuse' mode  which is essential if they want to create a fueling station on orbit for the Artemis program.
Again, hats off to engineering at SpaceX, y'all did good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ChuckMcM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker - Compose]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/docker-compose/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/docker-compose/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Ever heard the phrase: "It works on my machine!"? This phrase encapsulates a common frustration in modern application deployment, where developers often encounter inconsistencies between their local environments and those of their colleagues or production servers.

For instance, Dev A might run the application flawlessly on their PC, while Dev B struggles to replicate the same success, even with the exact same workflow and dependencies. These discrepancies, due to OS differences, software versions, or configurations, cause delays and increased troubleshooting.
Docker
Docker resolves this issue by offering a consistent environment via containers. By bundling the app and its dependencies, Docker ensures uniform execution across machines, eliminating the "it works on my machine" …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[100 songs to get to know me]]></title>
        <id>https://tbskyen.bearblog.dev/100-songs-to-get-to-know-me/</id>
        <link href="https://tbskyen.bearblog.dev/100-songs-to-get-to-know-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I posted this image over on the bluesky, and it got like 100 likes, so now here we are. Rather than spam this as a 100 post thread, let's do it in a format which is suited for it: the blog.
These songs are in no particular order, except the order I am finding them in my playlists and deciding to put them on here.
1. ABBA - Lay All Your Love On Me


I genuinely don't quite know if my enjoyment of ABBA is something I came by honestly, or something which is simply genetically engineered into my Scandinavian soul. I remember hearing my mom blasting their songs on the home stereo in my childhood, and the association has put permanent nostalgia blinders on me for all of ABBA's greatest hits. Still, I think the beat is undeniable and the mournful tone of the chorus adds some real melancholy to th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by magicalhippo in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41829231</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41829231"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First off, the booster was going about 1250 km/h when it started its landing burn, it relied purely on drag to get it slowed down to that speed.
Going by the telemetry of the seconds before the landing burn and noting the speed vs time, it seems drag was around 40 m/s^2 when it was going at around 3000 km/h. Since drag depends on velocity squared though, it had reduced to just above 10 m/s^2 just before the engines lit at 1250 km/h, and so would quickly become negligible once the engines lit.
Going by Wikipedia, the Super Heavy[1] has 3400000 kg of fuel at launch, so 3% of that is about 102000 kg. For the landing burn, it used 13 Raptor v3 engines[2] to scrub speed. Each Raptor flows about 650 kg/s max, so 3% fuel is enough for about 12 seconds for the 13 engines.
The empty mass of the Super Heavy is about 275000 kg, so about 377000 kg before the landing burn with 3% fuel.
Using the sea-level vs vacuum performance of the Raptor v2 engines, one can estimate that each Raptor v3 produces about 2.45 NM of force at sea-level. So 13 of them would produce about 31.85 MN of force.
Using Newton's second law, F=ma, this gives an initial deceleration of about 84 m/s^2 and about 104 m/s^2 when empty. If we do a rough spreadsheet integration, we get that a burn of roughly 4 seconds is needed to scrub the speed assuming no other forces.
Now, comparing this with reality, the full 13 engines were lit for a little over 5 seconds.
In my simplified calculations I was assuming full throttle the whole way, which obviously isn't realistic, and I also assumed 3% fuel. So over all I think that's a pretty decent estimation.
[1]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SpaceX_Super_Heavy#Engines
[2]: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SpaceX_Raptor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>magicalhippo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: punch card loom]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53264</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/13/sunday-photoblogging-punch-card-loom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T16:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kids today probably don’t know about punched cards, but when I was at school we all had to play around with them a bit as we learnt about state-of-the-art computing …. But the technology derives from weaving, and from the Jacquard loom of 1804.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dtquad in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41828249</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41828249"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T14:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIMO and nonlinear control theories are probably some of the hardest topics in all of engineering. SpaceX control system also has to compensate for the fuel moving inside their rockets so the control algorithms probably involve some kind of fast numerical fluid simulation.
Another interesting thing SpaceX is doing is to use consumer-grade chips in triple redundancy configurations instead of using $100,000+ radiation-hardened aerospace/defense grade chips.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dtquad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JumpCrisscross in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827982</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827982"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T13:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> space shuttle was reusable
SpaceX builds vehicles. The Shuttle was “reusable” because they needed a term between the default for transportation capital expenditures (e.g. trains, planes, cars and ships) and the modified missiles that defined post-War spaceflight. “Reusable” in the Shuttle’s context meant  months of specialist overhaul time and the cost of a Falcon 9 launch in SRB booster replacements alone [0].
At the end of the day, in 2010, “the incremental cost per flight of the Space Shuttle was $409 million, or $14,186 per kilogram” [1]. ($591mm and $20,512 in 2024 dollars, respectively [2].) SpaceX’s prices per kg are around $3,170 on Falcon 9 [3] and $1,520 for Falcon Heavy [4]. Starship should bring those costs below $1000.
[0] https://forum.nasaspaceflight.com/index.php?topic=51959.0
[1] https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_Shuttle_program
[2] https://www.usinflationcalculator.com/
[3] https://www.spacex.com/media/Capabilities&Services.pdf LEO
[4] https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Falcon_Heavy LEO, theoretical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JumpCrisscross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ghc in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827495</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827495"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T12:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing could have prepared me for how that catch looked. I was sure the rocket was careening into the tower at the last second before it straightened out. The control algorithms must be incredible for the landing system to work within those small tolerances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ghc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dmix in "Starship Flight 5: Launch and booster catch [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827481</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41827481"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T12:40:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video of the catch
> Mechazilla has caught the Super Heavy booster!
https://x.com/spacex/status/1845442658397049011]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dmix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Chomsky & Radical Anthropology Journal - Human nature and the origins of language]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-chomsky-radical-anthropology-journal-human-nature-and-the-origins-of-language?v=1728819998</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-chomsky-radical-anthropology-journal-human-nature-and-the-origins-of-language?v=1728819998"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Chomsky & Radical Anthropology Journal
Title: Human nature and the origins of language
Date: 2008
Source: Radical Anthropology Journal, Issue #2. <radicalanthropologygroup.org/journal>

Noam Chomsky ranks among the leading intellectual figures of modern times and has changed the way we think about what it means to be human, revolutionising linguistics and establishing it as a modern science. He agreed to discuss just some of his ideas with Radical Anthropology. 
 Noam Chomsky is institute professor and professor of linguistics (emeritus) at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. would be a miracle that my granddaughter reflexively identified some elements of the blooming buzzing confusion as language-related and went on to acquire capacities of the kind that you and I are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aryanam - A Philosophy for Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-a-philosophy-for-anarchism?v=1728817377</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-a-philosophy-for-anarchism?v=1728817377"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aryanam
Title: A Philosophy for Anarchism
Date: October 4th 2024
Source: https://asranarshism.com/1403/07/13/a-philosophy-for-anarchism-en/

 Philosophy is nothing but a landscape of perspectives, worldviews, and paths, some meandering and some straightforward, some solitary and some crisscrossing with the neighboring paths, some long and some short, some trekked in multitude and some in solitude, some forgotten and some revered, some new and some ancient, all to understand and nourish the abilities and needs of self and a myriad of others. Being is becoming, the traveler and the path both change in the journey. Yet, even if the destination is all the same, not all paths are suitable for all. One needs to stay true to oneself and the path’s needs and abilities. To each according to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - An Eastern Europe mythbuster]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-an-eastern-europe-mythbuster?v=1728814949</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-an-eastern-europe-mythbuster?v=1728814949"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: An Eastern Europe mythbuster
Date: 24/07/2022
Notes: This article first appeared in the Summer-Autumn edition of Freedom journal.
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2022/07/24/an-eastern-europe-mythbuster/

 “Apparently, for the Western left, it is totally fine to publicly self-fellate over Kurdish, Palestinian or Irish self-determination, but just try bringing an Eastern European one to the table …” 
 ~ Eastern European Leftist Proverb, medium: Telegram 
 One of the more frustrating aspects of watching the most recent Russian special military operation imperialist war unfolding is the number of self-appointed experts from the Western left thinking they have some particularly insightful view. 
 While some make it rather difficult to give them the benefit of the do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Guérin - Proudhon In the Closet]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-guerin-proudhon-in-the-closet?v=1728814698</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-guerin-proudhon-in-the-closet?v=1728814698"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Daniel Guérin
Title: Proudhon In the Closet
Subtitle: The homophobia and misogyny of Pierre-Joseph Proudhon
Date: Originally written in 1969 & translated in 2013.
Notes: Translated by Jesse Cohn. A reinterpretation of Pierre-Joseph Proudhon’s well-known misogyny as a symptom of repressed homosexual desires. Daniel Guérin (1904–1988), was also author of Homosexualité et révolution (1953) and the widely read Anarchism: From Theory to Practice (1965/1970).
Source: Originally published in French in Essai Sur La Révolution Sexuelle (Après Reich Et Kinsey) by Daniel Guerin in 1969, published in Paris by Editions Pierre Belfond. See the English translation word document with the original French here: <academia.edu>. This English translation was published by Bastard Press in 2014: <wslib.w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Civil or Subversive]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-civil-or-subversive?v=1728813042</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-civil-or-subversive?v=1728813042"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Civil or Subversive
Subtitle: Individualist Writings from the UK
Date: 2016
Notes: A Dark Matter Collection
Source: PDF provided by publisher

 Originally published as 
Anarchism: Civil or Subversive
 published under creative commons 
 darkmatter.noblogs.org 
325.nostate.net 
This publication is dedicated to Alfredo Cospito, Nicola Gai, Olga Ekonomidou 
and the memory of Renzo Novatore, beautiful rebels... 
Contents
 Introduction by DMP
 Subversive Disassociation by L
 Beyond the Movement — Anarchy! by DMP
 To address moral elitism within the anarchist milieu in response to the rioters of August 6th onwards... by Anon
 Against the British ‘anti-capitalist movement’: Brief notes on their ongoing failure by Anarchist-nihilists
 Scandalous Thoughts by VQ
 Fragme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SECProto in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41825555</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41825555"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T05:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Funding road repairs, construction, and expansion from general tax revenues is similarly subsidizing a different mode of transit, and it's likely a much higher value than the 3b€ you mention (and likely more than overall railway sector subsidizing, tho I'm not familiar with Germany's budget). Also recognizing that other positive externalities exist, but pricing them at $0, seems silly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SECProto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by postpawl in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823619</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823619"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T23:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing on the cost-per-tonne for carbon reduction misses the broader value of railways. They're not just about reducing emission! They facilitate daily commutes, expand job opportunities, and help drive the economy. It’s a subsidy for businesses too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>postpawl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by addedlovely in "The ACF plugin on the WordPress directory has been taken over by WordPress.org"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823043</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823043"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt you've lost the plot, time to step down or put independent governance in-place.
How can you expect any developer to devote time to writing a plugin if the dictatorship of Matt can rug pull it at any time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>addedlovely</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nurtbo in "PayPal (USA) will automatically share data about you to participating stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822875</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822875"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy laws actually work! Let’s pass more of them.
> Information gathered about you after the effective date of our updated Privacy Statement, November 27, 2024, will be shared with participating stores where you shop, *unless you live in California, North Dakota, or Vermont.* For PayPal customers in California, North Dakota, or Vermont, we’ll only share your information with those merchants if you tell us to do so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nurtbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by PlunderBunny in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822853</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822853"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t forget too that the cost of proving roads is also ‘subsidised’ in most countries, but we’re tend to be a bit blind to that.
(This is not an argument against rail - I just find that subsidies are often mentioned with respect to rail but not with roads).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PlunderBunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lexicality in "The ACF plugin on the WordPress directory has been taken over by WordPress.org"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822119</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822119"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's very funny that Matt's original complaint was that WPEngine didn't contribute enough, and he has now banned them from contributing and stolen what they had previously provided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lexicality</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things I've learnt on Bearblog since I started my blog]]></title>
        <id>https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/things-ive-learnt-on-bearblog-since-i-started-my-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/things-ive-learnt-on-bearblog-since-i-started-my-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T18:27:51.629Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People really like to talk about writing, don't they? I don't personally mind it, in fact I like writing too, but it feels like every other post that is on the trending tab is about either blogging or writing or Bearblog.
It's quite barebones, and I wish it would be simpler to talk to bloggers. Not many blogs have a comments section, and if I want to talk about their post, I may have to email them or go onto a different social media platform to do so. I know I don't have a dedicated comments section or guestbook, and perhaps that makes me a hypocrite, but I do wish other blogs had one. I'll likely set a guestbook up, now that I think about it.
Rubidium hasn't been mentioned on Bearblog once in its history, which is slightly alarming.
Blogging is well and truly alive, which I love because it's far more interesting than the tacky Twitter vignettes or heavily processed Instagram posts.
It was pointless trying to promote my main blog over social channels...everyone here is getting by without doing so, and seems quite content with it. Fame isn't an issue, and I like that.
etc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You are not obliged to be deep and meaningful on your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/you-are-not-obliged-to-be-deep-and-meaningful-on-your-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/you-are-not-obliged-to-be-deep-and-meaningful-on-your-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:52:50.174Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog is a text-form media. It is literally just about putting your thoughts out there for a few people to read. On the Bear Blog you are free to write whatever the fuck you want. You can write poetry, write your to-do lists, plan your D&D campaign, anything. Anything you want, including bizarre shit your mind is telling you. It is anonymous if you want to. If you already have a blog tied to your real identity, create another one, just for incoherent rumblings about something that bothers you. Indescribable shit. It can be a sentence long. Even one word. Be yourself. Be a schizo. Be a prophet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by idlewords in "Turkish language has a gossip tense"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820919</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820919"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not a tense but a grammatical mood, it's called the inferential mood. A bunch of languages have it to distinguish eyewitness accounts from reported speech.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inferential_mood
Verb tense has to do with an action's relationship to time, mood expresses the speaker's relationship and attitude to the action. English is pretty low on moods (indicative, imperative, subjunctive), while other languages have a more fun arsenal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>idlewords</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by naming_the_user in "The phone ban has had a big impact on school work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820690</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820690"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It really can't be underestimated either for children or adults how much we are dependent on ease of access.
If you're stuck in a room and the only thing you can do is read a math textbook you are going to do it. If you are stuck in a room and you have a math textbook and a novel you now have a choice.
A phone? A phone is everything else. You're putting "the thing we are supposed to be doing" and "everything else" in the same place. I can't even do it as an adult, I need to put my phone on the other side of the room if I want to read something proper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>naming_the_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UN helps over 500,000 get citizenship + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/un-helps-over-500-000-get-citizenship-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/un-helps-over-500-000-get-citizenship-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UN highlights citizenship gains for stateless; Pakistan struggles with polio resurgence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eatbots in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819655</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819655"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported this exact bug to Zendesk, Apple, and Slack in June 2024, both through HackerOne and by escalating directly to engs or PMs at each company.
I doubt we were the first. That is presumably the reason they failed to pay out.
The real issue is that non-directory SSO options like Sign in with Apple (SIWA) have been incorrectly implemented almost everywhere, including by Slack and other large companies we alerted in June.
Non-directory SSO should not have equal trust vs. directory SSO. If you have a Google account and use Google SSO, Google can attest that you control that account. Same with Okta and Okta SSO.
SIWA, GitHub Auth, etc are not doing this. They rely on a weaker proof, usually just control of email at a single point in time.
SSO providers are not fungible, even if the email address is the same. You need to take this into account when designing your trust model. Most services do not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eatbots</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bsuvc in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819233</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819233"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another example of how weasley Zendesk can be:
They created a fake band called "Zendesk Alternative" just in an attempt to pollute the Google results if you search for an alternative to Zendesk.
http://zendeskalternative.com/
While not illegal, it shows the way they think, a sort of manipulative pettiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bsuvc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by maeil in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819179</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819179"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A $1.3 billion revenue company being too tight to pay this after all, even on their 2nd chance, is so short-sighted it's absurd. They're putting out a huge sign saying "When you find a vuln, definitely contact all our clients because we won't be giving you a penny!".
Incredible. This must be some kind of "damaged ego" or ass-covering, as it's clearly not a rational decision.
Edit: Another user here has pointed out the reasoning
> It's owned by private equity. Slowly cutting costs and bleeding the brand dry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maeil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bsuvc in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819150</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819150"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It sounds like the author got stiffed by Zendesk on this bug, $0 due to email spoofing being out of scope.
The $50k was from other bug bounties he was awarded on hackerone.
It's too bad Zendesk basically said "thanks" but then refused to pay anything. That's a good way to get people not to bother with your big bounty program. It is often better to build goodwill than to be a stickler for rules and technicalities.
Side note: I'm not too surprised, as I had one of the worst experiences ever interviewing with Zendesk a few years back. I have never come away from an interview hating a company, except for Zendesk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bsuvc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i love you, rss]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-love-you-rss/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-love-you-rss/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before this blog, I'd pondered the idea of starting a Patreon or a newsletter of some sort. I liked the idea of doing a semi-regular thought or artdump, and the idea of people wanting to tune into said dumps. But I always hesitated for two reasons.
One was that I didn't do anything on a schedule, and if I did do something regularly, I'd stop as soon as it became a task on my to-do list.1 And two was that I've developed a habit of wanting to escape my audience if I knew it was there – worse if I knew who was in it. The awareness made it difficult for me to write or draw or post freely, always thinking about how it would look and if it was good enough and if the people I knew were watching would be offended.
RSS comes as a relief for the overly self-conscious me. While not knowing who is rea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jandrewrogers in "Working from home is powering productivity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41816635</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41816635"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T05:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think a lot of people are talking past each other. I’ve mostly WFH since long before the pandemic, in many different capacities at many companies. A lot of people have tunnel vision and the reality is more nuanced than most allow.
For IC work that requires minimal collaboration, WFH is often more productive. Fewer interruptions, more focus. However, when the role requires detailed collaboration and regular interaction with others, productivity for WFH falls off a cliff. This has been measurable at every company I’ve worked for that does a decent job of collecting these metrics. And anecdotally, I can feel it in my own job. When I am doing focus work, WFH is great and I get a lot done. When I need a lot of whiteboard time or deep discussions with my peers, WFH is very inefficient regardless of the remote setup, and the difference is so stark that it is difficult to argue.
I think most people are talking their own book. If you are an IC or mostly just do individual focus work, then of course WFH is great. If you need to iteratively collaborate with people on complex design problems or work products, WFH objectively has low efficiency in every organization I’ve seen try it, including companies that are remote-centric.
There is a lot of motivated reasoning in these discussions and little acknowledgement that productivity between WFH and RTO varies greatly depending on the task at hand. Every company and most roles are a mix of these types of tasks. I think many companies these days recognize this and try to allocate accordingly, but it creates legal, social, and other issues if you treat employees differently in this regard based on the nature of their roles. The reality that some people must commute to do their jobs effectively creates a class system of sorts but organizations needs all roles to be setup to ensure reasonable productivity.
This is not a black and white situation, it is a complex social problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jandrewrogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the dreaded chronic fatigue cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/the-dreaded-chronic-fatigue-cycle/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/the-dreaded-chronic-fatigue-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i haven't been able to make much art lately. which is pretty frustrating, because i genuinely want to work on art. but i have been nonstop stressed for the past month. and unfortunately, being stressed out makes my health problems flare up, which means that my ability to concentrate goes completely out the window.
every now and then, i'll pull out my sketchbook to doodle something, or sketching stuff in MS Paint, or whatever. i'm trying to keep my creative skills engaged, even if it's in small amounts. but man... it's rough. i keep fantasizing about drawing beautiful illustrations, and not having the physical strength to do anything about it.
i'm accustomed to this cycle, but that doesn't make it any less miserable, you know? i can't even begin to count how many times i've been through this. my best coping method for this dreaded cycle is to avoid beating myself up over it, try to be patient and forgiving with myself, and chip away at projects when i'm able to.
it feels kind of embarrassing to keep reposting art from my archives, though. i've been posting art to mastodon/bluesky, since i'm trying to rebuild my online presence in a post-cohost world. and... i desperately wish i had newer pieces to show. it'll happen when it happens - i shouldn't risk pushing my body further when i'm already in a lot of pain - but i still feel sad about it.
just gotta take a deep breath, and be patient. in the meantime, i'd like to take the downtime to study art styles i find compelling. i've gravitated towards 90s anime fantasy art for years, despite my shockingly-minimal exposure to anime, so it'd be fun to study some artbooks. and maybe i'll take the time to work on more weird little web projects - we'll see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CyberArk is streamlining serverless governance by codifying architectural blueprints]]></title>
        <id>af07d7584dfeb69d151856df82af697cb9969f9a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-cyberark-is-streamlining-serverless-governance-by-codifying-architectural-blueprints/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Ran Isenberg, Principal Software Architect at CyberArk and an AWS Serverless Hero. Serverless architectures enable agility and simplified cloud resource management. Organizations embracing serverless architectures build robust, distributed cloud applications. As organizations grow and the number of development teams increases, maintaining architectural consistency, standardization, and governance across projects becomes crucial. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Aleksandrov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brenner’s satisfactory]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45640</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/11/brenners-satisfactory/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford “Mathematics is the art of the perfect.  Physics is the art of the optimal.  Biology, because of evolution, is the art of the satisfactory”. That’s Sydney Brenner speaking.  He should know a thing or two.  He won a Nobel Prize. It’s a shame, is it not?  Economies are always changing.  Not just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - COVID-19 UK Mutual Aid groups: a list]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list?v=1728638595</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list?v=1728638595"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T09:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: COVID-19 UK Mutual Aid groups: a list
Date: 13/03/2020
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2020/03/13/covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list/

As the global COVID-19 pandemic is upon us, a number of mutual aid groups have started forming across the country. The groups aim at providing community support to those who are more at risk from the virus: be it help with running errands or cooking.
COVID-19 is a novel virus most affecting people’s respiratory systems. While in around 8o% cases the symptoms will be mild, it can lead to death. It is estimated that 2-3 people out of a hundred will die. This can easily mean hundreds of thousands of deaths in the UK alone.
We must do everything we can to prevent this from happening.
The virus, while very unlikely to kill us all, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - It’s spelt Sisterhood, not Cis-terhood]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-it-s-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood?v=1728638156</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-it-s-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood?v=1728638156"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T09:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: It’s spelt Sisterhood, not Cis-terhood
Date: 22/05/2018
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2018/05/22/its-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood-statement/

 The signatories of this letter strongly condemn the actions and doctrines of the Trans Exclusionary Radical Feminists (TERFs)*. This strain of feminism recently gained notoriety due to their problematic opposition of the proposed reforms to the Gender Recognition Act 2004 (these reforms proposes to allow trans and non- binary people to self- declare their gender without, as is the case now, going through humiliating legal and medical process). This law could help to make the lives of a highly discriminated against minority easier. TERFs however claim that the aim of the proposed law change is a threat to cis women.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O Bluesky é diferente pois é só um dos lugares]]></title>
        <id>https://joselito.blog.br/o-bluesky-e-diferente-pois-e-so-um-dos-lugares/</id>
        <link href="https://joselito.blog.br/o-bluesky-e-diferente-pois-e-so-um-dos-lugares/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eu imagino que você já tentou usar o Mastodon pelo menos uma vez. Ou talvez use, longe de mim julgar. Não é de hoje que redes sociais dominadas por big techs não são exatamente os locais mais saudáveis pra ter um delicioso "debate de ideias". Sempre é bom buscar alternativas.
Lembra como foi o processo? Alguém finalmente te convencia, aí então você ia lá "beleza então me fala aí onde me cadastro?" e você ouvia que tinha que "escolher uma instância". Mesmo indo no site oficial você era direcionado a uma página com inúmeras instâncias (hoje isso mudou).
"Como é amigo? O quê é uma instância?" E ai começava uma considerável — ainda que interessante — explicação sobre como o Mastodon funciona, geralmente dando um certo destaque para o fato de que seu usuário agora tem o dobro de arrobas do que …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>