<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-09T02:24:23.400Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-09T02:24:23.400Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 8, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCxe5GcFMqSxt-WdxIa1_WC</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCxe5GcFMqSxt-WdxIa1_WC"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T18:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 8, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
Trump not violating any law
‘He who saves his Country does not violate any Law’
Trump Stuns By Saying ‘I Don’t Know’ When Asked Directly NBC’s Kristen Welker ‘Don’t You Need to Uphold the Constitution?’
Joe DePaolo, May 4th, 2025 [mediaite.com]
National Guard to be sent to L.A. amid clashes; Newsom calls Hegseth’s threat of Marines ‘deranged’
[Los Angeles Times, June 7, 2025]
Trump’s Rubicon moment
ZACK STANTON, 06/08/2025 [politico.com/playbook]
Trump: “If Governor Gavin Newscum, of California, and Mayor Karen Bass, of Los Angeles, can’t do their jobs, which everyone knows they can’t, then the Federal Government will step in and solve the problem, RIOTS & LOOTERS, the way it should be solved!!!”
….
What Trump is doing is i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/8/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293499</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-8-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T10:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our strategic daily links: ancient music, new COVID variant, banana trouble, China minerals, UK follies, Gaza horrors, Ukraine war, vanishing privacy, Trumpishness, Musk world, hapless Dems, immigration troubles, Mr. market, AI, and wretched excess]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sunday Morning Movie Presents: Shadowlands (1993) Run Time: 2H 11M]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292422</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-sunday-morning-movie-presents-shadowlands-1993-run-time-2h-11m.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T10:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shadowlands is a beautiful movie about the love between C.S. Lewis, played by Anthony Hopkins, and Joy Gresham, played by Debra Winger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>semper loquitur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your Smartphone Is a Parasite, According To Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293516</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/your-smartphone-is-a-parasite-according-to-evolution.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-08T09:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is having a smartphone worse than having head lice?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/7/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293476</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-7-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T10:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our scintillating daily links: lingering mono effects, why big hail, Musk threatens new party, China rare earths break for Big 3, EU military pork, UK pension raid? moar Israel attacks on Lebanon, US to audit Urkraine, plane route disruption, food on credit, dollar worries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Trump’s Contradiction-Riddled Strategy to Preserve US Hegemony]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293491</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/michael-hudson-trumps-contradiction-riddled-strategy-to-preserve-us-hegemony.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T10:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump does have a plan to shore up America''s flagging power, even if, when you put the pieces together, it does not make much sense.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Tourism Pushed Barcelona to Breaking Point, and How Social Movements Are Fighting Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293494</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/how-tourism-pushed-barcelona-to-breaking-point-and-how-social-movements-are-fighting-back.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T10:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barcelona features locals turning activists to curb tourism levels that hurt everyday life, particulalry for lower income. residents]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBMsyEOzXNFgZkJ2xVlrObb</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBMsyEOzXNFgZkJ2xVlrObb"/>
        <updated>2025-06-07T06:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing New Coffee Break Writers!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293482</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/announcing-new-coffee-break-writers.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T21:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please welcome Nat Wilcox Turner and Curro Jimenez, who will be giving Monday, Wednesday, and Thursday Coffee Break features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Working Class Life in 17th-Century Italy, Science in Decline, AI and Scientific Understanding, and Neanderthal Art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293439</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-working-class-life-in-17th-century-italy-science-in-decline-ai-and-scientific-understanding-and-neanderthal-art.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part the First. Tales from the Crypt. Subtitled The lives of 17th century Milan’s working poor – their health, diet, and drug habits – emerge from thousands of bodies buried under a public hospital.  This article appeared in Science on 1 May 2025: In 1456, the Duke of Milan established a medical institution dedicated to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gavin Rae: &ldquo;Weak Myths&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/weak-myths</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/weak-myths"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T14:28:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in Poland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Golden Dome Dangers: How Trump’s Scheme Threatens to Make the US Less Safe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293470</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/golden-dome-dangers-how-trumps-scheme-threatens-to-make-the-us-less-safe.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Trump's Golden Dome is set to backfire, except for the grift, which is presumably the real point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/6/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293431</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-6-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our stealthy daily links, including the Donald and Elon break up while Trump finally gets Xi on the phone, and NATO goes for 5 percent defense spending.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aditya Bahl: &ldquo;Freedom Fighter?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/freedom-fighter</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/freedom-fighter"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manmohan Singh’s India.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Rare Earth Ban Starts Shutting Down Auto Production]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA06UG7rog1xDXl-iUqvqJ1</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA06UG7rog1xDXl-iUqvqJ1"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T08:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Germany and Japan have reported the first shutdowns. These shutdowns will become worse over time. While China is providing some licenses for Rare Earths, they’re slow walking them and customs approval, and I’ve been told (though cannot confirm) that so far they have given none to Indian companies. (Maybe that little Pakistan kerfuffle wasn’t cost free?)
This is all very amusing and instructive on a number of levels. America banned something that China could handle the bans on: semiconductors. China, after much provocation, banned something that there is simply no way of replacing in the next few years:
“There is no solution for the next three years except to come to an agreement with China,” said Andreas Kroll, managing director of Noble Elements, rare earths importer for medium-sized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access Claude Sonnet 4 in Amazon Q Developer CLI]]></title>
        <id>1d2439d32ee1a9b0caeebf083fd33eba3e8f79b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/access-claude-sonnet-4-in-amazon-q-developer-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T02:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer now supports Claude Sonnet 4 within the CLI, bringing advanced coding and reasoning capabilities to your development workflows at no additional cost. This latest model excels in coding with a state-of-the-art 72.7% for agentic coding on the SWE-bench (see Claude 4 announcement for more information). With enhanced coding and reasoning capabilities, it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now open – AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region]]></title>
        <id>9b737f301236fc9a1f97ad9542f52ea3a36fd7c6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-taipei-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T01:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced that AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region is generally available with three Availability Zones and Region code ap-east-2. The new Region brings AWS infrastructure and services closer to customers in Taiwan. Skyline of Taipei including the Taipei 101 building As the first infrastructure Region in Taipei and the fifteenth Region […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS API models and publicly available resources for AWS API definitions]]></title>
        <id>0b7f6978dcbe0b0b5e4efb6e4a86d6709a0b0876</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-aws-api-models-and-publicly-available-resources-for-aws-api-definitions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T20:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS now provides daily updates of Smithy API models on GitHub, enabling developers to build custom SDK clients, understand AWS API behaviors, and create developer tools for better AWS service integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Eclipse workflows with Amazon Q Developer, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>05ebebc2340e29f825c6ffee0271b9f005815008</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/streamline-your-eclipse-workflows-with-amazon-q-developer-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Q Developer plugin for the Eclipse integrated development environments (IDE). This release builds upon the developer experience introduced in our November 2024 public preview, bringing powerful AI-assisted development capabilities directly into Eclipse 2025-03(4.35.0) and later versions. The integration significantly improves how developers write, test, and maintain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madhu Balaji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing an agentic coding experience in Visual Studio and JetBrains IDEs]]></title>
        <id>932be76c45353da0993964a23f6f8878cdea155c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-an-agentic-coding-experience-in-visual-studio-and-jetbrains-ides/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers spend countless hours on repetitive tasks like debugging code, writing unit tests, and validating build processes – time that could be better spent on innovation and problem-solving. To address these challenges, Amazon Q Developer has expanded its intelligent coding assistant capabilities to Visual Studio and JetBrains Integrated development environments (IDEs). This new agentic experience […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing up to 45% price reduction for Amazon EC2 NVIDIA GPU-accelerated instances]]></title>
        <id>c63d6de4890142659cd2619871034949323b6a87</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-up-to-45-price-reduction-for-amazon-ec2-nvidia-gpu-accelerated-instances/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T17:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces significant price reductions of up to 45 percent for NVIDIA GPU-accelerated EC2 instances, increasing accessibility to these high-demand resources for generative AI workloads amid industry-wide GPU shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing our newest 2025 AWS Heroes cohort]]></title>
        <id>f3a0d5a098455913668033ff260b56d4caefa33a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-our-newest-2025-aws-heroes-cohort/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T17:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS community is a vibrant network of innovators, problem-solvers, and thought leaders who drive cloud technology forward. Today, we’re excited to shine a spotlight on three exceptional individuals who embody the spirit of innovation, knowledge-sharing, and community building. From architecting scalable solutions for millions of users to fostering inclusive tech groups, these professionals are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AGI Is Not Multimodal]]></title>
        <id>683fb98b77c3d76051ac142c</id>
        <link href="https://thegradient.pub/agi-is-not-multimodal/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T14:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["In projecting language back as the model for thought, we lose sight of the tacit embodied understanding that undergirds our intelligence." –Terry Winograd
The recent successes of generative AI models have convinced some that AGI is imminent. While these models appear to capture the essence of human]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin A. Spiegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raymond Geuss: &ldquo;Storyteller&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/storyteller</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/storyteller"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T13:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alasdair MacIntyre (1929-2025).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Financiers Win, They Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB8ETjO7BgYRjgHXhozxgmi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB8ETjO7BgYRjgHXhozxgmi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T12:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the simplest lenses to look at an industrial society is whether it’s run by financiers or capitalists.
Socrates famously noted that some people live to eat and others eat to live.
Capitalists need money so they can do things. Financiers do things so they can get money. To a financier it doesn’t matter how money is made, so long as they won’t go to prison. All that matters is rate of return.
A capitalist has something they want to do: Ford wanted to build cars. Edison wanted to invent. The Wright Brothers wanted to fly. They need money so they can do whatever it is that turns their crank.
Capitalists create great societies. Financiers destroy them.
As soon as rate of return becomes the only consideration, a society becomes less interested in doing new things or doing old things well …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brussels’s media machine: EU media funding and the shaping of public discourse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New report exposes a vast, previously under-scrutinised system through which the European Union annually disburses €80 million a year to media projects across Europe and beyond]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an AI Agent that puts humans in the loop with Knock and Cloudflare’s Agents SDK]]></title>
        <id>3YwK1RRHXn4kGrNazu4AKd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-agents-at-knock-agents-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Knock shipped an AI Agent with human-in-the-loop capabilities with Cloudflare’s Agents SDK and Cloudflare Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bell (Guest author)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models what they don’t know]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of MIT researchers founded Themis AI to quantify AI model uncertainty and address knowledge gaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Winn | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Short Summary Of Why China Is Winning &amp; The West Fading]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T03:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s about living in reality:
The main difference between American and Chinese society today is less that one has more dumb people and one has more smart people and more that within public life being stupid is relentlessly shamed as stupid in one and being smart is relentlessly shamed as stupid in the other.
These days American society assigns intelligence credentials based not on who can demonstrate a meticulous well developed understanding of how anything works but who can give the most smart sounding post hoc rationalization for half baked ideas people desperately want to be true.
If you do the former and it yields answers people don’t like they’ll reach deep into their bag of fantasyland narratives to try to invalidate your credibility. If you provide the latter you’re celebrated not o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI stirs up the recipe for concrete in MIT study]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With demand for cement alternatives rising, an MIT team uses machine learning to hunt for new ingredients across the scientific literature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Paul Laurent | MIT Concrete Sustainability Hub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models the broad strokes to sketch more like humans do]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SketchAgent, a drawing system developed by MIT CSAIL researchers, sketches up concepts stroke-by-stroke, teaching language models to visually express concepts on their own and collaborate with humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shipps | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze media content using AWS AI services]]></title>
        <id>df70aecbbf09cdd2b5cd5b057a82fffb9d66bac9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/analyze-media-content-using-aws-ai-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations managing large audio and video archives face significant challenges in extracting value from their media content. Consider a radio network with thousands of broadcast hours across multiple stations and the challenges they face to efficiently verify ad placements, identify interview segments, and analyze programming patterns. In this post, we demonstrate how you can automatically transform unstructured media files into searchable, analyzable content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Bradham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora DSQL, MCP Servers, Amazon FSx, AI on EKS, and more (June 2, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>75057629af595e8c8b702253ca50ca0709ea6ed9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-aurora-dsql-mcp-servers-amazon-fsx-ai-on-eks-and-more-june-2-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s AWS Summit Season! AWS Summits are free in-person events that take place across the globe in major cities, bringing cloud expertise to local communities. Each AWS Summit features keynote presentations highlighting the latest innovations, technical sessions, live demos, and interactive workshops led by Amazon Web Services (AWS) experts. Last week, events took place at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Questions: How to help students recognize potential bias in their AI datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courses on developing AI models for health care need to focus more on identifying and addressing bias, says Leo Anthony Celi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne Trafton | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>