<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-06T06:40:01.237Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-05-06T06:40:01.237Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Soon Empty Shelves]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBKpBDqrGaM2sxiu-GT8KMd</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBKpBDqrGaM2sxiu-GT8KMd"/>
        <updated>2025-05-06T04:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just listened to Chuck Todd say the following three things regarding economics, “eveything is unstable; everything is uncertain and we’re probably about a month a way from empty shelves.”
Ian and others far brighter than me, what say you?
I’m speechless.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 5, 2025 (#545)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22346</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/05/daily-reading-list-may-5-2025-545/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T22:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at what enterprise tech buyers are spending money on, which seven agentic patterns you should pay attention to, and seven programming myths that waste your time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent coding at your fingertips: Introducing an agentic coding experience in your IDE]]></title>
        <id>241234825bcbf19ef1ffd1abd9c0b67cc9113d97</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-agentic-coding-experience/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T22:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in March, I wrote about the new agentic coding experience within the Amazon Q Developer CLI. Recently, Amazon Q Developer announced that it has added a similar experience to the integrated development environement (IDE). Agentic coding in the IDE allows you to work with Amazon Q Developer to read and write files locally, run […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: A roadmap for revolutionizing health care through data-driven innovation]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/qa-roadmap-revolutionizing-health-care-through-data-driven-innovation-0505</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/qa-roadmap-revolutionizing-health-care-through-data-driven-innovation-0505"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new book coauthored by MIT’s Dimitris Bertsimas explores how analytics is driving decisions and outcomes in health care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sara Feijo | MIT Open Learning</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New tool evaluates progress in reinforcement learning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/new-tool-evaluate-progress-reinforcement-learning-0505</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/new-tool-evaluate-progress-reinforcement-learning-0505"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“IntersectionZoo,” a benchmarking tool, uses a real-world traffic problem to test progress in deep reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Laboratory for Information and Decision Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Across the Pond, Tyrants Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291767</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/tyranny.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The leaders of the three largest countries in Western Europe (excluding Russia) are acting like tyrants as their economies implode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Kirk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Nova Premier, Amazon Q Developer, Amazon Q CLI, Amazon CloudFront, AWS Outposts, and more (May 5, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>1d0450f31c741d4ae51fcdff9efb4bd6f73510d7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-nova-premier-amazon-q-developer-amazon-q-cli-amazon-cloudfront-aws-outposts-and-more-may-5-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:25:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I went to Thailand to attend the AWS Summit Bangkok. It was an energizing and exciting event. We hosted the Developer Lounge, where developers can meet, discuss ideas, enjoy lightning talks, win SWAGs at AWS Builder ID Prize Wheel, take a challenge at Amazon Q Developer Coding Challenge, or learn Generative AI at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer in GitHub (in preview) accelerates code generation]]></title>
        <id>6d10f8f6de34d288a4f77a7277284a37e58dce95</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-developer-in-github-now-in-preview-with-code-generation-review-and-legacy-transformation-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T16:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is now available in preview on GitHub, enabling developers to assign tasks to an AI agent that can develop features, conduct code reviews, enhance security, and migrate Java code, all directly within GitHub issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling with safety: Cloudflare's approach to global service health metrics and software releases]]></title>
        <id>5D2xgj0sJ6yj8oOh6qrNUb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/safe-change-at-any-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Cloudflare tackles the challenge of scaling global service health metrics to safely release new software across our global network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harshal Brahmbhatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental Collapse, Not Just Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAOrcWgdRBl1kUnScAunbRn</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAOrcWgdRBl1kUnScAunbRn"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T12:06:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I talk about the environment I usually say “Climate change & Environmental Degradation.” It’s important to understand that while these two reinforce each other, they aren’t the same thing.
A UK-wide decline in bug splats recorded on car number plates indicates an “alarming” fall in the number of flying insects, UK scientists said in a survey published yesterday.
The 2024 Bugs Matter report revealed the numbers of flying insects found stuck to vehicle number plates had dropped by nearly 63 per cent since 2021.

This study from Germany in 2017 found a:
More than 75 percent decline over 27 years in total flying insect biomass in protected areas
And there were decreases in the 1900s as well. Bug biodiversity and biomass is WAY down. Here’s a lovely chart from 2019.

We’re seeing this sort of crash, in both biodiversity and biomass for all sorts of species, not just bugs. Problem is that our food production and a pile of environmental processes related to water and atmosphere renewal are dependent on animals and plants. There’s massive loss of plankton, mammals, reptiles, bacteria in our soil and so on.
This stuff isn’t independent of climate change, but even without any climate change there’d still be plenty of it. The loss of wild areas, plus tons of pollution and the side effects of extraction and energy generation are largely to blame.
Collapse of this “web of life” or “food web” is a huge danger to us, as well as being a monstrous crime against other forms of life.
So don’t think “climate change is it”. It isn’t, and it may not even be as important as loss of biodiversity.
 
This blog has always been free to read, but it isn’t free to produce. If you’d like to support my writing, I’d appreciate it. You can donate or subscribe by clicking on this link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/5/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291711</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-5-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our scintillating daily links, including Trump and the Constitution, AI spiritual fantasies, and whale urine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Neverending Tariffs War? Proposes 100% Tariffs on Foreign Movies; De Minimus Exclusion Ends, Hurting the Poor; Financial Times on Tariff Evasion, Official and Via Trans-Shipment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291741</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/trumps-neverending-tariffs-war-proposes-100-tariffs-on-foreign-movies-deminimus-exclusion-ends-hurting-the-poor-financial-times-on-tariff-evasion-official-and-via-trans-shipment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A battlefield update on Trump's tariff wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU Zombie Uses Trump as Cover to Further Feed on Citizens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291714</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/the-eu-zombie-uses-trump-as-cover-for-further-feeding-on-citizens.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T10:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ursula and company are inching towards using emergency powers for first installment of 900 billion 'rearmament' because Trump.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the State Sent Californians’ Personal Health Data to LinkedIn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291719</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/how-the-state-sent-californians-personal-health-data-to-linkedin.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T09:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The state’s health insurance exchange transmitted pregnancy and domestic abuse data during a marketing campaign. It is reviewing its website practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsibility to Protect and Humanitarian Military Intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291704</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/responsibility-to-protect-and-humanitarian-military-intervention.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-05T04:31:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humanitarian military intervention sounds like an oxymoron and often winds up being one. Nevertheless, there are rules of engagement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – May 4, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDfuroW1F-gjzvGzJAE9q-y</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDfuroW1F-gjzvGzJAE9q-y"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T18:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – May 4, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
Trump not violating any law
‘He who saves his Country does not violate any Law’
‘We’re Not Stopping’: Trump Border Czar Vows to Ignore Judges
[The Daily Beast, via MSN 03-18-2025]
Judges Who Rule Against Trump Become Target of New MAGA War
Malcolm Ferguson, May 2, 2025 [The New Republic]
At least 11 federal judges and their families have been threatened and harassed since they ruled against President Trump on issues of deportations, federal funding, and his war on “wokeness.”
The judges, under anonymity, told Reuters that they had received multiple intimidating calls and emails to their homes and offices. Some have been subject to the disturbing “pizza box” method, in which antagonists will anonymously send a pizza to the home…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/4/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291664</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-4-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T10:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our strategic daily links: flying bike, snake venom, COVID politics, Chinese pharmaceuticals, Brazil engergy, Gaza horrors, Ukraine burning, Real ID, vanishing privacy, hopeless homeless, Trumpishness, DOGEy moves, immigration troubles, nervous markets, Democrats lost, AI everywhere, and wretched excess]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sunday Morning Movie Presents: The Strange Case of Senor Computer (2000) Run Time 1h 20m]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291643</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/the-sunday-morning-movie-presents-the-strange-case-of-senor-computer-2000-run-time-1h-20m.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T10:30:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sunday Morning Movie presents The Strange Case of Senor Computer (2000) A wonderful little movie  about an intelligent robot and its very human relationships.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>semper loquitur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Underage Workers, Millions of Dollars and Trucks Full of Dead Chickens — Inside the Business of Killing in Response to Bird Flu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291676</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/underage-workers-millions-of-dollars-and-trucks-full-of-dead-chickens-inside-the-business-of-killing-in-response-to-bird-flu.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-04T09:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The federal government has a single contractor to assist with killing infected flocks, leading to delays and the use of controversial culling methods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/3/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=291640</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-3-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T10:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our funky daily links: falcon trek, Trump threatens China w/ Iran oil santionsl, RFK, Jr. still not backing measles vaccination, climate impact of satellites, UN out of dough? Reform triumphant, India-Pakistan staredown, EU seizes some Russian assets, driverless trucks in TX, UK to ban crypto leverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtMIyCZEmXVefpMo5PfWuL</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtMIyCZEmXVefpMo5PfWuL"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T09:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza, the US and China: the future of war and the end of civilisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gaza-the-us-and-china-the-future</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gaza-the-us-and-china-the-future"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T08:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza sets a terrifying precedent: the radical reinterpretation of the laws of war is bound to have serious consequences on the destructiveness of future conflicts — including a US-China war]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;On the Brink?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink-2</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink-2"/>
        <updated>2025-05-03T00:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India and Pakistan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 2, 2025 (#544)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22324</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/02/daily-reading-list-may-2-2025-544/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T23:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at what it means to fine-tune a model, how the Agent Development Kit intersects with MCP, and failing to understand vibe coding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel AI model inspired by neural dynamics from the brain]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/novel-ai-model-inspired-neural-dynamics-from-brain-0502</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/novel-ai-model-inspired-neural-dynamics-from-brain-0502"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T19:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New type of “state-space model” leverages principles of harmonic oscillators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Conner-Simons | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer elevates the IDE experience with new agentic coding experience]]></title>
        <id>f3ff1bed68c2118a8d7bd68d42a69c816654807f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-developer-elevates-the-ide-experience-with-new-agentic-coding-experience/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T16:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new interactive, agentic coding experience for Visual Studio Code allows Q Developer to intelligently take actions on behalf of the developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a more accessible GitHub CLI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/building-a-more-accessible-github-cli/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/building-a-more-accessible-github-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How do we translate web accessibility standards to command line applications? This is GitHub CLI's journey toward making terminal experiences for all developers.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/building-a-more-accessible-github-cli/">Building a more accessible GitHub CLI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Franklin Ramírez Gallegos: &ldquo;Noboa Victorious&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/noboa-victorious</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/noboa-victorious"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T12:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in Ecuador.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mathias Fuelling: &ldquo;Hang-Ups&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hang-ups</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hang-ups"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T11:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Tulathimutte’s ‘Rejection’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UR-Values Of The Right, Center and Left]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA2bMCDH5zOpbV-1WYAVZsL</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA2bMCDH5zOpbV-1WYAVZsL"/>
        <updated>2025-05-02T08:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The left looks at people who are hurting and immediately asks “how can we help them?” 
The center looks at hurting people and says “can insiders profit from this?” 
The right looks at people who are hurting and says “how can we hurt them more?”
There’s some overlaps between the right and center on this, but the right’s ur-Value is cruelty to the weak and outsiders. If they can make money hurting people, that’s great. The center just wants money. Lots of it. That’s their ur-value. If making money helps or hurts someone, OK.
The left’s ur-value is kindness. They see someone hurting, and they want to help.
The center has a modicum of shame. Being around people who are hurting, like homeless people, bothers their conscience a little bit, so they want them removed from their sight.
The right wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 1, 2025 (#543)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22300</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/01/daily-reading-list-may-1-2025-543/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T23:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at using Gradio to build an MCP server, how many developers there are in the world, and why devs don't trust your "build vs buy" guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirteen new MCP servers from Cloudflare you can use today]]></title>
        <id>17j3OSuM89oMb5wurF4Tij</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/thirteen-new-mcp-servers-from-cloudflare/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now connect to Cloudflare's first publicly available remote Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers from any MCP client that supports remote servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nevi Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP Demo Day: How 10 leading AI companies built MCP servers on Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>6VjjFQfl3i9xgTfebvWEk4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/mcp-demo-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re teaming up with Anthropic, Asana, Atlassian, Block, Intercom, Linear, PayPal, Sentry, Stripe, and Webflow to launch new remote MCP servers, built on Cloudflare, to enable Claude users to manage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025: A month of innovation for Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>3c54f5572b22149e031b448987bc03f3144f0b98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/april-2025-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T12:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As April 2025 comes to a close, I’m amazed by the innovations that Amazon Q Developer has launched in the past few weeks. Generative AI is evolving fast, enabling developer experiences that were just not possible a few months ago. Each new launch helps make Q Developer the most capable generative AI–powered assistant for software […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Britain Is Toast, Period]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDYxMkn1nvaV6DlCik7Jqnc</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDYxMkn1nvaV6DlCik7Jqnc"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T10:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long term readers will know that I’ve been negative on Britain for a long time. Corbyn was their last chance to turn things around, but Corbyn lacked the necessary ruthlessness to win, and was destroyed by absolutely bullshit allegations of anti-semitism. Starmer became Labour leader after him, on promises of left wing policies which even a child should have disbelieved, and ruthlessly purged Labour of all left wingers.
Conservatives ran stupid governments with horrid policies which led to inflation and continued de-industrialization, and Starmer backed into power.  His policies are worse than the Conservatives, with draconian cuts to social welfare policies like child support, heat for old people, and wheelchairs for cripples. The last British steel plant is shutting down, and the next pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making AI models more trustworthy for high-stakes settings]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/making-ai-models-more-trustworthy-high-stakes-settings-0501</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/making-ai-models-more-trustworthy-high-stakes-settings-0501"/>
        <updated>2025-05-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new method helps convey uncertainty more precisely, which could give researchers and medical clinicians better information to make decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Nova Premier: Our most capable model for complex tasks and teacher for model distillation]]></title>
        <id>496773c478c81014d943125964afe6878996616a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-nova-premier-our-most-capable-model-for-complex-tasks-and-teacher-for-model-distillation/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nova Premier is designed to excel at complex tasks requiring deep context understanding, multistep planning, and coordination across tools and data sources. It has capabilities for processing text, images, and videos while also serving as a teacher model for distilling smaller, more efficient models for production use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – April 30, 2025 (#542)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22286</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/04/30/daily-reading-list-april-30-2025-542/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T23:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at avoiding skills atrophy in the age of AI, the future of middle management, and a guide to Kubernetes debugging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT-Portugal Program enters Phase 4]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-portugal-program-enters-phase-4-0430</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-portugal-program-enters-phase-4-0430"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T20:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New phase will support continued exploration of ideas and solutions in fields ranging from AI to nanotech to climate — with emphasis on educational exchanges and entrepreneurship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lisa Capone | MIT Portugal Program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating a CDK v1 Application to CDK v2 with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>13b7b4ca9103d4354f450c6acd40d0e06d49b5a4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/migrating-a-cdk-v1-application-to-cdk-v2-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T19:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction: AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) is an open-source software development framework for defining cloud infrastructure in code and provisioning it through AWS CloudFormation. As of June 1, 2023, AWS CDK version 1 is no longer supported. To avoid the potential issues that come with using an outdated version and to take advantage of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Rahul Sharad Gaikwad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing streamable HTTP transport and Python language support to MCP servers]]></title>
        <id>5BMzZem6hjKhNsSnI5l3BZ</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/streamable-http-mcp-servers-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're continuing to make it easier for developers to bring their services into the AI ecosystem with the Model Context Protocol (MCP) with two new updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Morrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada’s Future &amp; The New Carney Government]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAvoFonlan6RbdgM6TlnK19</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAvoFonlan6RbdgM6TlnK19"/>
        <updated>2025-04-30T03:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DAVOS/SWITZERLAND, 26JAN13 – Mark J. Carney, Governor of the Bank of Canada is seen during the Session ‘The Global Economic Outlook’ at the Annual Meeting 2013 of the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, January 26, 2013.
Copyright by World Economic Forum
swiss-image.ch/Photo Moritz Hager

Carney has won a minority government. He will have to govern with the support of the NDP. The NDP was slaughtered in this election, and there were a few ridings where people strategically voting for the Liberals actually led to the Conservatives winning. And, it’s worth pointing out that the Conservatives increased their seat count, which is why Poilievre is sticking around as leader, despite losing the election and his own seat. (A loyal MP will stand down and let him run in a by-election in a sa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – April 29, 2025 (#541)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22267</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/04/29/daily-reading-list-april-29-2025-541/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T23:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how to measure collaboration among software team members, how to develop superpowers in the AI age, and seven dilemmas you'll face as a (engineering) manager.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing second-generation AWS Outposts racks with breakthrough performance and scalability on-premises]]></title>
        <id>2d9cdd400b07f9a523543476d36d63f2c6d94397</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-second-generation-aws-outposts-racks-with-breakthrough-performance-and-scalability-on-premises/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-29T19:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces significant upgrades to Outposts racks, featuring the latest x86-powered EC2 instances and new accelerated networking options designed for ultra-low latency and high-throughput on-premises workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>