<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-28T12:47:22.780Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-28T12:47:22.780Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277441</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our ravishing daily links: fundamentalists' brains? Long Covid in kids, 25 F temp increases coming? China rare earths clampdown, Macron authoritarianism, Ukraine ballsitic misiles, Wilkerson on US decline, Trump + Harris agree debate rule, moar Durov, Stoller on antitrust, Burning Man richfest, strikes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G.A. Cohen on the output bias]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53064</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/g-a-cohen-on-the-output-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Originally drafted for a conference at Frankfurt in 2018 to mark the 40th anniversary of Karl Marx’s Theory of History: A Defence. I’ve done a bit of editing of my conference script and added a few footnotes etc, but it isn’t necessarily produced to the scholarly standards one might require of a journal article.) In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peer Review: What Does It Really Mean Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277485</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/peer-review-what-does-it-really-mean-today.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why peer review is not what you might think it is, and what can be done to remedy that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distortions and Distractions of the Democratic National Circus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277483</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/on-the-distortions-and-distractions-of-the-democratic-national-circus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A well-targeted rant about the offensive shallowness and neglect of concrete material needs of voters that the Democratic Party now embodies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why People Stay After Local Economies Collapse − A Story of Home Among the Ghosts of Shuttered Steel Mills]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277481</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/why-people-stay-after-local-economies-collapse-%e2%88%92-a-story-of-home-among-the-ghosts-of-shuttered-steel-mills.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why many community members don't leave in the face of localized collapse, and how they adapt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The (Electoral) Politics of Age Gaps]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53062</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/the-electoral-politics-of-age-gaps/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’ nomination locks in another Boomer presidency. This single generation — those born in the nineteen years between 1946 and 1964 — is guaranteed another presidency. 36 consecutive years, not counting the Biden Interregnum (he’s technically too old). Despite being a Boomer, you may have noticed that she’s the young, exciting candidate. Yes, the generational […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are Liberal Zionists Cheering as Harris Echoes Biden on Gaza?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331961</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/why-are-liberal-zionists-cheering-as-harris-echoes-biden-on-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T06:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hours after Kamala Harris gave her acceptance speech at the Democratic convention, the president of the “pro-Israel, pro-peace” organization J Street took a victory lap in an effusive e-mail to supporters. “Wow,” Jeremy Ben-Ami wrote. “What a week! As J Streeters leave the Democratic National Convention fired up and ready to go, it’s clear we’re having a greater impact than ever.” He added that “the vice president’s remarks on Israel-Palestine were perhaps the clearest articulation of J Street’s values from a presidential nominee.” More
The post Why are Liberal Zionists Cheering as Harris Echoes Biden on Gaza? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abba A. Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris and the Need for Diplomacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331785</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/harris-and-the-need-for-diplomacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T06:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no sign of Harris’s positions on Biden’s policy choices that would suggest strong differences or alternative approaches to change the direction of U.S. policy.  Harris at this point cannot deviate from President Biden’s key positions on sensitive issues, although Vice President Hubert Humphrey probably lost the election in 1968 to Richard Nixon because of a belated critique on U.S. policy in Vietnam.  Biden’s unwavering support for Israel could ultimately hurt Harris in key states such as Michigan.  More
The post Harris and the Need for Diplomacy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Papua’s Green State Vision: Social Movement, Therefore “Terrorism”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331768</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/west-papuas-green-state-vision-social-movement-therefore-terrorism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T06:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apart from the brutality it undergirds, almost always fuelling violence, there’s something truly unhinged about political disinformation, especially in Indonesian-occupied West Papua because it’s so at odds with reality, not to say bizarre. Yet it’s orchestrated at the highest levels of government in Indonesia and readily accepted by powerful governments and transnationals, which have their own systems of disinformation, including peddling Indonesia’s, and lying by commission and omission as a standard activity to advance geostrategic and economic objectives. More
The post West Papua’s Green State Vision: Social Movement, Therefore “Terrorism” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raki Ap – Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surprise: Doctors and TV Viewers LIKE Ask-Your-Doctor Ads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331989</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/surprise-doctors-and-tv-viewers-like-ask-your-doctor-ads/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study by ZoomRx found that many doctors and patients like ask-your-doctor ads. Patients said they had asked their doctors about a specific med––as the ads tell them to––and doctors said the ads can facilitate “helpful conversations.” One doctor in the study even said the ads could inspire patients “to think about symptoms that  More
The post Surprise: Doctors and TV Viewers LIKE Ask-Your-Doctor Ads appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martha Rosenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democratic Party Convention: Lesser Evilism Strikes With a Vengeance and a Cacophony of Corporate Media Hype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331968</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/democratic-party-convention-lesser-evilism-strikes-with-a-vengeance-and-a-cacophony-of-corporate-media-hype/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[24,500 full size posters reading “We Heart Joe” were held high by virtually every Democratic Party Convention delegate and attendee jammed into Chicago’s United Center to cheer for yesterday’s disgraced and withdrawn presidential candidate, Genocide Joe Biden. That the Biden-Harris administration presided over a new congressionally approved $20 billion for the racist Zionist, apartheid Israeli  More
The post Democratic Party Convention: Lesser Evilism Strikes With a Vengeance and a Cacophony of Corporate Media Hype appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Mackler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joy: The Fairy Tale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331965</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/joy-the-fairy-tale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is on its last bony legs. As I write this we are less than 30 days out from the autumnal equinox which officially sticks the fork in the season’s withering carcass and signals the arrival of more dark than light/ more bouts of the shivers as we slide into another winter. The Maine state  More
The post Joy: The Fairy Tale appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Rhames</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Lynch, Probability and the Cyber Industrial Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331876</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/mike-lynch-probability-and-the-cyber-industrial-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It began as a devastating, confined storm off the coast of Sicily, striking the luxury yacht Bayesian in the form of a devastating water column resembling a tornado.  Probability was inherent in the name (Thomas Bayes, mathematician and nonconformist theologian of the 18th century, had been the first to use probability inductively) and improbability the nature of the accident.  More
The post Mike Lynch, Probability and the Cyber Industrial Complex appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Eli Lilly’s Decision to Lower the Starter Price of Blockbuster Weight-Loss Drug Zepbound]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331971</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/on-eli-lillys-decision-to-lower-the-starter-price-of-blockbuster-weight-loss-drug-zepbound/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, President Biden and I co-authored an op-ed demanding that Novo Nordisk and Eli Lilly substantially lower the outrageously high prices they are charging Americans for popular weight-loss and diabetes drugs. In fact, we said that if these profitable pharmaceutical companies “refuse to substantially lower prescription drug prices in our country and end their  More
The post On Eli Lilly’s Decision to Lower the Starter Price of Blockbuster Weight-Loss Drug Zepbound appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernie Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Braveheart Asymptote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331786</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/letter-from-london-braveheart-asymptote/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I write this from a London hospital bed having—most powerfully—imagined bagpipes the moment I came round from my operation. Drugs will do that for you. The pipes—the great Highland bagpipe—will do that for you. Playing alongside was an anaesthetist, a surgeon into Bach (you always find out), plus nurses and student nurses. At one point  More
The post Letter from London: Braveheart Asymptote appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Views the US Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331951</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/china-views-the-us-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China’s Analytical Challenges China’s America watchers have the same tough job that faces Donald Trump’s campaign: coming up with a new game plan after Joe Biden passed the torch to Kamala Harris. China’s economic woes, Taiwan’s future, and global competition with the US make the analytical task for China more challenging Contrary to what may  More
The post China Views the US Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Our Left Strategy Going Forward in the US?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331811</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/whats-our-left-strategy-going-forward-in-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After this week’s Democratic National Convention—which went well on their terms for what the Democratic leaders wanted—I  strongly believe Kamala Harris will defeat Donald Trump for the presidency.  When one looks seriously at her fundraising (almost $500 million in a month), trends in poll numbers, people volunteering to knock on doors, enthusiasm, a successful convention  More
The post What’s Our Left Strategy Going Forward in the US? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Scipes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distortions and Distractions of the Democratic National Circus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331987</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/on-the-distortions-and-distractions-of-the-democratic-national-circus/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I suffered through much of the three nights of non-reality programming called the 2024 Democratic National Convention. I watched nearly the whole fucking thing—the jugglers, acrobats, gladiator contests, cock fighting, and the dancers too. I sat mesmerized by an unlimited bounty of bread and circus offerings—lions and Christians, tight-rope walkers and card tricks—I might have  More
The post On the Distortions and Distractions of the Democratic National Circus appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taliban American Style?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/28/taliban-american-style/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T04:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Americans vilify the Taliban and are horrified at the draconian rules they impose on every resident and organization,and especially their oppression of Afghani women and girls. So why are millions of freedom-loving Americans rushing to vote for candidates who plan to impose white Christian nationalism (WCN) on our country? Yes, Christianity and Islam have different religious  More
The post Taliban American Style? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patricia Ramsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook operates a little differently in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8351</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/facebook-operates-differently-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Swan, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Rampant celebrity cryptocurrency scam ads are as Australian as Tim Tams, koalas or the Great Barrier Reef, according to American Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen, who says the tech giant’s lack of focus on Australia has let scams run wild on its platform compared with other markets. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zbowling in "Microsoft donates the Mono Project to the Wine team"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371554</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371554"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T19:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked on Mono a lot back in the early 2000s (back in the SVN days before it moved to Git, even). This move makes a lot of sense. Things evolved a lot over the years. Mono's legacy goals, which are to be a portable CLR (.NET) runtime for platforms that Microsoft didn't care about, don't make much sense today.
Mono made a lot of sense for running places where full .NET didn't, like in full AOT environments like on the iPhone where you can't JIT, or for random architectures that don't matter anymore but once did for Linux (Alpha, Itanium, PPC, MIPs, etc.). When Microsoft bought Xamarin (which itself was born out of the ashes of the Novell shutdown of the Mono effort) and started the DotNET Core efforts to make .NET more portable itself and less a system-provided framework and merge in a lot of the stuff Mono did a single more focused project made more sense.
Mono was still left out there to support the edge cases where DotNET Core didn't make sense, which was mostly things like being a backend for Wine stuff in some cases, some GNOME Desktop stuff (via GTK#, which is pretty dead now), and older niche use cases (second life and Unity still embed mono as a runtime for their systems). The project was limping, though, and sharing a standard library but different runtimes after much merging. Mono's runtime was always a little more portable (C instead of C++) and more accessible to experiment with, but we need that less and less, but it's still perfect for Wine. So, having it live on in Wine makes sense. It's a natural fit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zbowling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pif in "Why is the Oral-B iOS app almost 300 MB? And why is Colgate's app even bigger..?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371345</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41371345"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T18:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My question is: why do an Oral-B app and a Colgate app even exist?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277445</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler : Politics; syndemics; "It's too soon to tell"; Detective sought for Kamala mask video; Pandemics are mobility-borne ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by silverquiet in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369889</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369889"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years back it started showing me obvious political ragebait. I ignored it and then it started showing me pictures of women whose nipples were obviously showing through their clothing, which was an improvement, but still not the reason I signed up for Facebook. I've always understood it as the algorithm is looking for engagement and will try some lowest common denominator tactics to engage in it. As someone who just wanted to see the odd picture of a friend or relative, I don't have much use for Facebook these days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>silverquiet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by object-a in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369244"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's funny because Facebook's news feed in the last couple years is unusable, filled with AI slop and clickbait. Twitter similarly requires aggressive use of block + mute to eliminate scams, clickbait, and other content I'm not interested in.
I don't know if this is due to their changes in moderation policy, or if AI has overwhelmed them, but I vastly preferred the old news feeds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>object-a</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Malidir in "Zuckerberg claims regret on caving to White House pressure on content"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369086</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41369086"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Pavel's interview with Tucker Carlson, he mentions how he (VK) met with Zuckerberg, and he told them new features they were planning.  And Zuck nicked them all.
Zuck is on a major PR campaign drive, I would not trust a word he says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Malidir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21618</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/27/security/privacy-aware-infrastructure-purpose-limitation-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we’ve been diligently working to incorporate privacy into different systems of our software stack over the past few years. Today, we’re excited to share some cutting-edge technologies that are part of our Privacy Aware Infrastructure (PAI) initiative. These innovations mark a major milestone in our ongoing commitment to honoring user privacy.  PAI offers [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fog of War and Narrative, Israel and Hezbollah Attacks Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277442</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/fog-of-war-and-narrative-israel-and-hezbollah-attacks-edition.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T15:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An attempt at informational forensics on the Israel-Hezbollah pitched battle on Sunday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Getting Multiple Library Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:08:47.894Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read a lot. Probably more than a lot of people, but still not as much as some.
When you read a lot, libraries can become your best friend. Although I would love to buy all of the books, it's just not sustainable. As much as I love having a physical collection, there are times when just borrowing a book over buying it, makes more sense.
I loved visiting libraries growing up. There was one next to my middle school that I would go to after school. I remember getting lost in the pages of a book, tucked in a corner between shelves.
I went to libraries less and less growing up. Then e-books happened. I still read a lot, and found myself buying most of the e-books I read. At some point, I got a Kindle Unlimited subscription. Despite its name, the book selection really wasn't unlimited, especially if you read outside of the genre of their book offerings.
Enter Libby.
If you haven't heard of it, Libby is a game changer for anyone who loves reading. All you need is a library card, and suddenly you have access to the library's entire e-book collection.
I started a Libby account with a local library card to start with. Simple enough, right? But then I had an epiphany: as long as I'm a California resident, I can get different library cards across the state. Now that is the real game changer. More library cards = even more selection of books.
Now, every time I visit a new California town, I try to stop by their library to get a card. Yesterday, we visited a new town for my birthday. We passed a library while roaming around town. Guess what I did?
I got myself yet another library card.
Thinking about collecting all of the cards up and down California at this point. A librarian Thanos, if you will.
27/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do You Do for Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/what-do-you-do-for-fun/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/what-do-you-do-for-fun/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo by Wonder Woman
People in the first world take having fun very seriously. We sure spend enough money on it. Some kinds of fun are pricing themselves out of the middle-class range. Tickets and all that goes with them (parking, food, souvenirs) to major league sports and top-tier concerts can easily take a family outing into four figures. A day at a Disney theme park for a family of four is well over $1000.
I've never been to a Disney Park, and my last concert was 15 years ago. I guess I'll die without seeing Bruce Springsteen. I heard the other day that he's reached billionaire status, and I'm not giving a billionaire any of my dough to be entertained for three hours, no matter how good a showman he is. I enjoy amateur and minor league sports. Hell, I like watching my grandson's socce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277375</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our munchy daily links: giant python, cow gene editing, China skirting US resrictions, SKorea EV antipathy, Macron impeachmenet threat, UK fuel poverty, massive Russia strikes Ukraine grid, Kamala-Trump debate row, Durov detainment, Zuck censorship admission, Christmas supply chain woes, lousy air attentant and Intel pay]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Amigos No More? US and Canada Warn of Dire Economic Consequences if Mexico Persists With Judicial Reforms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277432</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/three-amigos-no-more-us-and-canada-warn-of-dire-economic-consequences-if-mexico-persists-with-judicial-reforms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T10:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico's President AMLO responds by refusing to discuss the matter with US Ambassador Ken Salazar while giving the Mexican people a brief history lesson on US interference in Latin America.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rising Democratic Threat of “Hopeful Militarism”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277430</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-rising-democratic-threat-of-hopeful-militarism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T09:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Team Democrat messaging strategy boils down to "War is love."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irrationality and mass paranoia invade our societies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T08:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“But why are they attacking us? What have we done to them to make them hate us and bomb us like this?”. These are surprising and thought-provoking questions from ordinary Russians living in the Kursk region, asked by reporters sent to cover the advance of Ukrainian troops into this Russian territory. And they are all the more surprising given that these Russians do not live in Vladivostok or Siberia, but practically straddle the Russian border with Ukraine, just a few dozen kilometers from (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Palestine, 
Antifascism, 
Ukraine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Forgiveness, Foreclosure, & Christianity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277390</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/michael-hudson-forgiveness-foreclosure-christianity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T06:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson reprises a favorite theme of how the salutary practice of debt forgiveness came to an end under Greco-Roman oligarchs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Poverty Reduction Under Capitalism is a Myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331864</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/why-poverty-reduction-under-capitalism-is-a-myth/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T06:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From its beginnings, the capitalist economic system produced both critics and celebrants, those who felt victimized and those who felt blessed. Where victims and critics developed analyses, demands, and proposals for change, beneficiaries, and celebrants developed alternative discourses defending the system. Certain kinds of arguments proved widely effective against capitalism’s critics and in obtaining mass  More
The post Why Poverty Reduction Under Capitalism is a Myth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Awareness of Capitalists’ Use of Colonialism Encourages International Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331866</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/awareness-of-capitalists-use-of-colonialism-encourages-international-solidarity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T06:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Studying capitalism, Karl Marx examined the Industrial Revolution in Europe. He explored conflict between worker and employer. In their book Capital and Imperialism (Monthly Review Press, 2021), authors Utsa Patnaik and Prabhat Patnaik emphasize that Marx’s followers believed that, with the onset of capitalism, “accumulation [has] occurred only on the basis of the generation of  More
The post Awareness of Capitalists’ Use of Colonialism Encourages International Solidarity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’s Failed Opportunity?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331738</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/harriss-failed-opportunity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T06:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’s language of “opportunity agenda” leans right. She shared at the DNC, “My mother kept a strict budget. We lived within our means. Yet, we wanted for little and she expected us to make the most of the opportunities that were available to us, and to be grateful for them.” Such words could easily have been said by a Republican and reflect the party’s ideas about “fiscal responsibility.” More
The post Harris’s Failed Opportunity? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warmonger Confessions: More Frankness on AUKUS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331872</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/warmonger-confessions-more-frankness-on-aukus/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with satellite states and subject powers is that their representatives are rarely to be trusted, especially on matters regarding security. Their idea of safety and assurance is tied up in the interests of some other power, one who supposedly guarantees it through a promised force of arms come the place and come the  More
The post Warmonger Confessions: More Frankness on AUKUS appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Survived Chicago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331874</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/i-survived-chicago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Kamala Emanuel (the Other Kamala) and I were touring on the west coast, people frequently wished us luck in Chicago, particularly with regards to the Chicago police, who will, for good reason, forever be associated with the police riots at the Democratic National Convention in 1968. I wasn’t worried about the cops.  I’ve been  More
The post I Survived Chicago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rovics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Will Hear the Names of the Dead: The DNC in Chicago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331858</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/you-will-hear-the-names-of-the-dead-the-dnc-in-chicago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luxury SUVs carried important people into important buildings for important events. And between us and the importance, there were police with rifles strapped to their chests. A couple of weeks ago, I plunged into Lake Michigan. Unlike usual, the water felt warm. It was easy to run all the way in and easy to float  More
The post You Will Hear the Names of the Dead: The DNC in Chicago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danaka Katovich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealed: RFK, Jr’s Best Dope Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331751</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/revealed-rfk-jrs-best-dope-stories/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. used to shoot heroin with Keith Richards, which I guess is about as cool as shooting heroin gets. Despite his experience with needles, “Bobby” (as his friends call him) gets a lot of grief from Democrats, medical experts, and his family for being an antivaxx conspiracy monger. Bobby’s druggie past is no secret—his  More
The post Revealed: RFK, Jr’s Best Dope Stories appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Bonner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workers, Unchecked: The Case for Card Check This Labor Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331730</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/workers-unchecked-the-case-for-card-check-this-labor-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The process of union certification is a critical area of labor rights, acting as a precursor to collective bargaining. One method, card check, simplifies this process by allowing workers to express their desire for union representation through majority sign-up. Because it reduces opportunities for employer interference and expedites union certification, card check has come under  More
The post Workers, Unchecked: The Case for Card Check This Labor Day appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayley Brown – Sylvia Allegreto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money or Your Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331856</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/money-or-your-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Money or Your Life. Alphonse Daumier’s caricature of the Europeans ready to kill Greece unable to pay back the money it borrowed primarily from England, February 15, 1850. Public Domain In 2009, Greece had a deficit of 6 percent of GDP. But concocted statistics made the deficit 12.5 percent of GDP. This higher deficit became  More
The post Money or Your Life appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Story of the Scab: How Organized Labor Shames Its Traitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331735</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/the-story-of-the-scab-how-organized-labor-shames-its-traitors/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over its long history, the American labor movement has displayed a remarkably rich vocabulary for shaming those deemed traitors to its cause. Some insults, such as “blackleg,” are largely forgotten today. Others, such as “stool pigeon,” now sound more like the dated banter of film noir. A few terms still offer interesting windows into the  More
The post The Story of the Scab: How Organized Labor Shames Its Traitors appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Afflerbach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris: A Hubert Humphrey for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331766</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/27/kamala-harris-a-hubert-humphrey-for-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T05:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The party is over in Chicago. The liberals won. Kamala Harris gave a typical acceptance speech with a bit more military machismo than some Democrats might have given. The chants of USA, USA echoed nauseatingly in the hall. Some of my somewhat left-leaning friends didn’t join in the USA chants, but posted messages on their  More
The post Kamala Harris: A Hubert Humphrey for 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price Gouging Part Two]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45576</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/26/price-gouging-part-two/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford When you are only concerned with one thing and have only one tool things can go awry quite easily.  So it is with our price theory friends.  They bask in the rigor of their thinking and look askance at the inability of regular folks to grasp the point of the logic of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first six months of Vision Pro by Michael Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8348</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/first-six-months-vision-pro-michael-ball/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T21:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Ball, writing about the first six-months of Apple’s spatial computing, and — whether Apple likes it or not — virtual reality headset, Vision Pro: The Vision Pro is clearly the most ambitious of their product launches since the iPhone, the first to be wholly developed under the purview of CEO Tim Cook (though various […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ndesaulniers in "DOJ sues realpage for algorithmic pricing scheme that harms renters"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41360283</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41360283"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies are culluding to suppress wages by algorithm, too.  Look up a company called Aon, and their product called Radford Data & Analytics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ndesaulniers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SeptemBest: A Quality Blog Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/septembest-blog-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/septembest-blog-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know what you’re thinking:
“Not another blog challenge!”
But hear me out...
There’s been a debate lately about the existence or non-existence of blog challenges. The criticism has been that quantity takes precedence over quality. Even though there haven’t been any requirements for daily posts, it’s sort of become the norm to post every day.
With that in mind, I propose a kind of anti-challenge for the month of September. A "challenge" where quality comes first – and only.
The idea is to blog in the way you normally do. Whether that’s one post every two weeks or two a day doesn’t matter. Then, at the end of September, you choose the text that you think was your "best" during the month.
The post that...
...you are most proud of.
...was the hardest to write.
...is the most personal.
...best represents you.
...made you think in new ways.
Or whatever you base "best" on. Your favorite, simply put.
Why this challenge?
As a reader, perhaps someone visiting your blog for the first time, it gives a good picture of who you are as a blogger. This no-pressure approach might also lead your writing into new unexplored territory. Diving back into the ideas and perspectives that resonated with you most can offer fresh and valuable insights.
If you want to join SeptemBest, as I’ve chosen to call it, contact me and I’ll add you to the list below. Then come back to me on October 1st with your “winning text,” and it will be added here along with the rest of the contributions.
Please note: I really want to emphasize that this is not a competition, despite the name. The idea is for it to be a fun, low-pressure, and interesting exploration on a personal level.
Participants
Robert Birming
Alexandra
Netigen
Nikki
Jd
Jedda
Brandon
Dominik
Shrutarshi Basu
Lou Plummer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: S3 Conditional writes, AWS Lambda, JAWS Pankration, and more (August 26, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>4cb2b61c9474efcc91420feeff2904beeee6b491</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-s3-conditional-writes-aws-lambda-jaws-pankration-and-more-august-26-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T18:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS User Group Japan (JAWS-UG) hosted JAWS PANKRATION 2024 themed ‘No Border’. This is a 24-hour online event where AWS Heroes, AWS Community Builders, AWS User Group leaders, and others from around the world discuss topics ranging from cultural discussions to technical talks. One of the speakers at this event, Kevin Tuei, an AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scrlk in "NSA releases 1982 Grace Hopper lecture"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41359832</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41359832"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great quote at 45:26 regarding vertical vs. horizontal scaling: https://youtu.be/si9iqF5uTFk?t=2726
> "Now back in the early days of this country, when they moved heavy objects around, they didn't have any Caterpillar tractors, they didn't have any big cranes. They used oxen. And when they got a great big log on the ground, and one ox couldn't budge the darn thing, they did not try to grow a bigger ox. They used two oxen! And I think they're trying to tell us something. When we need greater computer power, the answer is not "get a bigger computer", it's "get another computer". Which of course, is what common sense would have told us to begin with."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scrlk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RETINAS: Real-Time Infrastructure Accounting for Sustainability]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21592</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/26/data-infrastructure/retinas-real-time-infrastructure-accounting-for-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T16:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are introducing a new metric— real-time server fleet utilization effectiveness —as part of the RETINAS initiative to help reduce emissions and achieve net zero emissions across our value chain in 2030. This new metric allows us to measure server resource usage (e.g., compute, storage) and efficiency in our large-scale data center server fleet in [...]
Read More...
The post RETINAS: Real-Time Infrastructure Accounting for Sustainability appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your Next Experiment by Learning Better Proxy Metrics From Past Experiments]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/64c786c2a3ac</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/improve-your-next-experiment-by-learning-better-proxy-metrics-from-past-experiments-64c786c2a3ac?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T15:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Aurélien Bibaut, Winston Chou, Simon Ejdemyr, and Nathan Kallus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Lap Around the Sun]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/another-lap-around-the-sun/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/another-lap-around-the-sun/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:41:42.947Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating another year of being alive.
That's it.
That's the post.
A reflection post upcoming at some point, but not today.
Today, the plan is to bask in the sun, spend the day in one of the cutest towns, and enjoy the sound of the waves crashing on the shore.

...and of course, snapping photos of all of the things
26/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lessons learnt from Blaugust 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/lessons-learnt-from-blaugust-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/lessons-learnt-from-blaugust-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm writing this post based on Blaugust's fifth-week theme, explaining some of the lessons I have learned through my participation in Blaugust this month. Here is the description of this week's theme:
"This week is a reminder that the goal of Blaugust is to refresh the content creators out there for the coming year, and not to burn them out in the process. Some folks are going to cross the finish line and immediately go dormant and others will want to process their thoughts about the proceedings. This space is reserved as a bit of a cooldown lap so that you can share your own experiences."
As mentioned above, Blaugust's goal is to refresh content creators and not burn them out. As such, for this last week of August, I will not be forcing myself to write on a certain day if I don't feel up …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use This Curse on Your Worst Enemy]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/use-this-curse-on-your-worst-enemy/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/use-this-curse-on-your-worst-enemy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I have one favorite thing in the whole world to think about, it's me. Left to my own devices, I am definitely my own favorite thing to contemplate. I'm constantly evaluating whether I feel good enough and if not, what I can do to rectify that situation. Do I need a snack? Maybe some cell phone time is called for. Maybe I am working too hard, and I need a break. Are people treating me with enough respect? Are my co-workers doing their fair share of tasks? Are raises coming up? Will I get what I deserve?
If I had the power to do one thing to my worst enemy, I would make that bastard as self-centered as possible, because brothers and sisters, let me tell you, a self-centered existence is a miserable existence. Until I was 43, the answer to the internal question "Do I feel good enough?" was…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Algorithmic Macroprudential Risk, and a legal case related to possible rent inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53048</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/26/algorithmic-macroprudential-risk-and-a-legal-case-related-to-possible-rent-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to The New York Times (23 August), The Justice Department “filed an antitrust lawsuit on Friday against the real estate software company RealPage, alleging its software enabled landlords to collude to raise rents across the United States.” I am not an expert in law or anti-trust, but there is another (systemic risk management) angle to this story that the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by red_admiral in "Australian employees now have the right to ignore work emails, calls after hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41354732</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41354732"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:14:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like the Swiss implementation of this. A manager _can_ contact an employee on a Sunday, but then the employee is immediately on weekend-rate overtime even if they just got an email with "deal with this next week". So, many companies have systems that hold back e-mail sent outside of working hours until the next working day unless specially authorised and costed.
Never underestimate an economics-based solution to a legal problem, a.k.a. "if you really want to ban it, tax it".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>red_admiral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make America “Lethal” Again: a Review of Some Speeches at the DNC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331775</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/make-america-lethal-again-a-review-of-some-speeches-at-the-dnc/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T06:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The just concluded Democratic National Convention at the United Center in Chicago was by most accounts a success. On Monday, the first night, Joe Biden gave his valedictory address, after which the audience breathed a sigh of relief. Not just because the long, self-indulgent peroration was over, but because Biden was finally out: one geezer down, one more to go. Two days later, state delegates conducted a celebratory roll-call vote, formally designating Kamala Harris and Tim Walz the Democratic Party nominees for president and vice-president. More
The post Make America “Lethal” Again: a Review of Some Speeches at the DNC appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World Without Artworks That Auction Off for $80 Million?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331726</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/a-world-without-artworks-that-auction-off-for-80-million/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fine art has been a wonderful vehicle for “wealth signaling among the ultra-rich,” the Duke University sociologist Lisa Keister recently noted, ever since ancient times. The latest twist on that signaling? Billionaires are now commissioning giant statues of their nearest and dearest. Mark Zuckerberg of Facebook fame has just unveiled a seven-foot tall statute of  More
The post A World Without Artworks That Auction Off for $80 Million? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Fear of the US Becoming an Authoritarian State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331800</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/understanding-the-fear-of-the-us-becoming-an-authoritarian-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberals see former President Donald Trump as the leading perpetrator of creating an authoritarian state. Organizations backing him, like the conservative Heritage Foundation, which released Project 2025, reinforce this perception. Trump claimed not to know who was behind Project 2025; however, a CNN review found that at least 140 people who worked for him were involved. The  More
The post Understanding the Fear of the US Becoming an Authoritarian State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imperialism: Conrad, Lenin and Heart of Darkness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331802</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/imperialism-conrad-lenin-and-heart-of-darkness/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[125 years after it was first serialized in three installments in Blackwood’s Magazine in 1899, Joseph Conrad’s novella Heart of Darkness continues to be widely read and to be scrutinized by teachers, students and scholars. There’s a lot to scrutinize. No work of modernist fiction has been studied more often —according to critic par excellence  More
The post Imperialism: Conrad, Lenin and Heart of Darkness  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Donahue (1935-2024) – Greatest Champion of Free Speech for the Peoples’ Interest of the 20th Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331764</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/phil-donahue-1935-2024-greatest-champion-of-free-speech-for-the-peoples-interest-of-the-20th-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T05:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was 1967 when the national media was covering our auto safety initiatives. A call came on the hallway phone outside my $90-a-month boarding room. “Hello, I’m Phil Donahue. I want to invite you on my new syndicated television talk show in Dayton, Ohio. You’ve come a long way without my help, but can you  More
The post Phil Donahue (1935-2024) – Greatest Champion of Free Speech for the Peoples’ Interest of the 20th Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Was Never Really the Alternative He Pretended To Be]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331798</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/26/rfk-jr-was-never-really-the-alternative-he-pretended-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 19, 2023, Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. launched his long-shot presidential bid as a Democrat. On October 9, 2023, he declared himself an “independent” and began courting (and in some states, creating) “third parties” for their nominations. He received 19 votes for the Libertarian Party’s nomination at its 2024 national convention over Labor Day  More
The post RFK Jr. Was Never Really the Alternative He Pretended To Be appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mquander in "Removing stuff is never obvious yet often better"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353884</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353884"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T03:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know if this calculator was good or bad, but the rationale sounds superficially ridiculous.
> Visitors who didn't see the calculator were 16% more likely to sign up and 90% more likely to contact us than those who saw it. There was no increase in support tickets about pricing, which suggests users are overall less confused and happier.
Of course if you hide the fact that your product might cost a lot of money from your users, more of them will sign up. Whether they are better off depends on whether they end up getting a bill they are unhappy with later at some unspecified future date, or not. That's not something you will figure out from a short-term A/B test on the signup page. So this seems like totally useless evidence to me.
I see this dynamic frequently with A/B tests. For example, one of my coworkers implemented a change that removed information from search result snippets. They then ran an A/B test that showed that after removing the information, people clicked through to the search result page more often. Well, obviously, it makes sense that they might click through more often, if information they wanted which was previously in the snippet, now requires them to click through. The question of which is actually better seemed to have been totally forgotten.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mquander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by steelframe in "Australian employees now have the right to ignore work emails, calls after hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353270</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41353270"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T01:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've dabbled in management a few times in my career. This meant attending manager-only meetings and trainings. I'll never forget one time when a manager in a focus group said something along the lines of, "The tech sector is going through a rough patch, so we can turn the screws on our employees and they'll have to take it because they will have a hard time trying to find a job somewhere else." This is at a company where most of the employees are on work visas, so losing their job can very rapidly escalate into having to leave the country in short order.
After I picked my jaw up off the floor I realized I simply lacked the scruples I'd need to be "one of them." I also started looking into every legal protection I had available to me in my jurisdiction.
I know not every manager is like that. I'd like to think I wasn't. But there are enough of them that think that way that legal protections often need to be there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>steelframe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jawns in "Police Chief Says Cops Have a 5th Amendment Right to Leave Body Cameras Off"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352340</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352340"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T23:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In general, courts have held that Fifth Amendment protections against self-incrimination pertain to testimonial evidence, not broadly to any possible evidence that might be incriminating.
The Fifth Amendment does not extend to physical evidence or other non-testimonial evidence, even if such evidence is potentially incriminating. For example, courts have held that things like blood samples, fingerprints, handwriting samples, and even video or audio recordings do not fall under the protection of the Fifth Amendment because they are not considered testimonial in nature.
The report notes that it is the police chief, not a lawyer representing him, who is making the preposterous argument that the Fifth Amendment justifies his conduct.  Any lawyer who tried to make that argument would be made a laughing stock.
Indeed, I would think that this internal affairs report, where the chief is essentially admitting that he knew he'd done something wrong and was trying to prevent incriminating evidence from being recorded, would be pretty damning in front of a jury, because it establishes that he was well aware of the recklessness of his conduct.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jawns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by koverstreet in "Linux Pipes Are Slow"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352339</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41352339"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T23:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my sideprojects is intended to address this: https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/
The idea is a syscall for getting a ringbuffer for any supported file descriptor, including pipes - and for pipes, if both ends support using the ringbuffer they'll map the same ringbuffer: zero copy IO, potentially without calling into the kernel at all.
Would love to find collaborators for this one :)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>koverstreet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leshokunin in "Database “sharding” came from Ultima Online? (2009)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41351603</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41351603"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T21:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For context, Raph Koster is not only the person who designed Ultima Online, but generally considered one of the top theoricians in game design. This isnt some guy who has a small blog and came up with a neat explanation for how some word came about in the early days of the web. Its the guy who did it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leshokunin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The asterism: the proposed new symbol for the fediverse. So say we]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8342</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/asterism-proposed-new-symbol-fediverse/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The asterism, ⁂, a typographic symbol made up three stars, is being proposed as the new symbol for the fediverse. If the fediverse needs a symbol, it’s not half bad. Does the web have a symbol? I’m not even sure. But for those who came in late, the fediverse can be defined thusly: The fediverse […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bryanlarsen in "Is Telegram really an encrypted messaging app?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41350809</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41350809"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T20:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try the mud puddle test: log into your account on a new device using the password recovery flow.   Can you see your old messages?
If the answer is yes then law enforcement can too.
https://www.forbes.com/sites/anthonykosner/2012/08/05/how-se...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bryanlarsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by arianvanp in "Lidl's Cloud Gambit: Europe's Shift to Sovereign Computing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348977</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348977"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T17:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaia-X is a disaster. The article misrepresents it. Gaia-X is not a framework for what a European cloud should look like. This would be useful.
In beautiful EU bureaucratic style It's a framework for how to talk about how a European Cloud could look like.
It's not about technical standards. It's about how we can talk about how we can think of maybe eventually deciding on how we can come up with standards that might one day lead to talk about implementations.
It represents to me everything that is wrong with the EU today. A bureaucratic monster that can't decide how to talk about things or come to any form of alignment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>arianvanp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Years and Still Settling In]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/two-years-and-still-settling-in/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/two-years-and-still-settling-in/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks two years since closing on our house in the San Francisco Bay Area (California). It feels both like it just happened yesterday, and a lifetime ago.
Buying this house was not the easiest. During the entire nightmare of a process, I remember thinking that I wanted to blog about it (I wasn’t writing yet then) in detail, so that all first time homebuyers could avoid the stress we endured. Also, no one ever teaches you any of this in school, so I’m not exactly sure how anyone could know the process until they’re knees deep in it already.
Yes, there are plenty of articles out there about the house buying process, but it still doesn’t truly prepare you for the real thing. At least it didn’t for us.
I want to caveat that this house was not my first house. In 2012, I bought my first hou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by devman0 in "Arrest of Pavel Durov, Telegram CEO, charges of terrorism, fraud, child porn"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348206"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of really terrible takes in this comment section. Telegram didn't have encrypted groups by default, and telegram possessed a lot of content on their servers that they had been made aware was illegal and didn't cooperate. Nothing more, nothing less.
The comparisons to other providers is off base because either other providers are cooperating more when they possess actionable, unencrypted information and taking steps to detect or prevent such recurrences or they are like Signal and do not have access to the underlying material in the first place or store it for very long anyway.
One cannot legally run a hosted, unmoderated content platform in the developed world, one will always be required to remove illegal materials and turn over materials in cooperation with law enforcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devman0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One-Thing Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://matanabudy.com/one-thing-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://matanabudy.com/one-thing-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:46:58.541Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love apps that do only one thing but do it well. I don’t need an app to solve all my problems in one interface. This usually leads to one of the following:
The app solves many problems I have, but it solves each one poorly.
The app solves some problems I have and some that I don’t, making parts of it useless to me.
I don’t want what they call a Super-app. I want an app designed to solve something specific, one that has been thoughtfully crafted to address a particular need. This doesn’t mean that I want an app for every little thing. The “one thing” could also be a big thing; it just needs to be focused.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mazambazz in "Arrest of Pavel Durov, Telegram CEO, charges of terrorism, fraud, child porn"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348050</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41348050"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems like the Kim Dotcom situation again.
Why are these service providers being punished for what their users do? Specifically, these service providers? Because Google, Discord, Reddit, etc. all  contain some amount of CSAM (and other illegal content), yet I don't see Pichai, Citron, or Huffman getting indicted for anything.
Hell, then there's the actual infrastructure providers too. This seems like a slippery slope with no defined boundaries where the government can just arbitrary use to pin the blame on the people they don't like. Because ultimately, almost every platform with user-provided content will have some quantity of illegal material.
But maybe I'm just being naive?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mazambazz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aragorn Eloff - Do Anarchists Dream of Emancipated Sheep?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aragorn-eloff-do-anarchists-dream-of-emancipated-sheep?v=1724591914</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aragorn-eloff-do-anarchists-dream-of-emancipated-sheep?v=1724591914"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T13:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aragorn Eloff
Title: Do Anarchists Dream of Emancipated Sheep?
Subtitle: Contemporary Anarchism, Animal Liberation and the Implications of New Philosophy
Source: Chapter from ‘Anarchism and Animal Liberation: Essays on Complementary Elements of Total Liberation’ (ISBN: 0786494573). <academia.edu>

 Everything fits together, from the bird whose brood is crushed to the humans whose nest is destroyed by war. 
 —Louise Michel 
 In this essay I explore the relations between contemporary anarchism and animal rights/liberation through the lens of Deleuze/Guattari-inflected complex systems theory. Specifically, I look at the liberalism and normative practices endemic to the mainstream animal rights movement, engaging with some of the more salient critiques that have emerged from Leftist an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reclaim the Night!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Reclaim-the-Night</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Reclaim-the-Night"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T12:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Though the sun is rising in the east, rain is pouring, and tides are visiting to and fro in the Ganges, nothing can diminish the spark that was raised against the heinous rape that happened at one of the most premium medical colleges, known as R. G. Kar Medical College, in Kolkata. Yes, Kolkata, known as the safest city in India, to all the people throughout the nation is experiencing turmoil after decades over a shivering issue. On August 9, a postgraduate trainee doctor found rape and (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
India, 
Feminisms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Salmali Das, Sankha Subhra Biswas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Perfect Blogger]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/the-perfect-blogger/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/the-perfect-blogger/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend a lot of time thinking about blogging; about my own blog and those of the people I read regularly and the ones I discover as I explore. Every once in a while I discover a real gem where someone's efforts are all at once entertaining, thought provoking, inspiring and original. I'll often be stricken with a pang of jealousy. "I want to write like that", I'll tell myself, knowing that I won't. Alas, I write like me. I might get some inspiration or an idea for a day's entry from one of my favorite bloggers, but I'm never going to be them.
The writing I like the best is the personal kind. I like knowing what makes people tick. As much as I like reading well written technical pieces that tell me how to do cool things with my MacBook and my iPhone, I like it best when I find out what it i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auraj - People’s uprising against an autocratic state]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/auraj-people-s-uprising-against-an-autocratic-state?v=1724575985</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/auraj-people-s-uprising-against-an-autocratic-state?v=1724575985"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Auraj
Title: People’s uprising against an autocratic state
Subtitle: The present, past and future of Bangladesh
Date: 24 July 2024
Notes: The writer is a member of the anarchist group Auraj network. Auraj (which means “anarchy” in Bangla) is an anarchist network of Bangladeshi students and other people from different professions. Auraj has published various translations of Anarchist thinkers such as Bakunin, Kropotkin, Rudolf Rocker, and others in Bangla. Auraj also frequently publishes articles on Bangladesh’s political and economic scenario. Auraj has shown solidarity with the recent labor movements (movements of garment workers, jute mill workers), student movements, and civil rights movements in Bangladesh. Although members of Auraj have individually taken part directly in many…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday Photoblogging: Tempio del Valdier, Frasassi Caves, Italy.]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53034</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/25/sunday-photoblogging-tempio-del-valdier-frasassi-caves-italy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Ronzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confederación Nacional del Trabajo - CNT on the re-foundation of the IWA]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/confederacion-nacional-del-trabajo-cnt-on-the-re-foundation-of-the-iwa?v=1724573647</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/confederacion-nacional-del-trabajo-cnt-on-the-re-foundation-of-the-iwa?v=1724573647"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T08:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Confederación Nacional del Trabajo
Title: CNT on the re-foundation of the IWA
Subtitle: CNT-E’s XI Congress agreements on internationalism
Date: 5 April 2016
Source: Retrieved on 25th August 2024 from www.cnt.es

 The CNT would like to announce and explain the agreements made during our December 2015 Congress with regards to the current International Workers’ Association (IWA). We believe that it is necessary to explain our position on the drift of our international, so that this internal situation can be made publically known in order to openly and quickly begin the process of its re-foundation. 
 In the CNT we consider international solidarity to be critical in this historical moment, marked by the global organization of capitalism. As expected, the economic crisis has served as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oulipo in "Ask HN: What are you working on (August 2024)?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41344737</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41344737"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T05:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey guys! We're engineers/designers from France, and we've built the Ultimate DIY Battery that you can repair and refill!
It works with 90% of the bikes/motor brands on the market, so I assumed that some people here might be interested, if they got a non-functional batteries but they still want to use their e-bike?
We believe that everybody should have control about stuff they own, and we should fight against planned obsolescence!
Here are a few videos about our founder on the battery itself, why we built it, and how to assemble it:
- What is the Gouach Battery: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NsuW1NPkvNk
- Presentation of the pack: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mLoCihE0eIA
- Presentation of the fireproof and waterproof casing: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EDJpt7RDbRM
Here are the juicy bits: https://docs.gouach.com
We'd love some feedback from the e-bike DIY builder community
Oh, and it's launching as a Kickstarter in September and there is an offer for early-backers here https://get.gouach.com/1 for a 25% discount on the battery!
You can follow us on Instagram https://www.instagram.com/gouach.batteries to get the latest news!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oulipo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wenc in "Anthropic Claude 3.5 can create icalendar files, so I did this"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41344714</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41344714"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T05:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You just have to double check the results whenever you tell Claude to extract lists and data.
99.9% of it will be correct, but sometimes 1 or 2 records are off. This kind of error  is especially hard to notice because  you're so impressed that Claude managed to do the extract task at all --  plus the results look wholly plausible upon eyeballing -- that you wouldn't expect anything to be wrong at all.
But LLMs can get things ever slightly wrong when it comes to long lists/tables. I've been bitten by this before.
Trust but verify.
(edit: if the answer is "machine verifiable", one approach  to ask an LLM to write a Python validator which it can execute internally. ChatGPT can execute code. I believe Sonnet 3.5 can too, but I haven't tried.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wenc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by joegibbs in "Ask HN: What are you working on (August 2024)?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41343553</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41343553"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T01:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working on a kind of strategy game called Fall of an Empire (https://fallofanempiregame.com), it's a bit like a mix between Crusader Kings, Total War, Mount and Blade type games (just the overworld, not the battles), but rather than expanding you're trying to prevent an empire from collapsing.
It's a ton of work, especially with the number of systems - you've got combat, resource management, settlement development, food managment, espionage, diplomacy etc - these all need to play together well. And then you've got to add in the storyline, graphics, marketing -but I think I'm making pretty good progress.
I'm still using Unreal Engine 4 because I started work on that version and I haven't needed to upgrade to 5 since it's been released.
I've got a free prologue that I'm releasing on October 1, so now until then is a lot of polishing to make it work well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joegibbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shirro in "NASA announces Boeing Starliner crew will return on SpaceX Crew-9"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41343184</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41343184"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T00:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing was awarded more money for their vehicle, had years of extra time and two previous demonstration flights. This flight should have been close to flawless given the additional time Boeing had for remediation and testing. Boeing engineers should have understood their systems well enough to convincingly demonstrate the vehicle met NASA's safety requirements. Even after much additional testing during the flight they couldn't make their case. Starliner will probably complete its third uncrewed return intact and people might question if NASA was being overly cautious but perhaps Boeing should have supplied a crewed vehicle with reliable thrusters and avoided this embarrassment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shirro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hintymad in "NASA announces Boeing Starliner crew will return on SpaceX Crew-9"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41341311</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41341311"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T20:39:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wonder if there are books or articles that analyze how and why Boeing declined so fast and so spectacularly. Boeing used to be able to build 747 under budget and ahead of schedule, just like Lockheed could dazzle the world by creating U2 ahead of schedule and under budget with fewer than 200 people (or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hintymad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by KronisLV in "You are not dumb, you just lack the prerequisites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41339152</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41339152"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T16:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lovely article, though honestly getting those prerequisites also takes a lot of time, effort and either motivation or discipline in ample amounts.
As someone who was the “smart kid” growing up, going to the university without good work ethic was pretty eye opening, no longer being able to coast on intuitively getting subjects, but rather either having to put in a bunch of effort while feeling both humbled and dumb at times, or just having to sink academically.
Even after getting through that more or less successfully and having an okay career so far, I still definitely struggle with both physical health and mental health, both of which make the process of learning new things harder and slower than just drinking a caffeinated beverage of choice and grokking a subject over a long weekend. Sometimes it feels like trying to push a rock up a muddy slope.
And if I’m struggling, as someone who’s not burdened by having children to take care of or even not having the most demanding job or hours to make ends meet, I have no idea how others manage to have a curious mind and succeed the way they do.
Admittedly, some people just feel like they’re built different. Even if I didn’t have those things slowing me down as much (working on it), I’d still be nowhere near as cool as people who dive headfirst into low level programming, electrical engineering, write their own simulations, rendering or even whole game engines and such. Maybe I’m just exposed to what some brilliant people can do thanks to the Internet, but some just manage to do amazing things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KronisLV</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for the Little Things]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/looking-for-the-little-things/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/looking-for-the-little-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've written before about how I've had a gratitude practice for a long time, nothing too elaborate, just three bullet points in my journal each night. I'm often grateful for some of life's little comforts over and over again, things like a good meal I didn't have to cook or an especially entertaining show on TV. A long time ago, I read The Miracle of Mindfulness by Vietnamese Buddhist monk, Thich Nhat Hanh in which he encourages a junior monk to peel an orange while savoring the moment, to do nothing but feel and smell and taste the orange. When I have the presence of mind to do such things, I like to savor moments of small joy while they are happening and then to reflect on them afterwords. I'm not above escaping from my present reality at times and looking forward to something that's hap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mubu in "Reddit banned me for developing Geddit"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41336679</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41336679"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T08:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reddit was my favorite website growing up. I'd discover new interesting subs, read random posts and comments. The frontpage was somewhat interesting too, but now it feels like a bot fest and propaganda machine.
I still use Reddit but way less than I used to before, and I no longer use it for fun but just to read niche tech subs.
I refuse to use the official mobile app. I've always used Baconreader and then Relay on Android. Relay survived the API changes and adopted a subscription model.
But thanks to Revanced I was able to patch an old version of Relay to use my own API key for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mubu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ExoticPearTree in "Microsoft formally deprecates the Windows Control Panel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41336094</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41336094"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T06:24:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I swear, MS kills all the useful features in Windows.
For comparison, configuring a network interface using Control Panel is simple, straight forward and allows me to change all the settings I want. Trying to do the same thing using the Settings app is complex, it hides pretty nuch all of the advanced settings that you want to see or change. And on top of that, it doesn’t even show you how long that interface has been connected to the network and how much data was transferred both ways: incredible debugging info lost.
Oh, and the fact that you can’t tick which updates you want and which you don’t…
I’m pretty sure others have other gripes with the “streamlined experience”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ExoticPearTree</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by helipad in "Did you lose your AirPods?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41334843</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41334843"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T01:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I left my AirPods Pro at a school sports field an hour away, and I didn't realize until the next morning after it been raining heavily. I gave them up for lost and needed headphones for work – so ordered some from Apple with same day delivery.
A week later, I got a Find My notification that they had been spotted – at the same sports field. I figured what the hell, put on a podcast and drove the hour to see if I could find them. Worst case scenario, a couple of hours of driving.
Using Find My and the directional feature points you in the right direction to within feet, I found them in the tall grass.
The case had been perfectly watertight, and they'd barely lost a percent of power in a week. Remarkable really all round.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>helipad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did you lose your AirPods?]]></title>
        <id>https://alexyancey.com/lost-airpods/</id>
        <link href="https://alexyancey.com/lost-airpods/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T23:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A friend found some AirPods on the ground and tapped them to his phone, revealing only the serial number and the last four digits of the owner's number. He turned to me for help.
All Out
Could I really brute-force spam all phone numbers ending in 1234 and find the right owner? This seemed a bit impractical, so I had to think of ways to whittle the number down to something more manageable.
Area Code
I started with the assumption that the owner lived near me in the Portland metropolitan area. With that, I restricted the search to our local area code*. Sure, they could be from out of town, but hey, let's give it a shot.
999 numbers is a manageable list, but I wanted to trim the number a bit more. Sure, sending a thousand SMS messages isn't much to a determined spammer, but I didn't want to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Robson: &ldquo;To Be Continued&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/to-be-continued</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/to-be-continued"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T21:17:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Wei Shujun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish packages to AWS CodeArtifact using Amazon CodeCatalyst Actions]]></title>
        <id>e8258fd18a1ab4295fa19354682af40f46311ed2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/publish-packages-to-aws-codeartifact-using-amazon-codecatalyst-actions/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T20:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst is a unified software development service for development teams to quickly build, deliver and scale applications on AWS while adhering to organization-specific best practices. Developers can automate development tasks and innovate faster with generative AI capabilities, and spend less time setting up project tools, managing CI/CD pipelines, provisioning and configuring various development environments […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Shahzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by screye in "Meta cancels high-end mixed reality headset after Apple Vision Pro struggles"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332212</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332212"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T19:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A counter point on premium VR headsets. They are teleportation devices.
I've used every popular VR device, but one Vision Pro experience stood out - 'The Haleakala environment'[1]
It was literally like being transported there. I know because I had been in that exact spot a few years before. I have a rich visual memory which served as reference, and no exaggeration, it felt like was there. I was immediately in tears. It was profound.
The Vision pro's lack of a killer app because development is unintuitive, userbase is small, the UX is alien and the hardware costs of constructing these experience is still rather high. Give it a few years. The hardware is already there. This isn't a solution in search of a problem. This is PalmOS, a solution that is too early to the market.
I have family with disabilities. Being able to teleport my loved ones to places they could never go themselves is worth the $3000. If I could record my most profound memories with 'VR recorder', I would. My parent missed my graduation because of being continents away. You think they wouldn't want to be teleported to it ? Wedding photographers cost $4000+, so we can relive those memories through shoddy snapshots. Why not be teleported back to the most beautiful day ?
Don't knock it till you try it.
[1] https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wK63OSmF1FM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>screye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0cf8612b2e1e in "Microsoft formally deprecates the Windows Control Panel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332053</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332053"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T19:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t enjoy the modern white space heavy configuration to be split almost multiple pages? Win10, I have to scroll to see the entire sound options on a single non-exhaustive page given the comically low information density.
The new pages seem designed by someone who only knew how to build a vertical layout and just stacked all controls without a care for the user. I am also amused how the modern window takes a good second plus to paint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0cf8612b2e1e</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TulliusCicero in "Microsoft formally deprecates the Windows Control Panel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332019</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41332019"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T19:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But... don't the control panel windows have more functionality (and usability) in practice?
I still go to "Sounds" even on Windows 10/11 because it's easier to read and seems to have more functionality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TulliusCicero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How empirical is ’empirical’ macroeconomics?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45572</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/23/how-empirical-is-empirical-macroeconomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T18:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll At a first glance, DSGE models seem to imply total ignorance because representative agents (or representative groups of agents with limited heterogeneity) featuring objective utility functions populate the literature. At a second glance, however, it becomes obvious that “methodological individualism” prevails and even dominates. To understand this dominance one only has to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Blogkeeping and CSS Help Wanted]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-blogkeeping-and-css-help-wanted/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-blogkeeping-and-css-help-wanted/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are random days when I look at my blog and am tempted to scrap it all. It’s not because I hate it, or am unhappy with it, but mostly because I have this need and want to start all over again; a new slate if you will.
I start thinking: does this tiny corner of the internet I’ve created reflect who I am? Sometimes I’m OK with my answer, and then there are days when I’m not.
I’m not super happy with my dark mode color palette. I want to make changes to it but I don’t have a clue on what I want yet. I wish I can keep my theme on light mode, but I also don’t want to burn peoples retinas. The dark mode stays. Pending updates later.
Robert recently created a Bear theme, Bearming. This inspired me to make tiny changes to my page until I can figure out what I want.
Changed my blockquote to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CliffStoll in "Cautionary tale on using Chase bank for indie business"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41330893</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41330893"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar experience: Citibank Retirement.
I had about $80,000 in IRA/CD's. I'd created & contributed to them over a period of 35 years.
Last year, it's time to retire, and Citibank won't give me half the money.  It seems that some CD's are for "Cliff Stoll" and some for "Clifford Stoll".
Citibank Retirement demanded a "Marriage Certificate, Divorce Decree, or Court Order" to demonstrate that "Cliff Stoll" is the same person as "Clifford Stoll".
Took more than 8 months, dozens of emails, five visits to Citibank offices, and a letter to the Citibank president, to shake loose money that I'd deposited across three decades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CliffStoll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How PyTorch powers AI training and inference]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21568</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/23/ml-applications/pytorch-ai-training-inference/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T16:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about new PyTorch advancements for LLMs and how PyTorch is enhancing every aspect of the LLM lifecycle. In this talk from AI Infra @ Scale 2024, software engineers Wanchao Liang and Evan Smothers are joined by Meta research scientist Kimish Patel to discuss our newest features and tools that enable large-scale training, memory efficient [...]
Read More...
The post How PyTorch powers AI training and inference appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On waking up to write every morning]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/on-waking-up-to-write-every-morning/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/on-waking-up-to-write-every-morning/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I want to write about why I do this—why I wake up early and take the trouble to get up, go upstairs, and make some coffee. I’ve been wondering about this these past few days. Why make myself go through it? Why not just stay in bed and sleep an extra hour? Such a nice, soft, warm bed.
Every day I tell myself the same thing: “You’ll feel much better if you do!” And it’s true! I don’t know of any tonic that’s as good for my mood, energy, and mental health as a solid hour of writing in the morning before life starts. It feels like a luxury, really, having the time to do this, and I’m grateful. It’s just me, the sunrise, my dog sitting next to me, and the sound of the pen as it scratches meaning on paper, echoing in the silent dining room.
I’ve been writing this way for a bit over a year…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Internet and security trends during the 2024 U.S. Democratic National Convention]]></title>
        <id>1tSorsvJdfnMLtfjL0Jw1f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/internet-security-trends-2024-us-democratic-convention"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T14:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This analysis highlights the 2024 Democratic National Convention’s impact on Internet traffic and security, with spikes in interest for sites related to Kamala Harris and the Democrats, as well as news sites, plus pre-convention attacks on political organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Practices for working with Pull Requests in Amazon CodeCatalyst]]></title>
        <id>9d5fa8083ea0a2adaa25b3e468f4416b7ccfbddc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-for-working-with-pull-requests-in-amazon-codecatalyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to the Well-Architected DevOps Guidance, “A peer review process for code changes is a strategy for ensuring code quality and shared responsibility. To support separation of duties in a DevOps environment, every change should be reviewed and approved by at least one other person before merging.” Development teams often implement the peer review process […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fahim Sajjad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessing Amazon Q Developer using Microsoft Entra ID and VS Code to accelerate development]]></title>
        <id>9d66aeba842bce1fe217e4d75736dab43a40f72c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accessing-amazon-q-developer-using-microsoft-entra-id-and-vs-code-to-accelerate-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview In this blog post, I’ll explain how to use a Microsoft Entra ID and Visual Studio Code editor to access Amazon Q developer service and speed up your development. Additionally, I’ll explain how to minimize the time spent on repetitive tasks and quickly integrate users from external identity sources so they can immediately use […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mangesh Budkule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How A/B Testing and Multi-Model Hosting Accelerate Generative AI Feature Development in Amazon Q]]></title>
        <id>89662c44e5b3e2a8f5b40f7decc5c325c781017d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-a-b-testing-and-multi-model-hosting-accelerate-generative-ai-feature-development-in-amazon-q/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T12:02:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In the rapidly evolving landscape of Generative AI, the ability to deploy and iterate on features quickly and reliably is paramount. We, the Amazon Q Developer service team, relied on several offline and online testing methods, such as evaluating models on datasets, to gauge improvements. Once positive results are observed, features were rolled out […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Srinivas Somarouthu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luke Roberts: &ldquo;Counter-Music&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/counter-music</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/counter-music"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amelia Rosselli’s ‘Sleep’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apsara Conference 2024 Is Here]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/91c1ad508b6e</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/apsara-conference-2024-is-here-91c1ad508b6e?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T10:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apsara Conference 2024 of Alibaba Cloud will be held in Hangzhou, China from September 19th to 21st, 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liao - The Equality Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-the-equality-society-a-preliminary-archival-reconstruction-of-the-chinese-american-anarchi?v=1724403295</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-the-equality-society-a-preliminary-archival-reconstruction-of-the-chinese-american-anarchi?v=1724403295"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T08:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Liao
Title: The Equality Society
Subtitle: A Preliminary Archival Reconstruction of The Chinese American Anarchist Movement
Date: 8/20
Source: https://www.thecommoner.org.uk/the-equality-society-a-preliminary-archival-reconstruction-of-the-chinese-american-anarchist-movement/

 “Anarchism is still the most beautiful ideal, and I think someday it will come,” wrote Lau Chung-Si (Ray Jones) from a small apartment in San Francisco. At the time he put these words to paper in 1974, he was a relic of another time. Jones was a Chinese man who, in 1909, immigrated to the United States and quickly became enamoured with the ideas of anarchism. He was involved in a collective of Chinese American anarchists in San Francisco named Pingsheh (Equality Society). He also attended meetings held by ot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.31: kubeadm v1beta4]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/23/kubernetes-1-31-kubeadm-v1beta4/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/23/kubernetes-1-31-kubeadm-v1beta4/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the Kubernetes v1.31 release, kubeadm is
adopting a new (v1beta4) version of
its configuration file format. Configuration in the previous v1beta3 format is now formally
deprecated, which means it's supported but you should migrate to v1beta4 and stop using
the deprecated format.
Support for v1beta3 configuration will be removed after a minimum of 3 Kubernetes minor releases.
In this article, I'll walk you through key changes;
I'll explain about the kubeadm v1beta4 configuration format,
and how to migrate from v1beta3 to v1beta4.
You can read the reference for the v1beta4 configuration format:
kubeadm Configuration (v1beta4).
A list of changes since v1beta3
This version improves on the v1beta3
format by fixing some minor issues and adding a few new fields.
To put it simply,
Two n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading: good for your mental and overall health?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8339</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/reading-good-mental-overall-health/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T21:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ceridwen Dovey, writing for the New Yorker, in 2015: For all avid readers who have been self-medicating with great books their entire lives, it comes as no surprise that reading books can be good for your mental health and your relationships with others, but exactly why and how is now becoming clearer, thanks to new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use AWS CloudFormation Git sync to configure resources in customer accounts]]></title>
        <id>aebf09b75aba8adfcdae97ec0df726ceec9f277b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-aws-cloudformation-git-sync-to-configure-resources-in-customer-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T19:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS partners often have a requirement to create resources, such as cross-account roles, in their customers’ accounts. A good choice for consistently provisioning these resources is AWS CloudFormation, an Infrastructure as Code (IaC) service that allows you to specify your architecture in a template file written in JSON or YAML. CloudFormation also makes it easy […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Z. Beard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Wesfarmers Health implemented upstream event buffering using Amazon SQS FIFO]]></title>
        <id>b921c566b9aecfbcceb2043dd006b2cf6490b9ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-wesfarmers-health-implemented-upstream-event-buffering-using-amazon-sqs-fifo/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T17:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers of all sizes and industries use Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) applications to host their workloads. Most SaaS solutions take care of maintenance and upgrades of the application for you, and get you up and running in a relatively short timeframe. Why spend time, money, and your precious resources to build and maintain applications when this could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robbie Cooray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the hardware and co-design of MTIA]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21571</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/22/ml-applications/meta-mtia-hardware-co-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this talk from AI Infra @ Scale 2024, Joel Colburn, a software engineer at Meta, technical lead Junqiang Lan, and software engineer Jack Montgomery discuss the second generation of MTIA, Meta’s in-house training and inference accelerator. They cover the co-design process behind building the second generation of Meta’s first-ever custom silicon for AI workloads, [...]
Read More...
The post Inside the hardware and co-design of MTIA appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Concept of Home]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-concept-of-home/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-concept-of-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other day I was thinking about the concept of home. What does home really mean? When you think of home, what is the first thing you think of? They say that home is where the heart is, and I wholeheartedly agree. A home doesn’t have to be a place, but if you had to put a place to it, where would you consider home to be?
My cousins, back in my birth country, will ask: “When are you coming home?” It always stops me in my tracks. I haven’t lived there for 32 years. I left when I was relatively young, and only visit every few years for a short period of time. Although I try to hold on to my culture, my identity closely tied to it, the country itself is more of a distant past than a present reality. And yet, to them, it is still my home.
Then there are my friends from where I spent most of m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go wild: Wildcard support in Rules and a new open-source wildcard crate]]></title>
        <id>1NVmSxeyTXrlaivG80ZNzS</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/wildcard-rules"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re excited to announce wildcard support across our Ruleset Engine-based products and our open-source wildcard crate in Rust. Configuring rules has never been easier, with powerful pattern matching enabling simple and flexible URL redirects and beyond for users on all plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Cano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cochrane on PRICE-GOUGING]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45567</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/22/cochrane-on-price-gouging/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T12:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Price-gouging is now a topic in politics.  Kamala Harris has put it there.  Naturally there has been the predictable outcry of opposition coupled with and equally predictable sneer of disapproval: how could she say something so uneducated?  Has she no grasp of Econ.101?  Oh the illiteracy! Perhaps even more predictable is that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Am Not Proud]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/i-am-not-proud/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/i-am-not-proud/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My definition of pride is caring about what other people think of me and for the most part I don't. That's a bold statement and I don't mean for it to be. I definitely care about how people treat me and that's often tied into their opinion so I'm not being an absolutist. Some things that a lot of people find important are of little interest to me, cars for example. I drive a 2005 Toyota Camry with 230K miles on it that is a hand me down from my mother. I'm almost 60. I also don't try to appear neutral on controversial topics. My wife has to shush me around Republicans because I have a tendency to tell her the latest asshole thing they've done at a volume level loud enough to be heard by people who may disagree with me. I'll lower my voice so as not to embarrass Wonder Woman, but I really d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now open — AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia) Region]]></title>
        <id>c7447db6c34719e72bdc50b8f0ffb80c00a60878</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-malaysia-region/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T01:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia) Region bolsters cloud innovation, empowering local businesses and government initiatives while aligning with Malaysia's sustainability goals through Amazon's renewable energy commitment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>