<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-03T06:31:13.249Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-03T06:31:13.249Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329902</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/329902/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T20:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329898</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/329898/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T20:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276095</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics  Charts Friday: New RCP charts (bad news for Trump); many Covid updates (a little good news); new study on Covid and traffic safety; Kamala's VP search; aphantasia and prosopometamorphopsia. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rahimnathwani in "The Marshmallow Test does not reliably predict adult functioning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140863"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T17:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The findings of the original study were called into question by a larger 2018 study[0]. The original study had 90 students. Some folks did a study with 900 people. They found the same correlation that the original study did. But when they controlled for household income, they found most of the correlation disappeared.
The obvious conclusion is that household income is a predictor of both:
- inability to delay gratification, and
- higher academic achievement
This makes sense when you consider that someone growing up in a poor household may have both:
- less reliable/continuous/predictable access to material things, meaning they would rationally seize immediate opportunities rather than taking the risk of a larger future opportunity, and
- less academic support
Now, this new study (OP) goes even further, finding that the correlation itself is weak.
[0] Watts, T. W., Duncan, G. J., & Quan, H. (2018). Revisiting the Marshmallow Test: A Conceptual Replication Investigating Links Between Early Delay of Gratification and Later Outcomes. Psychological Science, 29(7), 1159-1177. https://doi.org/10.1177/0956797618761661]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rahimnathwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelseyfrog in "The upstream cause of the youth mental health crisis is the loss of community"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140196</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140196"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, yes, we've doubled down on mediating social interactions through economic relationships. Most of the interactions adults have in their lives are with or in the framing of economic relations. Homes, are being invaded with tablets and mobile devices which bring along with them framing interactions as economic relations through ad and consumer frames. Workplaces are inherently settings of economic relations, and third places outside of the consumer setting are becoming extinct because they are non-monetizable.
This last category, non-consumer third places are formerly the domain of kid-friendly community-building activities. When we talk about creating more of these and the response is, "they aren't economically viable," it's exactly the kind of economic calculus framing that I'm talking about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelseyfrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm JC... Probably?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/im-jc-probably/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/im-jc-probably/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T15:10:10.164Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was supposed to do an Intro Post yesterday, but I’ve never been good at it so I delayed it until I could figure out what to say. Here we are a day later, and I still don’t quite have the words for it. I always fall back to a post I’ve written of not wanting to talk about myself as an explanation. Either way, I’ve come to realize that I never did do a proper introduction on this blog, outside of my About me page. In my defense, I think what I have written on there is enough to kind of get a gist for who I am.
But since I’m writing a post anyways, I figured I’d say something else that doesn’t completely repeat everything written on there.
Online, I typically go by JC(Probably), but most people in real life call me Jedda. You can tell a lot about how people know me, and from what moment in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eyepopping Factory Construction Boom in the US Reaches New Highs Amid Big Corporate & Strategic Rethink]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276088</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/eyepopping-factory-construction-boom-in-the-us-reaches-new-highs-amid-big-corporate-strategic-rethink.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T14:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New factory building shows that reshoring plans are translating into action. But how many will produce successful operations?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on social media addiction]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/on-social-media-addiction/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/on-social-media-addiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being in my early 20s, there should be no surprise that I have grown up with and have extensively used social media platforms to socialise, communicate, and share ideas with other people. It is no secret that these platforms can and have caused harm to their user's mental health (me included!), but even knowing this I've sat on my hands for years before actually taking action to remedy this situation.
However, as a lot of you know, it's not easy to just drop social media cold turkey. In my opinion, I think there are a few main reasons why this is the case, and I will attempt to argue against each one in this post.
1. Social media is addictive
Multi-million dollar companies spend huge amounts of capital and time to create algorithms where their sole purpose is to make you spend more time on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276072</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T10:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our dynamic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel: Armageddon?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276070</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/israel-armageddon.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T10:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel, as John Mearshimer put in in a new post, has gotten itself in deep kimchee. Who else will it drag into its desperate mess?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could Russia Become First G-20 Economy to Launch a Full-Fledged Central Bank Digital Currency?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276005</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/could-russia-become-first-g-20-economy-to-launch-a-full-fledged-central-bank-digital-currency.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Big moves are afoot on the digital ruble.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Omar Radi free !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Omar-Radi-free</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Omar-Radi-free"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T08:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Press release. 
Press releases

/ 
Social movements, 
Morocco]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ninety Pre-Election Days in Two Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276064</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/ninety-pre-election-days-in-two-charts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T07:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Election statistical models performed poorly in the US this year.  That's to be expected when faced with tail risk events.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Mountaineer’s Prayer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329531</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/a-mountaineers-prayer/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T06:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am tired of talking about J.D. Vance. And I’m not one for introspection (just ask my husband). But as a daughter of Appalachia and a professor of anthropology at a public university, J.D. Vance’s claim to represent Appalachia and his threats to attack our nation’s universities and their professors, who he’s labeled “the enemy,” are personal for me. Echoing other Appalachia-raised writers who have recently weighed in, I say to J.D. Vance: you are a hillbilly phony (Caleb Miller). You don’t represent us (Neema Avashia). And you can keep your “elegy” (Ivy Brashear) because hillbillies don’t need one (Meredith McCarroll). Your Hillbilly Elegy is a political platform disguised as a memoir, and I call bullshit. More
The post A Mountaineer’s Prayer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah D. Phillips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I’ll Fucking Shoot You in the Face”: the Police Murder of Sonya Massey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329520</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/ill-fucking-shoot-you-in-the-face-the-police-murder-of-sonya-massey/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T06:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deputy Sean Grayson didn’t turn on his body camera until after he’d shot Sonya Massey three times. This is probably why he thought he could get away with saying he killed Massey in self-defense, as she was charging toward him with a pot of boiling water. What Grayson didn’t realize is that his partner’s body cam recorded the entire fatal encounter, showing that the diminutive, unarmed Massey was hiding from the Springfield deputy, when Grayson walked around the kitchen counter, shot her in the face and left her to bleed out. Then he lied about it…lies that were caught on tape and exposed as lies on tape. More
The post “I’ll Fucking Shoot You in the Face”: the Police Murder of Sonya Massey appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blank Checks for War: Congressional Abdication from Tonkin to Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329560</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/blank-checks-for-war-congressional-abdication-from-tonkin-to-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the U.S.- backed carnage in Gaza continuing and the threat of growing violence looming throughout the region (in Lebanon, Iran, and who knows where else), we need to think more deeply than ever about how the American people have historically been excluded from foreign policy decision-making. An upcoming anniversary should remind us of what sent us down this undemocratic path. More
The post Blank Checks for War: Congressional Abdication from Tonkin to Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian G. Appy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Methane Emissions “Fastest in Decades”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329763</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/methane-emissions-fastest-in-decades/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study shows methane (CH4) emissions behaving like a sprinter on speed, setting decadal records. This is bad news. It’s 80-times more powerful than CO2 at trapping heat. “Global emissions of methane, a powerful planet-heating gas, are ‘rising rapidly’ at the fastest rate in decades, requiring immediate action to help avert a dangerous escalation  More
The post Methane Emissions “Fastest in Decades” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Folly of Atomic Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329774</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/the-folly-of-atomic-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This past June, a couple of my sisters and I drove from California to Minnesota. One of the states we traveled through was Idaho. We gassed up in a town called Atomic City, which advertised itself as the first city in the United States to have nuclear-powered electricity. This town is inside what grounds of  More
The post The Folly of Atomic Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuela: An Attempted Coup By Any Other Name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329794</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/venezuela-an-attempted-coup-by-any-other-name/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We will coup whoever we want! Deal with it.” Elon Musk, 25 July 2020, Twitter Once again, as in 2002, Venezuela has been the victim of a combined media and diplomatic coup attempt, but this time with the added element of organized crime and a cyber-attack. Millions of eligible voters cast their electronic ballots before  More
The post Venezuela: An Attempted Coup By Any Other Name appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Paez Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living With Heat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329561</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/living-with-heat/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The earth gets hotter, as rich nations continue their coal, oil and gas burning spree, while those who urge a course correction get…thrown into prison. The latest casualty of a judiciary dedicated to preserving ecocidal plutocracy is Extinction Rebellion’s Roger Hallam, sentenced to five years in jail in the U.K. for his efforts to stop the corporate insanity defiling the planet. You may think “defiling” is a strong word. But with a heat index of 144 degrees Fahrenheit in Dubai July 16, multiple heat domes baking enormous swaths of the globe this month at record-smashing temperatures for record-smashing lengths of time, and the four hottest days IN A ROW ever recorded in July, you might want to thank Hallam for attempting to arrest this calamity. More
The post Living With Heat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’s Stairway to Heaven]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329751</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/harriss-stairway-to-heaven/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forgive me if I am not among those measuring the drapes in the Oval Office so that come January 20, 2025, Kamala Harris can move seamlessly into the White House. I am sure that I am in a minority. Since President Joe Biden’s renunciation on July 21, the vice president has been all things to  More
The post Harris’s Stairway to Heaven appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Sista Souljahs the NABJ]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329838</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/trump-sista-souljahs-the-nabj/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:57:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Trump is arguably the first bona fide media-created presidential nominee. Although he subsequently tapped a political nerve, journalists fueled his launch.” This was the conclusion of The Shorenstein Center on Media, Politics and Public Policy, a Harvard Kennedy School research center that wrote about the 2016 contest between Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton. The media  More
The post Trump Sista Souljahs the NABJ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishmael Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza, India, Bhagat Singh, and the Right to Violently Rebel Against Imperial Repression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329589</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/gaza-india-bhagat-singh-and-the-right-to-violently-rebel-against-imperial-repression/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza Israel is waging a genocidal war against the people of Gaza, murdering in excess of 40,000 persons, with more victims almost certainly dead under the rubble left by relentless bombing. The British medical journal The Lancet suggest that if indirect deaths—from starvation, diseases, and the like—are taken into account, up to 186,000 deaths can  More
The post Gaza, India, Bhagat Singh, and the Right to Violently Rebel Against Imperial Repression appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Yates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Left Can Only Win If There is a Left]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329749</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/the-left-can-only-win-if-there-is-a-left/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the main obstacles to organizing oppositional political movements and parties? There are many. Deeply-seated racism, sexism, and imperialism keep us divided and in line. Corporate power dominates our political system. Leadership against such a system must both oppose the existing order and envision an alternative to it. Yet, many who might help do  More
The post The Left Can Only Win If There is a Left appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Moser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Harris Has Evolved on Marijuana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329815</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/how-harris-has-evolved-on-marijuana/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most Americans, Vice President Kamala Harris has evolved on marijuana. In 2010, when she was San Francisco’s district attorney, Harris urged voters to reject a proposed ballot initiative to legalize the adult-use marijuana market. At the time, Harris’ position aligned with that of most California voters, 54 percent of whom ultimately decided against the measure. But  More
The post How Harris Has Evolved on Marijuana appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Armentano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revenge of the Sovereignistas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329772</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/revenge-of-the-sovereignistas/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They were all buddy-buddy for the cameras, going for a joy ride in a deluxe limo and toasting each other at a gala dinner. In June, North Korean leader Kim Jong-un was determined to welcome Russian President Vladimir Putin in grand style on his first visit to Pyongyang in 24 years. A red carpet, flowers, and champagne: it  More
The post Revenge of the Sovereignistas appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Lesson from the French Popular Front for Left Presidential Candidates in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329797</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/a-lesson-from-the-french-popular-front-for-left-presidential-candidates-in-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My perspective is informed by this strategic analysis from Jerry Harris, the scholar of transnational capital: “The neo-fascist bloc seeks stability through repression, and creating a mass base through religious fundamentalism, patriarchy, and white supremacy. The neo-Keynesian bloc seeks stability and renewed political legitimacy through neo-Keynesian reformism, and economic expansion through the green modernization of  More
The post A Lesson from the French Popular Front for Left Presidential Candidates in the US appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schwartzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Our Descendants Look Back on This Chapter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329812</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/when-our-descendants-look-back-on-this-chapter/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s almost always simple to look back in history with a clear eye and note misdeeds and murder. Genocides pop out as self-evident, colonialism screams loudly, but for some reason, while in the throes of it all, many individuals, especially those who consider themselves conservative and level-headed, completely miss what is occurring right under their  More
The post When Our Descendants Look Back on This Chapter appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If Only the Democrats Had a Project 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329810</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/if-only-the-democrats-had-a-project-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life, as John Fitzgerald Kennedy once mused, is unfair. And since the moment he horrifically oversold that point with splattered skull fragments on a limousine trunk, life seems to grow more unfair with every passing presidency. As someone who has spent two score and seven years paying close attention to the dishonest ways elected officials  More
The post If Only the Democrats Had a Project 2025 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assange, CIA Surveillance and Spain’s Audencia Nacional]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329808</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/assange-cia-surveillance-and-spains-audencia-nacional/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sordid story on the CIA-backed operation against the WikiLeaks publisher Julian Assange during his time cramped in London’s Ecuadorian Embassy continues to froth and thicken. US officials have persisted in their reticent attitude, refusing to cooperate with Spain’s national high court, the Audiencia Nacional, regarding its investigation into the Agency’s espionage operations against the  More
The post Assange, CIA Surveillance and Spain’s Audencia Nacional appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right-Wing Press Fears Reform Could Restrain Republican Supreme Court]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329814</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/right-wing-press-fears-reform-could-restrain-republican-supreme-court/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Murdoch press should be happy that there won’t be another Biden presidency. Instead, outlets like the Wall Street Journal and the New York Post are furious at the outgoing president’s demand for Supreme Court reforms. President Joe Biden announced a push to reform the Supreme Court in light of mounting criticism that the justices  More
The post Right-Wing Press Fears Reform Could Restrain Republican Supreme Court appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ari Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Smearing of Cori Bush for Being Truthful About the Gaza War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329803</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/the-smearing-of-cori-bush-for-being-truthful-about-the-gaza-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soon after the Gaza war began 10 months ago, a prominent newspaper columnist denounced Congresswoman Cori Bush under a headline declaring that “anti-Israel comments make her unfit for reelection.” The piece appeared in the newspaper with the second-largest readership in Missouri, the Kansas City Star. Multimillion-dollar attacks on Bush followed. Bush’s opponent, county prosecutor Wesley Bell,  More
The post The Smearing of Cori Bush for Being Truthful About the Gaza War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Kamala Harris be a Truly Transformed Candidate and President?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329750</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/can-kamala-harris-be-a-truly-transformed-candidate-and-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The invitation to Benjamin Netanyahu to address Congress for the fourth time is an irremovable stain on the United States as is the Biden/Bibi relationship. No matter what pressure his biggest benefactor puts on him, the Israeli Prime Minister will not change. The question today is whether or not Kamala Harris will change now that  More
The post Can Kamala Harris be a Truly Transformed Candidate and President? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Tax Code Rewards Corporate Price Gouging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329820</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/our-tax-code-rewards-corporate-price-gouging/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next year, we’ll have to make one of the most important decisions about the future of our economy. Will we hand more power and wealth to big corporations and the rich — or invest in a healthy and resilient economy that works for all of us? In 2017, Republican lawmakers passed tax loopholes and cuts  More
The post Our Tax Code Rewards Corporate Price Gouging appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakeen Mabud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collective Care and Sustaining Social Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329790</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/collective-care-and-sustaining-social-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview with Helia Rasti and Ashanti Alston This interview is with social movement veterans who have sacrificed much, and learned a great deal, trying to change the world. Each in their own way have gained valuable insights into the personal, interpersonal, and structural dynamics at play when confronting established power and have essential lessons  More
The post Collective Care and Sustaining Social Change appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Messersmith-Glavin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sal Rosselli: A Tribute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329583</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/sal-rosselli-a-tribute/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I get a kick watching Sal Rosselli at Labor Notes, the huge biannual rank- and- file workers’ gathering in Chicago, sponsored by the magazine of the same name. He’s always there meeting, talking, on a panel, on the move, working, full of energy, out of the limelight, but known by many, health care workers especially.  More
The post Sal Rosselli: A Tribute appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cal Winslow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“You Stink” Say Desperate Soap Product Makers in New Ads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329587</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/you-stink-say-desperate-soap-product-makers-in-new-ads/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are online or on TV and radio you can’t miss it: personal care corporations telling you that you stink. Just trying to sell products. Even if you are using deodorant on “those places,” your body smells all over say a disturbing number of ads. And, if you smell all over, you are probably  More
The post “You Stink” Say Desperate Soap Product Makers in New Ads appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martha Rosenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olympian Water Music]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329869</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/olympian-water-music/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It just kept rolling along, painting always unpredictable, always alluring patterns on its surface, caressing the embankment, gracefully sliding through the shadows under bridges, not giving a French fig about the humongous fascist-inspired spectacle rampaging in, on, and around it. In its noble nonchalance, the Seine stole the show. As the rain bucketed down, the  More
The post Olympian Water Music appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Firefighters Are Fighting For a Just Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329832</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/chicago-firefighters-are-fighting-for-a-just-contract/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the past two years, four Chicago Firefighters have died on the job, including Jermaine Pelt, an eighteen-year veteran, whose death was ruled a homicide. 2023 alone was, according to the Illinois Fire Institute, the deadliest year for Chicago Firefighters since 1998. So far, 2024 hasn’t seen any deaths on the job, but that should not conceal  More
The post Chicago Firefighters Are Fighting For a Just Contract appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grizzly Bear Killed Over Bait in Idaho, Legal Action Initiated]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329781</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/grizzly-bear-killed-over-bait-in-idaho-legal-action-initiated/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 18, the same day the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals thought it was too far-fetched that a grizzly bear could be killed over a black bear bait station, news broke that a hunter had just killed a threatened grizzly bear at a bait station on national forest land near the Lower St. Joe River  More
The post Grizzly Bear Killed Over Bait in Idaho, Legal Action Initiated appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comstock’s Revenge: Project 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329564</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/comstocks-revenge-project-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:46:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Project 2025” is the ultra-conservative Heritage Society’s blueprint for what a Republican presidential administration, a Trump presidency, could look like.  Its goal is to turn the historic clock back and return the U.S. to the good old days of the Comstock era. The social and economic changes that followed the Civil War were traumatic and  More
The post Comstock’s Revenge: Project 2025 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nsámbu Za Suékama - Deixis and the Queer/Trans Struggle]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nsambu-za-suekama-deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminis?v=1722571298</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nsambu-za-suekama-deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminis?v=1722571298"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T04:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nsámbu Za Suékama
Title: Deixis and the Queer/Trans Struggle
Subtitle: A Missive from a Dialectical Transfeminist
Date: May 13, 2024
Notes: Author’s note: a straight-through read would make 200+ minutes. Please take your time with such a hefty work. Breaks are encouraged. If you are Black, trans/queer, and operating in good faith, feel free to highlight passages you would like to learn more about. Medium allows authors to interact with their readers. I might be able to provide clarification if I have spoons.
Source: <medium.com/@riptide.1997/deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminist-4dae1e366f07>

“Deah’s plenty cunjuh in dis neighbuhhood. Deah wuz a man and his wife libed yuh. Duh man couldn git wuk an he went away. Attuh he lef, duh wife wuz t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Imprisoned Anarchists - Concerning the anti-judicial position]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/some-imprisoned-anarchists-concerning-the-anti-judicial-position?v=1722570985</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/some-imprisoned-anarchists-concerning-the-anti-judicial-position?v=1722570985"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Some Imprisoned Anarchists
Title: Concerning the anti-judicial position
Date: October 28, 2014
Source: Greece – Dialogue between Kontra newspaper and imprisoned anarchist comrades concerning the stance of the comrades in the terror-trials. <web.archive.org/web/20160409234906/http://actforfree.nostate.net/?p=18034>. Retrieved on 19/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 BELOW ARE THE TRANSLATIONS OF A SERIES OF TEXTS THAT WERE WRITTEN BY ANARCHIST COMRADES AFTER THE CRITICISM OF LEFTIST NEWSPAPER “KONTRA” ABOUT THE ANTI-JUDICIAL POSITION THAT SOME OF THEM HOLD TOWARDS THE TERROR COURT IN KORIDALLOS PRISON 
 On 28/7/14, the report of “KONTRA” newspaper (which also goes online through www.eksegersi.gr) on the ongoing terror-trial of the Pefki case (which involves imprisoned anarchist comrad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Langer - Enough! Dance!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/julian-langer-enough-dance?v=1722568619</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/julian-langer-enough-dance?v=1722568619"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Julian Langer
Title: Enough! Dance!
Date: 18/7/24
Source: https://ecorevoltblog.wordpress.com/2024/07/18/enough-dance/

1
 The ghost of Turgenev crying 
 “Enough!” 
 Is in my ears 
 My activities are glorious 
 While several seasons 
 Fighting disease 
 Living closely with personal existential uncertainty 
 My body is marked 
 There is a thin line 
 Across my left eyelid 
 A scar from where it was removed 
 I am tired of this 
 There is a book 
 Being written 
 The first section poems like this 
 I wonder if it’s my last 
 I don’t know 
2
 All things are possible 
 So say Shestov and Fondane 
 Yes, all things are possible 
 Including the impossibility 
 Of my writing another book after this 
 Yes, all things are possible 
 What is most possible though 
 For all life 
 It seems is i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignatius - Fist Full of Concrete]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-fist-full-of-concrete-some-thoughts-towards-insurrection?v=1722568569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-fist-full-of-concrete-some-thoughts-towards-insurrection?v=1722568569"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignatius
Title: Fist Full of Concrete
Subtitle: Some Thoughts Towards Insurrection
Date: 2023
Notes: Published by Long Leaf Distro 2023 
 Longleaf_distro@protonmail.com 
 Reproduce to your heart’s content.
Source: Retrieved on 4 July 2023 from ia800301.us.archive.org/4/items/zines-anarchism/Fist_Full_of_Concrete-screen.pdf

It Doesn’t Have to Be This Way, You Know
 There is a beauty that creeps in under the plastic blinds, covering the window, in the form of sunlight. A beauty that seems an attempt by the world outside to draw some contrast to the words I write here, and that you will read later on. That for all the expression of pain, and dissatisfaction, and desire for more, there is still beauty to be found here, bouncing around the walls of this mold infested apartment. 
 This …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Ridin’ Dirty: A Basic Reference for Freight Hopping]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping?v=1722567881</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping?v=1722567881"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Ridin’ Dirty: A Basic Reference for Freight Hopping
Date: 07/20/2024
Source: https://warzonedistro.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/20/ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping/

A Few Words From the Distro
 Riding freight is a core skill for anti-work, anti-school, individualist anarchists, lifestylists, nomads, oogles, crust punk dirty kids, and travelers. 
 Hate your job? Quit and go train hopping! 
 Sick of school? Drop out and go train hopping! 
 Feeling suicidal with no fun and excitement in your life? 
 Try something new, open a new chapter and go train hopping! 
 But train hopping is very dangerous! You SERIOUSLY could die. 
 But you could also die in a car wreck on the way to work, or die from getting shot to death by a mass shooter. 
 At the end of the da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delfina Vannuci & Richard Singer - Come Hell or High Water]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/delfina-vannuci-richard-singer-come-hell-or-high-water?v=1722566512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/delfina-vannuci-richard-singer-come-hell-or-high-water?v=1722566512"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T02:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Delfina Vannuci & Richard Singer
Title: Come Hell or High Water
Subtitle: A Handbook on Collective Process Gone Awry
Date: 2010
Notes: Originally published by AK Press. ISBN-13: 9781849350181,
Source: AK Press

PREFACE
 Welcome to the collective book on collective process! Over the course of the twenty or so years that AK Press has been publishing and distributing anarchist and radical literature, we've gotten a lot of requests for good, short overviews of topics that are of interest to the folks in our communities: anarchism, worker's rights, solidarity economics, and countless other things. We do our best to seek out books to publish or distribute that meet our readers’ needs, but it can take a while to find exactly the right author or book. One of the most common requests we get…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - The Problem Of Buddhist Socialism in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-the-problem-of-buddhist-socialism-in-japan?v=1722564274</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-the-problem-of-buddhist-socialism-in-japan?v=1722564274"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T02:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: The Problem Of Buddhist Socialism in Japan
Date: 1970
Source: Retrieved on 7/31/24 from https://noselvesnomasters.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ichikawa-hakugens.pdf

(1)
 The formation of Buddhist socialism in Japan made a belated start and its influence was little compared with that of Christian socialism in Europe, or even with the revolutionary movement (1851-1864) which occurred in the period of “idle peace” started by Hong Xiuquan (洪秀全) in China. The reason for the belated start seems to be indirectly concerned with national isolationism and the slow development of capitalism in Japan. The Communist Manifesto was published 20 years before the Meiji Restoration and the first volume of Das Kapital was issued a year before the Meiji Restoration. Directly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Hamas, anarchists in the West and Palestine solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-author-from-stoking-the-embers-collective-hamas-anarchists-in-the-west-and-palestine?v=1722563828</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-author-from-stoking-the-embers-collective-hamas-anarchists-in-the-west-and-palestine?v=1722563828"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Hamas, anarchists in the West and Palestine solidarity
Subtitle: An analysis
Date: July 15th 2024
Notes: Anonymous author from Stoking the Embers Collective
Source: Retrieved on August 1, 2024 from https://libcom.org/article/hamas-anarchists-west-and-palestine-solidarity-analysis

 In the West, it is practically impossible to speak publicly about Hamas in any way that isn't an outright and total condemnation. Behind such remarkable limitation of the spectrum of public debate lies the idea that Hamas represents an "evil" so deep that it lacks any complexity. In parliaments, universities and newspapers, Hamas is never discussed, simply because -- it is assumed -- there is nothing to discuss. The idea that Hamas is simply a "terrorist" group that wants nothing but dea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer just reached a $260 million dollar milestone]]></title>
        <id>f5ea5adef0b32f32d4d01cabbf34df85e6d89efd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-just-reached-a-260-million-dollar-milestone/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T23:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help them be more productive, developers all over the world are turning to generative AI-powered assistants like Amazon Q Developer, the most capable assistant for accelerating software development. While Amazon Q Developer is great at providing code suggestions, writing new code is one of many things developers have to do on a day-to-day basis. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aytul Arisoy Cholkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Māori Data Lens for the Well-Architected Framework]]></title>
        <id>cdca0a814b524dedcad257755ec5f53c08efc5b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/introducing-the-maori-data-lens-for-the-well-architected-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Aotearoa New Zealand, we have been listening and learning to better understand Māori aspirations when using cloud technology. We have been learning from Māori customers, partners, and advisors who have helped us on this journey. A common theme was how to safeguard Māori data in a digital world. Together with a group of Māori […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Hind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by MarkusQ in "CrowdStrike representatives issue trademark infringement notice to ClownStrike"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41134498</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41134498"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike definitely has the chops when it comes to taking sites down, I'll give them that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MarkusQ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eskibars in "Australia starts peanut allergy treatment for babies"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41133686</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41133686"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T21:13:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our son is very allergic to peanuts and less so to cashew, and sesame. We went through oral immunotherapy and it's been absolutely life changing. He used to need an epi pen in case of chance encounter, but now he eats 2 whole peanut m&ms every day to keep his dosage up. It's been difficult finding an allergist in Germany that's willing to accept this and move forward
Obviously everyone's mileage will vary, but I'm happy to see this treatment being more widely adopted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eskibars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Praiseworthy by Alexis Wright wins 2024 Miles Franklin Literary Award]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8133</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/praiseworthy-alexis-wright-wins-2024-miles-franklin-literary-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As called/guessed by yours truly, Praiseworthy, the 2023 novel by Waanyi/Gulf of Carpentaria based Australian author Alexis Wright, has won the 2024 Miles Franklin Literary Award. Praiseworthy has cleaned up on the awards circuit since publication, also winning the other major Australian literary award, the Stellar Prize. Wright also won the Miles Franklin in 2007, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tomcam in "Russ Cox is stepping down as the Go tech lead"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41133238</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41133238"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T20:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMHO Go has been one of the best-managed open source projects ever. Hats off to Google for supporting it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tomcam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday 004 - El Nido Waters]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-el-nido-waters/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/throwback-thursday-004-el-nido-waters/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T20:14:02.064Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the same trip where I took the photo of Nemo in El Nido, Philippines.

August 2014, Philippines, GoPro Hero 3
Not a huge fan of how I edited this. It's too high-def for my taste now, but this is why I like posting these throwback photos because I get to see how my post-processing preferences have changed over the years. The sky is a bit blown out as well, but that may also be due to the original photo (that I don't have access to at the moment).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ainar-g in "Russ Cox is stepping down as the Go tech lead"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41132815</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41132815"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T19:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you, rsc, for all your work.  Development in Go has become much more enjoyable in these 12 years: race detector, standardized error wrapping, modules, generics, toolchain updates, and so on.  And while there are still things to be desired (sum types, better enum/range types, immutability, and non-nilness in my personal wishlist), Go is still the most enjoyable ecosystem I've ever developed in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ainar-g</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Hundred Rabbits is a small collective exploring the failability of modern tech"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41132532</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41132532"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T19:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Site: "This website has no tracking or analytics."
Privacy Badger blocked tracking from:
    googleads.g.doubleclick.net
    static.doubleclick.net
    play.google.com
    www.google.com
    www.youtube.com

    
    

If you use anything from Google, you will be tracked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[new issue of RWER]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45508</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/01/new-issue-of-rwer-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[real-world economics review Please click here to support this journal and the WEA Issue no. 108July 2024 download whole issue The creationist foundations of Herman Daly’s steady state economyJohn Gowdy and Lisi Krall2 Data: a critical perspectiveCarlos Guerrero de Lizardi16 Enlightenment Epistemology and the Climate CrisisAsad Zaman29 Fabulous MacroeconomicsGerald Holtham33 A Tour of the Jevons […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276027</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Kamala's VP search; Trish Greenhalgh on Long Covid; Covid and class ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Blaugust]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/hello-blaugust/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/hello-blaugust/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Martin.
I'm an IT coordinator, currently living and working in Rostock, Germany.
I like good coffee, very complex and very simple music, independent radios, books, art, independent movies and small, playful and heartfelt web stuff.
I started blogging quite recently, and this is my first year participating in Blaugust.
Previously, I participated in the Junited 2024 and July Reply 2024 blogging challenges.
My goals for Blaugust 2024 are not to think too much about writing, to write as much as I can, and to improve my English writing skills.
I’m also excited to see what other participants write throughout the month.
So here we go...
📌 Side note(s): This is a blog post I've written as a part of the Blaugust 2024 blogging challenge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by drewchew in "Robot dentist performs first human procedure"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41131364</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41131364"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T17:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will robot dentists facilitate the option to lay face down for procedures so that the debris and saliva falls out instead of needing the suction tool?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>drewchew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code July 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_92</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_92"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code July 2024 Release (1.92)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Birthday Month with a side of Blaugust]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/birthday-month-with-a-side-of-blaugust/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/birthday-month-with-a-side-of-blaugust/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh hello, August.
challenge.
In July I got this wild idea to start some sort of a challenge in August to celebrate my birthday month. I didn’t know what kind of challenge I wanted to do, and was just planning on making it up as I went along. I was leaning towards some sort of casual photo challenge, but one posted here instead of my photoblog. While I was contemplating what to do, I came across Blaugust. I no longer had to make things up as I went along because someone already did it for me.
What and When?
Blaugust is an annual challenge, that happens every August, hosted by Belghast that started in 2013. From what I understand, it started out within the gaming community but has expanded to various different blogging communities throughout the years.
Who?
This year, there are ~74 people (f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A recent spate of Internet disruptions]]></title>
        <id>66ab8bd24a25d6000ae1c5d6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-recent-spate-of-internet-disruptions-july-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Radar is constantly monitoring the Internet for widespread disruptions. Here we examine several recent  noteworthy disruptions detected in the first month of Q3, including traffic anomalies observed in Bangladesh, Syria, Pakistan, and Venezuela]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wildfires Can Create Their Own Weather, Further Spreading the Flames − An Atmospheric Scientist Explains How]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276018</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/wildfires-can-create-their-own-weather-further-spreading-the-flames-%e2%88%92-an-atmospheric-scientist-explains-how.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A worked example of how human activity does not just have direct environment effects but also feedback loops, here on weather.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by NathanielBaking in "How I got my laser eye injury"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41128892</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41128892"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Safety guys always ruin the fun.  I was in the Marine Corps and every time we got to test some new piece of gear the safety officer was like "No, you can't live fire it off the flight deck of the ship" or "No, not here, that village is down wind of the dust you will kick up when it goes off." No, that has a kill distance of 6 miles, you have to fire it into a hill."  Blah, blah, blah.
So after I got out I joined the National Guard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NathanielBaking</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DannyBee in "How I got my laser eye injury"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41128339</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41128339"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T12:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I laser weld, and beyond my own PPE, interlocks (gun won't fire if it's not touching metal, etc), the most important part of the whole setup is laser safety curtains.
Because it's a 2500 watt laser, if i didn't have laser safety curtains , the relections/etc could very easily blind someone at a fairly long distance.
The NOHD (nominal ocular hazard distance) is something like 10km (2500 watt laser, 0.06mm spot size, divergence is very very small).  The actual hazard distance is shorter, but still, kinda crazy.
(as for why i have a laser welder - i got it cheap and besides the downsides above, it is very easy to weld ~anything without much skill.  A person who has never welded in their life can weld sheet metal and have it come out basically perfect in 5 minutes)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DannyBee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275999</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our pragmatic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Kamala Harris Sold Out Struggling Homeowners to Save Banks in 2012 and Then Lied About It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275793</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/how-kamala-harris-sold-out-struggling-homeowners-to-save-banks-in-2012-and-then-lied-about-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala is  under scrutiny for policy flip-flops. Even worse is her lying about the badge of shame known as the 2012 National Mortgage Settlement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naomi Hossain: &ldquo;Bloody July&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bloody-july</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bloody-july"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unrest in Bangladesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why write?]]></title>
        <id>https://tanmay.bearblog.dev/why/</id>
        <link href="https://tanmay.bearblog.dev/why/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why write?
I have a ritual. Every time I set out to do something new, be it a new habit, a new course, or a new adventure in life, I ask myself, why? This exercise in setting a purpose is essential because it stays as a reminder of your initial vision about what you set out to do. So, as I launch this blog, I want to openly share the purpose and vision behind it.
This isn't just another hobby project for me. Ever since I was 13, I have wanted to write. To share my ideas with friends, aka people, across the world. There was even a time when I wanted to try to write a self help book, to understand the world and life in general, more effectively. I have always been enamoured by great ideas. For it is these great ideas, passed down from generation to generation, which have survived the test of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The blog that refuses to die]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-refuses-die/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-refuses-die/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T06:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I wrote that I had decided to end this blog. When I woke up this morning, I immediately realized that it was the wrong decision.
Crazy? Maybe.
But that’s how it sometimes is. You can’t always reason your way to the right decision. At least, I can’t. I’d been pondering this for weeks...
It was only when the idea became a reality that I realized it was a bad one. I wish I could avoid taking these detours in my decision-making process, but I’ve come to realize that will probably never happen.
And when you think about it, that “detour” is actually a shortcut to the right decision. Weeks of theoretical pondering didn’t help at all, while taking concrete action gave me an answer in a few hours.
Detours can be shortcuts, at least sometimes and for me. Sorry for the confusion — and welcome to my world. I hope you have the patience to stick around...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bpm140 in "After 10 years, Yelp gave my app 4 days"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41126247</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41126247"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T04:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“they also told me my usage was higher than other developers...”
Next you’ll tell me that they’re NOT actually experiencing higher-than-normal call volumes!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bpm140</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on 4, 5 and 6 October 2024 for our next Autumn Meetings!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Join-us-on-4-5-and-6-October-2024-for-our-next-Autumn-Meetings</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Join-us-on-4-5-and-6-October-2024-for-our-next-Autumn-Meetings"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Autumn Meetings of CADTM Europe will occur on October 4, 5 and 6 October 2024. As of 2023, the venue will be the Simenon Youth Hostelin Liège, Belgium. 
English]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dinobones in "Suspicious data pattern in recent Venezuelan election"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123650</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123650"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T21:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's this re-explained with a simpler example.
Imagine you have 1,000 votes. You want to show that your political party got 60% of the vote, so, you claim:
My party: 600 votes
Opposition: 300 votes
Other: 100 votes
Presto, we got a good breakdown. The people will buy it....
It makes sense that 600 is exactly 60% of 1,000, because this was an artificial example.
But in the real world, we don't get 1,000 votes.
We get 10,058,774 votes. What are the odds that the % of votes you get is a round number like 60%, or 51.2%? They're infinitesimally small. You're much more likely to get ugly numbers, like 59.941323854% of the vote, unless you choose some artificial percentage and work backward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dinobones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by suzzer99 in "Suspicious data pattern in recent Venezuelan election"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123621</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123621"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T21:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More on this. The Carter Foundation, the only impartial observers who were in Venezuela for the election, and who previously defended Venezuela's election system following Chavez's 2004 win, has called on Maduro's government to release local vote tallies, which apparently it is never going to do:  https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/31/world/americas/venezuela-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suzzer99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moderate drinking is not beneficial, in fact is it harmful]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8131</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/moderate-drinking-not-beneficial-in-fact-harmful/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Le Page, writing for New Scientist: Drinking even small amounts of alcohol reduces your life expectancy, rigorous studies show. Only those with serious flaws suggest that moderate drinking is beneficial. That’s the conclusion of a review of 107 studies looking at how drinking alcohol affects people’s risk of dying from any cause at a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by purec in "After 10 years, Yelp gave my app 4 days"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41123194"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:39:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I got the same email. Despite my hobby project (a random food picker) having been broken and not used for years (because of yelp API updates), they also told me my usage was higher than other developers...
The email also arrived in my spam folder, so I was lucky to even see it. Once I got back to them they did increase the cutoff by a few days but it has since been stopped.
Their new prices seemed insane to me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>purec</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do people find things they like]]></title>
        <id>https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/how-do-people-find-things-they-like/</id>
        <link href="https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/how-do-people-find-things-they-like/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[one of my favorite things about people is their hobbies
i absolutely love watching people do the things they love doing, again and again
people who've turned a passion into mastery, who don't tire - they just show up over and over because of the love they have for their craft
it blows my mind
so i started to wonder: how do people find things they truly like?
i've been sitting with this question for a while now. i don't know if i've ever liked something well enough to stick to it long-term
my memory fails me (yes, i have shit memory at the ripe young age of my early 20's), but from what i can remember from my childhood, i loved reading, skating and writing
i remember reading Diary of a Wimpy Kid and Dork Diaries. my older sister and i created something that was an amalgamation of the two. i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leros in "After 10 years, Yelp gave my app 4 days"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41122250</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41122250"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I built a service around helping podcasters automatically convert their audio podcast into a YouTube channel. I went through tons of review with Google in order to get access to the YouTube API and make sure everything I was doing was in compliance with their terms - literally months of back and forth. I had been testing in my development and staging environments against their API for 6+ months. I launched in production, got a few videos uploaded to YouTube, and they disabled my API key. I spent months emailing them and never got anything more than the same boilerplate copy/pasted answer. I could have pivoted or something, but I just shut it down and moved on.  Lesson learned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Arainach in "I prefer rST to Markdown"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41121444</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41121444"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>To which I say, are you really going to avoid using a good tool just because it makes you puke? Because looking at it makes your stomach churn? Because it offends every fiber of your being?"
Yes.  A thousand times yes.  Because the biggest advantage of Markdown is that it's easy to read, and its second-biggest advantage is that it's easy to write.  How easy it is to parse doesn't matter.  How easy it is to extend is largely irrelevant.
Markdown may or may not be the best tool for writing a book, but Markdown is the best tool for what it does - quickly writing formatted text in a way that is easy to read even for those who are not well versed in its syntax.
I don't want to write a book.  If I did I'd use LaTeX before RST.  I want something to take notes, make quick documentation and thread comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arainach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iconic landmarks in San Francisco, CA]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/iconic-landmarks-in-san-francisco-ca/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/iconic-landmarks-in-san-francisco-ca/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of my favorite views in the city.
The Embarcadero holds a special place in my heart because it's the first place I felt most at home in when we first moved into the city. When we moved to California in 2019, I worked in the building right behind Cupid's Span. During lunch time, I would walk down Embarcadero, eat lunch at the Ferry Building, or just go to the building's rooftop to admire the views of the Bay Bridge.
It can get a little touristy in this area since at the end of the Embarcadero is Fisherman's Wharf. Most of the time tourists don't venture this far up away from Pier 39 (where the seals are), but sometimes they do because of the Ferry Building.
I have walked, biked, scootered, and longboarded up and down this strip, and is truly one of my favorite things to see and do.

Cupid's Span - Sculpture by Claes Oldenburg and Coosje van Bruggen.

San Francisco Clocktower and Ferry building - opened in 1898.

Oakland Bay Bridge - the bridge that connects San Francisco > Treasure Island > Oakland. Not to be mistaken for the Golden Gate Bridge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plan your advertising campaigns with Amazon Marketing Cloud on AWS Clean Rooms, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>0845eeabbaa8bb45492bdd2b7c000edbcba69b50</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/plan-your-advertising-campaigns-with-amazon-marketing-cloud-on-aws-clean-rooms-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T16:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advertisers can now leverage first-party data with Amazon Marketing Cloud on AWS Clean Rooms, enabling differentiated insights, audience discovery, and effective campaign planning and measurement while maintaining data privacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Designing Well-Architected systems]]></title>
        <id>fd890d549c6239c39b295530b8c82fcb3e8e28c2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-well-architected-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T16:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The design of cloud workloads can be a complex task, where a perfect and universal solution doesn’t exist. We should balance all the different trade-offs and find an optimal solution based on our context. But how does it work in practice? Which guiding principles should we follow? Which are the most important areas we should […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vittorio Denti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kaycebasques in "I prefer rST to Markdown"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41120772</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41120772"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T16:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Context: I've been a technical writer for ~12 years. I actually started out my career migrating a startup's docs from Word to Sphinx. Then I did a lot of time on Google's proprietary CMS/platform for developer docs. Then a few years on Eleventy-based sites. For the last two years I've been back on a Sphinx-based site (pigweed.dev). I've also done some odd jobs for readme.com-based startups and have dabbled in Docusaurus, Astro, and Hugo.
reStructuredText (reST) by itself can be pretty rough. reST combined with Sphinx is pretty great. I.e. the strengths of Sphinx far outweigh the weaknesses of reST. For big, professional docs sites (+100 pages, +10 contributors) I have pretty strong opinions that Sphinx is probably the most responsible choice, long-term.
> The most important difference betw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kaycebasques</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by codingwagie in "Jeff Bezos' management rules are slowly unraveling inside Amazon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41120696</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41120696"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T16:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a long time Amazonian. The big problem is legacy employees run every part of the company. Almost any manager of managers has been at Amazon a long time, in that same job for a long time. There is no upward mobility at the company, unless you have been in some org 5+ years. In Alexa, the people running the core ML teams have been in Alexa since it started. Most people in decision making positions just got there first (10-15 years ago)
The software engineering paradigms used within the company create brittle rube goldberg machines of events flowing everywhere in the company. Almost all of them are on maintenance mode, where the oncall burns out the engineers and prevents them from creating new products. There is no knowledge sharing between team members. Legacy team members guard their technical platform knowledge to solidify their place on the team.
The engineers themselves are not students of computer science, but just crunch out tickets.
If Amazon wants to change they need to remove a significant amount of tenured employees, and actually promote young engineers into decision making positions.
AWS hasnt released an innovative product in a really long time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>codingwagie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of JulyReply — and the rebirth of this blog]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/end-julyreply-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/end-julyreply-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the end of the JulyReply challenge. A huge thank you to everyone who participated! I hope it brought joy, inspiration, and new connections. May the spirit of JulyReply live on in your writing and interactions.
The original title of this blog post was The end of JulyReply — and this blog. I wrote that I was going to end this blog and continue writing in Swedish elsewhere. Shortly after having published it, I realized it was the wrong decision.
Please see the post The blog that refuses to die to read more on this change of heart.
Sorry about the confusion — it feels quite embarrassing to be honest. I hope you have the patience to keep following this neverending rollercoaster ride of mine...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zharknado in "Creativity fundamentally comes from memorization?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41119684</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41119684"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OP and others here are stretching the definition of “memorize” to mean “anything that leads to something being retained in memory.” I reject this idea.
The trauma of burning your hand on a hot pan creates a memory you won’t soon forget, but almost no one would understand it as an act of memorization.
Memorization to me refers to a set of cargo-culty “learning” practices wherein we believe that by using language to drill exposure to an abstract representation of a concept, that somehow we will absorb the concept itself.
We do this mainly because experts suck at empathizing with learners and fail to understand that the symbol has meaning for them but not for the learner.
It’s the difference between drilling vocabulary flashcards and actually reading, listening, or talking to someone.
Young c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zharknado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natalia Buier - Challenging the Separation of the Economic and the Political]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/natalia-buier-challenging-the-separation-of-the-economic-and-the-political?v=1722433962</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/natalia-buier-challenging-the-separation-of-the-economic-and-the-political?v=1722433962"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Natalia Buier
Title: Challenging the Separation of the Economic and the Political
Date: 2020
Notes: Excerpted from “High-Speed Contradictions: Spanish Railways between Economic Criticism and Political Defense” In Assetization: Turning Things into Assets in Technoscientific Capitalism.
Source: Retrieved on 31st July 2024 from pure.mpg.de

 CGT, Confederación General del Trabajo, is the confederation that represents the majoritarian sector of Spanish anarcho-syndicalism. The railway section of CGT is among the strongest in the confederation, and the 2015 elections, despite a frontal attack against the union aimed at reducing its representation, secured the presence of CGT in the works’ council of both RENFE and ADIF (Administrador de Infraestructuras Ferroviarias, the Spanish railway…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>300d4fcca3cc4ddfaa28c69451423124ef91adaa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how Amazon Q Developer, a generative AI-powered assistant for software development, helps create Terraform templates. Terraform is an infrastructure as code (IaC) tool that provisions and manages infrastructure on AWS safely and predictably. When used in an integrated development environment (IDE), Amazon Q Developer assists with software development, including code generation, explanation, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Rahul Sharad Gaikwad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balance deployment speed and stability with DORA metrics]]></title>
        <id>8a8dea22000e821c0a8e952928cc68ca33f60778</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/balance-deployment-speed-and-stability-with-dora-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Development teams adopt DevOps practices to increase the speed and quality of their software delivery. The DevOps Research and Assessment (DORA) metrics provide a popular method to measure progress towards that outcome. Using four key metrics, senior leaders can assess the current state of team maturity and address areas of optimization. This blog post shows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rostislav Markov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unified Grid: How We Re-Architected Slack for Our Largest Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16924</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/unified-grid-how-we-re-architected-slack-for-our-largest-customers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All software is built atop a core set of assumptions. As new code is added and new use-cases emerge, software can become unmoored from those assumptions. When this happens, a fundamental tension arises between revisiting those foundational assumptions—which usually entails a lot of work—or trying to support new behavior atop the existing architecture. The latter […]
The post Unified Grid: How We Re-Architected Slack for Our Largest Customers appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Nomad - On Why Dr John Drury Is A Collaborationist Asshole]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tom-nomad-on-why-dr-john-drury-is-a-collaborationist-asshole?v=1722415859</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tom-nomad-on-why-dr-john-drury-is-a-collaborationist-asshole?v=1722415859"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Tom Nomad
Title: On Why Dr John Drury Is A Collaborationist Asshole
Subtitle: A Review of Cop-Out: The Significance of Aufhebengate
Date: 2013, May
Source: Retrieved on July 29, 2021 from <theanvilreview.org/print/aufhebengate>

 On many levels it seems almost pointless to write yet another text on Aufhebengate, especially a review about a book on the scandal and the controversies and collaboration-sympathizing that occurred in the vain, and inexplicable, attempt to defend John Drury from his own actions. Usually interpersonal issues point more to the poverty of the militancy and viability of certain circles of so-called “radical scenes” than anything of consequence. In these cases I would usually not waste my time writing a critique of a second-rate academic who writes for a gener…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liao - A Catalyst for Fascist Reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction?v=1722415497</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction?v=1722415497"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Liao
Title: A Catalyst for Fascist Reaction
Date: 7/20/2024
Source: https://www.thecommoner.org.uk/a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction/

 The fallout from the attempted assassination on United States presidential candidate, Donald J. Trump, will bring an increase in fascist propaganda and reactionary attitudes, while also having serious societal repercussions for marginalized groups and political dissidents. While anarchists typically, and rightfully, disparage engagement in electoral politics, the occurrence of this event will likely have effects far beyond just the 2024 United States election. The main focus of this article is to engage with the likely fallout and effects of such an assassination attempt, rather than discuss the actuality of the attempt in a substantive manner. 
 Lik…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubled by Google Maps Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52892</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/31/troubled-by-google-maps-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just got home from a wonderful trip to Prague, Budapest, and Krakow. All three cities have a rich history of Jewish communities, and one can visit synagogues, musea, and Jewish cemeteries. We visited a number of them, including the very impressive Dohány Street Synagogue in Budapest, which was once the largest synagogue in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[floating in desire]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/floating-in-desire/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/floating-in-desire/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T03:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had the best small-town weekend again with K.
Country drives, flea market barn jaunts, dinner with his mom, double dog walks + cuddled-up binging our favorite show.

out-the-car-window farm gem
He took me to see his parent's house, where he grew up which he’s called home his entire life.
It's strange to witness someone have such an intimate connection to land and environment. The ease and pride as he recounts the tapestry of stories that make up his town. I envy his deep roots.
I've moved so many times that I've lost count of how many addresses I've held.
He said he wanted to share his roots with me. Might have been the most romantic thing anyone has ever said to me.

red rubber ball, Courtice, ON
On Sunday, he took me to the Courtice Flea Market, where I found two records that I immediately bought:

Tony Molina, Confront The Truth, 2016. Think: Weezer, The Beatles, with a dash of punk.

Cat Power, Moon Pix, 1998. What a breathtaking cover.
 ✧ you're my internet crush✧
•only two links today bc i've been frolicking in the wildflowers•



Garden of Love Tarot. This gorgeous deck is a burlesque take on the original Tarot de Marseilles. Yes pls.
Cassidy Williams's post about how hard it is to be paid for creative work filled me with over-brimming madness, frustration, and sadness. How do we change our perceptions of money?
heart eyes:
peach cobbler blizzard
Your dad's car by The Rills + Split lip by Delores Forever. Playback: infinity loop.
Heart spoons for stirring coffee
true-blue laughing with your head back
sensual hand massages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by woodruffw in "Our audit of Homebrew"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41115214</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41115214"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T23:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the author of this post and one of the people behind the audit; happy to answer questions about it.
If you're having trouble finding the audit itself (it's linked indirectly), I'm linking a copy here as well[1].
[1]: https://github.com/trailofbits/publications/blob/eb9344f2261...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>woodruffw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The three main processes used to produce decaffeinated coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8120</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/three-processes-produce-decaffeinated-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tangentially related to the previous post. Do you drink decaffeinated coffee? Did you know there are three common methods used by decaf coffee producers to extract caffeine: the carbon dioxide method, Swiss water process, and finally, solvent-based methods. Not all methods are one-hundred percent effective though, as minute quantities of caffeine remain in the finished […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 28, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240730</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240730"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee happy hour, discount prices for early bird customers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8113</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/coffee-happy-hour-discount-prices-early-bird-customers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee happy hours at cafes? This is the first I’ve heard of the idea, but I like it. A growing number of Australian cafes are offering coffees priced at about three dollars a cup, for a couple of hours daily. This compared to the current average cost of about five dollars. Cafe owners concede happy-hour […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.0: Europe is moving to the Right and far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Version-2-0-Europe-is-moving-to-the-Right-and-far-Right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Version-2-0-Europe-is-moving-to-the-Right-and-far-Right"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In light of the new distribution of seats among the legislative groups in the European Parliament, we are publishing version 2.0 of an article first published in June 2024. This new version has been greatly augmented and updated due to the many events that have taken place in the EU during July. 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Paris 2024 Summer Olympics has impacted Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>66a93d504a25d6000ae1c295</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/paris-2024-summer-olympics-impacted-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T19:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post explores the impact of the Paris 2024 Summer Olympics on Internet traffic in France and beyond, concentrating on web activity during the opening ceremony and the initial days of competition. Let the games continue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day Log 001 - working out, naming plants, and green tea lattes]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/day-log-001-working-out-naming-plants-and-green-tea-lattes/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/day-log-001-working-out-naming-plants-and-green-tea-lattes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven't been feeling like myself lately. It’s a similar story to feeling like every day is the same, so I’m not going to go into that again. I’m trying my best to remediate and course correct before it’s too late, but I’m not sure if I’m doing that great of a job.
When I get into this head space, one of the things that helps is working out and running. Runners high and all that. I attempted to wake up 2 hours before my meeting to give myself time to get a workout in but I failed… epically. It’s no surprise because I really am NOT a morning person, so 5am wake up calls are next to impossible.
So maybe I should’ve set a more attainable goal for myself.
It’s still a few hours before noon and I’m already exhausted. The goal is to get a workout in after work instead, or sometime in the evenin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryanmcbride in "Why doesn't advice work?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111883</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111883"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:33:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rules I have for myself when giving advice are:
1. Unsolicited advice is always criticism.
2. LISTEN TO THEIR ACTUAL PROBLEM ALL THE WAY.
3. Never tell someone what they should do, tell them what you would do in that situation.
4. Remember that the purpose of giving advice is just to illuminate options, not to have someone follow what you recommend to the letter.
5. As the advice giver understand that  you could be the one who is wrong.
It's never about trying to convince someone to do what you want, it's about showing them an option and letting them decide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryanmcbride</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aquafox in "The Truth About Linear Regression (2015)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111493"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people don't appreciate linear regression. 
1) All common statistical tests are linear models: https://lindeloev.github.io/tests-as-linear/
2) Linear models are linear in the parameters, not the response! E.g. y = a*sin(x)+bx^2 is a linear model.
3) By choosing an appropriate spline basis, many non-linear relationships between the predictors and the response can be modelled by linear models.
4) And if that flexibility isn't enough, by virtue of the Taylor Theorem, linear relations are often a good approximation of non-linear ones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aquafox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by noodlesUK in "If we want a shift to walking, we need to prioritize dignity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111375</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41111375"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T16:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think one of the key points that is often not understood widely is that car-centric infrastructure causes things to be spaced so much farther apart (with unpleasant empty tarmac) than necessary. If every building is surrounded by a border of 15 meters of roads, that significantly expands the distances that a person needs to travel to get anywhere. This further prioritises cars and drives demand and cultural norms.
I don't think we should be trying to get away from cars altogether by any means, but I think we should seriously consider banning them almost entirely from city centres. There's still a need for emergency vehicles and goods to be transported within the city, so we would still need some roads, but we could eliminate a considerable number of lanes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noodlesUK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cheeseomlit in "If we want a shift to walking, we need to prioritize dignity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41110501</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41110501"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Had a somewhat similar experience in Houston (minus police), which seems to be a city whose infrastructure is comprised of one 9000-lane monstrosity of a freeway. I was staying in a hotel right across the street from the office I was working in, maybe a 3 minute walk. A coworker offered to give me a ride each morning, and when I mentioned I could just walk they said 'the only pedestrians around here are homeless people'. So I guess that's their general attitude about walking, which might explain the attention from police.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cheeseomlit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by i80and in "A eulogy for Dark Sky, a data visualization masterpiece (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41110132</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41110132"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Sky was genuinely the most irreplaceable app I've ever used. I don't think I'll ever forgive Apple's butchering it for spare parts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>i80and</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by samldev in "Is a 'slow' swimming pool impeding world records?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41107938</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41107938"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a college swimmer, qualified for Olympic Trials in 2012 and 2016. There are absolutely slow and fast pools. It basically comes down to two things:
1. The depth - which is only 7ft in Paris, unusually shallow for a competition pool.
2. The sides. Does the water spill over the sides into the gutters, or smash into a wall and bounce back, creating more chop.
A trained eye can see all the swimmers in Paris struggling in their last 10-20 meters (heck, an untrained eye can spot some of these). Bummer that it makes the meet feel slow but at least it generally affects all the swimmers equally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samldev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kmarc in "If we want a shift to walking, we need to prioritize dignity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41106512</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41106512"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While taking a walk near downtown Austin, TX, a police car stopped next to me and the officers started asking weird questions. Including if I know where I am at, where I go, or is there someone who could help me with these apparent struggles in my life.
It took me a couple awkward minutes to realize that I'm the only one standing on my feet and not sitting in a car wherever I was looking. I apologized (???) and told them I was heading to a museum, bc I'm a visitor here and that's what we do right? I added a colleague's address and assured them that I'm not "confused", and will take an Uber now.
This was simply unbelievable in my world; for the next week I observed my colleague, whenever they took me out, or went to somewhere: we never walked outside. From the building to the parking lot, from the destination parking lot to the resto and vice versa.
Today, of course, I know that there are walkable cities too, I enjoy walking from my Chicago hotel to the office building :-) every single time I enjoy my US visits, but after a couple weeks I can't wait to get back to my 98% car free European life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kmarc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jbverschoor in "LG and Samsung are making TV screens disappear"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41106094</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41106094"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T04:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Samsung, I will never ever buy one of your tvs again after you injected ads in my tv]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jbverschoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I used AI to generate a robots.txt that blocks AI]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/ai-scrapers-post/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/ai-scrapers-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T03:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so fucking lazy. I've never really messed with robots.txt. I'm kinda new to personal blogging; back in the 2000s I had a tech blog but I wanted everything to index my site. I even submitted my link to a bunch of off brand search engines to get my name out there.
But now there's AI bots scraping websites like iFixit literally a million times a day.
I don't hate AI. I'm not an AI doomer. But that's fucking silly.
Maybe it's just me or maybe Google is terrible these days, but all I could find were blog posts six months old or more that just listed individual scrapers that are probably outdated anyway. So I asked Claude 3.5 to generate me a robots.txt file to block all known AI scrapers and I think it did alright! Here's what I got:
(edit: updated on 7/30/2024 for clarity)

# Block AI Crawlers
User-agent: GPTBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: ChatGPT-User
Disallow: /

User-agent: CCBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: Google-Extended
Disallow: /

User-agent: anthropic-ai
Disallow: /

User-agent: Claude-Web
Disallow: /

User-agent: ClaudeBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: cohere-ai
Disallow: /

User-agent: PerplexityBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: FacebookBot
Disallow: /

# Allow Search Engine Crawlers
User-agent: Googlebot
Allow: /

User-agent: Bingbot
Allow: /

User-agent: Slurp
Allow: /

User-agent: DuckDuckBot
Allow: /

User-agent: Applebot
Allow: /

User-agent: Baiduspider
Allow: /

User-agent: Yandexbot
Allow: /

# Default rule
User-agent: *
Allow: /]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and Multicloud: Existing capabilities & continued enhancements]]></title>
        <id>3ad3398ec7978d558ff6e7bf3304bd20c3a758d9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-and-multicloud-existing-capabilities-continued-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T23:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS extends existing operational/management capabilities to simplify multicloud oversight. Learn about their approach, recent hybrid/multicloud service launches (18 in 2023), and helpful resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nravi20 in "SAM 2: Segment Anything in Images and Videos"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41104600</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41104600"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T23:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi from the Segment Anything team! Today we’re releasing Segment Anything Model 2! It's the first unified model for real-time promptable object segmentation in images and videos! We're releasing the code, models, dataset, research paper and a demo! We're excited to see what everyone builds! https://ai.meta.com/blog/segment-anything-2/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nravi20</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jph00 in "FastHTML – Modern web applications in pure Python"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41104448</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41104448"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T22:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi all. Jeremy here -- I created this project. Thank you @bpierre for sharing it!
I wrote my first web app ~30 years ago, and have built some pretty big projects, including founding fastmail (written in Perl) and leading the first major production version of Kaggle (written in C#).
Frankly, I've enjoyed creating web apps less and less over the last few years. So I decided to try to create something that I'd personally enjoy using. I like coding with Python, it's got a great ecosystem, and deployments like Dropbox and Instagram show that it can scale right up.
FastHTML brings together Python, hypermedia based apps with HTMX, the powerful and flexible ASGI/Uvicorn/Starlette trio, a new Python component system called FastTag (FT -- based on many similar projects from the functional programming world), an API design inspired by FastAPI, and a few more bits and pieces into something I've now written around a dozen apps with. I'm really loving it!
I hope some of you get a chance to try it out -- let me know what you think.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jph00</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital and growth]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45503</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/29/capital-and-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T21:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We’ve lots of evidence from different times and places that the elasticity of output with respect to capital is indeed small. In his famous paper which kickstarted this approach to thinking about economic growth, Robert Solow estimated (pdf) that only one-eighth of the increase in US GDP per worker between 1900 and 1949 was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only some search engines can access and index Reddit content]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8109</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/only-some-search-engines-access-index-reddit-content/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T21:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google, and Brave Search, are apparently the only search engines permitted to crawl Reddit, and index content published there. Other search engines, including Bing and Duck Duck Go, are presently being prevented from accessing the “front page of the internet” forum and discussion website. Reddit appears to be concerned that search engines other than Google […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java 21 Virtual Threads - Dude, Where’s My Lock?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3052540e231d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/java-21-virtual-threads-dude-wheres-my-lock-3052540e231d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting real with virtual threads]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Llama 3.1, Mistral Large 2, AWS Step Functions, AWS Certifications update, and more (July 29, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>e41b9826185fe73ffc313cb5af4abba941bb013f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-llama-3-1-mistral-large-2-aws-step-functions-aws-certifications-update-and-more-july-29-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m always amazed by the talent and passion of our Amazon Web Services (AWS) community members, especially in their efforts to increase diversity, equity, and inclusion in the tech community. Last week, I had the honor of speaking at the AWS User Group Women Bay Area meetup, led by Natalie. This group is dedicated to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saul Nelson: &ldquo;Volume and Shape&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/volume-and-shape</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/volume-and-shape"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tropical Modernism at the V&A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing your applications with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>135275189c4d14e80cdccdb60c74a99c2f0e35ea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/testing-your-applications-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing code is a fundamental step in the field of software development. It ensures that applications are reliable, meet quality standards, and work as intended. Automated software tests help to detect issues and defects early, reducing impact to end-user experience and business. In addition, tests provide documentation and prevent regression as code changes over time. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Svenja Raether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OpenID Connect with AWS Toolkit for Azure DevOps to perform AWS CodeDeploy deployments]]></title>
        <id>03a6fcf4bb262fc14a5703bc5eb893441a48c0e8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-openid-connect-with-aws-toolkit-for-azure-devops-to-perform-aws-codedeploy-deployments/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Many organizations with workloads hosted on AWS leverage the advantage of AWS services like AWS CloudFormation, AWS CodeDeploy, and other AWS developer tools while integrating with their existing development workflows. These customers seek to maintain their preferred version control systems, such as GitHub, and continue using their established continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth CADTM-Africa University, in coordination with the World March of Women (WMW) and the National Forum on Economic and Social Strategies (FNSES),]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-fourth-CADTM-Africa-University-in-coordination-with-the-World-March-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-fourth-CADTM-Africa-University-in-coordination-with-the-World-March-of"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the slogan “Avoiding the Scenario of ‘Lost' Economic Decades: A Feminist Perspective on the Debt Crisis in Africa, the Necessary Reform of the International Financial Architecture, and the Global Tax System”. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Africa]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM Afrique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding downtime: modern alternatives to outdated certificate pinning practices]]></title>
        <id>669eb83f58eb3b000a368e32</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/why-certificate-pinning-is-outdated"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of outages caused by certificate pinning is increasing. We’ll explore why certificate pinning hasn’t kept up with modern standards and recommend alternatives to improve security while reducing management overhead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unione Sindacale Italiana - Italian syndicalists speak out]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unione-sindacale-italiana-italian-syndicalists-speak-out?v=1722255434</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unione-sindacale-italiana-italian-syndicalists-speak-out?v=1722255434"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T12:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Unione Sindacale Italiana
Title: Italian syndicalists speak out
Subtitle: The USI-AIT denounces what happened at the latest “IWA Congress” in Warsaw
Date: December 29, 2016
Source: Retrieved on 29th July 2024 from lifelongwobbly.com

 The Unione Sindacale Italiana was one of the founding members of the International Workers Association in 1922. Refounded in 1977 after Italy’s “Hot Autumn,” they have been the second-largest and most workplace-focused IWA section for a long time after the Spanish CNT. They have a reputation for avoiding sectarianism, prioritizing solidarity, and maintaining cool heads. Together with the CNT and the German FAU they organized the recent Bilbao Conference of revolutionary unions, and were expelled from the IWA shortly after. [This and all other footnote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tensors from Scratch #2: Elementwise operations and Broadcasting]]></title>
        <id>https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a series of blog posts that will hopefully let you understand what exactly are Tensors, and how you can too implement them from scratch in C. I will be going from basic definitions, illustrations, and explanations to the actual code implementation in this series.
Don't worry, I'm here to help :)
In the part 1 of "Tensors from Scratch" we discussed about what tensors actually are how the shape of a tensor can give us important information about the tensor itself. As a recap:
tensor is an umbrella term for "mathematical objects" or "containers" that have a rank/dimensionality associated with them.
Scalars are rank-0 tensors, vectors are rank-1 tensors, matrices are rank-2 tensors and so on.
One important property of a tensor is its shape. Shape is defined as: the number of elements p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amor y Rabia - Beyond the IWA]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/amor-y-rabia-beyond-the-iwa?v=1722240371</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/amor-y-rabia-beyond-the-iwa?v=1722240371"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T08:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Amor y Rabia
Title: Beyond the IWA
Subtitle: An Interview with the CNT’s International Secretary
Date: January 4, 2017
Notes: This interview was originally published in Spanish, in two parts. English translation by Lifelong Wobbly.
Source: Retrieved on 29th July 2024 from libcom.org

 Discretely, almost silently, something is happening which will have serious consequences for the future of the international Anarchist movement: the reorganization of anarcho-syndicalism on a global scope, at the initiative of the CNT. Following the agreements of its XI Congress in 2015, the CNT – together with the German FAU and the Italian USI – has organized an international conference of anarcho-syndicalist and revolutionary unions (November 26–27, Bilbao). To understand the goals of this conferen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europop]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52897</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/29/europop/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One reaction I heard to the Olympic opening ceremony was that continental Europe has been rubbish at popular music for the past century. Given that Céline Dion had just nailed Edith Piaf’s Hymne d’amour the timing of this opinion wasn’t great, but still, I found myself semi-agreeing on first reaction. Admittedly, the so-called anglosphere has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics?v=1722231189</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics?v=1722231189"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics
Date: 07/26/2024
Source: https://unravel.noblogs.org/from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics/

From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics
 Anarchists who want to take action, when confronted with the choice of tactics, often default to large mass actions, like black bloc. Imagination is ceded to tactical hegemony; autonomy diminishes; creativity recedes; resistance is franchised with stale, processed, prepackaged ideologies and tactics; questionable organizational methods like spokes-councils and democratic decision making give a participatory veneer to a sealed deal–just like in any liberal democracy; most participants spectate rather than act, learning by passive imitation of the leaders rather th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchistische Büchermesse Berlin-Kreuzberg, The Friends of the Class War - When the exhaustion of concepts intensifies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchistische-buchermesse-berlin-kreuzberg-the-friends-of-the-class-war-when-the-exhaustion-of?v=1722229498</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchistische-buchermesse-berlin-kreuzberg-the-friends-of-the-class-war-when-the-exhaustion-of?v=1722229498"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchistische Büchermesse Berlin-Kreuzberg, The Friends of the Class War
Title: When the exhaustion of concepts intensifies
Date: 2024
Notes: Source in German: https://anarchistischebuechermesse.noblogs.org/?p=231 English translation: The Friends of the Class War
Source: https://www.autistici.org/tridnivalka/abmb-when-the-exhaustion-of-concepts-intensifies/

 As we are unfortunately repeatedly confronted with groups that support the Ukrainian side in the war between Russia and the Ukraine from an allegedly “anarchist” position, and as an article appeared in April (When ideology gets in the way of solidarity) in which ABC-Belarus was surprised that we described them as supporters of the war and therefore we did not invite them to the bookfair, here are a few words from us. More tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudden Stratospheric Warming is bringing weird weather to parts of Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8103</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/sudden-stratospheric-warming-weird-weather-parts-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Niño and La Niña are global metrological events most people are probably familiar with. In Australia, the influence of one or other seems more pronounced over the summer months. El Niño marks periods when ocean temperatures in parts of the Pacific Ocean rise by a certain amount, while La Niña events refer to occasions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[showing that you care on the tiny internet]]></title>
        <id>https://oak.bearblog.dev/showing-that-you-care-on-the-tiny-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://oak.bearblog.dev/showing-that-you-care-on-the-tiny-internet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T18:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, I have enjoyed reading various Bear Blog blogs. It's really interesting to see different viewpoints, and thoughts that are less filtered, and more raw. It reminds me of a simpler era of the internet before social media took over.
A recurring theme that has caught my attention - is mental health, various dealings, thoughts, struggles, and victories. All in all these blogs are written by different people at different points in their lives. Yet, they are connected by this platform on this corner of the internet.
Usually, there are not many interactions with the blog author. It’s just a thought written into the void. Nonetheless, I feel sometimes it’s important to show that somebody hears them. blogline by Robert actually inspired me to write this post.
Maybe an email or a simple upvote is all needed to show that you care?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get bored with me: The BearBored Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/get-bored-with-me-the-bearbored-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/get-bored-with-me-the-bearbored-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was inspired by Sit.
What is this?
I am bored. I want to get bored a bit more. Get bored with me. Come join.
The goal?
The goal of the challenge is to waste time. To be as unproductive. To "bear the boredness". (I swear I could think of a better name)
You will need...
A timer (I use the iPhone built-in Clock app. Feel free to choose your own.)
A notebook / sheets of paper
A pen
How to get started:
Step 1: Decide on how long you want to get bored.
15-60 minutes. 5-12 sessions with each session 3-5 minutes long.
Step 2: Write down on your notebook a list of numbers from 1 to X. (X = the number of sessions you chose). 
1.54:59 
Step 3: Start the timer, do nothing and get bored.
Step 4: When each session ends, think of one word that captures the theme of that session. It can be a noun, a verb, an adjective; an emotion, an action, some random vocabulary. Your choice! Write that word down next to the numbered list. 
1.54:59 Distraction 
That is all!
Note:
These are rules I follow when I am doing the challenge. Feel free not to.
No usage of pen and paper besides writing down the keyword. By all means think but let your thoughts slip. Do not write them down. The goal is to be unproductive.
Try not to doze off during the challenge.
Try not to engage in any other activities besides sitting or pacing. Pause the timer if you need to drink water or adjust your posture.
I have been trying this for a couple of days. Turns out getting bored for an hour is way harder than, say, focusing on a textbook and study for an hour. I want to post this to see if anyone is interested in such a format. Write me emails about what more I can do to get the most out of this challenge. Feel free to join me on this journey as well. Let me know if you do!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We have a blogline]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blogline/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blogline/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eriq's entry in my guestbook led me to his recent post, Going from spark to a steady fire. He describes how passions often ignite intensely before rapidly fading away.
I completely resonate with this, just as he did after reading my post I wish I was more dedicated:
It's ridiculous how well that echoes into what I've written above.
Several others have reached out about the same post. One email started with "Dude, that's my life too." The sender described being incredibly invested in a project one week and wanting to abandon it entirely the next.
I've been on the brink of shutting down this blog multiple times, as recently as yesterday. It's hanging by a thread. I’m fighting to keep it going, but the outcome is far from certain.
It's living on borrowed time, like a patient on a ventilator. I'm constantly considering pulling the plug. It's like a dragonfly that's been granted several extra lives, but now feels like its luck is running out. It's sneaking around like a cat aware that its nine lives are nearly spent.
It might sound bleak, but it's my reality. I doubt it will ever change. Yet, there's beauty in it too:
I'm not alone.
It becomes so clear when we share our doubts and shortcomings. When others comment on our posts or send messages.
We're not alone.
Blogging is a fantastic outlet for venting while also fostering a sense of community. Keeping a private diary doesn't have the same impact for me.
Blogging is both liberating and inclusive.
I'm not alone. You're not alone.
We have a blogline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaugust: A Festival of Blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/blaugust-a-festival-of-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/blaugust-a-festival-of-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I stumbled across the Blaugust blogging challenge and thought it would be a good idea to participate. So I decided to join in for the first time.
"Blaugust is a month-long event that takes place each August which focuses on blogging primarily and has started to include other forms of serialized content over the last several years. The goal is to stoke the fires of creativity and allow bloggers and other content creators to mingle in a shared community while pushing each other to post more regularly. Above all the goal of Blaugust has always been to prove to folks that they can in fact sit down every day and create something fresh and then share it with the world. Posting regularly builds a community and in this era of AI-slop content, our voices are needed even more than we ever have been at any point in the past."
– Belghast, Blaugust 2024 is Coming
I hope that Blaugust will help me avoid thinking too much about writing...
Wish me luck!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Liverpool]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52889</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/28/sunday-photoblogging-liverpool-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T07:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52883</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/27/flow/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T22:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you all experience flow? Or rather, as I think everyone does at times, do you experience it often? Obviously I have written plenty of words in my life, but this is not generally something you experience when writing blog posts unless you are maybe excoriating someone in an unnecessarily profane way that is–fundamentally–unfair. Like, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>