<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-06T02:17:11.436Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-06T02:17:11.436Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Access Claude Sonnet 4 in Amazon Q Developer CLI]]></title>
        <id>1d2439d32ee1a9b0caeebf083fd33eba3e8f79b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/access-claude-sonnet-4-in-amazon-q-developer-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T02:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer now supports Claude Sonnet 4 within the CLI, bringing advanced coding and reasoning capabilities to your development workflows at no additional cost. This latest model excels in coding with a state-of-the-art 72.7% for agentic coding on the SWE-bench (see Claude 4 announcement for more information). With enhanced coding and reasoning capabilities, it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now open – AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region]]></title>
        <id>9b737f301236fc9a1f97ad9542f52ea3a36fd7c6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-open-aws-asia-pacific-taipei-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T01:11:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced that AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region is generally available with three Availability Zones and Region code ap-east-2. The new Region brings AWS infrastructure and services closer to customers in Taiwan. Skyline of Taipei including the Taipei 101 building As the first infrastructure Region in Taipei and the fifteenth Region […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS API models and publicly available resources for AWS API definitions]]></title>
        <id>0b7f6978dcbe0b0b5e4efb6e4a86d6709a0b0876</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-aws-api-models-and-publicly-available-resources-for-aws-api-definitions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T20:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS now provides daily updates of Smithy API models on GitHub, enabling developers to build custom SDK clients, understand AWS API behaviors, and create developer tools for better AWS service integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your Eclipse workflows with Amazon Q Developer, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>05ebebc2340e29f825c6ffee0271b9f005815008</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/streamline-your-eclipse-workflows-with-amazon-q-developer-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce the general availability of Amazon Q Developer plugin for the Eclipse integrated development environments (IDE). This release builds upon the developer experience introduced in our November 2024 public preview, bringing powerful AI-assisted development capabilities directly into Eclipse 2025-03(4.35.0) and later versions. The integration significantly improves how developers write, test, and maintain […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madhu Balaji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing an agentic coding experience in Visual Studio and JetBrains IDEs]]></title>
        <id>932be76c45353da0993964a23f6f8878cdea155c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-an-agentic-coding-experience-in-visual-studio-and-jetbrains-ides/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers spend countless hours on repetitive tasks like debugging code, writing unit tests, and validating build processes – time that could be better spent on innovation and problem-solving. To address these challenges, Amazon Q Developer has expanded its intelligent coding assistant capabilities to Visual Studio and JetBrains Integrated development environments (IDEs). This new agentic experience […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing up to 45% price reduction for Amazon EC2 NVIDIA GPU-accelerated instances]]></title>
        <id>c63d6de4890142659cd2619871034949323b6a87</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-up-to-45-price-reduction-for-amazon-ec2-nvidia-gpu-accelerated-instances/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T17:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces significant price reductions of up to 45 percent for NVIDIA GPU-accelerated EC2 instances, increasing accessibility to these high-demand resources for generative AI workloads amid industry-wide GPU shortages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Helmer: Putin Hits Pause Button on Oreshnik-Level Retaliation for Ukraine Strike on Russian Nuclear Deterrence Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293408</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/john-helmer-putin-hits-pause-button-on-oreshnik-level-retaliation-for-ukraine-strike-on-russian-nuclear-deterrence-assets.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T15:36:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his latest talk with Ray McGovern on Dialogue Works, John Helmer gives far and away the best overview1 so far in the wake of Ukraine attacks on bridges and civilian trains, drone attacks targeting bombers in Russia’s nuclear deterrence forces, a failed new attack on Kerch Bridge, and phone discussions between Lavrov and Rubio […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/5/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293381</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-5-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T10:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daily links, including Trump-Putin talk, the US defends genocide at the UN (again), EU using Covid money for weapons, and the right abuses Tolkien.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Culture War is Brewing Over Moral Concern for AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293410</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/a-culture-war-is-brewing-over-moral-concern-for-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T10:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI systems increasingly display emotion — genuine or not — public opinion will split around calls for their rights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like China, a Mexico Tariffs Own Goal: US Dependence on Mexico Energy Trade Means “Those Tariffs Never Stood a Chance”?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293392</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/like-china-a-mexico-tariffs-own-goal-us-dependence-on-mexico-energy-trade-means-those-tariffs-never-stood-a-chance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T08:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More evidence of Trump cluelessness in his Mexico and China tariffs bobs and weaves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rajiv Sethi: American Leadership in Higher Education Is Being Lost for Good, to China’s Benefit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293394</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/rajiv-sethi-american-leadership-in-higher-education-is-being-lost-for-good-to-chinas-benefit.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T07:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why you can stick a fork in US higher education excellence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing our newest 2025 AWS Heroes cohort]]></title>
        <id>f3a0d5a098455913668033ff260b56d4caefa33a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-our-newest-2025-aws-heroes-cohort/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T17:37:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AWS community is a vibrant network of innovators, problem-solvers, and thought leaders who drive cloud technology forward. Today, we’re excited to shine a spotlight on three exceptional individuals who embody the spirit of innovation, knowledge-sharing, and community building. From architecting scalable solutions for millions of users to fostering inclusive tech groups, these professionals are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plastic Mulch Promised Better Harvests. It May Be Hurting the Soil Instead.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293374</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/plastic-mulch-promised-better-harvests-it-may-be-hurting-the-soil-instead.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plastic mulch pollution may linger for centuries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AGI Is Not Multimodal]]></title>
        <id>683fb98b77c3d76051ac142c</id>
        <link href="https://thegradient.pub/agi-is-not-multimodal/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T14:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["In projecting language back as the model for thought, we lose sight of the tacit embodied understanding that undergirds our intelligence." –Terry Winograd
The recent successes of generative AI models have convinced some that AGI is imminent. While these models appear to capture the essence of human]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin A. Spiegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raymond Geuss: &ldquo;Storyteller&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/storyteller</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/storyteller"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T13:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alasdair MacIntyre (1929-2025).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Financiers Win, They Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB8ETjO7BgYRjgHXhozxgmi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItB8ETjO7BgYRjgHXhozxgmi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T12:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the simplest lenses to look at an industrial society is whether it’s run by financiers or capitalists.
Socrates famously noted that some people live to eat and others eat to live.
Capitalists need money so they can do things. Financiers do things so they can get money. To a financier it doesn’t matter how money is made, so long as they won’t go to prison. All that matters is rate of return.
A capitalist has something they want to do: Ford wanted to build cars. Edison wanted to invent. The Wright Brothers wanted to fly. They need money so they can do whatever it is that turns their crank.
Capitalists create great societies. Financiers destroy them.
As soon as rate of return becomes the only consideration, a society becomes less interested in doing new things or doing old things well …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/4/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293325</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-4-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T10:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our wily daily links: Musk declares war on Trump, sentient mushrooms? Covid impact on kids. global heat understated? Trump whinges about Xi, EU poodles brace for fight with Trump, Israel halts Gaza aid after IDF kills, Khameni rejects US terms, moar on Ukraine attacks, parents don't read to kids,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAHA Influencers, the Future of Public Health, and Longings for Immortality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293257</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/maha-influencers-the-future-of-public-health-and-longings-for-immortality.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T10:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Make America Healthy Again (MAHA) Report has dropped!  The original document included phantom (hallucinated?) references, but those have been fixed apparently.  Or maybe not.  A graduate student who wrote a review with the same defects would get a flat “F”, but this does not seem to matter.  Could AI (Algorithmic Intelligence) have had anything […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie: What Do the Western Drone Attacks Mean for US – Russia Relations?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293367</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/rob-urie-what-do-the-western-drone-attacks-mean-for-us-russia-relations.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T09:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Ukraine's recent escalations: "Westerners sanguine about the prospect of nuclear war are fools."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s ‘One Big Beautiful Bill’ Continues Assault on Obamacare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293360</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/trumps-one-big-beautiful-bill-continues-assault-on-obamacare.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T09:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rather than end Obamacare, which would be politically costly,  the Trump Administration is working to hollow it out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brussels’s media machine: EU media funding and the shaping of public discourse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New report exposes a vast, previously under-scrutinised system through which the European Union annually disburses €80 million a year to media projects across Europe and beyond]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an AI Agent that puts humans in the loop with Knock and Cloudflare’s Agents SDK]]></title>
        <id>3YwK1RRHXn4kGrNazu4AKd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-agents-at-knock-agents-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Knock shipped an AI Agent with human-in-the-loop capabilities with Cloudflare’s Agents SDK and Cloudflare Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bell (Guest author)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models what they don’t know]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of MIT researchers founded Themis AI to quantify AI model uncertainty and address knowledge gaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Winn | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Short Summary Of Why China Is Winning &amp; The West Fading]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T03:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s about living in reality:
The main difference between American and Chinese society today is less that one has more dumb people and one has more smart people and more that within public life being stupid is relentlessly shamed as stupid in one and being smart is relentlessly shamed as stupid in the other.
These days American society assigns intelligence credentials based not on who can demonstrate a meticulous well developed understanding of how anything works but who can give the most smart sounding post hoc rationalization for half baked ideas people desperately want to be true.
If you do the former and it yields answers people don’t like they’ll reach deep into their bag of fantasyland narratives to try to invalidate your credibility. If you provide the latter you’re celebrated not o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI stirs up the recipe for concrete in MIT study]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With demand for cement alternatives rising, an MIT team uses machine learning to hunt for new ingredients across the scientific literature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Paul Laurent | MIT Concrete Sustainability Hub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models the broad strokes to sketch more like humans do]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SketchAgent, a drawing system developed by MIT CSAIL researchers, sketches up concepts stroke-by-stroke, teaching language models to visually express concepts on their own and collaborate with humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shipps | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze media content using AWS AI services]]></title>
        <id>df70aecbbf09cdd2b5cd5b057a82fffb9d66bac9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/analyze-media-content-using-aws-ai-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations managing large audio and video archives face significant challenges in extracting value from their media content. Consider a radio network with thousands of broadcast hours across multiple stations and the challenges they face to efficiently verify ad placements, identify interview segments, and analyze programming patterns. In this post, we demonstrate how you can automatically transform unstructured media files into searchable, analyzable content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Bradham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora DSQL, MCP Servers, Amazon FSx, AI on EKS, and more (June 2, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>75057629af595e8c8b702253ca50ca0709ea6ed9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-aurora-dsql-mcp-servers-amazon-fsx-ai-on-eks-and-more-june-2-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s AWS Summit Season! AWS Summits are free in-person events that take place across the globe in major cities, bringing cloud expertise to local communities. Each AWS Summit features keynote presentations highlighting the latest innovations, technical sessions, live demos, and interactive workshops led by Amazon Web Services (AWS) experts. Last week, events took place at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Questions: How to help students recognize potential bias in their AI datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courses on developing AI models for health care need to focus more on identifying and addressing bias, says Leo Anthony Celi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne Trafton | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 1, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBW-ZLGE0f5RIDMAeAtUXbw</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBW-ZLGE0f5RIDMAeAtUXbw"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T18:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 1, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
Strategic Political Economy
Why Are They Trying to Kill Us?
Conor Gallagher, May 28, 2025 [Naked Capitalism]
For all the talk of how incompetent our elites are, there’s one area where they show remarkable skill and determination: relentlessly creating conditions to shorten the lifespans of the disabled, poor, and working class.
Let’s look at just a few of the many examples before examining potential reasons it’s becoming so much more brazen.
In the US, policies to hurt the working poor and disabled are nothing new, but they’ve exploded in scope in recent years. Elites have collectively memory-holed an ongoing pandemic that has thus far officially killed more than 1.2 million (although that number is likely much higher), dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 30, 2025 (#563)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22772</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/30/daily-reading-list-may-30-2025-563/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's pre-vacation links look at building engineering ladders, why you should aim for greatness, and how to negotiate like an expert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and improved Amazon Q Developer experience in the AWS Management Console and chat applications]]></title>
        <id>cb688afe847e83387e4b36587700c5f9ca49d600</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/new-and-improved-amazon-q-developer-experience-in-the-aws-management-console/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer just launched a new agentic experience within the AWS Management Console, that enables builders to get deeper insights about their AWS resources and improve their operational troubleshooting efficiency. This expands the agentic capabilities of Amazon Q Developer from both the integrated development environment (IDE) and command line interface (CLI) to the AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Launchpad from Pega enables secure SaaS extensibility with AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>e9e104062df7c68c8a1a66d7e7c0c4390f1845b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-launchpad-from-pega-enables-secure-saas-extensibility-with-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we share how Pegasystems (Pega) built Launchpad, its new SaaS development platform, to solve a core challenge in multi-tenant environments: enabling secure customer customization. By running tenant code in isolated environments with AWS Lambda, Launchpad offers its customers a secure, scalable foundation, eliminating the need for bespoke code customizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Aleksandrov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare named a Strong Performer in Email Security by Forrester]]></title>
        <id>1V8L0Y4ySPeme0LzUNSodX</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-named-a-strong-performer-in-email-security-by-forrester/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forrester has recognized Cloudflare Email Security as a Strong Performer in the ‘current offering’ category in “The Forrester Wave™: Email, Messaging, And Collaboration Security Solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>