<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-26T06:45:05.600Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-26T06:45:05.600Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the US and the WTO Should Part Ways]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294582</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/why-the-us-and-the-wto-should-part-ways.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T05:11:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In another sign the old international order is breaking as the US flails about, a serious call for the US to leave the WTO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 25, 2025 (#575)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23333</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/25/daily-reading-list-june-25-2025-575/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T23:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the exciting new Gemini CLI, how Salesforce rolled out AI to their engineering teams, and where AI features should sit in your product's UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for OpenZFS now supports Amazon S3 access without any data movement]]></title>
        <id>becd74c154f4b3a13344b15c9ef71b24566da206</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-openzfs-now-supports-amazon-s3-access-without-any-data-movement/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T20:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now attach Amazon S3 Access Points to your Amazon FSx for OpenZFS file systems so that you can access your file data as if it were in S3. With this new capability, you can work with your file data using a broad range of applications that work with S3—all without any refactoring or data movement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing Our Asian Allies – And Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA_5DHONSDQ2FmVwyvLb9Gr</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA_5DHONSDQ2FmVwyvLb9Gr"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T20:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ian in his last post mentioned that our Asian allies are slipping away from us. While we pretend to strategically re-orient the Japanese are engaging in massive rearmament begun by Abe and being continued by the current government. Japan has lost confidence in the American security umbrella because of the deceit we’ve displayed in foreign relations. The Koreans? I lived in Korea. They’re simply apoplectic. Some are even at the point where they are willing to consider a loose confederation with the north, an entente of sorts so the South has the protection of the North’s nuclear umbrella and the North gains goods and services from the South.
This is simply unheard of. When I talked to one of my former students who now works in the foreign ministry and he told me this I was gobsmacked.
Ian’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Is Mamdani’s Win Over Cuomo The End of Democratic Party Neoliberalism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294479</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/mamdani-cuomo-new-york-primary-neoliberalism-progressives.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T18:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progressives in the Democratic party are declaring the ruling neoliberal class of the party leadership finished after NYC primary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Wilson Turner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Middle East Is Hastening Ukraine’s Fall &amp; The End of the European Era]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCldAklcjs27uMa83tGKrNn</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCldAklcjs27uMa83tGKrNn"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T14:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rarely spoken of is the effects of the Middle Eastern wars on Ukraine. For a long time, Ukraine got everything it wanted, but since Oct 7th, it has been #2, or worse, on America’s priority list. Mossad has a great deal of influence in America, just short of control, almost certainly due to a sickening collection of videos and pictures, and Israel has received the first cut off everything it needed: most especially of interceptor missiles.
Even so, the reason that Israel and the US called for a ceasefire and Iran did not (though it accepted one) is that Israel was less than a week from running out of air defense missiles, and as best I can tell, the US could only have supplied about another 7-10 days worth.
What this means for Ukraine is simple enough, they’re being absolutely hammered by R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Shale Can’t Scale If No One’s Left to Work It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294574</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/us-shale-cant-scale-if-no-ones-left-to-work-it.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A form of class warfare hits shale players Too few young workers like the industry and its long-term career prospects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merging AI and underwater photography to reveal hidden ocean worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/lobstger-merging-ai-underwater-photography-to-reveal-hidden-ocean-worlds-0625</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/lobstger-merging-ai-underwater-photography-to-reveal-hidden-ocean-worlds-0625"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOBSTgER research initiative at MIT Sea Grant explores how generative AI can expand scientific storytelling by building on field-based photographic data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Sea Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlanticism — not nationalism — is driving German rearmament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/atlanticism-not-nationalism-is-driving</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/atlanticism-not-nationalism-is-driving"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T11:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The policies now being implemented — from massive rearmament to the escalation of conflict with Russia — are not rooted in a cold pursuit of German national interests, but in their negation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/25/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294336</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-25-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T10:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[</a)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Looking Backwards’ and Forward: How Democrats Who Voted for Iraq Cashed In and How It Ensured the Rise of the Imperial Uniparty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294537</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/looking-backwards-and-forward-how-democrats-who-voted-for-iraq-cashed-in-and-how-it-ensured-the-rise-of-the-imperial-uniparty.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T10:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obama’s decision to “look forward” continues to reverberate into our endless wars of the present—and future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie: Why Did the US Attack Iran?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294563</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/rob-urie-why-did-the-us-attack-iran.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T09:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie points out that how many forces the US keeps in theater will reveal its  intent with Iran: deescalating versus trying to regroup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gen. Michael Kurilla and the Pivot to Asia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294520</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/gen-michael-kurilla-and-the-pivot-to-asia.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T04:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is diminishing Iran key to the famed pivot to Asia, or a distraction?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 24, 2025 (#574)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23292</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/24/daily-reading-list-june-24-2025-574/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T23:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at what AI to use right now, how to prioritize better, and why the AI revolution won't happen overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New: Improve Apache Iceberg query performance in Amazon S3 with sort and z-order compaction]]></title>
        <id>338ab1a5449dedd3d0a422376be4e668fc6d6075</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-improve-apache-iceberg-query-performance-in-amazon-s3-with-sort-and-z-order-compaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T20:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 now enables improved Apache Iceberg query performance through two new compaction strategies—sort and z-order—available for both S3 Tables and general purpose S3 buckets, helping organize data more efficiently by clustering similar values together and reducing file scanning during queries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – Circular Error Probability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294468</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-circular-error-probability.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circular error probability (CEP) is the metric weapons designers use to describe the accuracy of munitions. CEP is defined as the radius of a circle, centered on the intended target, within which 50% of projectiles or warheads are expected to land. As guidance technology has advanced, CEPs of modern missiles and drones have grown smaller. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran Screws Up &amp; Gaza Death Toll]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T17:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Iran has accepted the ceasefire offer. Iran was, as best I can tell, winning. The Iron Dome could not stop their more advanced missiles and was days from running out of interceptor missiles. Two weeks if the US sent its entire stockpile. The US attack on Iran’s nuclear facility was a dud, the enriched uranium has been moved, etc…
I said that Iran had finally gotten over its caution, but feared it would revert, and so it has. It’s clear that the sooner Khameini dies and is replaced the safer Iran will be, also because that will be the end of the non-nuclear fatwa. (It should be noted that 60% enriched is enough to create a dirty bomb which would render Israel uninhabitable, and Iran should inform Israel that it has created a number, read for missile deployment.)
Iran could have kept goi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are available in public beta for simple, global, and programmable compute]]></title>
        <id>5StUs8TMNjY9aDG2TzFJ06</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/containers-are-available-in-public-beta-for-simple-global-and-programmable/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Containers are now available in public beta. Deploy simple, global, and programmable containers alongside your Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabi Villalonga Simón</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Downgrading Uncle Sam, Not America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294509</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/downgrading-uncle-sam-not-america.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T13:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An orthodox economist describes inconsistencies in rating agencies' approach to downgrading US debt and their view of reserve currency status]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s craziest ceasefire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The smug idea that Israel can get away with anything without ever paying a price seems to have vanished]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/24/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294459</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-24-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daily links, including kabuki theater in West Asia, but is there a way out? Plus more militarization on the home front and how animals taught us culture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deluge of Metanarrative Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T07:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime anyone anywhere begins an argument or uses the word “narrative” my bullshit detector goes off. Because it’s a nonsense construct.
My suggestion is to follow French philosopher Jean-François Lyotards definition of “narrative.” He said: “Simplifying to the extreme , I define postmodern as incredulity toward metanarratives.”
So, if you hear someone use the term in a conversation, one of three things can happen: you can choose to remain willfully ignorant (I doubt many in this crowd would pursue this course), two, your bullshit detector can go off, like mine and you can begin an argument or three you can simply sit with a Cheshire cat grin and be skeptical.
But chose one, please.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 23, 2025 (#573)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23026</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/23/daily-reading-list-june-23-2025-573/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T23:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at why not all micromanagement is bad, agent-to-agent protocol truly becoming an industry standard, and why software development won't ever be the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture in an AWS landing zone]]></title>
        <id>d99d4df75c23e56992bed599dc075700701c55d6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/amazon-bedrock-baseline-architecture-in-an-aws-landing-zone/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T18:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore the Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture and how you can secure and control network access to your various Amazon Bedrock capabilities within AWS network services and tools. We discuss key design considerations, such as using Amazon VPC Lattice auth policies, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) endpoints, and AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to restrict and monitor access to your Amazon Bedrock capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdel-Rahman Awad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: re:Inforce re:Cap, Valkey GLIDE 2.0, Avro and Protobuf or MCP Servers on Lambda, and more (June 23, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>939e6ae6e5cce485ea26e1e9c5165b803613c28b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-reinforce-recap-valkey-glide-2-0-avro-and-protobuf-or-mcp-servers-on-lambda-and-more-june-23-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s hallmark event was the security-focused AWS re:Inforce conference. Now a tradition, the blog team wrote a re:Cap post to summarize the announcements and link to some of the top blog posts. To further summarize, several new security innovations were announced, including enhanced IAM Access Analyzer capabilities, MFA enforcement for root users, and threat […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangster empire: what the bombing of Iran reveals about the West]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T13:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have now entered a new phase of Western-led global savagery — prefigured by the genocide in Gaza — in which all pretences have been dropped and only the logic of raw, unrestrained violence remains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TACO Trump Bombs Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re getting a bit tired of Iran all the time, so am I, and we’ll see if we can slip in an article on something else.
In the meantime, Trump hit Iran’s nuclear enrichment site. As best I can tell, the attack was ineffective and did essentially no damage. Even if it had, Iran’s highly enriched, 60% stockpile, had already been moved. I’ve seen Israeli claims they know where, but there’s a good chance they’re lying and if the Iranians are smart, they’ve split it up and made sure that only a few people know where each package is, and no one knows where all the packages are, which doubles as “if you hit it, you lose your spy.”
Iran’s parliament has passed a motion asking for the Straits of Hormuz to be closed, it’s waiting for Khameini’s approval. Some ships appear to be already turning aw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs factor in unrelated information when recommending medical treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find nonclinical information in patient messages — like typos, extra white space, and colorful language — reduces the accuracy of an AI model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
War
[TW: This is what the “globalist” elites centered on the City of London and Wall Street have been scheming for ever since Franklin Roosevelt told Winston Churchill at the 1943 Casablanca Conference that there would be no restoration of the British empire.
[Now that Trump has fully thrown in with the pro-war faction, we will learn if those who supported Trump because they believed Trump would be a foil against the “globalist” elites, accept the chastening of a hard lesson learned. More importantly, now that Trump has allowed the globalists to steer us into a war against Iran, will those who supported Trump be vigilant against Trump using the war to exercise his “war powers” and impose authoritarian measures on the USA p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wars Metastize]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title says it own. So did Clausewitz.
We committed an act of war against a sovereign state that had every right to peaceful nuclear power.
Tulsi Gabbard told Donald Trump in March that Iran had NO nuclear weapons program.
There is a huge difference between radio medcine and nuclear power, and a nuclear weapons program. Iran has the former by legal right under the NNPT and does not, nor has plans for the latter.
This war will spiral out of control just like the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand in July 1914.
Prepare yourselves. We will all suffer before this is over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 20, 2025 (#572)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22998</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/20/daily-reading-list-june-20-2025-572/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T23:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how one company uses AI in their software workflow, debating single versus multi-agent systems, and why every service should have a killswitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDv1jIfsJz98n8W0jyQToUO</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDv1jIfsJz98n8W0jyQToUO"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T21:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts (no Iran/Israel war).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers present bold ideas for AI at MIT Generative AI Impact Consortium kickoff event]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/researchers-present-bold-ideas-ai-mit-generative-ai-impact-consortium-event-0620</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/researchers-present-bold-ideas-ai-mit-generative-ai-impact-consortium-event-0620"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presentations targeted high-impact intersections of AI and other areas, such as health care, business, and education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Diehl | MIT Schwarzman College of Computing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Robin: &ldquo;Waiting Game&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On ‘late capitalism’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Hear It or Actually Witness It?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Lagarde’s “global euro” is a fantasy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T12:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The euro remains plagued by structural and political flaws that make this impossible — and thank God for that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Big One]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several months ago I wrote two essays on Russian grand strategy. (My apologies on never completing the nuclear one, an extremely necessary but far too grim subject for my taste.) In that series of essays I made a few assertions I want to bring to your attention again in a more contemporary context. First, that the result of wars tend to confirm strengths of the coalition arrayed against the main combatants before the war even started. This is, in fact, not an assertion, but an iron law of warfare that still exists in chimpanzee warfare. See Strategy: a history, chapter one, by Freedman if you disagree.
 
Second, that big global dustups tend to run in about 100 year cycles these days.
So, take a look around–got a big hot war in the Ukraine slightly analogous to the Sino-Japanese war of the 1930s. Next, you got weird, unresolved shenanigans in the Middle East that have a weird reverse-appeasement type feal.
We’re quite possible looking at the two opening battles of WWIII, right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Operational Troubleshooting with Amazon Q Developer CLI]]></title>
        <id>6ca0238df379c9f06e7af49f9ea247df0b913de3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/streamline-operational-troubleshooting-with-amazon-q-developer-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is the most capable generative AI–powered assistant for software development, helping developers perform complex workflows. Amazon Q Developer command-line interface (CLI) combines conversational AI with direct access to AWS services, helping you understand, build, and operate applications more effectively. The Amazon Q Developer CLI executes commands, analyzes outputs, and provides contextual recommendations […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new AWS CDK EKS v2 L2 Constructs]]></title>
        <id>99b0d8b7cbff701292b81232dbf10edca9376525</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/announcing-the-new-aws-cdk-eks-v2-l2-constructs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today, we’re announcing the release of aws-eks-v2 construct, a new alpha version of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) L2 construct for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). This construct represents a significant change in how developers can define and manage their EKS environments using infrastructure as code. While maintaining the powerful capabilities of its predecessor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Luigi Restelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate development with secure access to Amazon Q Developer using PingIdentity]]></title>
        <id>a2400f3bcbd784c93bb5d83c61721efb7a0b8517</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-development-with-secure-access-to-amazon-q-developer-using-pingidentity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Customers adopting Amazon Q Developer, a generative AI-powered coding companion, often need authentication through existing identity providers like PingIdentity. By leveraging AWS IAM Identity Center, organizations can enable their developers to access Amazon Q Developer with their existing PingIdentity credentials, streamlining authentication and removing the need for separate login procedures. Amazon Q Developer can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sid Vantair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>