<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-02T12:46:46.261Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-02T12:46:46.261Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281482</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T10:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our hyperactive daily links: baby 'roo on the run, Idaho Covid shot curbs, epic Spanish floods, moar China sanctions blowback, NKorea worries, UK food shortage risks, Iran warns of big Israel strike, Russia annoyed with Turkiye, American shrinking leadership competence, Microsoft goaf addiction, decline of working musicians]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson and Richard Wolff: BRICS High Aspirations Versus Cautious First Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281529</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/michael-hudson-and-richard-wolff-brics-high-aspirations-versus-cautious-first-steps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T08:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson and Richard Wolff discuss the recent BRICS summit as well as its rapidly-evolving geopolitical backdrop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundi - The Consequences to Rahtid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T07:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fundi
Title: The Consequences to Rahtid
Date: February 1974
Notes: Transcribed from Documents of the Caribbean Revolution (Tunapuna: New Beginning, 1974) by Matthew Quest and Ryan Cecil Jobson.*
Source: Retrieved on 2024-11-02 from medium.com/clash-voices-for-a-caribbean-federation-from-below/joseph-edwards-the-consequences-of-rahtid-february-1974-71bdbe7668e6

Joseph Edwards, a Jamaican refrigeration mechanic, spoke of radical labor politics in Rasta idioms. Let’s reason “to Rahtid!”
His selected writings have been published as Workers Self-Management in the Caribbean (2014). When we read his ideas comparatively with Trinidad’s CLR James, Guyana’s Walter Rodney, and Jamaica’s Michael Manley and Trevor Munroe we can begin to see the antagonisms or debates within the Caribbean radic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A No-Win Dilemma for US Peace Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281500</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/a-no-win-dilemma-for-us-peace-voters.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T05:42:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working through the poor US election options for peace advocates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundi - Union Versus Menegement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-union-versus-menegement?v=1730521629</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-union-versus-menegement?v=1730521629"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T04:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fundi
Title: Union Versus Menegement
Date: 1970s
Notes: Transcribed by Mutt.
Source: Retrieved on 2 November 2024 from <organisemagazine.org.uk/2024/11/01/union-versus-menegement-joseph-edwards-theory-and-analysis>

This piece, authored by Joseph Edwards—also known as Fundi or the Caribbean Situationist—offers a unique perspective within the anti-authoritarian tradition of the Caribbean left.
Assumed to be the first publication of the Trinidadian labor organizing group, The New Beginning Movement (NBM) (1971–1978), this booklet was released as Abeng Pamphlet No. 1. The NBM drew inspiration from the Black Power Revolt and the legacy of C.L.R. James, applying his concepts of workers’ autonomy and self-management to forge a Pan-Caribbean International that extended links to Canada, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless containers at AWS re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>314d84d81ceb7ad31834e8a50e051e84e05cca98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/serverless-containers-at-aws-reinvent-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T22:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Invent is the premier learning conference hosted by AWS for the global cloud computing community. This year the Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) and AWS Fargate teams will share the latest trends, innovations, best practices, and tips to help you increase productivity, optimize costs, and enhance business agility. Join us in Las Vegas […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henrique Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning for Anthropic’s Claude 3 Haiku model in Amazon Bedrock is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>f4c8ebbba2f21c6bef599b672f6fee9619d9b320</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/fine-tuning-for-anthropics-claude-3-haiku-model-in-amazon-bedrock-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock Anthropic's Claude 3 Haiku model's full potential with Amazon Bedrock's fine-tuning for enhanced accuracy and customization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Organs of State Security Involved in Authenticating Election 2024 (or Not)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281480</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/the-organs-of-state-security-involved-in-authenticating-election-2024-or-not.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T21:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hamilton 68 has risen from the grave?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AJR, Nobel, and prompt engineering]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45700</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/01/ajr-nobel-and-prompt-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Well done AJR.  A prize deserved.  And remarkably little grumbling.  What’s wrong with that? In other news, my wife is deep into creating an artificial intelligence application.  One of the great challenges of getting AI to be useful is something called ‘prompt engineering’.   What have these two snippets of news have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fountain Pens and Writing Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/fountain-pens-and-writing-challenges/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/fountain-pens-and-writing-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, November.
New month, new things to talk about.
National Fountain Pen Day
Today is apparently National Fountain Pen Day. As always, I have no idea who comes up with these holidays, but here I am, fully embracing it. I wish I could do a similar ode to my fountain pens like I did with my cameras during National Camera Day, but I only have one fountain pen, so that would be a very short post. Ask me again next year— maybe I’ll have a different answer by then.
There are also a myriad of writing challenges starting up today, which is super exciting. These are the times when more people are motivated to write, which in turns means more things to read. It’s a win/win for everyone!
The two challenges I have my eye on are:
WeblogPoMo AMA (Ask Me Anything)
Link: weblogpomo.club/challenges
Host…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing serverless observability with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3fe6f0a5bc1d</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/enhancing-serverless-observability-with-python-3fe6f0a5bc1d?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key strategies and tools to leverage Python for effective serverless observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281491</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Friday's RCP polling: Bad news for Trump; more Section Three fun ; Epstein on Trump  (last minute tape); Boeing to vote on new contract Monday ("slight improvement") ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thenberlin in "Apple acquires Pixelmator"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42019513</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42019513"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putting concerns about future states aside, congrats to the Pixelmator team. I've been using the app for years and it's a really great piece of software, well designed and well built. It's always been incredible value for the price, especially given that it basically replaces Photoshop for a wide swath of the market without compromising on UX (which is a problem for other competitors) at a price point that's like 1-2 months of an Adobe subscription (I don't even know exactly what that costs any more because Pixelmator + parts of the Affinity suite got me out of their clutches).
Adobe must not be stoked about this news. And I'll just keep my fingers crossed this all heads in a direction that's more Logic than Dark Sky.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thenberlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First-Year Cohort Classes for PhD Students]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53347</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/01/first-year-cohort-classes-for-phd-students/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the spring, I’ll be teaching the second semester of our philosophy grad program’s first-year seminar. This is the seminar all PhD students in the philosophy department take together as a cohort during their first year in the program. The fall semester of the seminar typically leans towards the metaphysics and epistemology side of philosophy, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gina Schouten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beastieball Early Access Date & OST Pre-Order!!]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/beastieball-early-access-ost-pre-order/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/beastieball-early-access-ost-pre-order/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well hello there!
Some very exciting news in the world of Beastieball: the Early Access release date has been set for November 12th! That's like, less than 2 weeks away... I better get everything ready...
Here's the trailer!!


But wait, you want more?
Well. Okay.
How about the BEASTIEBALL Original Sound Track? It's now up for pre-order on Bandcamp!!
BEASTIEBALL Original Sound Track by Lena Raine

I wanted to take a moment to talk about how I'll be releasing the OST, since it's my first Early Access game:
When the game first releases, there's going to be a lot of music in the game! 61 tracks, with an estimated runtime of around 2 hours 40 mins. That's about as much as Chicory had when it released in full! However, there's a lot more music we want to add to the game on the road to its 1.0 r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lynndotpy in "Apple acquires Pixelmator"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42018783</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42018783"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T16:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there any way this can go bad?
When Apple acquired DarkSky, they absolutely destroyed a service that I loved and relied on. Four years on, Apple Weather is less reliable than DarkSky, and not even close to feature complete.
But DarkSky was a cross-platform service, whereas Pixelmator is software that's already Apple-only. I'm wondering how much I should be worried, and if I should already be abandoning ship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lynndotpy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gary Indiana <em>&amp;</em> Janique Vigier: &ldquo;Psychic Landmarks&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/psychic-landmarks</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/psychic-landmarks"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T15:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview (1950-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hansonkd in "A new dental scam is to pull healthy teeth to sell you expensive fake ones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42018001</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42018001"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This might sound stupid but I refuse to go to dentists that have "too nice" of an office.
Over the years I have lived in several places and had a variety of dentists and one common theme that sticks with me, the nicer and higher tech the office is, the more procedures they are going to recommend you. They need to pay for the equipment and office somehow.
I've had one dentist say I need 3 cavities filled. That I needed laser treatments, extra cleanings, etc. They made it sound like my teeth were going to fall out of my head. I was going to Brazil in a few months and so i decided to wait until I was there to get the work done.
The dentists there took xrays, etc and didn't find any problems. I even went to another dental clinic and the same thing. They had no idea what that dentist thought was wrong.
When I came back to the states i went to another dentist. Instead of being on a top floor with an army of technicians and the fanciest machines like the first one, this dentist had a small older office. He did the cleanings himself and again he found no problems and told me I had very healthy mouth and gums.
This has happened to me before when i went away to college my childhood dentist said I had cavities that I needed to fill. When i got to college and went to the dentist there, they couldn't find a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hansonkd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sgc in "Alexander the Great's tunic identified in royal tomb at Vergina?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42017262</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42017262"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T14:31:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apologies for the long response.
I am only partially qualified in that I am not a professional archeologist, but I have done post-doctoral archeological studies and have read enough archeological studies to understand the larger academic context.
It is not possible to present all the data informing a judgment in such a short work. Even in a book, it would not be possible. Thus it is common in archeology for papers to be written as part of an ongoing conversation / debate with the community - which would be defined as the small handful of other archeologists doing serious research on the same specific subject matter.
Part of that context here is that these tombs are well-established to be the royal tombs of Alexander's family, spanning a few generations including his father and his son. Thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sgc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dentists Are Pulling ‘Healthy’ and Treatable Teeth To Profit From Implants, Experts Warn]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281478</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/dentists-are-pulling-healthy-and-treatable-teeth-to-profit-from-implants-experts-warn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amid this booming industry, some implant experts worry that many dentists are losing sight of dentistry’s fundamental goal of preserving natural teeth and have become too willing to remove teeth to make room for expensive implants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Amazon Q reduced the time Amazon developers spent waiting for technical answers by 450k hours this year]]></title>
        <id>37da3117c216b131a1ae8bed3a30e668ff603684</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/reducing-time-spent-waiting-with-amazon-q/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Software development is complex and time consuming. Developers frequently need to stop building to get answers to hard, technical questions. What is the error in my code? How do I debug the logic? Where do I go to find this information? In 2024 Stack Overflow Developer Survey 53% of respondents agreed that waiting on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hank Cycyota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[second post]]></title>
        <id>https://travisporter.bearblog.dev/new-post/</id>
        <link href="https://travisporter.bearblog.dev/new-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T13:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking as someone who has been following Sabine for about two years and am generally a fan, I just watched this video
yesterday that made me a bit more skeptical of her views. And I mean a bit, like 10%. Prof dave explains raises a good point that just doing mathematics in theoretical physics is not a bad idea per se. I think it does take a bit of glamour out of physics for those new to the field but it’s obviously extremely fundamental.
As a “failed academic” myself though I do not empathize with Sabine. This is because I was terrible at my PhD program because of my inherent absolute disinterest. I saw brilliant people around me delve into world class knowledge levels from scratch in lasers, synthetic biology, RNA etc and they had the cajones (male and female) to push themselves to learn and in fact love math behind these fields. ( example of paper we had to read )
Sabine may be right that she disagrees with the direction of particle hunting, and she may be an incredibly smart person maligned by one particular academic institution, which is sad. But like math, I would love for her to fix the system not as an outsider but as a take-no-prisoners insider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding the Authentic Web]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/finding-the-authentic-web/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/finding-the-authentic-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not sure about you, but for me, the web feels untrustworthy these days. So much of the content is either AI generated or created just to sell something, it's really hard to find authenticity online. How do you know what sites to trust? Where do you find quality content?
I've been thinking about this problem for a couple of years now, trying to figure out a solution. I feel like we need to wall off parts of the web. You know, have a gated community to keep the riff-raff out. Of course, that feels a bit icky, and keeps out people who might be looking for a better web. It also creates an echo chamber, and that is another pressing issue with the internet. There is also the logistics of how you could do this. I mean, in a way, Medium does this with a login and blocking of articles and that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281470</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our energetic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Argentine President Javier Milei Fires His Foreign Minister for Voting Against US’ 62-Year Blockade of Cuba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281440</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/javier-milei-fires-foreign-minister-for-opposing-us-66-year-embargo-of-cuban-economy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T10:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, like last year, the only two countries that voted against lifting the blockade were the US and Israel. But Argentina was meant to stand with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Avoid a Franken-Future with AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281457</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/can-we-avoid-a-franken-future-with-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T09:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his new book, Mindless, historian Robert Skidelsky urges readers to reflect on the delicate balance between AI and our human essence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triumph of the Swill: A Night at the Garden with Trump and MAGA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340790</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/triumph-of-the-swill-a-night-at-the-garden-with-trump-and-maga/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T06:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trumpism is capacious. It contains contradictions and absurdities. It borrows from the left and the right. An explosive mix of love and hate propels it. Anyone can afford the price of admission. They only need to embrace Trump, MAGA, and conspiracies.
MAGA was in force on a crisp Sunday afternoon outside Madison Square Garden in late October. I joined tens of thousands of faithful seeking entry to the Woodstock of fascism. The lineup featured some of the worst people in America: Elon Musk, Stephen Miller, Rudy Giuliani, Tulsi Gabbard, RFK, Jr., JD Vance, Tucker Carlson, Elise Stefanik, Trump’s progeny, C-list racists and cranks, and the Demagogue-in-Chief himself.  More
The post Triumph of the Swill: A Night at the Garden with Trump and MAGA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unheeded Warnings: Sagan, Eisenhower and the Ultimate Gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340632</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/unheeded-warnings-sagan-eisenhower-and-the-ultimate-gamble/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even a “limited” nuclear war “could cause hundreds of millions or billions of humans worldwide to starve to death,” as these crop failures combine with broader ecosystem destruction, the breakdown of human support of agricultural systems, and the collapse of food transportation and distribution infrastructure. As Khrushchev once remarked, “The living would envy the dead.” More
The post Unheeded Warnings: Sagan, Eisenhower and the Ultimate Gamble appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David S. D’Amato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dangerous Hype: Big Tech’s Nuclear Lies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340801</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/big-techs-nuclear-lies/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last couple of months, Microsoft, Google, and Amazon, in that order, made announcements about using nuclear power for their energy needs. Describing nuclear energy using questionable adjectives like “reliable,” “safe,” “clean,” and “affordable,” all of which are belied by the technology's seventy-year history, these tech behemoths were clearly interested in hyping up their environmental credentials and nuclear power, which is being kept alive mostly using public subsidies. More
The post Dangerous Hype: Big Tech’s Nuclear Lies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M.V. Ramana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post Owner Jeff Bezos Isn’t Completely Wrong About the Media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340976</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/washington-post-owner-jeff-bezos-isnt-completely-wrong-about-the-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T06:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post owner Jeff Bezos is getting his share of criticism for stopping the paper’s presidential endorsement of Vice President Kamala Harris less than two weeks before the election.  Much of the criticism is well deserved, but Bezos correctly identifies the declining credibility of the mainstream media, including his Post as well as the New York Times.  
More
The post Washington Post Owner Jeff Bezos Isn’t Completely Wrong About the Media appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on a Phony Campaign: Strange Days]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340804</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/strange-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cockburn used to say, vote for whoever makes you happy, knowing that the vote-counting machines will probably record it for someone you despise. So I filled out my ballot, though not very joyfully, and drove to the drop-off site in our little mill town, where the ballot box was being "monitored" by four MAGA people, adorned in their red hats, who, undeterred by the drenching rain, recorded my arrival on their cellphones and asked to see my ID, a request I replied to with a customary Italian gesture, as I told them had left my papers in Juarez. More
The post Notes on a Phony Campaign: Strange Days appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuremberg on the Hudson]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340967</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/nuremberg-on-the-hudson/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump American Bund decided to use Madison Square Garden to stage yet another of its Trump Reich rallies—complete with a sea of red hats, bankrupt Rudy Giuliani (taking a break from his criminal trials and liquidating his assets), and a valium-packed Melania who, when she greeted her husband on stage, had the blank look  More
The post Nuremberg on the Hudson appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The United Nations: Problems by Design, Reform by Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340971</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/the-united-nations-problems-by-design-reform-by-demand/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former United Nations Special Rapporteur on the Situation of Human Rights in the Palestinian Territories Occupied, Richard Falk, and former United Nations Assistant Secretary-General and UN Humanitarian Coordinator for Iraq, Hans von Sponeck, are the authors of Liberating the United Nations: Realism with Hope (Stanford University Press, 2024). In this question and answer with Daniel Falcone, they  More
The post The United Nations: Problems by Design, Reform by Demand appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Falk, Hans Von Sponeck and Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Extremists Have a Plan for the Day after the Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340823</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/israels-extremists-have-a-plan-for-the-day-after-the-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the slogan ‘Gaza is Ours, Forever’, a large number of Israeli extremists and right-wing politicians met in the settlement of Be’eri, near the Gaza border region, on October 20-21. The group represented the who’s who in the Israeli right, far right and ultranationalists. They included Israeli Ministers Itamar Ben-Gvir, May Golan and Bezalel Smotrich,  More
The post Israel’s Extremists Have a Plan for the Day after the Genocide  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Any Metric, the U.S. Gamble to Harm Russia by Bombing Nordstream Was a Failure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340627</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/using-any-metric-the-u-s-gamble-to-harm-russia-by-bombing-nordstream-was-a-failure/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Years have passed since president Joe Biden allegedly ordered the bombing of the Nordstream 2 pipeline, and the dust has long settled. We can now answer whether the reckless white house gamble to damage Moscow succeeded or not. The answer is definitive: it failed. But did the white house really commit this massive economic, political  More
The post Using Any Metric, the U.S. Gamble to Harm Russia by Bombing Nordstream Was a Failure appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doubling Down on ‘Too Much Heat’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340788</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/doubling-down-on-too-much-heat/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Arctic News headline d/d October 4, 2024 refers to one of the most significant climate-related studies this year. It describes in detail the worldwide all-encompassing danger of loss of sea ice: Double Blue Ocean Event, 2025? It demands attention. A casual reading of climate change literature reveals several mentions of ecosystem impairment or  More
The post Doubling Down on ‘Too Much Heat’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A No-Win Dilemma for US Peace Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340796</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/a-no-win-dilemma-for-us-peace-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 24th, a U.S. presidential candidate told an interviewer, “Our day one agenda… also includes picking up the phone and telling Bibi Netanyahu that the war is over, because it’s basically our proxy war. We control the armaments, the funding, the diplomatic cover, the intelligence, etc., so we can end this in the blink  More
The post A No-Win Dilemma for US Peace Voters  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Benjamin - Nicolas J. S. Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nuclear Cautionary Tale]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340807</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/a-nuclear-cautionary-tale/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade ago, NuScale, the Oregon-based small modular nuclear company born at Oregon State University, was on a roll. Promising a new era of nuclear reactors that were cheaper, easier to build and safer, their Star Wars-inspired artist renditions of a yet to be built reactor gleamed like a magic bullet. As of last year,  More
The post A Nuclear Cautionary Tale appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Campell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mankind’s November 5 Hubris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340695</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/mankinds-november-5-hubris/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are warned that the election of November 5 could be the end of the great American experiment, the final nail in the coffin of its democracy. It is also predicted that this could be a great inflection point in world history. But what if all the warnings and hype are wrong? What if the  More
The post Mankind’s November 5 Hubris appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing State Blues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341031</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/swing-state-blues/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twice a year, every spring and fall, Ithaca, New York hosts one of the biggest used book sales in the United States. Staffed by a legion of volunteers who work for months accepting and organizing the steady stream of donations, the event supports the Tompkins County Library and runs over three successive weekends. As the  More
The post Swing State Blues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Interview With Carla Blank, Author of “A Jew in Ramallah”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340778</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/an-interview-with-carla-blank-author-of-a-jew-in-ramallah/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ishmael Reed: I’ve been reading these jazz biographies, where aspiring jazz musicians go to a concert and they see some great performer, and they either want an instrument like the one they have, or they want to imitate them. Now, when you were a child, did you ever go to some concert where you saw  More
The post An Interview With Carla Blank, Author of “A Jew in Ramallah” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishmael Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Einstein Opposed Zionist Colonization in Palestine and Predicted the Current Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340798</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/einstein-opposed-zionist-colonization-in-palestine-and-predicted-the-current-catastrophe/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks before the creation of the State of Israel, Shepard Rifkin, executive director of the Stern Group, requested that representatives of the group meet with Albert Einstein in the United States, “the greatest Jewish figure of the time” according to I.F. Stone. Einstein’s response was unequivocal: “When a real and final catastrophe should  More
The post Einstein Opposed Zionist Colonization in Palestine and Predicted the Current Catastrophe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Philpot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Venezuelans Think About Their Presidential Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340673</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/what-venezuelans-think-about-their-presidential-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been nearly three months since the Venezuelans went to the polls on July 28, and there is still contention domestically and abroad regarding the winner of the presidential election. This is not unexpected. The US has not recognized the legitimacy of the previous two presidential elections in Venezuela and had announced way before this  More
The post What Venezuelans Think About Their Presidential Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How US Imperialism Causes Death and Destruction in Gaza and Lebanon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340672</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/how-us-imperialism-causes-death-and-destruction-in-gaza-and-lebanon/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli military’s horrendous massacres in Gaza extend now to Lebanon. Housing, schools, and hospitals are destroyed.  Residents of Northern Gaza are being herded south, again. People starve. The U.S. government supplies the bombs, planes, and weapons. The war’s continuation relates to U.S. strategic interests in the region and U.S. pretensions to world domination. War  More
The post How US Imperialism Causes Death and Destruction in Gaza and Lebanon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Countries Are on the Brink of Going Nuclear?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340916</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/which-countries-are-on-the-brink-of-going-nuclear/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following Israel’s October 26, 2024, attack on Iranian energy facilities, Iran vowed to respond with “all available tools,” sparking fears it could soon produce a nuclear weapon to pose a more credible threat. The country’s breakout time—the period required to develop a nuclear bomb—is now estimated in weeks, and Tehran could proceed with weaponization if it  More
The post Which Countries Are on the Brink of Going Nuclear? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukraine War is Lost. Three Options Remain.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340913</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/the-ukraine-war-is-lost-three-options-remain/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I started listening to George Beebe a few years ago when he was warning about tensions in Ukraine, the real risk of escalation to nuclear war and the dangers of groupthink.  Back in 2021 he assessed that Russia was likely to invade Ukraine given the combination of the US’s determination to bring the country into  More
The post The Ukraine War is Lost. Three Options Remain. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That’s Entertainment: Popular Alternatives to the Presidential Campaign Circus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340899</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/thats-entertainment-popular-alternatives-to-the-presidential-campaign-circus/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although more than 50 million Americans have already voted — by mail or in person — “Election Day” formally falls on November 5. The candidates are making their “final arguments” in the media, pulling all stops out of their efforts to get supporters to the polls, and holding big events to enthuse those voters. So,  More
The post That’s Entertainment: Popular Alternatives to the Presidential Campaign Circus appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re in Some Deep Shit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340901</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/were-in-some-deep-shit/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not since Ralph Nader’s failed third-party bid for the presidency in 2000 has the blame game garnered the megaphone attention that this year’s duopoly has. Now, Jill Stein’s Green Party campaign has focused the hyper attention of Democrats, whose own candidate Kamala Harris says just about nothing in the realm of major policy initiatives, while  More
The post We’re in Some Deep Shit appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtuous, Smug and Venal: British Electoral Interference in the US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340909</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/virtuous-smug-and-venal-british-electoral-interference-in-the-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The British cannot help themselves.  They are a meddling island people who conquered huge swathes of the earth in a fictional fit of absentmindedness and remain haughty for having done so.  They have fought more countries they can name, engaged in more wars they care to remember.  They have overthrown elected rulers and sabotaged incipient democracies.  In the twilight  More
The post Virtuous, Smug and Venal: British Electoral Interference in the US appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Rural Wisconsin, it’s Not Obvious Which Way The Wind is Blowing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340904</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/in-rural-wisconsin-its-not-obvious-which-way-the-wind-is-blowing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Subterranean Homesick Blues, according to Bob Dylan, “You don’t need a weatherman to know which way the wind blows”—- sometimes things are so obvious that anyone can figure it out. Polling and the opinions of those supposedly in the know, indicate that the rural vote will decide the 2024 presidential election. That seems to be ceding an awful lot of  More
The post In Rural Wisconsin, it’s Not Obvious Which Way The Wind is Blowing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Black Case Against Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340813</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/the-black-case-against-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump was the worst president for Black people in the modern era, if not the nation’s history. Given a life of unremitting racial animus, under no circumstances should he receive a single vote from the Black community or other communities of color. After all, he’s never moderated his white nationalist sentiments and count on  More
The post The Black Case Against Donald Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clarence Lusane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yin Yang: In My Therapeutic, Serene, Safe Space]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341017</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/yin-yang-in-my-therapeutic-serene-safe-space/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To escape from the Gaza and Lebanon 24/7 genocide news reports, since October 2023 I’ve had to find a safe and serene space in which I could drown all the misery and carnage orchestrated and perpetrated by Netanyahu and senile Genocide Joe, his criminal co-partner, his secretaries of State and Defense, AIPAC, a subservient Congress,  More
The post Yin Yang: In My Therapeutic, Serene, Safe Space appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raouf Halaby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolves Vote with Their Feet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340699</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/wolves-vote-with-their-feet/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mexican gray wolf family living west of Flagstaff, Arizona near Kendrick Peak are blissfully unaware of the proximity of election day. They know nothing of the candidates’ positions, the ballot measures, nor the flood of robocalls asking for votes. They don’t know that they are in a battleground state, or even that they are  More
The post Wolves Vote with Their Feet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Greta Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resisting Slavery, Resisting Incarceration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341035</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/resisting-slavery-resisting-incarceration/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mumia Abu Jamal is one of the world’s best-known political prisoners.  Convicted in 1982 of murdering a Philadelphia police officer in a trial filled with prosecutorial misdeeds, falsehoods and other manipulations, he remains locked up in Pennsylvania’s State Correctional Institution-Mahanoy.  Despite ongoing health issues, censorship and the repression that is part of a prison sentence,  More
The post Resisting Slavery, Resisting Incarceration appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Return of a Dangerous Idea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340620</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/the-return-of-a-dangerous-idea/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now so discredited that no one dares speak its name. When the European Union launched ‘excessive deficit procedures’ against seven countries in June, demanding they take corrective action or face sanctions, the commissioner for economy Paolo Gentiloni insisted it had nothing to do with austerity. True, he conceded, Brussels was demanding the affected countries  More
The post The Return of a Dangerous Idea appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benoît Bréville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Trauma of Wild Animals: the Case of the Marmots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340676</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/01/on-the-trauma-of-wild-animals-the-case-of-the-marmots/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T05:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marmots were the perfect test species for a wildlife adversity index. Photo: Xochitl Ortiz Ross Psychologists know that childhood trauma, or the experience of harmful or adverse events, can have lasting repercussions on the health and well-being of people well into adulthood. But while the consequences of early adversity have been well researched in humans,  More
The post On the Trauma of Wild Animals: the Case of the Marmots appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xochitl Ortiz Ross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rewrite it in Rails]]></title>
        <id>https://dirkjonker.bearblog.dev/rewrite-it-in-rails/</id>
        <link href="https://dirkjonker.bearblog.dev/rewrite-it-in-rails/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T00:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022 I started building an application for creating Customs declarations. After evaluating some options and writing code in various programming languages and frameworks such as .NET/F#, Go, Rust, React, I eventually decided to write it in Ruby on Rails. Why? Because I was already familiar with Rails and because of that I could literally go 10x faster than I was with any of the aforementioned options that were quite new to me. I told myself that this was temporary, a proof of concept and that later on, I would rewrite it in a different language that wouldn't let me shoot myself in the foot as easily as I tend to do with Ruby. The Rails application however quickly grew in functionality and my colleagues really liked the application. I could quickly build features that would make them more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the potential of your supply chain data and gain actionable insights with AWS Supply Chain Analytics]]></title>
        <id>a767362e3e67b3fb251325f0bb3704f075366139</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/unlock-the-potential-of-your-supply-chain-data-and-gain-actionable-insights-with-aws-supply-chain-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T21:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uncover hidden insights with AWS Supply Chain Analytics, powered by Amazon QuickSight, enabling custom reporting and data visualization for smarter supply chain management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American bloggers, personal website publishers, may be among ‘enemies within’]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8771</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/american-bloggers-personal-website-publishers-possible-enemy-within/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T21:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American newspapers The Los Angeles Times, and The Washington Post, have come under fire for declining to endorse US Presidential candidate Kamala Harris. Their refusal to endorse Harris does not, however, from stem from a desire to back Donald Trump. Rather, both publications had prepared endorsements for Harris, but were blocked from publishing them by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whizzter in "ChatGPT Search"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42010739</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42010739"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T19:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is probably Google's Altavista moment, by making their results crappier by the year in search of Ad dollars everyone has felt that there is a potential for search to be better and once that becomes available they'll be in a continious game of catch-up.
Yes, Google has their own AI divisions, tons of money and SEO is to blame for part of their crappiness. But they've also _explicitly_ focused on ad-dollars over algorithmic purity if one is to believe the reports of their internal politics and if those are true they have probably lost a ton of people who they'd need right now to turn the ship around quickly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whizzter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new AWS CDK L2 construct for Amazon CloudFront Origin Access Control (OAC)]]></title>
        <id>256bac6df5ca4bba45172b78bdaefb354e029eff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/a-new-aws-cdk-l2-construct-for-amazon-cloudfront-origin-access-control-oac/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T18:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, we launched a new AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) L2 construct for Amazon CloudFront Origin Access Control (OAC). This construct simplifies the configuration and maintenance of securing Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) CloudFront origins with CDK. Launched in 2022, OAC is the recommended way to secure your CloudFront distributions due to additional security features compared […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh DeMuth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by freediver in "ChatGPT Search"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42010013</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42010013"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T18:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Been thinking about this a lot [1]. Will this fundamentally change how people find and access information? How do you create an experience so compelling that it replaces the current paradigm?
The future promised in Star Trek and even Apple's Knowledge Navigator [2] from 1987 still feels distant. In those visions, users simply asked questions and received reliable answers - nobody had to fact-check the answers ever.
Combining two broken systems - compromised search engines and unreliable LLMs - seems unlikely to yield that vision. Legacy, ad-based search, has devolved into a wasteland of misaligned incentives, conflict of interest and prolifirated the web full of content farms optimized for ads and algos instead of humans.
Path forward requires solving the core challenge: actually surfacing the content people want to see, not what intermiediaries want them to see - which means a different business model in seach, where there are no intermediaries. I do not see a way around this. Advancing models without advancing search is like having a michelin star chef work with spoiled ingredients.
I am cautiously optimistic we will eventually get there, but boy, we will need a fundamentally different setup in terms of incentives involved in information consumption, both in tech and society.
[1] https://blog.kagi.com/age-pagerank-over
[2] https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=umJsITGzXd0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freediver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/31/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281420</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-31-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T18:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~  Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Trump garbage truck stunt; Section Three has risen from the grave; Boeing stock remains stable, pensions are the sticking point ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central bank independence — a convenient illusion]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45697</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/31/central-bank-independence-a-convenient-illusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Today’s model of delegation has much to recommend it. But it should not be cloaked in euphemism. It is an abrogation of democratic sovereignty for pragmatic reasons, conditioned on the one hand by deeply entrenched and unflattering assumptions about electoral politics and, on the other, on an unquestioning acceptance of the private […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL Limitless Database is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>796bde085627d26f498ba44e8e4ff6e852668f0f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-aurora-postgresql-limitless-database-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T17:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurora PostgreSQL Limitless enables massive horizontal scaling for write throughput and storage by distributing workloads across multiple Aurora instances while using standard PostgreSQL queries and syntax.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attentive Blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/attentive-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/attentive-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T16:20:36.128Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the post The Art of Noticing, Andy Hawthorne writes about the importance of paying attention when it comes to photography. He describes how his alertness allowed him to capture an interesting and beautiful photo.
In his text, Andy also quotes the photographer Elliot Erwitt:
All the technique in the world doesn’t compensate for an inability to notice.
Wise and true words, which also apply to writing.
When we get hooked on something we're reading, it's often the author's "art of noticing" that draws us into the story. A character portrait, a setting, a situation. A sense of attention to details that transports the reader to that exact moment.
As bloggers, we have everything to gain by sharpening our attention. Every day, no matter how ordinary, is full of ingredients for exciting blog posts. By looking up and listening closely, we can easily contribute to every blog challenge that comes our way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;With the Grain&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/with-the-grain</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/with-the-grain"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T15:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Restoration in Thamesmead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workers Builds: integrated CI/CD built on the Workers platform]]></title>
        <id>6uKjGQLUKCb33wGIcOQE1Y</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-builds-integrated-ci-cd-built-on-the-workers-platform"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers Builds, an integrated CI/CD pipeline for the Workers platform, recently launched in open beta. We walk through how we built this product on Cloudflare’s Developer Platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serena Shah-Simpson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Baselime from AWS to Cloudflare: simpler architecture, improved performance, over 80% lower cloud costs]]></title>
        <id>6heSTMT0I5jl0vpeR9TucD</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/80-percent-lower-cloud-cost-how-baselime-moved-from-aws-to-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post-acquisition, we migrated Baselime from AWS to the Cloudflare Developer Platform and in the process, we improved query times, simplified data ingestion, and now handle far more events, all while cutting costs. Here’s how we built a modern, high-performing observability platform on Cloudflare’s network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Tane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What happens if Americans claim asylum from a Trump regime?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53337</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/31/what-happens-if-americans-claim-asylum-from-a-trump-regime/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T11:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump has made very public threats to persecute his political opponents should he be re-elected and statements by him and by other leading Republicans suggests that he might persecute others on the grounds of their religion or their membership of certain social groups. If this were happen (rather than simply being bluster) then it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On a Clean Slate]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/on-a-clean-slate/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/on-a-clean-slate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the idea of a clean slate. Long time readers of my blogs will know this because I’ve deleted all my posts in search of a clean slate dozens of times. I always get the itch around the New Year or my birthday to start fresh and to have my blog reflect the most recent version of myself. So, I try and throw everything away so that I can rebuild from scratch.
After a couple of decades of starting a with a “clean slate” online and in my personal life, I’ve come to realize that there is no such thing. A clean slate doesn’t truly exist.
In order to have a clean slate, you would need to erase everything that came before. Sure, I can delete the blogs so the public does not see them, but I still wrote them. I still allowed these ideas and concepts to flow from my brain to my hands and manifest…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python #1 on Github + speedup via Codon / Cython]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/python-1-on-github-speedup-via-codon-cython/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/python-1-on-github-speedup-via-codon-cython/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T00:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Recently there's a report from Github on the rise of snake language to be the top on Github. Yes, Python overtakes Javascript!

Below is a nice time series graph showing language progression over time:

Inspired by this achievement, I once again write how to speedup Python to almost near C/C++ speed! The tools we are using: Codon and Cython to speedup integrate calculation in Python.
Python code
First lets take a look at the original python code.
def f(x):
    return x ** 2 - x

def integrate_f(a, b, N):
    s = 0
    dx = (b - a) / N
    for i in range(N):
        s += f(a + i * dx)
    return s * dx

Fairly simple and straightforward.
Codon code
Now here's the Codon version:
def f(x: float) -> float:
    return x ** 2 - x

def integrate_f(a: float, b: float, N: int) -> float…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asdfman123 in "Google CEO says more than a quarter of the company's new code is created by AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42002212</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42002212"/>
        <updated>2024-10-31T00:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work for Google, and I just got done with my work day. I was just writing I guess what you'd call "AI generated code."
But the code completion engine is basically just good at finishing the lines I'm writing. If I'm writing "function getAc..." it's smart enough to complete to "function getActionHandler()", and maybe suggest the correct arguments and a decent jsdoc comment.
So basically, it's a helpful productivity tool but it's not doing any engineering at all. It's probably about as good, maybe slightly worse, than Copilot. (I haven't used it recently though.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asdfman123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yreg in "Steam games will need to disclose kernel-level anti-cheat on store pages"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42001633</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42001633"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T23:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've just reinstalled GTA V last week and I was very surprised to find out that I now have to install a rootkit to run it.
They had the balls to add a mandatory kernel extension into a game that I've bought 10 years ago and that I wish to play in single player only.
I find it utterly ridiculous. As usual, piracy would have been the superior experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yreg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending October 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241030</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241030"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If voting in the US election, Australians would elect Kamala Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8764</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/us-election-australians-elect-kamala-harris/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent poll of voters in Australia and New Zealand has found most would prefer Democrat candidate Kamala Harris to win the upcoming American Presidential election, over her Republican rival Donald Trump: “Fifty per cent of Australians say they’d vote for Harris compared to 26 per cent who say they’d vote for Trump,” says David […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dmz73 in "M4 MacBook Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42000130</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42000130"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T20:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mac OS calls home every time you execute an application. 
Apple is well on its way to ensure you can only run things they allow via app store, they would probably already be there if it wasn't for the pesky EU.
If you send your computer/phone to Apple for repair you may get back different physical hardware.
Those things very much highlight that "your" Apple hardware is not yours and that privacy on Apple hardware does not actually exist, sure they may not share that data with other parties but they definitely do not respect your privacy or act like you own the hardware you purchased.
Apple marketing seems to have reached the level indoctrination where everyone just keeps parroting what Apple says as an absolute truth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dmz73</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lukev in "M4 MacBook Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999793</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999793"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T20:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really respect Apple's privacy focused engineering. They didn't roll out _any_ AI features until they were capable of running them locally, and before doing any cloud-based AI they designed and rolled out Private Cloud Compute.
You can argue about whether it's actually bulletproof or not but the fact is, nobody else is even trying, and have lost sight of all privacy-focused features in their rush to ship anything and everything on my device to OpenAI or Gemini.
I am thrilled to shell out thousands and thousands of dollars to purchase a machine that feels like it really belongs to me, from a company that respects my data and has aligned incentives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lukev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by skrebbel in "Google CEO says more than a quarter of the company's new code is created by AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999727</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999727"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T20:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To my experience, AIs can generate perfectly good code relatively easy things, the kind you might as well copy&paste from stackoverflow, and they'll very confidently generate subtly wrong code for anything that's non-trivial for an experienced programmer to write. How do people deal with this? I simply don't understand the value proposition. Does Google now have 25% subtly wrong code? Or do they have 25% trivial code? Or do all their engineers babysit the AI and bugfix the subtly wrong code? Or are all their engineers so junior that an AI is such a substantial help?
Like, isn't this announcement a terrible indictment of how inexperienced their engineers are, or how trivial the problems they solve are, or both?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skrebbel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwaway48476 in "Steam games will need to disclose kernel-level anti-cheat on store pages"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999692</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999692"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T20:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the crowdstrike disaster 3rd party kernel drivers need to be shunned for non critical applications.
Games publishers have been bad actors in this space for a long time now. The genshin impact anticheat was used in a malware campaign. Rockstar was very misleading trying to imply their kernel driver not being compatible with the steam deck was valves fault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway48476</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by uniformlyrandom in "Google’s TOS doesn’t eliminate a user’s Fourth Amendment rights, judge rules [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999255</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41999255"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T19:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Google’s hash match may well have established probable cause for a warrant to allow police to conduct a visual examination of the Maher file.
Very reasonable. Google can flag accounts as CP, but then a judge still needs to issue a warrant for the police to actually go and look at the file. Good job court. Extra points for reasoning about hash values.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>uniformlyrandom</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Wirklich, ich lebe in finsteren Zeiten!”, some random thoughts on our responsibility as intellectuals / poets / writers / researchers / teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53329</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/30/wirklich-ich-lebe-in-finsteren-zeiten-some-random-thoughts-on-our-responsibility-as-intellectuals-poets-writers-researchers-teachers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T18:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We live in an age which silence is not only criminal but suicidal”, wrote James Baldwin in his “Open Letter to My Sister, Angela Y. Davis”. The year was 1970. I wonder if there has ever been a time when silence was neither criminal nor suicidal. I would like to live there and then, for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Macarena Marey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify and enhance Amazon S3 static website hosting with AWS Amplify Hosting]]></title>
        <id>ccdba42ff38124d2621c7b1dee7250dda057dd2d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-and-enhance-amazon-s3-static-website-hosting-with-aws-amplify/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy static sites with streamlined configuration, custom domains, SSL, CDN, and one-click updates using Amazon S3 with AWS Amplify Hosting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by carlgreene in "M4 MacBook Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41996119</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41996119"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s amazing is that in the past I’ve felt the need to upgrade within a few years.
New video format or more demanding music software is released that slows the machine down, or battery life craters.
Well, I haven’t had even a tinge of feeling that I need to upgrade after getting my M1 Pro MBP. I can’t remember it ever skipping a beat running a serious Ableton project, or editing in Resolve.
Can stuff be faster? Technically of course. But this is the first machine that even after several years I’ve not caught myself once wishing that it was faster or had more RAM. Not once.
Perhaps it’s my age, or perhaps it’s just the architecture of these new Mac chips are just so damn good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>carlgreene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gxonatano in "Jaywalking legalized in New York City"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41995957</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41995957"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's not forget that jaywalking was essentially created by the automotive industry and its lobbyists, to make life more convenient for drivers. It started in car-heavy places like California, and eventually became a law virtually everywhere in the US, but was never really enforced in New York City, where most people walk or take public transit, rather than drive. If, like most New Yorkers, you walk several kilometers a day, through dozens of intersections, it's ludicrous to suggest that you should only walk at crosswalks, and only when the walk sign is lit. New Yorkers don't have a concept of "jaywalking"; it's just "walking."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gxonatano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia conducts large-scale nuke drills + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/russia-conducts-large-scale-nuke-drills-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/russia-conducts-large-scale-nuke-drills-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel bans UNRWA operations, threatening aid; Putin conducts nuclear drills simulating attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jcmontx in "M4 MacBook Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41995823</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41995823"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "up to 1.8x faster when compared to the 16-inch MacBook Pro with M1 Pro"
I insist my 2020 Macbook M1 was the best purchase I ever made]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jcmontx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 2 | A global overview of political, social and economic situations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-2-A-global-overview-of-political-social-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-2-A-global-overview-of-political-social-and"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday, October 8, 2024, marked the second day of the CADTM network's international council. On the agenda: the political, economic and social situation, and the state of struggles in sub-Saharan Africa, the Middle East and North Africa, South Asia and Latin America. Sub-Saharan Africa: Mali, Niger, Burkina Faso, the new deal 
English

/ 
Latin America, 
Africa, 
Illegitimate debt, 
South Asia, 
North Africa and the Middle East, 
South, 
CI 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Broulaye Bagayoko, CADTM International, Maxime Perriot, Omar Aziki, Sushovan Dhar, Veronica Carrillo Ortega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy F. Walton: &ldquo;Tangled Legacy&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/tangled-legacy</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/tangled-legacy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fethullah Gülen (1941-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: On Maintaining Streaks]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/re-on-maintaining-streaks/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/re-on-maintaining-streaks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About six weeks ago, I opened up a Duolingo account. I don’t have a great desire to become bilingual, but I’ve read about all the benefits of learning a new a language and I figured, what the heck. I started with Latin, which I was enjoying, but decided I should switch to something a bit more practical. Being in the United States, Spanish was the logical choice, and so I moved my lessons over to Spanish.
Every day, I take three or four minutes to do my little challenges. It’s been a fun little distraction, but one that occasionally irritates me. For example, I’ve mistyped and lost hearts, which of course, prompts the app to sell me a membership, something I’m not interested in at this time. I don’t allow many notifications from apps on my phone, so Duolingo sends me emails to remind me to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning From The Inside Out]]></title>
        <id>https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/learning-from-the-inside-out/</id>
        <link href="https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/learning-from-the-inside-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve come to realize that education works best when it’s built around the learner. Not just teaching someone information but lighting a fire in them to seek out knowledge on their own.
That’s when it all changes. When students are genuinely curious, and they’re allowed the freedom to explore that curiosity, they become teachers to themselves.
They’re learning not because they have to but because they want to. That inner motivation is what takes learning beyond just facts and assignments—it makes it something exciting and meaningful.

But how do we actually make this shift? I’ve been thinking a lot about that, especially when I look back on how much public schooling is still rooted in traditional “chalk and talk” methods. A teacher at the front, lecturing while students sit passively—it has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Lasts Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/nothing-lasts-forever/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/nothing-lasts-forever/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the central tenets of Buddhism is that everything is decaying. Eventually, everything falls apart. One just has to buy a home to see the truth in this. Trust me. Today, lots of people were disappointed that a well-liked Internet service, Omnivore, which allowed you to save articles to read later, subscribe to newsletters without using your personal email, and have some articles automatically archived, was turning off its servers on November 15. Some folks had just transitioned to using Omnivore, only to find that their efforts were now wasted. It was my favorite way to read a couple of my favorite writers, so I had to scramble to come up with an alternative.
People have seen it happen time and again. Huge, popular websites and companies have just disappeared or changed so completely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time to Put an End to World Bank Impunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Time-to-Put-an-End-to-World-Bank-Impunity</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Time-to-Put-an-End-to-World-Bank-Impunity"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T08:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
World Bank, 
Illegitimate debt, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ntulpule in "Google CEO says more than a quarter of the company's new code is created by AI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41992028</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41992028"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T04:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I lead the teams responsible for our internal developer tools, including AI features. We work very closely with Google DeepMind to adapt Gemini models for Google-scale coding and other Software Engineering usecases. Google has a unique, massive monorepo which poses a lot of fun challenges when it comes to deploying AI capabilities at scale.
1. We take a lot of care to make sure the AI recommendations are safe and have a high quality bar (regular monitoring, code provenance tracking, adversarial testing, and more).
2. We also do regular A/B tests and randomized control trials to ensure these features are improving SWE productivity and throughput.
3. We see similar efficiencies across all programming languages and frameworks used internally at Google and engineers across all tenure and experience cohorts show similar gain in productivity.
You can read more on our approach here:
https://research.google/blog/ai-in-software-engineering-at-g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ntulpule</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[to play a game]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/to-play-a-game/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/to-play-a-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T03:43:16.090Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[lately, i've been reflecting on how i feel about video games... i mean, alright, i already do that a lot. my relationship with games has been messy and strained for a long time. but, i found myself wondering if i liked the idea of playing games more than actually playing them.
back on cohost, i wrote occasionally about my game design preferences. it's a little nervewracking for me to open up about it, admittedly. a lot of game enthusiast mindsets revolve around "the harder the game, the better" as a general philosophy. how people interpret or iterate on that philosophy can differ greatly, but no matter what, the general concept of "challenge" dominates game design discussions.
but honestly... it bores me to think of games that way. i can see why people feel compelled by difficult, skill-de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s perspective of the October 30 OVHcloud outage]]></title>
        <id>Vn5VV2dLkJbOn1YNqSSBv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-perspective-of-the-october-30-2024-ovhcloud-outage"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 30, 2024, cloud hosting provider OVHcloud (AS16276) suffered a brief but significant outage. Within this post, we review Cloudflare’s perspective on this outage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryton Herdes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marianne Enckell - Ronald Creagh, an appreciation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marianne-enckell-ronald-creagh-an-appreciation?v=1730240392</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marianne-enckell-ronald-creagh-an-appreciation?v=1730240392"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Marianne Enckell
Title: Ronald Creagh, an appreciation
Date: 2024
Notes: Scanned from original.
Source: Anarchist Studies 32.1 (2024)

 An ‘inimitable singularity’: this is how Ronald Creagh described the American utopian communities he studied for his doctoral thesis. [1] But Ronald himself was also an inimitable singularity. 
 A cosmopolitan by family and culture, with British, Italian, Egyptian roots, he had studied in France and written his MA on the free thought periodicals in nineteenth century North America – after having been a priest for many years. He then turned towards the early anarchist movement; this led him to visit the CIRA library (Centre international de recherches sur l’anarchisme) in Lausanne, in the early ’70s. My mother, who was in charge at that time, sugges…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Clark - Ronald Creagh (1929-2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-clark-ronald-creagh-1929-2023?v=1730239852</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-clark-ronald-creagh-1929-2023?v=1730239852"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Clark
Title: Ronald Creagh (1929-2023)
Date: 2024
Notes: Scanned from original
Source: Anarchist Studies 32.1 (2024)

 Ronald Creagh took great satisfaction from the fact that he was born in Alexandria, Egypt, a historic city that was the centre of ancient learning. He grew up in a multicultural milieu in Port Said, Egypt. He was the offspring of a British-Sicilian father and a Franco-Lebanese mother and was taught Sicilian by his paternal grandmother. He said that Sicilian was his first language. 
 In 1947, his family migrated to Australia, while Ronald moved to France to become a Roman Catholic priest. He took a degree in sociology at the Sorbonne, a masters’ degree at the École Pratique des Hautes Études, and then taught at the Institute of Human Sciences and Techniques and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0xFACEFEED in "GitHub cuts AI deals with Google, Anthropic"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989925</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989925"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a programmer of over 20 years - this is terrifying.
I'm willing to accept that I just have "get off my lawn" syndrome or something.
But the idea of letting an LLM write/move large swaths of code seems so incredibly irresponsible. Whenever I sit down to write some code, be it a large implementation or a small function, I think about what other people (or future versions of myself) will struggle with when interacting with the code. Is it clear and concise? Is it too clever? Is it too easy to write a subtle bug when making changes? Have I made it totally clear that X is relying on Y dangerous behavior by adding a comment or intentionally making it visible in some other way?
It goes the other way too. If I know someone well (or their style) then it makes evaluating their code easier. The more time I spend in a codebase the better idea I have of what the writer was trying to do. I remember spending a lot of time reading the early Redis codebase and got a pretty good sense of how Salvatore thinks. Or altering my approaches to code reviews depending on which coworker was submitting it. These weren't things I were doing out of desire but because all non-trivial code has so much subtlety; it's just the nature of the beast.
So the thought of opening up a codebase that was cobbled together by an AI is just scary to me. Subtle bugs and errors would be equally distributed across the whole thing instead of where the writer was less competent (as is often the case). The whole thing just sounds like a gargantuan mess.
Change my mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0xFACEFEED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifth Estate Collective - Remembering Ronald Creagh]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fifth-estate-collective-remembering-ronald-creagh?v=1730239379</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fifth-estate-collective-remembering-ronald-creagh?v=1730239379"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fifth Estate Collective
Title: Remembering Ronald Creagh
Date: 2023, Fall
Notes: Accessed October 21, 2024 at https://www.fifthestate.org/archive/414-fall-2023/remembering-ronald-creagh/
Source: Fifth Estate #414, Fall 2023

 Longtime French anarchist scholar and activist Ronald Creagh died on September 8 at age 94. 
 He was in touch with anarchists and anti-authoritarians on several continents. Those who knew him personally appreciated his broad-minded openness and supportive spirit. 
 Some Fifth Estate staffers were among those who found him engaging and attentive in conversations on many subjects. In recent years he was a regular reader of our online current and past articles and enjoyed discussing them. 
 Ronald was born in Egypt in 1929, the son of a Lebanese mother and an Eng…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by onlyrealcuzzo in "OpenAI builds first chip with Broadcom and TSMC, scales back foundry ambition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989707</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989707"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As anyone with 2 brain cells should have.
You don't just acquire $7T.
The ENTIRE US domestic Net Investment isn't even $1T: https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/W790RC1Q027SBEA
Gross Fixed Capital Formation (Net Investment + Deprecation) isn't much more: https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/NFIRSAXDCUSQ
Google, Apple, and Microsoft together don't even spend $100B on CapEx per year. And they're worth almost $10T put together.
Asking for $7T when you're a $100B company is so ridiculous it's beyond belief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>onlyrealcuzzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "OpenAI builds first chip with Broadcom and TSMC, scales back foundry ambition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989594</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989594"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> OpenAI considered building everything in-house and raising capital for an expensive plan to build a network of factories known as "foundries" for chip manufacturing. The company has dropped the ambitious foundry plans for now due to the costs and time needed to build a network
That framing massively undersells how insane Sams ambitions were there, he was floating the idea of somehow raising seven trillion dollars to build thirty six fabs dedicated to making AI silicon. The TSMC execs reported more or less laughed in his face when he brought it up it them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Libertario editorial collective - Neither Chavez nor Carmona: Self-management is the way]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/el-libertario-collective-neither-chavez-nor-carmona-self-management-is-the-way?v=1730236456</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/el-libertario-collective-neither-chavez-nor-carmona-self-management-is-the-way?v=1730236456"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: El Libertario editorial collective
Title: Neither Chavez nor Carmona: Self-management is the way
Date: April 21, 2002
Source: Retrieved on October 24, 2024 from https://www.nodo50.org/ellibertario/descargas/folleto-abril-02.txt

 Given the political crisis that Venezuela is going through and that was manifested in the events before, during and after April 11, we anarchists consider it necessary to state our position. In this regard, therefore: 
 1) Hugo Chavez's contradictory policies have not benefited the most disadvantaged sectors of the country, increasing in three years of management the rates of poverty, unemployment and social insecurity. In addition, his government repeats errors and vices characteristic of previous ones. But in no way do the sectors of the current oppositi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Barnard - Primitive communism and mutual aid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/primitive-communism-and-mutual-aid?v=1730236264</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/primitive-communism-and-mutual-aid?v=1730236264"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alan Barnard
Title: Primitive communism and mutual aid
Subtitle: Kropotkin visits the Bushmen
Date: December 17, 1992
Source: Socialism (ASA Monographs); Ideals, Ideologies and Local Practice. Chris M. Hann (editor). <routledge.com/Socialism-Ideals-Ideologies-and-Local-Practice/Hann/p/book/9780415083225>

 But still we know that when the Europeans came, the Bushmen lived in small tribes (or clans), sometimes federated together; that they used to hunt in common, and divided the spoil without quarrelling; that they never abandoned their wounded, and displayed strong affection to their comrades. 
 Peter Kropotkin (1987a [1902]:83) 
 Concepts such as ‘anarchist’, ‘communist’, ‘socialist’, and even ‘Bushman’, are artificially constructed. This does not mean that they have no meaning. On…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nohara Shirõ - Anarchists and the May 4 Movement in China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nohara-shiro-anarchists-and-the-may-4-movement-in-china?v=1730236095</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nohara-shiro-anarchists-and-the-may-4-movement-in-china?v=1730236095"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nohara Shirõ
Title: Anarchists and the May 4 Movement in China
Date: January 1975
Notes: Translated by Philip Billingsley.
Source: Momoyama Gakuin University Library, Japan: <stars.repo.nii.ac.jp/record/7177/files/KJ00004276158.pdf> & <libcom.org/library/anarchists-may-4-movement-china>

Translator’s Note
 Until the post-Cultural Revolution thaw that began in 1979, Chinese readers found it next to impossible to gain access to information about the strong anarchist influence within their country’s revolutionary movement. From the point of view of the ruling Communist Party, in whose favour historical materials were invariably rewritten, this was a necessity borne out by the fact that, when people took to the streets in 1989 to demand a degree of control over their own lives, among t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr Big police stings: true crime that reads like crime fiction]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8755</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mr-big-police-stings-true-crime-fiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A police method of prosecuting people suspected of being responsible for committing a serious crime, almost reads like something from a crime novel: Police manufacture a chance meeting with the suspect, then offer them paid work of a non-criminal nature before introducing jobs that appear to break the law. Through a series of interactions over […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When you miss the moment, watching it pass…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8757</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/when-you-miss-the-moment-watching-it-pass/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time 30 October once fell on a Saturday. The stop here had been unintentional. Unplanned. But that’s how it is for a lot of these stories. I hadn’t been to this place before, yet here I was. At ten minutes to midnight. It would be Sunday in eleven minutes. Not twenty minutes earlier, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thih9 in "GitHub cuts AI deals with Google, Anthropic"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41988665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41988665"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use cursor and its tab completion; while what it can do is mind blowing, in practice I’m not noticing a productivity boost.
I find that ai can help significantly with doing plumbing, but it has no problems with connecting the pipes wrong. I need to double and triple check the updated code - or fix the resulting errors when I don’t do that. So: boilerplate and outer app layers, yes; architecture and core libraries, no.
Curious, is that a property of all ai assisted tools for now? Or would copilot, perhaps with its new models, offer a different experience?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thih9</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Semantic Versioning to Simplify Release Management]]></title>
        <id>d6504957efc7f48d4d5fdb9ca03252f8f24e605b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/using-semantic-versioning-to-simplify-release-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any organization that manages software libraries and applications needs a standardized way to catalog, reference, import, fix bugs and update the versions of those libraries and applications. Semantic Versioning enables developers, testers, and project managers to have a more standardized process for committing code and managing different versions. It’s benefits also extend beyond development teams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Kindred</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage Amazon Q Developer and AWS Chatbot within Slack]]></title>
        <id>348872cb14a26271b8eae4c0424f149ec4aace0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/leverage-amazon-q-developer-and-aws-chatbot-within-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Amazon Q Developer and its ability to be integrated into AWS Chatbot allows users who use Microsoft Teams or Slack to stay within their communication platform and interact with a conversational generative artificial intelligence (AI) AWS expert. Amazon Q Developer is a conversational generative AI chatbot that provides AWS assistance in the form of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_95</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_95"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code October 2024 Release (1.95)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless ML: Lessons from Capital One]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b262f848e25</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/serverless-ml-lessons-from-capital-one-4b262f848e25?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for migrating an ML model to serverless for scalability and manageability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Impressions: Lamy Safari and Midori Notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/first-impressions-lamy-safari-and-midori-notebook/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/first-impressions-lamy-safari-and-midori-notebook/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought a Lamy Safari, my first fountain pen, a couple of weeks ago. I tend to get obsessed over things when I first get into them, and thus end up in an endless rabbit hole of research. I knew this would happen.
I go back and forth between purely taking digital notes for work and using pen and paper. For the past few years, I’ve switched to digital note taking because it’s easier to cmd + f to find what I’m looking for. However, with the constant game of musical chairs that is my dual-laptop setup for work, I end up using different applications for notes and, in turn, losing them anyway1.
And so, armed with this new pen I wanted to practice writing with, I decided to switch back to pen-and-paper mode, and back to the work notebook I’ve used on and off since 2017 2.
This is where I ran in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Deeper into Projen: Exploring Advanced Features]]></title>
        <id>a94bc5a3754a86fa5518650bbc94d6f15d679528</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/diving-deeper-into-projen-exploring-advanced-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will be highlighting Projen’s powerful features that cater to various aspects of project management and development. We’ll examine how Projen enhances polyglot programming within Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud Development Kit constructs. We’ll also touch on its built-in support for common development tools and practices. In our previous blog, we introduced you to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating billions of records: moving our active DNS database while it’s in use]]></title>
        <id>24rozMdbFQ7jmUgRNMF4RU</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/migrating-billions-of-records-moving-our-active-dns-database-while-in-use"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DNS records have moved to a new database, bringing improved performance and reliability to all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Fattouche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the next-level of AI-powered workflows with Amazon Q Developer inline chat]]></title>
        <id>009a040a805940f8fc8938b162d51952a92ec7fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-inline-chat/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, Amazon Q Developer announced support for inline chat. Inline chat combines the benefits of in-IDE chat with the ability to directly update code, allowing developers to describe issues or ideas directly in the code editor, and receive AI-generated responses that are seamlessly integrated into their codebase. In this post, I will introduce the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Yapur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forced offline: the Q3 2024 Internet disruption summary]]></title>
        <id>3xoUhxvPcDFTiYCT9CjHhs</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/q3-2024-internet-disruption-summary"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third quarter of 2024 was particularly active, with quite a few significant Internet disruptions. Underlying causes included government-directed shutdowns, power outages, hurricane damage, terrestrial and submarine cable cuts, military action, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by addicted in "Steve Ballmer was an underrated CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978723</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978723"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T02:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article doesn’t understand what was fundamentally wrong with Ballmer’s leadership and what Nadella actually changed.
The specific technologies that were successful is irrelevant. Microsoft has and continues to invest in nearly every computer related technology that may come around the corner or they got late on.
The problem with Microsoft was everything went through Windows. The entire company was designed to promote Windows.
This was the fundamental flaw with Microsoft that Nadella changed. He quickly not just made Windows just another part of Microsoft’s business, to a great extent he actively devalued it.
The fact that Ballmer invested in Azure, etc before Nadella would all be irrelevant because under Ballmer Azure would have remained a red headed step child to Windows, so it’s unlikely to have seen much success under him anyways. Same goes for pretty much everything else Microsoft is doing right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>addicted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by not_a_bot_4sho in "Steve Ballmer was an underrated CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978402"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T01:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Funny story. I used to see Steve almost every weekday for a couple of years.
I can't speak to his business skills, but I can attest that he never once offered a tip for his daily black iced tea. We'd even have it ready for him before he showed up so he never had to wait! He would pay with cash, and I'd hand him his change and drink, and that was that.
It's funny to me now: one of the richest men in the world and he never once offered a tip.
Frugality aside, he was always very polite and warm so I can't be mad. Makes for a good ice breaker story.
Edit: holy moly, this is a sensitive subject. Please remember this was from a time before tipflation. Tipping meant you left your change behind once in a while only if you felt the desire to show appreciation. It wasn't an obligation. Yes, I still do think it's a funny story. Roast me for being entitled lol]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>not_a_bot_4sho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post cancellations]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53321</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/29/washington-post-cancellations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T00:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until last Friday, I subscribed to two newspapers: the Washington Post and the Neue Zürcher Zeitung. As of Friday, I only subscribe to NZZ. I shared my cancellation on Facebook and was surprised by how many people in my network commented that they had done the same. This included people who almost never comment or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eszter Hargittai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 1st1 in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977945</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977945"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T00:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> How large is the Flutter team, today? Google doesn't publish this information, but my guess is that the team is about 50 people strong.
> That's 50 people serving the needs of 1,000,000. Doing a little bit of division, that means that every single member of the Flutter team is responsible for the needs of 20,000 Flutter developers! That ratio is clearly unworkable for any semblance of customer support.
This is a weird exercise. Python, for example, is a #1/#2 language in the world and there's only 50 active core devs, 90% of which don't even work on Python full time. Somehow we make that work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>1st1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by deergomoo in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41976613</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41976613"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Most people don't realize how many apps written in Flutter they use daily, simply because it's impossible to tell
You can't be serious. Maybe on Android, but on other platforms—especially iOS—they stick out like a sore thumb.
A number of them just look like Material Design Android apps awkwardly transplanted over, but I know that's down to the developer so I won't hold that against Flutter. But scrolling through the Flutter showcase[0] and calling those apps up to look at screenshots on the App Store—none of them look like native iOS apps. They don't look bad (mostly), but they don't fit in.
Don't get me wrong, I don't expect anyone else to care or even notice. But for those of us that do care, you can absolutely tell.
[0] https://flutter.dev/showcase]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deergomoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 economic laureates and more Nobel nonsense]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45693</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/28/the-2024-economic-laureates-and-more-nobel-nonsense/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Steven Klees I am quite sure that this year’s three Nobel Laureates in economics — Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson – are very competent new institutionalist economists.  Lars Syll offers a thoughtful critique of their substantive arguments, but he misses the main point for me.  New institutional economics, by and large, is nonsense.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From thousands to millions: the film budgets of Stanley Kubrick]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8750</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/thousands-millions-film-budgets-stanley-kubrick/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late American filmmaker Stanley Kubrick made his first feature, Fear and Desire, on a budget of a little over fifty-thousand dollars (US), in 1952. Almost thirty-years later, Kubrick had a budget of nineteen million dollars to make The Shining. I expect many successful filmmakers move along a similar budget trajectory. But it sounds like Kubrick […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by plorkyeran in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975288</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975288"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> That's 50 people serving the needs of 1,000,000. Doing a little bit of division, that means that every single member of the Flutter team is responsible for the needs of 20,000 Flutter developers! That ratio is clearly unworkable for any semblance of customer support.
If "only" 50 people working on a project used by one million people was unworkably low then every single successful project out there would be doomed. I've certainly worked on things with much worse ratios than that.
> one has to critically assess why a team that loves external contributions has only managed to merge contributions from 1,500 developers over a span of nearly a decade.
External contributions from 1500 developers over a decade is a lot. That is an unusually high number, not a low one, and backs up Flutter's claim to love external contributions.
The fact that this person thinks that they can just magically conjure up dozens of volunteer PR reviewers is wild. Everything about this post makes it pretty clear that they don't have the slightest clue of the scope of what they're trying to do. This feels like one of the standard examples of an ex-bigco person setting off on their own with no understanding how just how much the bigco did in the background to facilitate their job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>plorkyeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ttul in "So long WordPress"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974901</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974901"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It gets so much worse. Today, my sales guy was trying to register for WordCamp, a conference that we have been attending for years as an essential place to meet customers. And then he encountered the registration form for a WordPress.org login, which neatly specifies that you affirm you have no “affiliation with WP Engine, whether financial or otherwise.” [1]
Of course, my company does have an affiliation with WP Engine. We use their service to host our website. Therefore, nobody on my team can register for a WordPress.org account.
I wrote an open letter to Matt Mullenweg complaining about the requirement and stating that I believe it violates the Sherman Act and Section 3 of the Clayton Act by being an overly broad prohibition that is clearly anti-competitive and has no clear business justification (aside from limiting competition).
Matt and the rest of the people backing Automattic should take note: Moves like this that destroy your community will eventually usher in a replacement. WordPress is pretty neat, but it only got that way because thousands of people put millions of hours into building add-ons and hosting services to make it blossom into what it is today. If their efforts are redirected in another direction, WordPress will wither away to nothing in a few years.
https://www.linkedin.com/posts/ksimpson_open-letter-to-matt-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ttul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SurgeArrest in "New iMac with M4"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974651</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974651"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading this on 2017 iMac 27" - is the first 5k iMac that couldn't be used as a monitor after the computer inside is irrelevant. 
I hope EU will push for some law that requires all AIO computers to work in monitor-only mode if internal hardware is no longer good enough or no longer supported by software updates.
I love the 5k screen on this iMac but the CPU is too old for photo or video editing as software got so much slower over the years. 
I could have used this screen for many more years, but now it will hit landfill... Apple is only "green" in their presentations - in reality they care more about inifite sales only.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SurgeArrest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rock bottom]]></title>
        <id>https://flecha248.bearblog.dev/rock-bottom/</id>
        <link href="https://flecha248.bearblog.dev/rock-bottom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rock bottom is very often where we begin our healing journey. This is not because we suddenly see the light, nor because our worst days are magically transmuted into some type of epiphany, and not because someone saves us from our own madness. Rock bottom becomes a turning point because it is only at that point that most people think: I never want to feel this way again.
That thought is not just an idea. It is a declaration and a resolution. It is one of the most life-changing things you can ever experience. It becomes the foundation upon which you build everything else.
When you decide you truly do not ever want to feel a certain way again, you set out on a journey of self-awareness, learning, and growth that leads you to radically reinvent who you are.
In that moment, fault becomes irrel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 Years of Amazon ECS: Powering a Decade of Containerized Innovation]]></title>
        <id>a104b5e60ff355bb5245b7686517b8829f9bfefc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/celebrating-10-years-of-amazon-ecs-powering-a-decade-of-containerized-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade of AWS innovation: Amazon ECS evolved from simplifying container orchestration to powering massive operations like Prime Day and enabling customers like SmugMug to seamlessly migrate petabytes of data and scale efficiently with "blazingly-fast" performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New code editor in AWS Lambda console, Amazon Q Business analytics, Claude 3.5 upgrades, and more (October 28, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>d2bccde1d7f3d42d9e6a3a70e09425042cd11315</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-code-editor-in-aws-lambda-console-amazon-q-business-analytics-claude-3-5-upgrades-and-more-october-28-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks ago, I had the wonderful opportunity to host subject matter experts from across Asia Pacific in the global 24 Hours of Amazon Q live stream event. This continuous 24-hour stream offered insights from AWS experts on Amazon Q Developer and Amazon Q Business, featuring use cases, product demos, and Q&A sessions. The highlight for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raphael Sassaki - Moore on Jerusalem, Eternalism, Anarchy and Herbie!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/raphael-sassaki-moore-on-jerusalem-eternalism-anarchy-and-herbie?v=1730130515</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/raphael-sassaki-moore-on-jerusalem-eternalism-anarchy-and-herbie?v=1730130515"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Raphael Sassaki
Title: Moore on Jerusalem, Eternalism, Anarchy and Herbie!
Date: January 2017
Notes: Originally published in Folha de São Paulo.
Source: Retrieved on 28th October 2024 from alanmooreworld.blogspot.com

Raphael Sassaki: How did you come up with the idea of Jerusalem, which tells a story that spreads through 1000 years in Northampton? How was the writing of it?
Alan Moore: Rather than originating from a single idea, Jerusalem is more the convergence of several different impulses and concepts. Foremost amongst these were the growing need to talk about the tiny but historically peculiar district I was raised in, and the simultaneous urge to talk about my family in a way that included both its history and its mythology. This, I soon realised, would require the proposed b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Moore - Fandom has toxified the world]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alan-moore-fandom-has-toxified-the-world?v=1730130220</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alan-moore-fandom-has-toxified-the-world?v=1730130220"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alan Moore
Title: Fandom has toxified the world
Subtitle: On superheroes, Comicsgate and Trump
Date: 26 October 2024
Source: Retrieved on 28th October 2024 from www.theguardian.com

About a decade ago, I ventured my opinion that the adult multitudes queueing for superhero movies were potentially an indicator of emotional arrest, which could have worrying political and social implications. Since at that time Brexit, Donald Trump and fascist populism hadn’t happened yet, my evidently crazy diatribe was largely met with outrage from the fan community, some of whom angrily demanded I be extradited to the US and made to stand trial for my crimes against superhumanity – which I felt didn’t necessarily disprove my allegations. 
 Ten years on, let me make my position clear: I believe that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 CAIRFI fellowships & research awardees announced]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2f650898e71e</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/2024-cairfi-fellowships-research-awardees-announced-2f650898e71e?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T12:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One announces 2024 award recipients out of the Center for Responsible Financial Innovation at Columbia University RFP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Gold in Them Thar Reels]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53316</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/28/theres-gold-in-them-thar-reels/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T11:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of the gold rush is deeply rooted in the American psyche. “There’s gold in them thar hills.” Anyone can abandon his family and community to gamble big on themselves. Thanks to this rugged individualism and the natural bounty of our territory, there’s a chance that you can strike it rich. More than American, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of US democracy: a flowchart]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53310</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/28/the-end-of-us-democracy-a-flowchart/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s not much I can do about it, but I still spend a lot of time thinking about what I, and others outside the US, should do if that country ceases to be a democracy. But, it doesn’t seem as if lots of other people are thinking this way. One possibility is that people just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vldmrs in "Ask HN: What are you working on? (October 2024)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41968277</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41968277"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've noticed that my son spends way too much time on YouTube or playing Minecraft and one of the few offline activities he enjoys doing on his own is coloring. And since he comes to me every time he wants a new coloring book and we spend about 10 minutes together searching for each picture, I made a website with a collection of coloring books for him. The site is very simple, but to be honest, I haven't had so much fun with the process of creation for a long time.
https://colorango.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vldmrs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudolf Rocker - The Truth About Spain]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-rocker-the-truth-about-spain?v=1730091464</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-rocker-the-truth-about-spain?v=1730091464"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T04:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rudolf Rocker
Title: The Truth About Spain
Date: 1936
Source: This text was retrieved on 2024-10-16 from https://www.scribd.com/document/292981558/Rocker. Clarifications for text which was obscured in the original source were retrieved on 2024-10-27 from https://stars.library.ucf.edu/prism/

 If there is any event that can bring about a rediscovery of inner strength on the part of organized labor and the libertarian elements of the world, it is the grand struggle against Fascism now being waged in Spain. After the unresisting defeat of the labor movement in Germany the effect of the heroic battle of the Spanish workers, peasants, and intellectuals against the Fascist bandits is that of a refreshing thunderstorm. It is the first time since Fascism made its appearance in Europe that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t Figure Out Your Personality Type?]]></title>
        <id>https://josephlee.bearblog.dev/cant-figure-out-your-personality-type/</id>
        <link href="https://josephlee.bearblog.dev/cant-figure-out-your-personality-type/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T04:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to struggle with explaining why some of my friends or family members didn’t quite fit into any of the 16 MBTI personality types. A friend of mine seemed like an INFP but had traits of an ISTJ, and my cousin felt like an ESFP, yet was as considerate as an ESFJ.
Then I stumbled upon Personality Ninja (or "NXT"), which uses 32 types instead of just 16. Suddenly, things started to make sense.
At first, I thought, “What? There are only 16 types!” But after trying it out with friends, I realized their new descriptions actually felt accurate. This system offered flexibility and depth the original 16 types didn’t seem to capture.
Curious, I dove deeper into whether 32 types could really work—and found out there’s no reason they can’t! If you look back at Carl Jung, who created the concept of cognitive functions, he didn’t enforce the rigid stacks we see in MBTI or the Harold Grant function model.
Personality Ninja’s approach allows both the first and second functions to be in the same attitude (both extraverted or both introverted), unlike MBTI’s requirement for them to be opposites.
This flexibility means types don’t have to follow TeSi or SiTe formats—they can be TeSe or SiTi. It was the answer I’d been looking for: my friend turned out to be FiSi, while my cousin was FeSe.
So if you’ve ever felt stuck trying to fit yourself or others into the 16 types, it might be worth exploring the 32-type approach!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No one stopped writing diaries, they started publishing blogs instead]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8747</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/personal-websites-blogs-replaced-written-diaries/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mali Waugh, writing for The Age: I also think that keeping a written diary is not really done any more. I wonder whether part of this is that people are much more accepting of traditionally private things being put in the public domain. For the most part, this is a good thing but also sometimes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[october]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/october/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[what a month.
cohost went read-only on the first. i went to a user meetup / wake in northampton the following weekend. i continued my job hunt (successful, btw). i tried (and largely failed) to rest. i learned that i am extremely bad at being unemployed.
everyone i talked to told me that it's pretty normal to not do anything in that window, that it's normal and reasonable to need a break. unfortunately, it did not feel like i was resting, it just felt like i couldn't do anything (distinct! not fun!).
anyway. tomorrow i start a new job, which will give me some structure in my day again. i get novelty—meeting new people, working on new things, experiencing and solving new problems. i'm looking forward to it.
weird, rough month. i am tired. someday i will be able to rest, but it is not right now.
i want to actually keep up with this blog more. i hadn't really realized it had been nearly a month since my last post. time flies. when i have things to write about, i'll do it here. that's about all i can promise.
ok that's it bye]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i cut all my hair off]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/shaved-head/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/shaved-head/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I finally did it. I talked about it already in this post about my hair troubles and finally went through with it and cut all my hair off.

I did it because my illness/medication related hair loss just didn't stop for months now and I didn't like any of it. The hair on all my clothes, on the floor, in the bed, the shower and sink drains. I never had especially voluminous hair; I was on the lower average of the amount, and it was fine hair. But with now less than half left and no signs of slowing down, it was shitty to style, was constantly stringy even when it wasn't greasy, and had no volume at all. The edges of where my face met my hair were really thinning as well; thankfully no bald spots. I like having very long hair, but not when it is so little.
I also thought about the regrowth …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Nîmes]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53308</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/27/sunday-photoblogging-nimes/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T09:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>