<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-05-13T12:59:08.462Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-05-13T12:59:08.462Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/13/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292099</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-13-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T10:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our racous daily lnks: raccoon's meth pipe, dollar and yuan crash? Merz sinking fast, US-Hamas talks, Ukraine delusions, tax bill winners, RFK, Jr. dirty dives, South Africans welcomed, US vacation rentals collapse,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Curious Case of the Hostile Takeover Bid by a Bank Facing Criminal Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292131</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/the-curious-case-of-a-hostile-takeover-by-a-spanish-bank-facing-criminal-prosecution-for-alleged-systemic-bribery-and-blackmail.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T10:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite facing prosecution on a number of charges, including widespread corporate espionage, Spain's BBVA still wants to take over its third biggest rival. The ECB has already given its blessing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decisive Win for Pensioners, Taxpayers in Kentucky as Judge Wingate Rejects Attorney General’s “Get Out of Jail for Almost Free” Scheme for KKR and Blackstone]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292187</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/decisive-win-for-pensioners-taxpayers-in-kentucky-as-judge-wingate-rejects-attorney-generals-get-out-of-jail-for-almost-free-scheme-for-kkr-and-blackstone.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T09:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The plaintiffs seeking to claw back funds from misbehaving finance titans like KKR and Blackstone continue their winning streak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Looted Companies — Now They’re Looting the Government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292166</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/they-looted-companies-now-theyre-looting-the-government.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-13T04:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poor and self-serving corporate oversight practices are going bigger and badder as they are taken to government.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 12, 2025 (#550)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22445</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/12/daily-reading-list-may-12-2025-550/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T23:46:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at data streaming patterns, why you should ask new CEOs (or any leader) for a growth plan, and why "taste" is an unsung ingredient in tech success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: South America expansion, Q Developer in OpenSearch, and more (May 12, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>31b7368b2fa8e86563fb64470f0e54f705c9b0e0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-south-america-expansion-q-developer-in-opensearch-and-more-may-12-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T18:51:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always been fascinated by how quickly we’re able to stand up new Regions and Availability Zones at AWS. Today there are 36 launched Regions and 114 launched Availability Zones. That’s amazing! This past week at AWS was marked by significant expansion to our global infrastructure. The announcement of a new Region in the works […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement event-driven invoice processing for resilient financial monitoring at scale]]></title>
        <id>54a20271c515e5d9da95eefa68861102c29e4300</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/implement-event-driven-invoice-processing-for-resilient-financial-monitoring-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how to build a Business Event Monitoring System (BEMS) on AWS that handles over 86 million daily events with near real-time visibility, cross-Region controls, and automated alerts for stuck events. You might deploy this system for business-level insights into how events are flowing through your organization or to visualize the flow of transactions in real time. Downstream services also will have the option to process and respond to events originating within the system or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grey Newell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[&quot;Art of the Cave”: Trump Walks Back China Tariffs For 90 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCFtkAzfAzegEx3cU0zDwjT</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCFtkAzfAzegEx3cU0zDwjT"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T14:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, maybe. Who the hell knows what he’ll do. Anyway, tariffs are back to 10% on either side and negotiations will continue.
Note that China got what they wanted, minus 10%—no negotiations until the tariffs are removed.
There will still be a two month trade burp. Ships weren’t leaving China for the US at all, literally zero. Lot of freight companies are about to make a mint, though. So expect some shortages, but nothing worse than Covid, and hopefully lasting less time.
The fundamental problem remains, however, which is that there’s no certainty around any of this, so business people can’t make long term plans, including plans to build or relocate manufacturing. Trump and the US can’t be trusted to stay steady on policy, so avoiding making big plans involving the US makes sense.
The Great Power picture is clearer, however. The US tried to impose its will on China and failed. China wouldn’t negotiate till its pre-conditions were met. The world has two great powers, with the EU bidding to become the third (I think they’ll fail, but that’s what the rearmament is about.)
And, in economic terms, China is by far the pre-eminent great power. It isn’t even close. The era of American hegemony is officially over. The US tried to impose its will on the world and failed.
This blog has always been free to read, but it isn’t free to produce. If you’d like to support my writing, I’d appreciate it. You can donate or subscribe by clicking on this link.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enemy of the state: the political persecution of Ulrike Guérot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/enemy-of-the-state-the-political</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/enemy-of-the-state-the-political"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T12:38:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, Guérot was one of Germany’s most respected political scientists. But after she criticised the pandemic response and the proxy war in Ukraine, she found herself cast as a public enemy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/12/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292100</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-12-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T10:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our haute daily links, including Trump firing copyright chief for raising questions about AI theft, a luxury Air Force One gift, and a US-China deal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Long Until You Lose Your Constitutional Rights?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292091</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/how-long-until-you-lose-your-constitutional-rights.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T10:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump adviser Stephen Miller is talking about suspending habeas corpus due to “invasion.” Whether that happens or not, we’re still seeing constitutional rights continue to erode as the “War on Terror” comes home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Doubles Down on Gaza Cruelty With Threat to Cut UN World Food Programme Funding if the UN Rejects US Scheme (and a BRICS Note)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292098</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/trump-doubles-down-on-gaza-cruelty-with-threat-to-cut-un-world-food-programme-funding-if-the-un-rejects-us-scheme.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T09:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another US disgrace in the form of  a threat against the World Food Programme to advance a US son-of-floating pier scheme to feed Gazans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the People Profiting from US Military Aid to Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292111</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/meet-the-people-profiting-from-us-military-aid-to-israel.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T09:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A genocide backed by economic interests is a big problem involving powerful actors. However, many people are taking action to affect the status quo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“How Long Is It Before Reform Implodes?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292125</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/how-long-is-it-before-reform-implodes.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-12T07:43:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Reform less formidable than its stunning success in recent local council elections indicates?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Leaders Continue To Live In A Delusional LaLa Land With Respect To The Ukraine War]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABWpb204I0w8z_8SRt0rN7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABWpb204I0w8z_8SRt0rN7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T21:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Putin’s goals by GrimJim

So, the Europeans have said that Russia must grant an unconditional 30 day ceasefire, or they’ll ramp up aid to Ukraine and put on more sanctions, including some against Nord Stream II. They claim Trump is onside, but Trump hasn’t confirmed this.
The Russians have indicated willingness for a thirty day ceasefire, but they have a condition: for those thirty days, weapon shipments from the West to Ukraine must stop and Putin has straight up rejected the unconditional ceasefire.
What a surprise.
What Europeans want is for Russia, which is winning on the ground, to give them thirty days to rearm Ukraine. Can’t imagine why Russia won’t go for that.
The Euros are delusional. They have no leverage. They’ve already said they intend to end all energy purchases from Russia …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – May 11, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDulYEVhDv-lVTGikwny1Fi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDulYEVhDv-lVTGikwny1Fi"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T18:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – May 11, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
Strategic Political Economy
Congressman Casten: Trump’s Assault on the Rule of Law Is Causing Capital Flight Out of U.S. by Foreign Investors
Pam Martens and Russ Martens, May 5, 2025 [Wall Street on Parade]
Last Wednesday, Congressman Sean Casten, Democrat of Illinois, stated the following in an open meeting of the House Financial Services Committee:
“For the first time in my memory, foreign investors are not only fleeing U.S. equities but are fleeing U.S. Treasuries. I met with banks last week – banks under our jurisdiction – who said that the international community is putting a risk premium on investments in the United States because of regulatory risk and because they question whether the rule of law that they depend on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Великая Отечественная война — The Great Patriotic War]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCezdzb8hZKH8AZVkIU6lMJ</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCezdzb8hZKH8AZVkIU6lMJ"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T12:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soviet War Propaganda showing gratitude for the allies. I own about a dozen WWII Soviet posters.

This post is for a Russian friend of mine. Руфина Сергеевна Гашева, Rufina Sergeyevna Gasheva was born 14 October 1921. Ruffik, as she asked me to call her–was proud to have a young American friend. I have a stack of letters to prove it.
I met Ruffik back in 2002. I was in Moscow with my soon to be wife and her best friend, Nastya (diminutive of Anastasia). Nastya dearly wanted to see her babushka, which was the last thing I wanted to do. Hear stories from some old lady? Good grief. But I went to keep my wife-to-be happy. One of the best decisions I ever made. After meeting Cpl. Ed Neidermeir of the 42 Division (aka: Rainbow Division) who saw his first action on 16 June 1918, meeting Ruffik an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/11/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=292047</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/05/links-5-11-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-05-11T10:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our strategic daily links:dancing robots, global toxics, China trade war, gulf of America, Romanian election, Gaza horrors, Ukraine burning, vanishing privacy, Democrats adrift, self deportations, DOGEy moves, dollar troubles, AI diagnosis, and wretched excess]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItANNCWfcZXq6BJBvza5r3Ie</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItANNCWfcZXq6BJBvza5r3Ie"/>
        <updated>2025-05-10T11:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 9, 2025 (#549)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22420</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/09/daily-reading-list-may-9-2025-549/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T23:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at state of the art video understanding with Gemini, what to do when you're asked to meet impossible goals, and how devs feel about AI generated code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Radley <em>&amp;</em> Nicholas Fairwood: &ldquo;Colonial Legacies&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/colonial-legacies</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/colonial-legacies"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T17:16:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the DRC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design system annotations, part 2: Advanced methods of annotating components]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-2-advanced-methods-of-annotating-components/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-2-advanced-methods-of-annotating-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>How to build custom annotations for your design system components or use Figma’s Code Connect to help capture important accessibility details before development.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-2-advanced-methods-of-annotating-components/">Design system annotations, part 2: Advanced methods of annotating components</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design system annotations, part 1: How accessibility gets left out of components]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-1-how-accessibility-gets-left-out-of-components/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-1-how-accessibility-gets-left-out-of-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T16:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Accessibility Design team created a set of annotations to bridge the gaps that design systems alone can’t fix and proactively addresses accessibility issues within Primer components.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/engineering/user-experience/design-system-annotations-part-1-how-accessibility-gets-left-out-of-components/">Design system annotations, part 1: How accessibility gets left out of components</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Both The UK and Germany Are Going to Go Full Anti-Democratic or Full Trumpian]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCAI7z293yb0ai6pnQp13G1</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCAI7z293yb0ai6pnQp13G1"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T15:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Starmer continues his massive austerity program, just kissed Trump’s ass with a terrible trade deal, and:

Meanwhile, in Germany:
Christian Democrat Friedrich Merz has been confirmed as Germany’s new chancellor. His grand coalition is off to a rocky start — and its call on Germans to swallow austerity is sure to make things worse…
… Merz’s cabinet completely sidelined the more socially conscious “Christian-social” wing of his party. New SPD head Lars Klingbeil initially promised a complete turnaround, a “generational change” for the party after the failures under previous chancellor Olaf Scholz. No one from the left wing of the SPD is represented in government…

What they’re going to try is some military Kenesianism. It won’t work.
So, the AfD, Germany’s right wing Trumpist style party…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tony Wood: &ldquo;Stricken Leviathans&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stricken-leviathans</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stricken-leviathans"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T12:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drug violence and the Mexican state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan Riley: &ldquo;Lenin in America&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/lenin-in-america</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/lenin-in-america"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T11:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tradition and adaptation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This is now Trump's war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/this-is-now-trumps-war</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/this-is-now-trumps-war"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T07:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plus: "How the establishment Is domesticating populism"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aeschylus Was Right 2,540 Years Ago And He Is Just As Right Today]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCuXrLMyQ1vOzY7iu_RVJbs</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCuXrLMyQ1vOzY7iu_RVJbs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-09T04:16:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2,540 year ago Aeschylus said,”in war truth is the first causualty.” Even though this might be true it should not preclude us from making every attempt possible at showing others the truth. I believe in the truth as much as I believe it is capable to be objective. Anyone who says that an “objective journalist is a myth,” is a liar with an agenda. Do we all have biases? You bet. It is in the recognition of said biases and overcoming them is how the truth emerges.
That said, the best, most balanced site concerning operational, strategic and tactical reporting on the Russo-Ukrainian Warcan be found at the Austrian Military Academy.
These two are the most recent, here and the Ukrainian Purgatory, here. Both are in flawless, if somewhat accented, English.
Perhaps we can claw back a bit of truth from the great Greek dramatists hell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 8, 2025 (#548)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22396</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/08/daily-reading-list-may-8-2025-548/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T22:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at implicit caching baked into Gemini 2.5, how Flipkart transformed internal data analytics, and what the intersection of Java and AI looks like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First-party tags in seconds: Cloudflare integrates Google tag gateway for advertisers]]></title>
        <id>3wpdZp6NrwT8NcND208zZT</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/google-tag-gateway-for-advertisers/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T18:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare introduces a one-click integration with Google tag gateway for advertisers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[April 2025 (version 1.100)]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_100</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_100"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code April 2025 Release (1.100)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing Education In The Age of &quot;AI” Is Simple, But Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItClsnhsgzNJNbsxnQNVo6RQ</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItClsnhsgzNJNbsxnQNVo6RQ"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T11:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As has been noted, AI is being used to cheat. A lot:
Lee said he doesn’t know a single student at the school who isn’t using AI to cheat. To be clear, Lee doesn’t think this is a bad thing. “I think we are years — or months, probably — away from a world where nobody thinks using AI for homework is considered cheating,” he said.

He’s stupid. But that’s OK, because he’s young. What studies are showing is that people who use AI too much get stupider.
The study surveyed 666 participants across various demographics to assess the impact of AI tools on critical thinking skills. Key findings included:
Cognitive Offloading: Frequent AI users were more likely to offload mental tasks, relying on the technology for problem-solving and decision-making rather than engaging in independent critical think…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 7, 2025 (#547)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22378</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/07/daily-reading-list-may-7-2025-547/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-08T01:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at emerging developer patterns for the AI era, characteristics of a high performing team, and lessons learned from building a multi-tenant Kubernetes environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I’m going to Moscow for the May 9 Victory Day Parade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/why-im-going-to-moscow-for-the-may</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/why-im-going-to-moscow-for-the-may"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T22:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We need to begin rebuilding the bridge that others have tried so hard to destroy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the works – AWS South America (Chile) Region]]></title>
        <id>52f0c5633b2cff994cf1f4668ca8e3b9cadbdb92</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/coming-soon-aws-south-america-chile-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces plans to launch a new AWS Region in Chile by the end of 2026 with three Availability Zones, marking the third AWS Region in Latin American alongside existing Regions in São Paulo and Mexico, and bringing AWS infrastructure and services closer to Chile including AI capabilities while supporting data residency requirements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QUIC restarts, slow problems: udpgrm to the rescue]]></title>
        <id>2baeaA3qbgFISPMjlZ74a4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/quic-restarts-slow-problems-udpgrm-to-the-rescue/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[udpgrm is a lightweight daemon for graceful restarts of UDP servers. It leverages SO_REUSEPORT and eBPF to route new and existing flows to the correct server instance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marek Majkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turns Out You Can’t Make A Deal With Trump (University and Law Firm Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAJXsUlOE0rAUL8syqBlwK7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAJXsUlOE0rAUL8syqBlwK7"/>
        <updated>2025-05-07T12:09:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NYTimes writes:
Columbia University, for example, agreed to concessions that included imposing new oversight over its Middle Eastern studies department and creating a security force empowered to make arrests. But that was not enough to restore the more than $400 million in grants that the Trump administration had canceled, or to prevent the administration from making even more demands.
Law firms like Paul Weiss, which thought they had escaped punishment by agreeing to do pro bono work for uncontroversial causes, discovered that Mr. Trump saw their agreements as a blank check for them to do his bidding.




As my colleagues have reported, the law firms discovered that they had agreed to deals that “did little to insulate them from his whims.” One expert at Yale Law School said the “admi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>