<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-13T12:46:36.284Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-13T12:46:36.284Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Chomsky & Radical Anthropology Journal - Human nature and the origins of language]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-chomsky-radical-anthropology-journal-human-nature-and-the-origins-of-language?v=1728819998</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-chomsky-radical-anthropology-journal-human-nature-and-the-origins-of-language?v=1728819998"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Chomsky & Radical Anthropology Journal
Title: Human nature and the origins of language
Date: 2008
Source: Radical Anthropology Journal, Issue #2. <radicalanthropologygroup.org/journal>

Noam Chomsky ranks among the leading intellectual figures of modern times and has changed the way we think about what it means to be human, revolutionising linguistics and establishing it as a modern science. He agreed to discuss just some of his ideas with Radical Anthropology. 
 Noam Chomsky is institute professor and professor of linguistics (emeritus) at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. would be a miracle that my granddaughter reflexively identified some elements of the blooming buzzing confusion as language-related and went on to acquire capacities of the kind that you and I are …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aryanam - A Philosophy for Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-a-philosophy-for-anarchism?v=1728817377</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aryanam-a-philosophy-for-anarchism?v=1728817377"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T11:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aryanam
Title: A Philosophy for Anarchism
Date: October 4th 2024
Source: https://asranarshism.com/1403/07/13/a-philosophy-for-anarchism-en/

 Philosophy is nothing but a landscape of perspectives, worldviews, and paths, some meandering and some straightforward, some solitary and some crisscrossing with the neighboring paths, some long and some short, some trekked in multitude and some in solitude, some forgotten and some revered, some new and some ancient, all to understand and nourish the abilities and needs of self and a myriad of others. Being is becoming, the traveler and the path both change in the journey. Yet, even if the destination is all the same, not all paths are suitable for all. One needs to stay true to oneself and the path’s needs and abilities. To each according to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280233</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US media manufactures consent for war with Iran, the Kamala campaign is in trouble, and the Chippendales show that unions are hot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - An Eastern Europe mythbuster]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-an-eastern-europe-mythbuster?v=1728814949</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-an-eastern-europe-mythbuster?v=1728814949"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: An Eastern Europe mythbuster
Date: 24/07/2022
Notes: This article first appeared in the Summer-Autumn edition of Freedom journal.
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2022/07/24/an-eastern-europe-mythbuster/

 “Apparently, for the Western left, it is totally fine to publicly self-fellate over Kurdish, Palestinian or Irish self-determination, but just try bringing an Eastern European one to the table …” 
 ~ Eastern European Leftist Proverb, medium: Telegram 
 One of the more frustrating aspects of watching the most recent Russian special military operation imperialist war unfolding is the number of self-appointed experts from the Western left thinking they have some particularly insightful view. 
 While some make it rather difficult to give them the benefit of the do…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Guérin - Proudhon In the Closet]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-guerin-proudhon-in-the-closet?v=1728814698</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-guerin-proudhon-in-the-closet?v=1728814698"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Daniel Guérin
Title: Proudhon In the Closet
Subtitle: The homophobia and misogyny of Pierre-Joseph Proudhon
Date: Originally written in 1969 & translated in 2013.
Notes: Translated by Jesse Cohn. A reinterpretation of Pierre-Joseph Proudhon’s well-known misogyny as a symptom of repressed homosexual desires. Daniel Guérin (1904–1988), was also author of Homosexualité et révolution (1953) and the widely read Anarchism: From Theory to Practice (1965/1970).
Source: Originally published in French in Essai Sur La Révolution Sexuelle (Après Reich Et Kinsey) by Daniel Guerin in 1969, published in Paris by Editions Pierre Belfond. See the English translation word document with the original French here: <academia.edu>. This English translation was published by Bastard Press in 2014: <wslib.w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De-risking Downsides]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280247</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/de-risking-downsides.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T10:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU starts a trade war with China. Like the “de-risking” from Russia, the US is once again poised to be the main beneficiary.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Civil or Subversive]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-civil-or-subversive?v=1728813042</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-civil-or-subversive?v=1728813042"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Civil or Subversive
Subtitle: Individualist Writings from the UK
Date: 2016
Notes: A Dark Matter Collection
Source: PDF provided by publisher

 Originally published as 
Anarchism: Civil or Subversive
 published under creative commons 
 darkmatter.noblogs.org 
325.nostate.net 
This publication is dedicated to Alfredo Cospito, Nicola Gai, Olga Ekonomidou 
and the memory of Renzo Novatore, beautiful rebels... 
Contents
 Introduction by DMP
 Subversive Disassociation by L
 Beyond the Movement — Anarchy! by DMP
 To address moral elitism within the anarchist milieu in response to the rioters of August 6th onwards... by Anon
 Against the British ‘anti-capitalist movement’: Brief notes on their ongoing failure by Anarchist-nihilists
 Scandalous Thoughts by VQ
 Fragme…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cash Will Soon Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280260</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/the-cash-will-soon-flow.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robbing Africa’s riches to save the climate (and power AI).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SECProto in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41825555</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41825555"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T05:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Funding road repairs, construction, and expansion from general tax revenues is similarly subsidizing a different mode of transit, and it's likely a much higher value than the 3b€ you mention (and likely more than overall railway sector subsidizing, tho I'm not familiar with Germany's budget). Also recognizing that other positive externalities exist, but pricing them at $0, seems silly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SECProto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animals and Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337381</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/13/animals-and-animals/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T05:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We belong to nature, we are one flesh and one blood with nature, we are one brain with nature. – Friedrich Engels, Dialectics of Nature, 1883. A year ago, the Israeli Defence Minister Yoav Gallant probably said more than he meant to: “We are fighting human animals and we act accordingly … We are imposing […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Animals and Animals appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swing State Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337404</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/13/swing-state-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T05:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the final countdown for America’s Presidential race. Trump’s failed summer debate debacle is a dimmed memory, as is the sugar high of Harris’ Age of Aquarius “joy” convention. Post Chicago (and also Milwaukee where she announced her Presidency), Harris’ campaign settled into the worst parts of Obama and Clinton’s campaigns (of course the facsimile […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Swing State Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Sommers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by postpawl in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823619</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41823619"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T23:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Focusing on the cost-per-tonne for carbon reduction misses the broader value of railways. They're not just about reducing emission! They facilitate daily commutes, expand job opportunities, and help drive the economy. It’s a subsidy for businesses too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>postpawl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by PlunderBunny in "Germany's 49-euro ticket resulted in significant shift from road to rail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822853</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822853"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T21:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t forget too that the cost of proving roads is also ‘subsidised’ in most countries, but we’re tend to be a bit blind to that.
(This is not an argument against rail - I just find that subsidies are often mentioned with respect to rail but not with roads).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>PlunderBunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lexicality in "The ACF plugin on the WordPress directory has been taken over by WordPress.org"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822119</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41822119"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T20:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's very funny that Matt's original complaint was that WPEngine didn't contribute enough, and he has now banned them from contributing and stolen what they had previously provided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lexicality</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Things I've learnt on Bearblog since I started my blog]]></title>
        <id>https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/things-ive-learnt-on-bearblog-since-i-started-my-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/things-ive-learnt-on-bearblog-since-i-started-my-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T18:27:51.629Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People really like to talk about writing, don't they? I don't personally mind it, in fact I like writing too, but it feels like every other post that is on the trending tab is about either blogging or writing or Bearblog.
It's quite barebones, and I wish it would be simpler to talk to bloggers. Not many blogs have a comments section, and if I want to talk about their post, I may have to email them or go onto a different social media platform to do so. I know I don't have a dedicated comments section or guestbook, and perhaps that makes me a hypocrite, but I do wish other blogs had one. I'll likely set a guestbook up, now that I think about it.
Rubidium hasn't been mentioned on Bearblog once in its history, which is slightly alarming.
Blogging is well and truly alive, which I love because it's far more interesting than the tacky Twitter vignettes or heavily processed Instagram posts.
It was pointless trying to promote my main blog over social channels...everyone here is getting by without doing so, and seems quite content with it. Fame isn't an issue, and I like that.
etc]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You are not obliged to be deep and meaningful on your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/you-are-not-obliged-to-be-deep-and-meaningful-on-your-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://gremlin.bearblog.dev/you-are-not-obliged-to-be-deep-and-meaningful-on-your-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:52:50.174Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog is a text-form media. It is literally just about putting your thoughts out there for a few people to read. On the Bear Blog you are free to write whatever the fuck you want. You can write poetry, write your to-do lists, plan your D&D campaign, anything. Anything you want, including bizarre shit your mind is telling you. It is anonymous if you want to. If you already have a blog tied to your real identity, create another one, just for incoherent rumblings about something that bothers you. Indescribable shit. It can be a sentence long. Even one word. Be yourself. Be a schizo. Be a prophet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by idlewords in "Turkish language has a gossip tense"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820919</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41820919"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T17:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not a tense but a grammatical mood, it's called the inferential mood. A bunch of languages have it to distinguish eyewitness accounts from reported speech.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Inferential_mood
Verb tense has to do with an action's relationship to time, mood expresses the speaker's relationship and attitude to the action. English is pretty low on moods (indicative, imperative, subjunctive), while other languages have a more fun arsenal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>idlewords</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War on the United Nations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337249</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/12/war-on-the-united-nations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T16:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was the week that Israel, with the backing of the Biden administration, went to war against…the United Nations by attacking UN peacekeepers (UNIFIL) in Lebanon and seizing the UN HQ in East Jerusalem. This brazen assault comes after a year of attacks on UN aid workers in Gaza, killing more than 300. After it has bombed UN food and supply convoys, UN health clinics, UN schools and refugee camps. After it has banned UN investigators from entering Gaza and threatened UN courts and prosecutors. All with the shameful acquiescence of Biden, Blinken and Harris.
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post War on the United Nations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eatbots in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819655</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819655"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T15:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported this exact bug to Zendesk, Apple, and Slack in June 2024, both through HackerOne and by escalating directly to engs or PMs at each company.
I doubt we were the first. That is presumably the reason they failed to pay out.
The real issue is that non-directory SSO options like Sign in with Apple (SIWA) have been incorrectly implemented almost everywhere, including by Slack and other large companies we alerted in June.
Non-directory SSO should not have equal trust vs. directory SSO. If you have a Google account and use Google SSO, Google can attest that you control that account. Same with Okta and Okta SSO.
SIWA, GitHub Auth, etc are not doing this. They rely on a weaker proof, usually just control of email at a single point in time.
SSO providers are not fungible, even if the email address is the same. You need to take this into account when designing your trust model. Most services do not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eatbots</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bsuvc in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819233</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819233"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another example of how weasley Zendesk can be:
They created a fake band called "Zendesk Alternative" just in an attempt to pollute the Google results if you search for an alternative to Zendesk.
http://zendeskalternative.com/
While not illegal, it shows the way they think, a sort of manipulative pettiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bsuvc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by maeil in "1 bug, $50k in bounties, a Zendesk backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819179</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41819179"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T14:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A $1.3 billion revenue company being too tight to pay this after all, even on their 2nd chance, is so short-sighted it's absurd. They're putting out a huge sign saying "When you find a vuln, definitely contact all our clients because we won't be giving you a penny!".
Incredible. This must be some kind of "damaged ego" or ass-covering, as it's clearly not a rational decision.
Edit: Another user here has pointed out the reasoning
> It's owned by private equity. Slowly cutting costs and bleeding the brand dry]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maeil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i love you, rss]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-love-you-rss/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-love-you-rss/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before this blog, I'd pondered the idea of starting a Patreon or a newsletter of some sort. I liked the idea of doing a semi-regular thought or artdump, and the idea of people wanting to tune into said dumps. But I always hesitated for two reasons.
One was that I didn't do anything on a schedule, and if I did do something regularly, I'd stop as soon as it became a task on my to-do list.1 And two was that I've developed a habit of wanting to escape my audience if I knew it was there – worse if I knew who was in it. The awareness made it difficult for me to write or draw or post freely, always thinking about how it would look and if it was good enough and if the people I knew were watching would be offended.
RSS comes as a relief for the overly self-conscious me. While not knowing who is rea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gas Crunch Looms as Demand Outpaces Supply Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280245</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/gas-crunch-looms-as-demand-outpaces-supply-growth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T13:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why a gas price squeeze looks likely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard D. Wolff & Michael Hudson: Israel’s End-Game Under Netanyahu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280243</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/richard-d-wolff-michael-hudson-israels-end-game-under-netanyahu.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T13:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Wolff and Michael Hudson discuss Israel as a colonial project in an era where demonizing the natives is no longer a winning propaganda strategy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diverse Delights]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/diverse-delights/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/diverse-delights/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days ago, I wrote about a growing idea to split this blog into two. I've been experimenting with this "behind the scenes" for a few days, and now I have an even better understanding of what the right path is for the moment.
The blog will remain as it is.
It became very clear as soon as I started practicing the new idea. It felt forced, limited, cumbersome, and...boring.
I began to ponder which text would fit on which blog. I considered which blog I should prioritize. And what would I do with things like the newsletter and guestbook?
More and more unanswered questions accumulated...
Everything indicated that the best course of action would be to stay put for now. I had more or less decided when a text by Kev Quirk appeared in my feed: Why Have Multiple Blogs?
That settled it! The final piece fell into place.
For the time being, this blog will continue to cover everything from Swedish Fika and Cinnamon Buns to Blog Tattoos and Writing as Meditation.
All in one delightful mess.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280214</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T10:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our unsparing daily links: one way sound? mineral green energy constraints. moar China-Phillippines dustup, NKorea to shut SK border, EU migrant returns, Greyzone journ arrest by Israel, foul mouthed robots, Haitians do eat cats, Musk election interference? central bankers beseiged, Boeing cutting workforce]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jandrewrogers in "Working from home is powering productivity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41816635</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41816635"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T05:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think a lot of people are talking past each other. I’ve mostly WFH since long before the pandemic, in many different capacities at many companies. A lot of people have tunnel vision and the reality is more nuanced than most allow.
For IC work that requires minimal collaboration, WFH is often more productive. Fewer interruptions, more focus. However, when the role requires detailed collaboration and regular interaction with others, productivity for WFH falls off a cliff. This has been measurable at every company I’ve worked for that does a decent job of collecting these metrics. And anecdotally, I can feel it in my own job. When I am doing focus work, WFH is great and I get a lot done. When I need a lot of whiteboard time or deep discussions with my peers, WFH is very inefficient regardless of the remote setup, and the difference is so stark that it is difficult to argue.
I think most people are talking their own book. If you are an IC or mostly just do individual focus work, then of course WFH is great. If you need to iteratively collaborate with people on complex design problems or work products, WFH objectively has low efficiency in every organization I’ve seen try it, including companies that are remote-centric.
There is a lot of motivated reasoning in these discussions and little acknowledgement that productivity between WFH and RTO varies greatly depending on the task at hand. Every company and most roles are a mix of these types of tasks. I think many companies these days recognize this and try to allocate accordingly, but it creates legal, social, and other issues if you treat employees differently in this regard based on the nature of their roles. The reality that some people must commute to do their jobs effectively creates a class system of sorts but organizations needs all roles to be setup to ensure reasonable productivity.
This is not a black and white situation, it is a complex social problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jandrewrogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the dreaded chronic fatigue cycle]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/the-dreaded-chronic-fatigue-cycle/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/the-dreaded-chronic-fatigue-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T21:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i haven't been able to make much art lately. which is pretty frustrating, because i genuinely want to work on art. but i have been nonstop stressed for the past month. and unfortunately, being stressed out makes my health problems flare up, which means that my ability to concentrate goes completely out the window.
every now and then, i'll pull out my sketchbook to doodle something, or sketching stuff in MS Paint, or whatever. i'm trying to keep my creative skills engaged, even if it's in small amounts. but man... it's rough. i keep fantasizing about drawing beautiful illustrations, and not having the physical strength to do anything about it.
i'm accustomed to this cycle, but that doesn't make it any less miserable, you know? i can't even begin to count how many times i've been through this. my best coping method for this dreaded cycle is to avoid beating myself up over it, try to be patient and forgiving with myself, and chip away at projects when i'm able to.
it feels kind of embarrassing to keep reposting art from my archives, though. i've been posting art to mastodon/bluesky, since i'm trying to rebuild my online presence in a post-cohost world. and... i desperately wish i had newer pieces to show. it'll happen when it happens - i shouldn't risk pushing my body further when i'm already in a lot of pain - but i still feel sad about it.
just gotta take a deep breath, and be patient. in the meantime, i'd like to take the downtime to study art styles i find compelling. i've gravitated towards 90s anime fantasy art for years, despite my shockingly-minimal exposure to anime, so it'd be fun to study some artbooks. and maybe i'll take the time to work on more weird little web projects - we'll see.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by robohydrate in "How long til we're all on Ozempic?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41812493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41812493"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T19:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been on tirzepatide (Mounjaro) for 4 months now. I'm down 13% of my body weight. I realized that frequent cannabis consumption interferes with the weight loss, so I've kicked the habit from daily to occasionally on weekends. I've started walking 2-3 miles a day, 2-3 days a week regularly, in addition to eating less and being more motivated to calorie count.
All this to say, this drug has been life changing for me. I spend more time doing things I want to do, depression and anxiety have less of a hold on me now. I feel that this drug has allowed me to be the best version of myself I have been in a long time. The only side effects so far have been positive. I do worry about what I will do once it's time to titrate off the weekly dose and the best I can think of is that the habits I'm forming in the time on the drug I will have the resolve to continue after cessation.
I say this because I have battled depression, anxiety and obesity issues my entire life. I've had many failed attempts at getting back to a healthy, productive and non-obese lifestyle. I don't know what is so different about having the drug help me, but I can tell you that it has been different.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>robohydrate</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by llamaimperative in "How long til we're all on Ozempic?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41812339</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41812339"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GP isn't talking about self-control, they're talking about the fact we've created a system that requires obscene amounts of self-control if you wish to maintain physical health.
People in the 50s weren't slimmer because they had ironclad determination to stay such.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>llamaimperative</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a critical post about cohost's problems]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.basementcommunity.com/negative-post-about-cohost/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.basementcommunity.com/negative-post-about-cohost/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know there's a big "well if you could do it better, why don't you just do it then???"-type defense towards people who criticize Cohost, as if they're trying to critique the work of a football player or an artist. But I don't think those are fair comparisons because many, many white-collar, nine-to-five workers have to navigate the same issues the Cohost staff did, which validates some of these arguments (not all, I'll admit).
This isn't a blog post about Cohost paying themselves salaries, but more about the actual work prioritization and team management skills. I'm not really interested in talking about their salaries because I understand they have to eat obviously, and if they weren't willing to work on Cohost as a side-project while having full-time jobs, then there was really no optio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280201</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-11-2024-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Friday's charts: RCP averages (good week for Trump); Covid (XEC has entered the chat); What, again, was Kamala thinking?! Boeing files unfair labor practice charge with NLRB against machinists (wowsers) ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How CyberArk is streamlining serverless governance by codifying architectural blueprints]]></title>
        <id>af07d7584dfeb69d151856df82af697cb9969f9a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-cyberark-is-streamlining-serverless-governance-by-codifying-architectural-blueprints/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T16:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Ran Isenberg, Principal Software Architect at CyberArk and an AWS Serverless Hero. Serverless architectures enable agility and simplified cloud resource management. Organizations embracing serverless architectures build robust, distributed cloud applications. As organizations grow and the number of development teams increases, maintaining architectural consistency, standardization, and governance across projects becomes crucial. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Aleksandrov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brenner’s satisfactory]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45640</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/11/brenners-satisfactory/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford “Mathematics is the art of the perfect.  Physics is the art of the optimal.  Biology, because of evolution, is the art of the satisfactory”. That’s Sydney Brenner speaking.  He should know a thing or two.  He won a Nobel Prize. It’s a shame, is it not?  Economies are always changing.  Not just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by freedomben in ""Begin disabling installed extensions still using Manifest V2 in Chrome stable""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41810118</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41810118"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T15:04:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agreed on hoping this is the inflection point, but only partial agreement that it's about adblock.  For sure Google wants adblock to die, but I think it goes even deeper than that.
I think it's part of a much bigger trend in tech in general but also in Google:  Removing user control.  When you look at the "security" things they are doing, many of them have a common philosophy underpinning them that the user (aka device owner) is a security threat and must be protected against.  Web integrity, Manifest v3, various DoH/DoT, bootloader locking, device integrity which conveniently makes root difficult/impossible, and more.
To all the engineers working on this stuff, I hope you're happy that your work is essentially destroying the world that you and I grew up in.  The next generation won't have the wonderful and fertile computing environment that we enjoyed, and it's (partly) your fault.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freedomben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economic Models Ignoring “Look Out the Window” Climate Change Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280198</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/economic-models-ignoring-look-out-the-window-climate-change-effects.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supposed forecasting mavens are simply ignoring the real economy effects, like poor harvests, of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by freedomben in ""Begin disabling installed extensions still using Manifest V2 in Chrome stable""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41809900</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41809900"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T14:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Notably, Firefox is not removing v2 support (at least for now as of March 2024)
> Firefox, however, has no plans to deprecate MV2 and will continue to support MV2 extensions for the foreseeable future. And even if we re-evaluate this decision at some point down the road, we anticipate providing a notice of at least 12 months for developers to adjust accordingly and not feel rushed.[1]
[1]: https://blog.mozilla.org/addons/2024/03/13/manifest-v3-manif...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freedomben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280188</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our free-ranging daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Norway, One of World’s Most Cashless Economies, Just Made It A Lot Easier to Pay With Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280129</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/another-largely-cashless-economy-norway-just-made-it-easier-rather-than-harder-to-pay-with-cash.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T10:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent trends and developments in Northern Europe suggest the shift away from cash and toward purely digital payment systems may have reached its upper limits -- at least for now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - COVID-19 UK Mutual Aid groups: a list]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list?v=1728638595</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list?v=1728638595"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T09:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: COVID-19 UK Mutual Aid groups: a list
Date: 13/03/2020
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2020/03/13/covid-19-uk-mutual-aid-groups-a-list/

As the global COVID-19 pandemic is upon us, a number of mutual aid groups have started forming across the country. The groups aim at providing community support to those who are more at risk from the virus: be it help with running errands or cooking.
COVID-19 is a novel virus most affecting people’s respiratory systems. While in around 8o% cases the symptoms will be mild, it can lead to death. It is estimated that 2-3 people out of a hundred will die. This can easily mean hundreds of thousands of deaths in the UK alone.
We must do everything we can to prevent this from happening.
The virus, while very unlikely to kill us all, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zosia Brom - It’s spelt Sisterhood, not Cis-terhood]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-it-s-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood?v=1728638156</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zosia-brom-it-s-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood?v=1728638156"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T09:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zosia Brom
Title: It’s spelt Sisterhood, not Cis-terhood
Date: 22/05/2018
Source: https://freedomnews.org.uk/2018/05/22/its-spelt-sisterhood-not-cis-terhood-statement/

 The signatories of this letter strongly condemn the actions and doctrines of the Trans Exclusionary Radical Feminists (TERFs)*. This strain of feminism recently gained notoriety due to their problematic opposition of the proposed reforms to the Gender Recognition Act 2004 (these reforms proposes to allow trans and non- binary people to self- declare their gender without, as is the case now, going through humiliating legal and medical process). This law could help to make the lives of a highly discriminated against minority easier. TERFs however claim that the aim of the proposed law change is a threat to cis women.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Years Do We Have Left?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336977</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/how-many-years-do-we-have-left/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:09:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m writing this letter sitting in a van set up for car camping in the Pacific Northwest. This little trip reminds me of my early days at CounterPunch when Alexander Cockburn was still taking trips all over the states in his boat-like 1960s cars, often on his way to speak at events around the country,  More
The post How Many Years Do We Have Left? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Becky Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Year of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336963</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/a-year-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one had expected that one year would be enough to recenter the Palestinian cause as the world’s most pressing issue, and that millions of people across the globe, would, once again rally for Palestinian freedom. The last year witnessed an Israeli genocide in Gaza, unprecedented violence in the West Bank, but also legendary expressions  More
The post A Year of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: The Call of the Wind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337020</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/roaming-charges-the-call-of-the-wind/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are already hundreds of allegations of price-gouging after Hurricane Helene and Milton. Harris was against price-gouging for about two days, then backed down after getting slapped by blowhards like Larry Summers–the Dick Cheney of economics. Nothing since, even though the evidence is everywhere. McDonalds is now suing the meatpacking industry for price-fixing... More
The post Roaming Charges: The Call of the Wind appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Fascism Look Like? A Brief Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336860</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/what-does-fascism-look-like-a-brief-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be good to be able to recognize fascism when you see it. Sight is our dominant sense (light travels faster than sound) and provides us warning. In addition, because “fascist” is an epithet as well as political term, it must be used carefully. In 1942, a New Hampshire Jehovah’s Witness named Chaplinsky was arrested after calling a Rochester city marshal a “damned fascist.” The U.S. Supreme Court upheld the arrest on the grounds that the expression constituted “fighting words,” excluded from constitutional protection. Recent court decisions in the U.S. have widened speech freedoms, but the word “fascist” remains highly charged, underlining the need for historical and political discretion. More
The post What Does Fascism Look Like? A Brief Introduction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robbing Africa’s Riches to Save the Climate (and Power AI)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336965</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/robbing-africas-riches-to-save-the-climate-and-power-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considered Angola’s crown jewel by many, Lobito is a colorful port city on the country’s scenic Atlantic coast where a nearly five-kilometer strip of land creates a natural harbor. Its white sand beaches, vibrant blue waters, and mild tropical climate have made Lobito a tourist destination in recent years. Yet under its shiny new facade is a history fraught with colonial violence and exploitation. More
The post Robbing Africa’s Riches to Save the Climate (and Power AI) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[American Reckoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336823</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/american-reckoning/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a former senior U.S. national security official, I spend much time deliberating with colleagues around the world on geopolitical risks and trends. It is by now a commonplace that unprecedented uncertainty governs the international scene. Great power rivalries and regional instabilities are escalating. New technologies have changed the playing field.  Furthermore, the U.S. itself has become a major source geopolitical risk.   More
The post American Reckoning  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Medish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DennisL123 in "Tesla Robotaxi"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41806626</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41806626"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Classic bait and switch setup. Selling people the future in 2 years time with little to nothing to show for today. Timelines will slip, plans will change, software won‘t be ready, prices will change. And that doesn’t even account for where Waymo is in two years from now, or what the Chinese EV industry is able to pull off until then.
Even this underwhelming event was originally announced on short notice to prop up perception when sales looked bad in April [1], delayed by two‘ish months, and then didn‘t even start on time. Oh, and implementing the robo taxi was a two-months project back then [1]. It‘s a ruse, folks.
[1] https://fortune.com/2024/07/16/elon-musk-tesla-robotaxi-dela...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DennisL123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corruption in High Places]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336800</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/corruption-in-high-places/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the feds start seizing government cell phones, that’s never a good sign for the officials to whom these devices belong. It’s also an omen for their boss that his days in charge may be numbered. This is exactly the hot water in which the brash, media-hungry mayor of New York City, Eric “Here for  More
The post Corruption in High Places appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Harris and Walz Lose]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336946</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/why-harris-and-walz-lose/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That Kamala Harris and Tim Walz could lose the presidential election in November to serial fraudster, convicted felon, adjudicated sexual abuser, and Wall Street stock jobber Donald Trump does not mean that they will, but it says a lot about the sad state of the Democratic Party that this election is close, especially as Trump’s campaign speeches sound like a variation of a gig by Cheech & Chong (“Don’s not here, man…”). More
The post Why Harris and Walz Lose appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil’s Local Elections: The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336954</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/brazils-local-elections-the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first round of Brazil’s 2024 local elections marked a victory for democracy, as 5,569 elections were held simultaneously on October 6th. Thanks to Brazil’s renowned electronic voting system, results were posted within hours after the polls closed. This same system was the target of conspiracy theories in 2022, which fueled an attempted military coup.  More
The post Brazil’s Local Elections: The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Mier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Booby-trap Attacks on Lebanon:  Indian Army Chief’s Shocking Views]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337172</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/booby-trap-attacks-on-lebanon-indian-army-chiefs-shocking-views/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India’s Chief of the Army Staff, General Upendra Dwivedi, in a TV interview to ‘Firstpost’ on 01st October 2024, has unabashedly defended the method adopted by Israel to use booby-trap weapons in Lebanon by describing it as a “masterstroke”. The Army Chief appears to be wholly oblivious of the fact that India is a ‘High Contracting  More
The post  Booby-trap Attacks on Lebanon:  Indian Army Chief’s Shocking Views appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>N.D. Jayaprakash</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Letter to Dominican President Luis Abinader: Stop Deportations Now!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337099</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/open-letter-to-dominican-president-luis-abinader-stop-deportations-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To President Luis Abinader, As writers, scholars, artists, activists, and people who believe in human rights, we write to condemn the unconscionable violence that your government has unleashed on Haitians, Dominicans of Haitian descent and Black Dominicans since your announcement on October 2nd to deport 10,000 Haitians per week.  The chosen date, October 2nd, commemorates  More
The post Open Letter to Dominican President Luis Abinader: Stop Deportations Now! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Convite Collective</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing Enurement to the End of the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336993</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/manufacturing-enurement-to-the-end-of-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country has seemingly chosen not to be prepared as much as grow inured. -David Wallace-Wells, “Sleeping Through Hurricane Helene,” New York Times, October 2, 2024 Live-streamed genocide inflicted by Israel and its sugar daddy the United States in Gaza, replete with regular images of dead Palestinian children being pulled from the rubble produced by  More
The post Manufacturing Enurement to the End of the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Shriveling Mighty Amazon River Drying Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336958</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/the-shriveling-mighty-amazon-river-drying-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil fuel CO2 emissions are taking the world’s time-honored ecosystems, like the world-famous Amazon River, down onto their knees. The problem is greenhouse gases like CO2 and CH4 trap heat and excessive levels, like we’ve been experiencing, create extreme heat; it’s a direct connection that’s destroying the world’s legendary ecosystems. Over time, the biosphere rejects  More
The post The Shriveling Mighty Amazon River Drying Out appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Trip to Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337045</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/my-trip-to-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September of 2012, I found myself at the Seattle African American Museum at a book launch for my first book my People are rising a memoir of my 10 years as the captain of the first panther chapter outside of the state of California. The book detailed my 10 years of dedicated revolutionary life  More
The post My Trip to Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving the Bumblebee Starts With Changing Our Farming Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336602</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/336602/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The weather warms. The snows recede, and vast swaths of wild flora mat the terrain. The first shoots of the perennials are green. What was once brown and hibernating transforms into a verdant, foliated sea. Not long after the transition, the first insects emerge, following lockstep with the plants. Flying pollinating insects congregate and feed  More
The post Saving the Bumblebee Starts With Changing Our Farming Practices appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmy Videle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Being Jewish And Being Israeli: Argentina’s Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336820</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/being-jewish-and-being-israeli-argentinas-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During my appointment to Buenos Aires in the worst years of the dictatorship and repression (1976-1980), I learned of this ambiguous distinction embodied by the Israeli Ambassador, Ron Nergard, in the capital of Argentina. When Jewish Argentine citizens were victims of repression (kidnapping, torture, disappearance, murder, fraud, dispossession)[1], many of them for the simple reason  More
The post Being Jewish And Being Israeli: Argentina’s Experience appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Howlett-Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Absolutely Do Not Need To Escalate Anything New York Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337080</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/we-absolutely-do-not-need-to-escalate-anything-new-york-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The headline reads “We Absolutely Need to Escalate in Iran” by the still inconceivably taken-seriously New York Times. In all these years after a previous century that saw an estimated 231 million people die in wars, we still have to tolerate the drums of war being beaten by those who will not be touched by  More
The post We Absolutely Do Not Need To Escalate Anything New York Times appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New GM Wheat Poses Risks for Farmers and the Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336767</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/new-gm-wheat-poses-risks-for-farmers-and-the-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The precautionary principle – the ethical equivalent of the common sense notion that it’s ‘better to be safe than sorry’ – means that when some economic or policy change may endanger the public, business and government leaders ought to thoroughly conduct research so as to avoid exposing anyone to unnecessary risks. Unfortunately, with our food  More
The post New GM Wheat Poses Risks for Farmers and the Environment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Pahnke – Jim Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banned Protests, State Repression and Battles in the streets, is this what International Intifada is going to look like? From The River to the Sea in Rome, Italy…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337085</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/banned-protests-state-repression-and-battles-in-the-streets-is-this-what-international-intifada-is-going-to-look-like-from-the-river-to-the-sea-in-rome-italy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This autumn the ominous winds swirling from the ever-intensifying, change of season weather carry with them an even more ominous threat of repression, state sponsored police violence and dictatorial fascist that now seems merged with a zionist crackdown on dissent. This is happening across the western world under the hegemonic control of the US and  More
The post Banned Protests, State Repression and Battles in the streets, is this what International Intifada is going to look like? From The River to the Sea in Rome, Italy… appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Leonardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“A Great Man”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337028</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/a-great-man/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going through my mother’s papers sometime after her death in 1985, I found an essay by the son of a family friend titled “David Ben-Gurion: A Great Man.” Ben-Gurion was the first prime minister of Israel. The essay was completed as a requirement for the traditional course of classes that the boy attended sometime in  More
The post “A Great Man”  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’s a Real Populist? Henry Wallace Set the Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337063</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/whos-a-real-populist-henry-wallace-set-the-standard/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, politicians on both sides of the aisle like to compete for the “populist” label. They would do well to consider the example of a real populist — Henry A. Wallace. Throughout his career, Wallace championed bold, progressive policies that put the “common man” first, even when it earned him enemies. His legacy reminds us that true populism means  More
The post Who’s a Real Populist? Henry Wallace Set the Standard appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A.J. Schumann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Won’t Just be Haitians Who Suffer From Anti-Immigrant Bias]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337065</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/it-wont-just-be-haitians-who-suffer-from-anti-immigrant-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For weeks now, right-wing pundits and politicians have spread baseless claims about Haitian immigrants. These lies have caused immense fear among the community, leading to bomb threats, harassment, and vandalism. The Haitian community in Springfield, Ohio — the first but not the last to be targeted — reported being “scared for their lives”. I’m not Haitian. I’m an  More
The post It Won’t Just be Haitians Who Suffer From Anti-Immigrant Bias appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chisom Okorafur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a Looming Care Crisis in the US and Our Safety Net Isn’t Ready]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337082</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/theres-a-looming-care-crisis-in-the-us-and-our-safety-net-isnt-ready/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My mom had a successful career, earned a good salary, and banked a healthy pension. She set me up to chase my own American dream. I got a great job and purchased my first house at 30. But no matter how successful we are, we can all fall victim to this country’s ailing care economy.  More
The post There’s a Looming Care Crisis in the US and Our Safety Net Isn’t Ready appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christina Keys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax Cuts for the Rich Create Division, Debt and Despair…Not Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337033</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/tax-cuts-for-the-rich-create-division-debt-and-despairnot-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supporters of tax cuts for the wealthy have long claimed that they lead to economic growth. The evidence is in: They don’t. High-end tax cuts have failed to meaningfully grow our economy, but they do grow our divides — economic and political. Over the past four decades, repeated reductions in the average federal tax rates paid by the wealthiest Americans have  More
The post Tax Cuts for the Rich Create Division, Debt and Despair…Not Jobs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Indivar Dutta-Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Cuba’s Report, US Blockade Comes Off as Weapon of War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337038</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/in-cubas-report-us-blockade-comes-off-as-weapon-of-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cuba’s foreign ministry annually reports on the U.S. economic blockade of Cuba and its recent impact mostly in order to enlighten delegates of the United Nations General Assembly prior to voting on a Cuban resolution.  For 31 consecutive years the General Assembly has overwhelmingly approved a resolution claiming “the necessity to put an end to the  More
The post In Cuba’s Report, US Blockade Comes Off as Weapon of War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans are Not Evil…Well, Not All of Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337027</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/republicans-are-not-evilwell-not-all-of-them/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I live in Oklahoma. It’s always been a conservative state. Save for Brad Henry, the lone Democratic Governor who served from 2003 to 2011, this state has elected only Republicans as governor for nearly the last 30 years. But I thought Trump would change things. Since 2016, there has been a concerted effort by some  More
The post Republicans are Not Evil…Well, Not All of Them appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Ware</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of the First Piano Duets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=337162</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/11/337162/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T05:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The season has changed, if reluctantly. Time to put the storm windows on the old clapbord house, tune the grand piano and take out a volume of 18th-century duets off the nearby music shelf. And so, this tribute to those composed by Charles Burney in the 1770s; these charming pieces were, like his four-volume History of  More
The post In Praise of the First Piano Duets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[O Bluesky é diferente pois é só um dos lugares]]></title>
        <id>https://joselito.blog.br/o-bluesky-e-diferente-pois-e-so-um-dos-lugares/</id>
        <link href="https://joselito.blog.br/o-bluesky-e-diferente-pois-e-so-um-dos-lugares/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T01:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eu imagino que você já tentou usar o Mastodon pelo menos uma vez. Ou talvez use, longe de mim julgar. Não é de hoje que redes sociais dominadas por big techs não são exatamente os locais mais saudáveis pra ter um delicioso "debate de ideias". Sempre é bom buscar alternativas.
Lembra como foi o processo? Alguém finalmente te convencia, aí então você ia lá "beleza então me fala aí onde me cadastro?" e você ouvia que tinha que "escolher uma instância". Mesmo indo no site oficial você era direcionado a uma página com inúmeras instâncias (hoje isso mudou).
"Como é amigo? O quê é uma instância?" E ai começava uma considerável — ainda que interessante — explicação sobre como o Mastodon funciona, geralmente dando um certo destaque para o fato de que seu usuário agora tem o dobro de arrobas do que …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gechr in "DeskPad – A virtual monitor for screen sharing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41804360</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41804360"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T22:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After trying various solutions - including DeskPad - I came up with a custom cross-platform (I'm on macOS, but assume it'll work elsewhere) solution that worked incredibly well on my 40" ultrawide monitor: OBS[1].
Having never used OBS before but knowing it was popular among streamers, I wondered if I could use it to (1) only share the specific applications I wanted to share and (2) share them at a resolution that people could actually read, without constantly being asked to zoom in.
I first tried setting up a virtual camera and sharing via my video stream, but it was laggy and the quality was so poor that people couldn't read what I was sharing. I quickly gave up on that approach.
Then I discovered Projectors[2]. By right-clicking on the main view in OBS and selecting "Windowed Projector (Preview)", it launches a separate window, which I can then share directly via Zoom, Teams, Meet, etc.
Whatever I drag into the OBS view is displayed in the Windowed Projector (similar to DeskPad), with the added bonus that I can choose to blur certain applications that might be dragged in. For example, if I open Slack or my password manager, the entire window blurs until I focus back on my terminal or browser.
It took a bunch of tweaking to perfect, but I'm very pleased with how well it works now.
---
[1] https://obsproject.com/
[2] https://obsproject.com/kb/power-of-projectors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gechr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re All Just Looking for Connection]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17027</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/were-all-just-looking-for-connection/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:39:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been working to bring components of Quip’s technology into Slack with the canvas feature, while also maintaining the stand-alone Quip product. Quip’s backend, which powers both Quip and canvas, is written in Python. This is the story of a tricky bug we encountered last July and the lessons we learned along the way about […]
The post We’re All Just Looking for Connection appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brett Wines</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia to remove low quality unsourced AI created content]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8661</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wikipedia-remove-low-quality-unsourced-ai-created-content/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wikipedia has created a task force to identity instances of poor quality, unsourced content, being generated by AI chatbots. The online encyclopaedia will still allow AI apps to compose articles, provided they do so in accordance with their policies: The purpose of this project is not to restrict or ban the use of AI in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Vale of Sorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://weirdwonder.bearblog.dev/the-vale-of-sorrow/</id>
        <link href="https://weirdwonder.bearblog.dev/the-vale-of-sorrow/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am running Mythic Bastionland with my home table. Here is what they knew when the campaign began.

The Land
The Vale’s sorrow knows no succor. Wanderers in the wilderness glimpse remnants of the Sun Guard’s emblem carved on ancient stones, the Queen’s face engraved on old metal coins. Little is remembered of what caused the Realm to fail. Harpists sing of a dying Queen seeking the cup of Solace. Others gossip of jealous lovers or sibling strife. What is known is in the last Age, the Sun Guard sallied forth from their Rotunda in the Queen’s Halls in Baelfyre, their eyes yearning for the City’s gleam. They were never seen again
They are lost and dispersed, withering in forgotten groves or rotting in hollows. There are rumors that their ancient hall still stands.
In these latter days of the fallen queen’s realm, peace extends no farther than a hold’s torchlight. The Forest and Wilderness cast long shadows. The Vale is a remote realm carved out with warrior’s blood on the edge of the empire across the Sea. There is word that lawlessness reigns, with roving warbands terrorizing the countryside and strange mystics shouting apocalyptic prophecies. Nature reclaims the queen’s road. craven opportunists find easy avenues to power

For the Players
You are hedge knights, come to this Land seeking opportunity, your knighthoods fresh as morning dew. You are the children of spring. Your new arms shine in the midday sun. You came to your knighthoods over the long cold winter, called to serve by the Seers and sworn to your oaths.
Despite whatever burgeoning relationships (good or ill) you may have, you are a Company, newly formed of foreigners sent to a land unseen by your fathers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardcover, a Goodreads-like online social catalogue for books]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8654</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/hardcover-goodreads-like-online-social-catalogue-books/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been trying out Hardcover, a social catalogue for book readers, founded by Adam Fortuna in April 2021. Like a few people I think, he was looking for an alternative to Goodreads (GR), which at the time was probably the big name in book social cataloguing. StoryGraph is one option, but Fortuna wanted to make […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BiteCode_dev in "Proposal: JavaScript Structs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41803003</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41803003"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:10:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Javascript is not simple AT ALL.
It has 3 ways to declare functions, multiple variations on arrow functions syntax, a weird prototyping inheritance system, objects you can create out of "new" on functions, object literals that can act an pseudo-classes, classes, decorators, for-i loop + maps + filter + for-in loop (with hasOwn) + forEach, async / await + promises and an invisible but always-on event loop, objects proxies, counter-intuitive array and mapping manipulations, lots of different ways to create said arrays and mappings, very rich destructuring, so many weirdnesses on parameter handling, multiple ways to do imports that don't work in all contexts, exports, string concatenation + string interpolation, no integer (but NaN), a "strict mode", two versions of comparison operators, a dangerous "with" keyword, undefined vs null, generators, sparse arrays, sets...
It also has complex rules for:
- scoping (plus global variables by default and hoisting)
- "this" values (and manual binding)
- type coercion (destroying commutativity!)
- semi-column automatic insertion
- "typeof" resolution
On top of that, you execute it in various different implementations and contexts: several browser engines and nodejs at least, with or without the DOM, in or out web workers, and potentially with WASM.
There are various versions of the ECMA standard that changes the features you have access to, unless you use a transpiler. But we don't even touch the ecosystem since it's about the language. There would be too much to say anyway.
There are only two reasons to believe JS is simple: you know too much about it, or you don't know enough.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BiteCode_dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress.org users required to denounce WP Engine affiliation]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8651</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wordpress-org-users-denounce-wp-engine-affiliation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T20:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samantha Cole, writing at 404 Media: The checkbox on the login page for WordPress.org asks users to confirm, “I am not affiliated with WP Engine in any way, financially or otherwise.” Users who don’t check that box can’t log in or register a new account. As of Tuesday, that checkbox didn’t exist. Automattic upping the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suleiman Mourad: &ldquo;In Defiance&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-defiance</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-defiance"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T19:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elias Khoury (1948-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leetharris in "Proposal: JavaScript Structs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41802034</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41802034"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T18:48:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am not sure how to really refine this thought I have had, but I have this fear that every language eventually gets so bloated and complicated that it has a huge barrier to entry.
The ones that stand out the most to me are C# and Typescript.
Microsoft has a large team dedicated towards improving these languages constantly and instead of exclusively focusing on making them easier to use or more performant, they are constantly adding features. After all, it is their job. They are incentivized to keep making it more complex.
The first time I ever used C# was probably version 5? Maybe? We're on version 12 now and there's so much stuff in there that sometimes modern C# code from experts looks unreadable to me.
One of the reasons I have so much fun working in node/Javascript these days is because it is simple and not much has changed in express/node/etc for a long time. If I need an iterable that I can simply move through, I just do `let items = [];`. It is so easy and hasn't changed for so many years. I worry that we eventually come out with a dozen ways to do an array and modern code becomes much more challenging to read.
When Typescript first came out, it was great. Types in Javascript are something we've always wanted. Now, Typescript is on version 5.6 and there is so much stuff you can do with it that it's overwhelming. And nobody uses most of it!
This is probably just old man ranting, but I think there's something there. The old version I used to debate about was C vs C++. Now look at modern C++, it's crazy powerful but so jam packed that many people have just gone back to C.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leetharris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 1 | The polycrisis of capitalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-1-The-polycrisis-of-capitalism</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-1-The-polycrisis-of-capitalism"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T17:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early October, the CADTM hosted its International Council after the Autumn Meetings in Liège. Members of the CADTM network travelled from Mexico, India, the Ivory Coast, Burkina Faso, the Democratic Republic of the Congo, Mali, Togo, Morocco, Spain, France, the Netherlands, and Belgium to participate in these two activities. Non-network members from Brazil, Poland, Austria, Finland, Cyprus, and Germany also attended the autumn meetings. 
English

/ 
Crisis, 
Capitalism, 
CADTM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International, Pablo Laixhay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert AWS console actions to reusable code with AWS Console-to-Code, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>bd5c592e02045e07840c7769739f27e8e489bc34</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/convert-aws-console-actions-to-reusable-code-with-aws-console-to-code-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Console-to-Code generates reusable infrastructure as code from your AWS console actions, supporting Amazon EC2, RDS, and VPC. With a few clicks, get CloudFormation, CDK (TypeScript, Python, Java), or CLI code - a game-changer for streamlining cloud automation workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering the Next Generation of AI Workloads on Amazon EKS with Anyscale]]></title>
        <id>2781074270abb1dc2ea44eb23f80527ea71ae913</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/powering-the-next-generation-of-ai-workloads-on-amazon-eks-with-anyscale/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T16:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ray is an open-source framework that manages, executes, and optimizes compute needs for AI workloads. It is designed to make it easy to write parallel and distributed Python applications by providing a simple and intuitive API for distributed computing. Ray unifies infrastructure by leveraging any compute instance and accelerator on AWS via a single, flexible […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apoorva Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging Tattoo]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blogging-tattoo/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blogging-tattoo/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tattoo caught my eye. Two words.
It turned out to be a slogan for a Swedish sports club.
What a perfect motto for blogging, I thought. It said:
"Always, regardless."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marina Forti: &ldquo;Hollow Steel&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hollow-steel</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hollow-steel"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Marghera.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by citricsquid in "Helping wikis move away from Fandom"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798956</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798956"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T14:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the person ultimately responsible for the Minecraft Wiki ending up in the hands of Fandom, it is great to see what Weird Gloop (and similar) are achieving. At the time of selling out, the Minecraft Wiki and Minecraft Forum cost tens of thousands of dollars per month to run and so it didn't feel too much like selling out, because we needed money to survive[1]. 15 years later, the internet is a different place, and with the availability of Cloudflare, running high-traffic websites is much more cost effective.
If I could do things over again, on today's internet, I like to believe Weird Gloop is the type of organisation we would have built rather than ending up inside Fandom's machine. I guess that's all to say: thank you Weird Gloop for achieving what we couldn't (and sorry to all who have suffered Fandom when reading about Minecraft over the years).
[1] That's a bit of a cop out, we did have options, the decision to sell was mostly driven by me being a dumb kid. In hindsight, we could have achieved independent sustainability, it was just far beyond what my tiny little mind could imagine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>citricsquid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cbm-vic-20 in "Helping wikis move away from Fandom"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798626</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798626"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "fan" in "Fandom" means the fan in your computer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cbm-vic-20</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CJ Desai: Why I joined Cloudflare as President of Product and Engineering]]></title>
        <id>1CTZpoSgblZPyzlutBC0kp</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cj-desai-why-i-joined-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am thrilled to embark on this journey to run Product and Engineering at Cloudflare, driving forward the mission of helping build a better Internet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CJ Desai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "Automating processes with software is hard"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798250</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41798250"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T12:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who spent most of a career in process automation, I've decided doing it well is mostly about state limitation.
Exceptions or edge cases add additional states.
To fight the explosion of state count (and the intermediate states those generate), you have a couple powerful tools:
   1. Identifying and routing out divergent items (aka ensuring items get more similar as they progress through automation)
   2. Reunifying divergent paths, instead of building branches

If you want to go back and automate a class of work that's being routed out, write a new automation flow explicitly targeting it. Don't try and kludge into into some giant spaghetti monolith that can handle everything.
PS: This also has the side effect of simplifying and concluding discussions about "What should we do in this circumstance?" with other stakeholders. Which for more complex multi-type cases can be never-ending.
PPS: And for god's sake, never target automation of 100% of incoming workload. Ever. Iteratively approach it, but accept reaching it may be impossible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro Life Tips for Grouchy People]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/pro-life-tips-for-grouchy-people/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/pro-life-tips-for-grouchy-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, being grouchy was a hallmark of my personality. A combination of untreated bipolar disorder and active alcoholism gave me a perpetual frown and a repertoire of caustic comments. Thankfully, I finally sought treatment for both issues, got my life in order, and most people who know me wouldn't describe me as ill-natured at all. I have to admit that in a lot of ways, I have it made. I work because I want to, not because I have to. My wife and kids love me. The rest of my family is self-sufficient and drama-free. I have adequate time for my hobbies.
But…
Nobody is perfect, and every once in a while, I succumb to the internal pressure to let things get to me. For some reason, things I would ordinarily overlook become sticking points. My job is helping people with technology, and I kn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“15 Best Economics Book Blogs and Websites in 2024”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45626</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/10/15-best-economics-book-blogs-and-websites-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Feedspot The best Economics Book blogs from thousands of Book blogs on the web and ranked by traffic, social media followers & freshness. Economics Book Blogs Here are 15 Best Economics Book Blogs you should follow in 2024 1. Real-World Economics Review Blog The Real-World Economics Review blog serves as a critical platform for economists, scholars, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Stock Markets’ Reactions to EU Climate Policy Shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32002</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/international-stock-markets-reactions-to-eu-climate-policy-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While policies to combat climate change are designed to address a global problem, they are generally implemented at the national level. Nevertheless, the impact of domestic climate policies may spill over internationally given countries' economic and financial interdependence. For example, a carbon tax charged to domestic firms for their use of fossil fuels may lead the firms to charge higher prices to their domestic and foreign customers; given the importance of global value chains in modern economies, the impact of that carbon tax may propagate across multiple layers of cross-border production linkages. In this post, we quantify the spillover effects of climate policies on forward-looking asset prices globally by estimating the impact of carbon price shocks in the European Union’s Emissions Trading System (EU ETS) on stock prices across a broad set of country-industry pairs. In other words, we measure how asset markets evaluate the impact of changes to the carbon price on growth and profitability prospects of the firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian di Giovanni, Galina Hale, Neel Lahiri, and Anirban Sanyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by seanhunter in "How to make Product give a shit about your architecture proposal"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41795621</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41795621"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T04:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most valuable life lessons is you can't get anyone else to care about what you want them to care about basically ever. You need to focus on the things you can control and one of the things you can't control is what someone else is going to care about.
So if you want something done and someone else has to agree, you have to figure out how the thing you want coincides somehow with their interests and concerns.
Then you explain the thing you want to them in terms of how it advances/affects the interests and concerns of the other person. So in the framing of TFA, product are never ever ever under any circumstances going to give a shit about your architecture proposal (because that is entirely in the domain of your concerns). But they may care about how the architecture is going to prevent them from delivering features that are on the roadmap coming up and how you have a solution that can fix that for example (because now you are in the domain of their concerns).  Notice this is not just "your architecture proposal", it is how your architecture proposal is going to get them what they want, and if you want to do this you need to think deeply and make sure you really understand what they want, not just what you want.
You're not trying to change their mind. You're trying to get what you want by showing them how it will also get them something they want.
I'm putting this here because I really wish someone had told me this 25 years ago near the start of my career.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Maddie, be green tea" - a discussion about presentation]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/maddie-be-green-tea-a-discussion-about-presentation/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/maddie-be-green-tea-a-discussion-about-presentation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T01:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(CW: Fat-shaming, dysphoria, discussions about body image issues)
I spoke to my Taiwanese trans friend last night about how our emotions changed post transition, and how I--personally--don't get angry much (if at all) unless I'm severely stressed out, overstimulated, and then someone throws the final straw on the haystack.
...I may be talking about recent days, but hey.
My friend's interjection came with a wry smile. "You want to be likeable?"
Obviously I paused at this question. It sounded vain and shallow, but this is Asia. Results matter more than intentions, as our parents would oft prove by pointing to our tests. It's why so many Reincarnation and Cultivation stories exist. The proliferation of  skills in Asian fantasy exists to give you the result without hard work. And why would har…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending October 06, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241009</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241009"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Cloudflare One: Digital Experience (DEX) monitoring notifications and seamless access to Cloudflare Gateway with China Express]]></title>
        <id>5CeN58bNiSOtUjklrzm0nG</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/roundup-dex-alerts-cloudflare-gateway-china-express"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup blog post shares the latest new features and capabilities at Cloudflare. Learn more about new Digital Experience (DEX) monitoring notifications and seamless access to Cloudflare Gateway with China Express.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guy Nir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mother Earth - Observations and Comments on Kropotkin and the European War]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-observations-and-comments-on-kropotkin-and-the-european-war?v=1728513329</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mother-earth-observations-and-comments-on-kropotkin-and-the-european-war?v=1728513329"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T22:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mother Earth
Title: Observations and Comments on Kropotkin and the European War
Date: 1915
Notes: An untitled excerpt and letter from ‘Mother Earth’, January 1915, New York City, published by Emma Goldman, edited by Alexander Berkman
Source: Retrieved on October 9, 2024 from https://mgouldhawke.wordpress.com/2024/10/05/observations-and-comments-on-kropotkin-and-the-european-war-mother-earth-1915/

 Of all the terrible features brought to light in the European War, there is one which no doubt will cause rejoicing in the camps of the various governments. It is the fact that the revolutionary movement of all shades has disclosed national and patriotic superstition and racial prejudice. 
 Before the war the Governments of Europe spent sleepless nights over the growth of Socialism, Synd…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog advice: Subscribe to yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://posts.arborelia.net/blog-advice-subscribe-to-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://posts.arborelia.net/blog-advice-subscribe-to-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:47:31.344Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should subscribe to your own blog.
It's not that weird. In a social media feed, you'd see your own posts. On a blog, you should see what your own posts look like to other people, even if it's just in the one feed reader that you use.
It's a good way to make sure the RSS/Atom version of your posts comes out looking right, the links work and point to the correct posts, the feed works at all, the images load in image-based posts, and so on.
Incidentally, if my posts ever come out terribly broken in your feed reader, please do let me know using that comment link down there (on my page, not in your feed reader).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So long, thanks for all the blog posts: Microsoft cans WordPad]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8647</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/thanks-blog-posts-microsoft-cans-wordpad/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is doing away with their old basic, but useful, word processor, WordPad, which has been bundled with Windows Operating Systems for nearly thirty-years. It will not be a feature at all in Windows 11. Yet another reason to migrate away from Windows all together, perhaps? Before switching to Word, I used to draft all […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by stego-tech in "US weighs Google break-up in landmark antitrust case"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41791020</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41791020"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loving the discourse in the comments here.  Speaking as someone who grew up alongside Google in a sense, I fall on the side of the "break it up" camp.  It was novel at the time to have a single company so nicely provide us with everything digitally that we could need - G Suite, YouTube, Search, Maps, Advertising, Books, Reader, etc - but in hindsight, we gave too much power to too unaccountable an entity, who in turn used it to choke off any avenues to challenge its dominance.
As for the rebuttal of "bUt ThE gDp", there's a counter-argument to be made that the GDP would have grown just as much with a higher diversity and stringent M&A regulations by spurring on new businesses and concepts, as opposed to mainstreaming fad after fad that seemingly solely benefits the established players.  There's another argument to be made equating GDP values to desirable targets creates a Goodhart's Law problem, thereby making GDP as a measure of growth or success a bad metric; the rise of income and wealth inequality these past few decades, when there was increased focus on GDP as a target of growth or success, could be viewed as evidence supporting said argument.
It's worth noting that this case against Google is likely to be the bellwether for future divestments and breakups.  Whatever comes next will be an invaluable learning experience for both sides, just like AT&T and Microsoft's own anti-trust woes were learning experiences for the current crop of companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stego-tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kristjansson in "PEP 760: No more bare excepts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41789903</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41789903"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My concern, and IMO what should be the overwhelming concern of the maintainers, is not the code that is being written, or the code that will be written, but all the code that has been written, and will never be touched again. A break like this will force lots of python users to avoid upgrading to 3.17, jettison packages they may want to keep using, or deal with the hassle of patching unmaintained dependencies on their own.
For those Python users for whom writing python is the core of their work that might be fine.  For all the other users for whom python is an foreign, incidental, but indispensable part of their work (scientists, analysts, ...) the choice is untenable. While python can and should strive to be a more 'serious', 'professional' language, it _must_ have respect and empathy for the latter camp.  Elevating something that should be a linter rule to a language change ain't that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kristjansson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving platform resilience at Cloudflare through automation]]></title>
        <id>2i9tHkPAfy7GxYAioGM100</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/improving-platform-resilience-at-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We realized that we need a way to automatically heal our platform from an operations perspective, and designed and built a workflow orchestration platform to provide these self-healing capabilities across our global network. We explore how this has helped us to reduce the impact on our customers due to operational issues, and the rich variety of similar problems it has empowered us to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Onikute</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eig in "Chemistry Nobel: Computational protein design and protein structure prediction"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41787261</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41787261"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T12:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I disagree with most of the comments here stating it’s premature to give the Nobel to AlphaFold.
I’m in biotech academia and it has changed things already. Yes the protein folding problem isn’t “solved” but no problem in biology ever is. Comparing to previous bio/chem Nobel winners like Crispr, touch receptors, quantum dots, click chemistry, I do think AlphaFold already has reached sufficient level of impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Indicator of Labor Market Tightness for Predicting Wage Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32101</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/a-new-indicator-of-labor-market-tightness-for-predicting-wage-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key question in economic policy is how labor market tightness affects wage inflation and ultimately prices. In this post, we highlight the importance of two measures of tightness in determining wage growth: the quits rate, and vacancies per searcher (V/S)—where searchers include both employed and non-employed job seekers. Amongst a broad set of indicators, we find that these two measures are independently the most strongly correlated with wage inflation. We construct a new index, called the Heise-Pearce-Weber (HPW) Tightness Index, which is a composite of quits and vacancies per searcher, and show that it performs best of all in explaining U.S. wage growth, including over the COVID pandemic and recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Heise, Jeremy Pearce, and Jacob P. Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring global poverty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Measuring-global-poverty</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Measuring-global-poverty"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T08:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To track progress towards its goal of eradicating extreme poverty by 2030., the UN relies on World Bank estimates of the share of the world population that fall below the so-called International Poverty Line (IPL). 
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Precarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mihaic in "John Carmack on inlined code (2014)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41785113</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41785113"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first heard the maxim that an intelligent person should be able to hold two opposing thoughts at the same time, I was naive to think it meant weighing them for pros and cons. Over time I realized that it means balancing contradictory actions, and the main purpose of experience is knowing when to apply each.
Concretely related to the topic, I've often found myself inlining short pieces of one-time code that made functions more explicit, while at other times I'll spend days just breaking up thousand line functions into simpler blocks just to be able to follow what's going on. In both cases I was creating inconsistencies that younger developers nitpick -- I know I did.
My goal in most cases now is to optimize code for the limits of the human mind (my own in low-effort mode) and like to be able to treat rules as guidelines. The trouble is how can you scale this to millions of developers, and what are those limits of the human mind when more and more AI-generated code will be used?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mihaic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by EvanAnderson in "European govt air-gapped systems breached using custom malware"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784970</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784970"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the discipline surrounding most "air gapped" machines I've seen I always find this quote appropriate:
"At best, an air gap is a high-latency connection" -Ed Skoudis - DerbyCon 3.0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EvanAnderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nullindividual in "Why the ISO format has to die"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784789</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784789"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author could use a bit of humility.
ISO isn’t useful in the author’s use-case. That’s fine, it is their project to do as they will. ISOs may still have uses elsewhere, such as PXE boot or just a near universally mountable read only container.
The author’s point to the age of the original ISO standard is irrelevant. Many old technologies are reliable and widely adopted, which in and of itself may make it superior to more modern technologies.
Author’s project, author’s will. But that was difficult to read due to their attitude and beyond the author’s use case, didn’t provide a reason for universally retiring ISO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nullindividual</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Serverless Streamlit App Deployment with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>801c833117b120c017f34599470ae8bce1d0bf6e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-serverless-streamlit-app-deployment-with-terraform/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphic created by Kevon Mayers. Introduction As customers increasingly seek to harness the power of generative AI (GenAI) and machine learning to deliver cutting-edge applications, the need for a flexible, intuitive, and scalable development platform has never been greater. In this landscape, Streamlit has emerged as a standout tool, making it easy for developers to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevon Mayers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs. The great hope of 1997's indie web.]]></title>
        <id>https://escape.bearblog.dev/blogs-the-great-hope-of-1997s-indie-web/</id>
        <link href="https://escape.bearblog.dev/blogs-the-great-hope-of-1997s-indie-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T01:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I think I'm out, they pull me back in.

The main problem with Blogs in 1997 is that it didn't take long to realize nobody else cared about it.
The good thing about Blogs in 2024 is that you go into it knowing nobody will care about it. How Fucking Refreshing.
These days there are places to connect in 300 characters or less, places to manage & moderate a growing community, and there are billionaire owned communities to help you become disappointed in your friends and family.
Sounds tedious AF.
I miss the ancient times when a simple RSS reader allowed people to lurk in the manner they preferred.
When an introvert could get a word in.
When you could fucking curse if it pleased you, because you're an adult and sometimes things suck.
Ya know?!?
So that's what I'll do here.
Curse.
But also share. With no pressure to be heard. And no pressure to respond.
If nothing else, a time capsule.
Of my journey in game development, and perhaps someday in setting up a studio. Video games have always been a wonderful escape for me. I'd call my game studio "Escape Element". So that'll be the blog's name too.
But don't be confused. This blog will be my personal take on things.
You could find all sorts of stuff here. It could be gamedev related stuff like art, music, or code (I dabble in all) ... or...
I may just need to rant about how stupid people are stupid.
Whatever is taking my attention at any given moment... I'm probably either in love with or pissed off at it, and it's well past time I let the universe know about it.
If following along sounds like it may provide you with an element of escape, come on back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Jedd in "Who died and left the US $7B?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41783447</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41783447"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T01:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fascinating reddit post was mentioned here about a month ago - about the mildly famous (if a little macabre) 'Buy, Borrow, Die' cycle used by the obscenely-wealthy to - multi-generationally - avoid tax obligations.
https://old.reddit.com/r/BuyBorrowDieExplained/comments/1f26...
HN comments:  https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41408772]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jedd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Compleat History of the Magic: the Gathering Metagame, Supplemental: Commander's Road to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/a-compleat-history-of-the-magic-the-gathering-metagame-supplemental-commanders-road-to-hell/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/a-compleat-history-of-the-magic-the-gathering-metagame-supplemental-commanders-road-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 24 2024, the Commander Rules Committee put out their quarterly update detailing the newest batch of changes to the format. These changes consisted of banning four cards from the format: Dockside Extortionist, Jeweled Lotus, Mana Crypt, and Nadu, Winged Wisdom.
Less than a week later, the Commander RC – the independent group of fans who had controlled the game’s most popular format for over a decade – was no more.
What follows is an attempt at understanding how the world's most popular card game got to this point.
A brief explanation of Commander
If you're unfamiliar: Commander is a casual Magic variant that has, in the last 10 years, become the most popular and widespread form of the game. In Commander, players play free-for-all multiplayer games, typically with four players, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by recursivedoubts in "A modest critique of Htmx"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782080</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782080"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These all look reasonable to me.
I especially go back and forth on attribute inheritance (it can be disabled via the htmx.config.disableInheritance option)
Three of the criticisms boil down to the fact that client-side state doesn't always play well w/htmx swaps (especially the simple ones) which is absolutely true.
And events can get crazy.  They are powerful, but crazy and at times hard to debug.  Such is event-driven life.
The one thing I don't agree with is the default queuing mode: it is not to cancel an existing request and replace it.  Instead it is to keep the current request in flight and queue one and only one additional request.  I'd need to sit down w/them to see if they were misinterpreting something, using the hx-sync attribute to implement the behavior they mention, or if there is a bug.
I would also like to take this opportunity to market our mug for people who don't like htmx:
https://swag.htmx.org/products/htmx-sucks-mug]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>recursivedoubts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oxford Comma users: people may think AI does your writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8643</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/oxford-comma-users-people-think-ai-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frequent use of the Oxford Comma, also referred to as the Serial Comma, is — apparently — a tell-tale sign a written work was composed using an AI chatbot. The repeat use of punctuation mark is among seven indicators researchers at Cambridge University, in the United Kingdom, identified after studying AI generated articles and essays. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road Not Taken]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45623</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/08/the-road-not-taken/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T19:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We all heterodox economists who have chosen the road ‘less traveled by’ know that this choice comes at a price. Fewer opportunities to secure ample research funding or positions at prestigious institutes or universities. Nevertheless, yours truly believes that very few of us regret our choices. One doesn’t bargain with one’s conscience. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of forgetting about music for a bit]]></title>
        <id>https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/the-art-of-forgetting/</id>
        <link href="https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/the-art-of-forgetting/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a piece of advice I've heard thrown around to composers a lot. You've probably heard it too.
"You should try to write at least a little bit of music every day."
This is bad advice.
For a multitude of reasons that I won't get into here, I've had a terrible few months. Just awful. My creative output has suffered as a result. I've still been making music, but it's been a slow, painstaking process. Lots of staring at empty Cubase sessions, wondering why I can't come up with any ideas. And while I have been happy with what I have managed to make, I haven't had that feeling that happens when you make something you really, really love, like you've figured out how to transform a part of yourself into a track and release it to the world.
I didn't fully realize it, but what I needed was a bre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Netflix’s TimeSeries Data Abstraction Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/31552f6326f8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-netflix-timeseries-data-abstraction-layer-31552f6326f8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Rajiv Shringi, Vinay Chella, Kaidan Fullerton, Oleksii Tkachuk, Joey Lynch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Like a Painter]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-painter/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-painter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a homeowner, you know how daunting it can feel to paint your entire house at once. Hiring someone to do it can be expensive, and doing it yourself can seem overwhelming.
But what if you painted one side every other year? It suddenly becomes a much more manageable task. It can even be enjoyable, perhaps combined with a barbecue with your neighbors. Plus, your house always looks beautiful.
Starting a blog can feel similarly overwhelming. We see other bloggers posting regularly, creating every possible slash page, and participating in every blogging challenge that comes along.
Let go of all that pressure. Start at your own pace, in your own way.
Begin with just one post. It doesn't have to be anything special, a paragraph or two is plenty. The main thing is to get started.
When the weekend comes, maybe you'll sit down and create an "About" page. Now you have both a blog post and a page that describes you and your blog.
Step by step, you'll build your blog on your own terms. No musts or deadlines. It's your blog, you set the rules – no one else.
Soon, you'll have painted a beautiful blog that looks great from every angle, year after year.
Community echoes
FW: Blog Like a Painter by Yordi
(I am) the painter with dried up paint cans by Jedda
Re: Blog Like a Painter by Helen Chong
Re: Blog Like a Painter by Dominik
Blog Like a Community by So... Axodys?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare acquires Kivera to add simple, preventive cloud security to Cloudflare One]]></title>
        <id>6e7vmGCa8tZRTNJWqYs1di</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-acquires-kivera"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition and integration of Kivera broadens the scope of Cloudflare’s SASE platform beyond just apps, incorporating increased cloud security through proactive configuration management of cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Kagan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Kubernetes virtual machines at Cloudflare with KubeVirt]]></title>
        <id>1149BgOuHn2l6ubvzlzHar</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/leveraging-kubernetes-virtual-machines-with-kubevirt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes team runs several multi-tenant clusters across Cloudflare’s core data centers. When multi-tenant cluster isolation is too limiting for an application, we use KubeVirt. KubeVirt is a cloud-native solution that enables our developers to run virtual machines alongside containers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Cichra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VHRanger in "Nobel Prize in Physics awarded to John Hopfield and Geoffrey Hinton [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41776411</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41776411"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T12:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoffrey Hinton wins the Nobel prize in physics for giving physics postdocs more reasonable job market options]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VHRanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unprecedented since 2019: over 200 people joined the CADTM Autumn Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Unprecedented-since-2019-over-200-people-joined-the-CADTM-Autumn-Meetings</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Unprecedented-since-2019-over-200-people-joined-the-CADTM-Autumn-Meetings"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From October 4–6, 2024, CADTM Europe organized its autumn meetings. Over 200 people took part. They included activists from India, Mali, Spain, Côte d'Ivoire, Morocco, Mexico, Brazil, Netherlands, France, Burkina Fasso, Togo and the Democratic Republic of the Congo. Many were activists from Liège, with a significant proportion being young people. It's an autumn festival unlike any we've seen since 2019, with a fighting, militant, anti-racist, and anti-fascist spirit. Friday, October 4: Screening (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
CADTM, 
Colonialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM Belgique, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pëtr Kropotkin - A Letter on the Present War]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/petr-kropotkin-a-letter-on-the-present-war?v=1728337063</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/petr-kropotkin-a-letter-on-the-present-war?v=1728337063"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T21:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pëtr Kropotkin
Title: A Letter on the Present War
Date: October 1914
Notes: Published in Freedom vol. XXVIII, no. 306.
Source: Retrieved on 7th October 2024 from freedomnews.org.uk

[Our comrade P. Kropotkin, having been asked by the Swedish Professor G. Steffen[1] to give his opinion upon the present war, gave it in a letter which we reproduce, with the additions he made to it in the three last paragraphs.]
 DEAR STEFFEN, — You ask my opinion about the war. I have expressed it on several occasions in France, and the present events, unfortunately, only reinforce it. I consider that the duty of every one who cherishes the ideals of human progress altogether, and especially those that were inscribed by the European proletarians on the banner of the International Working Men’s Associa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Zeldman: I stayed, and declined an Automattic severance]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8639</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/jeffrey-zeldman-declined-automattic-severance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City based web designer, standards advocate, founder of A List Apart, and many other things, Jeffrey Zeldman: I stayed because I believe in the work we do. I believe in the open web and owning your own content. I’ve devoted nearly three decades of work to this cause, and when I chose to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please write it, do not stream it]]></title>
        <id>https://rimarin.bearblog.dev/please-write-it-do-not-stream-it/</id>
        <link href="https://rimarin.bearblog.dev/please-write-it-do-not-stream-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T19:20:30.169Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I cannot help but notice an even stronger trend of content creators abandoning any written expression, in favour of untamed video or audio streams.
One guy had a very cool blog about FIRE and abandoned it completely to devote himself to video streams and become an entertainer; a week ago, a software engineering blogger started focusing on a podcast and I'm afraid it will end up the same way.
Writing forces you to organise your thoughts, divide them up logically and tell a coherent story. Ideas become condensed and accessible. Also easier to discuss, update and comment. Usually, you can go back and re-read at any time, streamed content seems doomed to be a one-off.
Of course reading is cognitively more demanding, but it is also the better option for learning and memory recognition. Not advocating against low-attention means of communication, but if the content is supposed to be educational, written content should be the default (possibly complemented by other mediums).
One annoying thing is the asymmetrical nature of time between creator and listener. When you write an article, you invest X time in writing it, but it only takes ~X/10 time to read it. It takes effort, but it pays off in terms of quality, while providing the best time-to-content ratio for the reader.
On the other hand, producing a video stream requires little effort and takes about the same time as the stream itself, but forces the watcher to invest much more time, while retaining less information.
While I cannot deny the power of videos to reach a wider audience, I wish they would more often consider the old-fashioned, forum-nostalgic boomers. These folks like to read ideas summarised in nice blog articles :)
P.S.: This article could have been a 20 minute video on YouTube or a 30 minute podcast, shall I switch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;On the Brink&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T18:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and escalation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: HIPAA eligible with Amazon Q Business, Amazon DCV, AWS re:Post Agent, and more (Oct 07, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>238beac9f3f87197236d630385a99ae1acba128a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-q-business-is-hipaa-eligible-amazon-dcv-aws-repost-agent-and-more-oct-07-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday, I had the privilege of attending China Engineer’s Day 2024(CED 2024) in Hangzhou as the Amazon Web Services (AWS) speaker. The event was organized by the China Computer Federation (CCF), one of the most influential professional developer communities in China. At CED 2024, I spoke about how AI development tools can improve developer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thermal design supporting Gen 12 hardware: cool, efficient and reliable]]></title>
        <id>5GRHH8385Hxg3UHjINuHz8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/thermal-design-supporting-gen-12-hardware-cool-efficient-and-reliable"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great thermal solutions play a crucial role in hardware reliability and performance. Gen 12 servers have implemented an exhaustive thermal analysis to ensure optimal operations within a wide variety of temperature conditions and use cases. By implementing new design and control features for improved power efficiency on the compute nodes we also enabled the support of powerful accelerators to serve our customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leslye Paniagua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philosophy & Public Affairs is not dead yet]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53257</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/07/philosophy-public-affairs-is-not-dead-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most interesting developments in the little world of political theory / philosophy in recent years has been the mass resignation of the editorial teams of both Philosophy & Public Affairs, and Journal of Political Philosophy. Public statements from both groups suggested they were disturbed by their existing publishers’ injunctions to publish in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do Climate Risk Indices Measure?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31740</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/what-do-climate-risk-indices-measure/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As interest in understanding the economic impacts of climate change grows, the climate economics and finance literature has developed a number of indices to quantify climate risks. Various approaches have been employed, utilizing firm-level emissions data, financial market data (from equity and derivatives markets), or textual data. Focusing on the latter approach, we conduct descriptive analyses of six text-based climate risk indices from published or well-cited papers. In this blog post, we highlight the differences and commonalities across these indices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hyeyoon Jung and Oliver Hannaoui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austerity, dispossession and injustice: Facets of the debt crisis in Sri Lanka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Austerity-dispossession-and-injustice-Facets-of-the-debt-crisis-in-Sri-Lanka</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Austerity-dispossession-and-injustice-Facets-of-the-debt-crisis-in-Sri-Lanka"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka defaulted on its external debt for the first time in its postcolonial history in April 2022. The International Monetary Fund (IMF)-led process of recovery that followed has not only been disastrous in terms of the economic policy package proposed by the Government. The underlying analysis of the causes of the debt crisis itself is also flawed. Sri Lanka provides lessons about both the broken global financial system and the widespread consequences of an unjust debt resolution (...)
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahilan Kadirgamar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>