<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-17T07:18:42.167Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-17T07:18:42.167Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Cryptocurrency as an Offshore Banking Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325604</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/us-cryptocurrency-as-an-offshore-banking-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T06:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Wall Street Journal ran a revealing op-ed today (June 14, 2024) by Paul D. Ryan, “Crypto Could Stave off a U.S. Debt Crisis.” Mr. Ryan, libertarian Republican House Speaker 2015-2019 and now at the right-wing American Enterprise Institute, writes that: “Stablecoins backed by dollars provide demand for U.S. public debt and a way to  More
The post US Cryptocurrency as an Offshore Banking Center appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Public Lands Conservation in Montana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325741</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/the-future-of-public-lands-conservation-in-montana/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A great recent article by Chris D’Angelo reports on the connection between Tim Sheehy, the Republican challenging Jon Tester for his senate seat, and PERC, the Bozeman-based Property and Environment Research Center that promotes what it calls “free market environmentalism.” While Montanans might wonder about Sheehy’s background and policy positions given the shifting sands in  More
The post The Future of Public Lands Conservation in Montana appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Years of Failed Education Reforms, Chicago Embraces Community Schools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325743</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/after-years-of-failed-education-reforms-chicago-embraces-community-schools/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Until now, we haven’t even tried to make big-city school districts work, especially for children of color,” Jhoanna Maldonado said when Our Schools asked her to describe what Chicago Mayor Brandon Johnson and his supporters have in mind for the public school system of the nation’s third-largest city. Johnson scored a surprising win in the 2023 mayoral  More
The post After Years of Failed Education Reforms, Chicago Embraces Community Schools appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Bryant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Food Companies Intentionally Make Their Products Addictive, and It’s Leading to Chronic Diseases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325746</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/food-companies-intentionally-make-their-products-addictive-and-its-leading-to-chronic-diseases/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t stop eating that bag of chips until you’re licking the salt nestled in the corners of the empty package from your fingers? You’re not alone. And it’s not entirely your fault that the intended final handful of chips was not, indeed, your last for that snacking session. Many common snack foods have been expertly  More
The post Food Companies Intentionally Make Their Products Addictive, and It’s Leading to Chronic Diseases appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melissa Kravitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nonfiction Summer Reading Recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325659</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/nonfiction-summer-reading-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. “The Emperor’s Nightmare” by Robert A. G. Monks (2022). Harvard lawyer, former CEO and Shareholder Rights Activist, Monks digs deep inside big corporate power and the devastating impact of this corpocracy on weakened democratic institutions. Constitutional reset is crucial, he concludes. 2. “Corporate Bullsh*t: Exposing the Lies and Half-Truths That Protect Profit, Power, and  More
The post Nonfiction Summer Reading Recommendations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fair Tax Agenda for Wall Street]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325558</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/a-fair-tax-agenda-for-wall-street/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is written testimony prepared for a June 12, 2024 Senate Budget Committee hearing on “Making Wall Street Pay Its Fair Share: Raising Revenue, Strengthening Our Economy.” Thank you, Chairman Whitehouse, Ranking Member Grassley, and members of the committee, for the invitation to participate in this important hearing. I am Sarah Anderson, Global Economy  More
The post A Fair Tax Agenda for Wall Street appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The French Left Unite Against Fascism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325650</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/the-french-left-unite-against-fascism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French politics has been in chaos since President Macron announced a snap general election after the victory of the far right Rassemblement Nationale (RN) in the European elections. Jordan Bardella’s RN list took 31,37 % of the vote. Eric Zemmour’s Reconquest list led by Marine le Pen’s niece, Marion Maréchal Le Pen, took another 5, 47%  More
The post The French Left Unite Against Fascism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catherine Curran Vigier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CPI Without Owner’s Equivalent Rent Has Been at Fed Target for a Year]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325568</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/cpi-without-owners-equivalent-rent-has-been-at-fed-target-for-a-year/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:24:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s a bit of an exaggeration, but the Consumer Price Index (CPI), excluding owners’ equivalent rent (OER) fell to 1.4 percent in June 2023 and has remained pretty close, but mostly above 2.0 percent ever since. We all know the Fed targets the Personal Consumption Expenditure Deflator, where the OER has a smaller weight, but  More
The post CPI Without Owner’s Equivalent Rent Has Been at Fed Target for a Year appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overwhelmed by Anger Around Us? Thoughts on How to De-escalate a Situation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325499</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/overwhelmed-by-anger-around-us-thoughts-on-how-to-de-escalate-a-situation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I leaned halfway out of the car window, furiously shaking a finger at the car zooming from behind us in the next lane. “You stay there!” I roared. “Let my mother out!” We were on the freeway and my mom had pulled to the shoulder to let an ambulance pass. As soon as it did,  More
The post Overwhelmed by Anger Around Us? Thoughts on How to De-escalate a Situation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melinda Burrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why economics is such an impossible science]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45424</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/17/why-economics-is-such-an-impossible-science/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T04:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll In a word, Economics is an Impossible Science because by its own definition the determining conditions of the economy are not economic: they are “exogenous.” Supposedly a science of things, it is by definition without substance, being rather a mode of behavior: the application of scarce means to alternative ends so as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Agricultural Imperialism in the EU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273398</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/michael-hudson-agricultural-imperialism-in-the-eu.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T04:49:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How the US has used control over the supply of key agricultural commodities to defend its hegemony.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baby’s Whirlwind Tour of Animal Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325655</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/babys-whirlwind-tour-of-animal-exploitation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T04:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other day I rewatched Howard Hawk’s classic 1938 romantic comedy, Bringing Up Baby, for the first time in what was probably decades. Katharine Hepburn and Cary Grant star as an eccentric heiress and straightlaced paleontologist who come into possession of a leopard. Apparently, the beloved film was a box-office bomb. Hepburn’s heiress, Susan Vance,  More
The post Baby’s Whirlwind Tour of Animal Exploitation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons in Decency, Fathers to Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325652</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/17/lessons-in-decency-fathers-to-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T04:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a scientist who researches peace and conflict, I find it important to systematically approach questions and see where the evidence leads me. It is a trait I developed from great mentorship, and a value that was instilled in me by my father from a very young age. He was medical doctor, with a specialty  More
The post Lessons in Decency, Fathers to Children appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wim Laven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intermezzo by Sally Rooney, on bookshelves in September 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7817</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/intermezzo-sally-rooney-bookshelves-september-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T21:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intermezzo, the fourth novel by Irish literary fiction author Sally Rooney, will be published on 24 September 2024*. The synopsis is classic Rooney: Aside from the fact that they are brothers, Peter and Ivan Koubek seem to have little in common. Peter is a Dublin lawyer in his thirties — successful, competent and apparently unassailable. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The WWDC edition of the Talk Show, ChatGPT, tall poppy syndrome]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7831</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wwdc-edition-the-talk-show-chatgpt-tall-poppy-syndrome/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T20:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Gruber, of Daring Fireball, presented another edition of the Talk Show, at Apple’s annual Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC). The live show featured usual Apple executives Craig Federighi and Greg Joswiak, who were joined this year by John Giannandrea, perhaps best known for his work with Siri, Apple’s digital assistant. I’m hardly an Apple aficionado, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sixteen Dad Jokes in Honor of Father’s Day (with Zeisgeistiana)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273395</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/sixteen-dad-jokes-in-honor-of-fathers-day-with-zeitgeistiana.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T19:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What will a future Zeitgeist historian think?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting (and reading) the classics]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/collecting-and-reading-the-classics/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/collecting-and-reading-the-classics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T17:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always loved reading, even as a child. I remember reading under the covers until 2am, way past lights out and my bedtime. I would go to the library after school and put my name down on the waiting list for newly released books. I'd (im)patiently wait for my turn.
But for some reason, I never appreciated the books we were assigned to read in school. I'm not quite sure if it's due to the selection of books, or just the fact that I was required to read it (I’m not great at being told what to do). Either way, I would read the books I wanted, and read cliff notes (are cliff notes still a thing today?) of those that I didn't read for school.
Needless to say, I completely regret showing a lack of appreciation for the classic books. To make up for it, I am attempting to build up a collection of books I admire that I should've appreciated a long time ago. The goal is to get the covers I remember from back in the day, instead of the more modernized version.
Yesterday’s thrift finds:
Bridge to Terabithia
A Wrinkle in Time
The Great Gatsby
The Metamorphoses
It joins my (still small) existing collection of:
Lord of the Flies
To Kill a Mockingbird
A Tale of Two Cities
Fahrenheit 451
Gulliver's Travels
One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest
Now I just need to find the time to re-read them all. Do you have a favorite classic must-read?
Bonus find: An original Sound of Music vinyl record -- this was a super happy find. I initially found a really scratched one, but thankfully found a total of THREE at the thrift store. I was able to pick the one that didn't have a lot of scratches on it. Super excited to play it on the record player.
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pclmulqdq in "The Raspberry Pi 5 Is No Match for a Tini-Mini-Micro PC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40698732</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40698732"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T17:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think a lot of people don't realize that there was a decent size, but small market for SBCs for low-volume embedded work (including hobbyists) before Raspberry Pi. You could get a lot of different kinds of boards with good Linux support and a not terrible price. Often, a processor vendor would explicitly provide support for these things because it was a good vector for selling chips.
Broadcom, having never wanted anything to do with this market since volumes were too low, had an abundance of a CPU SKU that was good for this. So some broadcom engineers founded Raspberry Pi to use up this excess stock, essentially getting these chips for free. The original RPi blew every other SBC out of the water on price performance (and many manufacturers out of the market) because by getting the most expensive component for free, they could sell Pis for an extremely low price. It also massively expanded the market for SBCs, as hobbyists flooded in to work with RPis.
5-10 years ago, the sweetheart deal with Broadcom went away. Now Raspberry Pi has to compete with everyone else for Broadcom SoCs, and during the semiconductor shortage of 2020, Broadcom had tremendous leverage. Now, Raspberry Pi pricing is nothing special, but they still have the brand name and they have captured the community (on the back of behavior that was borderline anticompetitive).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pclmulqdq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwup238 in "The Raspberry Pi 5 Is No Match for a Tini-Mini-Micro PC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40698163</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40698163"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T16:20:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That's because RaspberryPis are no longer cheap throw away computers meant for education or hobbyists, they're developer kits for manufacturers that need a CPU running a well supported mainline Linux in their products.
The only reason they don't cost $500 or more is because the foundation needs the hobbyist market to write and support the open source BSP, without which the RPi would be just another poorly supported also-ran in an already crowded market. With how well supported mainline Linux is on the Pi, EEs would be willing to pay a lot more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwup238</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Cracks in a Grey Sky: An Anthology of Do or Die]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cracks-in-a-grey-sky-an-anthology-of-do-or-die?v=1718546895</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cracks-in-a-grey-sky-an-anthology-of-do-or-die?v=1718546895"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T14:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Cracks in a Grey Sky: An Anthology of Do or Die
Subtitle: Voices from the Ecological Resistance
Date: 2016
Notes: End footnotes 1, 2 & 3 were missing from “Bashing the GE-nie back in the Bottle” in the source book & original source magazine, and so marked as missing. Text body footnotes were marked, but missing from “Reports and Thoughts on the Action in Derbyshire”, but found from the original source magazine and so added back in. A marked, but missing footnote from “An Open Letter to the Minister for Transport” was found in the original source magazine and so added back in.
Source: PDF provided by publisher

An Introduction
 It’s strange to put together a collection of articles from a publication that has been defunct for 13+ years and from nearly 9000 km a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273378</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T10:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our feather-light daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bird Flu Tests Are Hard To Get. So How Will We Know When To Sound the Pandemic Alarm?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273390</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/bird-flu-tests-are-hard-to-get-so-how-will-we-know-when-to-sound-the-pandemic-alarm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T10:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It’s hard to not compare this to covid, where early on we only tested people who had traveled."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Iceland (2011)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52781</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/16/sunday-photoblogging-iceland-2011/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T10:07:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny Things That I Like]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/tiny-things-that-i-like/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/tiny-things-that-i-like/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiny gatherings
Tiny cafés
Tiny concerts
Tiny art
Tiny lists
Tiny record stores
Tiny blog posts
Tiny automations
Least weasels
Tiny Things That I Don't Like
Cups of coffee
Website text
Screws
And you, what are some of your favorite tiny things?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BLKNSLVR in "What You Get After Running an SSH Honeypot for 30 Days"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40695141</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40695141"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T06:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I self-host a (non-critical) mail server and a few other things and occasionally look at live firewall logs, seeing the constant flow of illegitimate traffic hitting random ports all over the place, some hitting legitimate service ports but others just probing basically anything and everything. I decided to setup a series of scripts that detect activity on ports that aren't open (and therefore there's no legitimate reason for the traffic to exist) and block those IP addresses from the service ports since the traffic source isn't to be trusted.
Something that came out of analysis of the blocked IP addresses was that I discovered a few untrustworthy /24 networks belonging to a bunch of "internet security companies" whose core business seems to depend on flooding the entire IPv4 space with daily scans. Blocking these Internet scanner networks significantly reduced the uninvited activity on my open service ports. And by significantly I mean easily over 50% of unwanted traffic is blocked.
Network lists and various scripts to achieve my setup can be found here:
https://github.com/UninvitedActivity/UninvitedActivity
Internet Scanner lists are here:
https://github.com/UninvitedActivity/UninvitedActivity/tree/...
Large networks that seem responsible for more than their fair share of uninvited activity are listed here:
https://github.com/UninvitedActivity/UninvitedActivity/tree/...
I'm semi-aware of the futility of blocking IP addresses and networks. I do believe, however, that it can significantly reduce the load on the next layers of security that require computation for pattern matching etc.
Be aware: there are footguns to be found here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BLKNSLVR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Closing in on the Kill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325526</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/16/closing-in-on-the-kill/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T05:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reading a recent update on the consequences of firing up the fossil fuels, a longtime correspondent told me, “I look at my grandchild, age 5, and think about her early death.” The rest of the story is that grandparents have been getting their own lives cut short in heatwaves which have, by the way, […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Closing in on the Kill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lance Olsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just keep doing the bit (Karma Yoga Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been preparing for job interviews (looking to get into genai+backend roles you know). I like building projects and learning new stuff but job search is something that scares me. Partly because of the various uncertainties involved like places to apply, strenous interview processes, where I would work next, what kind of work I will get. It’s not the first time I am going through this process but it sucks (a lot in the beginning atleast). The other aspect is the grind.
Translation: I am not afraid of slap sir, I am afraid of job search
I could be solving some leetcode problems right now, I could be applying right now… I have many things to do even outside job search - oh no - fuck fuck fuck. That’s sort of the state of my mind - atleast in the background. Till I don’t build some momen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bognition in "French court orders Google, Cloudflare, Cisco to poison DNS to stop piracy"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40693760</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40693760"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last decade Tech has become part of the establishment. They are one of the dominant controlling forces.
The blackout was _not_ about preserving free speech, or any other moral high road.  It was purely about control. Tech hadn’t yet cemented their position as a dominant player and didn’t want to cede the control they had.
Now that they’ve embedded themselves in the ruling class they don’t care as much because they already have control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bognition</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by snowwrestler in "French court orders Google, Cloudflare, Cisco to poison DNS to stop piracy"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40693679</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40693679"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:21:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a decade ago, a ton of tech companies (including Google) coordinated a “blackout the Internet” day of protest against U.S. legislation that would have required them to alter DNS to fight piracy. Interesting that now that France actually does it, they say they will comply.
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protests_against_SOPA_and_PI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>snowwrestler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting for the nova]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52761</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/15/waiting-for-the-nova/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T22:20:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“You’re always building models. Stone circles. Cathedrals. Pipe-organs. Adding machines. I got no idea why I’m here now, you know that? But if the run goes off tonight, you’ll have finally managed the real thing.” “I don’t know what you’re talking about.” “That’s ‘you’ in the collective. Your species.” — William Gibson, Neuromancer Sometime in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "Perplexity AI is lying about their user agent"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40691483</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40691483"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T18:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two different questions at play here, and we need to be careful what we wish for.
The first concern is the most legitimate one: can I stop an LLM from training itself on my data? This should be possible and Perplexity should absolutely make it easy to block them from training.
The second concern, though, is can Perplexity do a live web query to my website and present data from my website in a format that the user asks for? Arguing that we should ban this moves into very dangerous territory.
Everything from ad blockers to reader mode to screen readers do exactly the same thing that Perplexity is doing here, with the only difference being that they tend to be exclusively local. The very nature of a "user agent" is to be an automated tool that manipulates content hosted on the internet according to the specifications given to the tool by the user. I have a hard time seeing an argument against Perplexity using this data in this way that wouldn't apply equally to countless tools that we already all use and which companies try with varying degrees of success to block.
I don't want to live in a world where website owners can use DRM to force me to display their website in exactly the way that their designers envisioned it. I want to be able to write scripts to manipulate the page and present it in a way that's useful for me. I don't currently use llms this way, but I'm uncomfortable with arguing that it's unethical for them to do that so long as they're citing the source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/hello-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/hello-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been keeping an eye on Bear Blog for a while. I really like the approach and philosophy. Bear Blog is simple, fast, customizable and focuses on privacy and pure writing. And since some of my favorite blogs also use this blogging platform, I thought I'd give Bear Blog a try too.
So here we go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s a Palestinian Life Worth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325519</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/15/whats-a-palestinian-life-worth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T14:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I have told my sons that they are not under any circumstances to take part in massacres and that the news of massacres of enemies is not to fill them with satisfaction or glee. “I have also told them not to work for companies which make massacre machinery, and to express contempt for people who […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What’s a Palestinian Life Worth? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I chose Bear for blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/chose-bear-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/chose-bear-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to start by saying that this will not be a "Bear is best" or "10 reasons why you should switch to Bear" kind of post.
There are many excellent blogging platforms available nowadays. The concept of "better" is not especially relevant. Ultimately, it depends on your personal preferences and requirements.
This post outlines why I chose Bear after trying many different tools. If your blogging preferences align with mine, then Bear might be the right platform for you too. If you're already happy with your current tool, congratulations – no need to keep reading.
Simplicity
At the last minute, I decided to leave this part out. Not that Bear isn't easy to use, it's very straightforward, but so are most other "indie platforms". You'll be up and running in no time, no matter what you pick.
Cu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273331</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T10:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our rambunctious daily links: Praise of decadence, psychedelics for health, US anti-vax campaign. uranium surge, US cops heart China drones, SA coalition, Gaza starvation accelerates, Putin peace plan, Trump selling to highest bidder, Biden wanders off at G-7, bump stocks back, AI candidate, moar bad Boeing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Snap Elections: ‘Cohabitation’ Could Reshuffle the Cards Between President and Prime Minister]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273362</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/french-snap-elections-cohabitation-could-reshuffle-the-cards-between-president-and-prime-minister.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T10:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the practical consequences if French President Emmanuel Macron's centrist bloc fares poorly in the upcoming snap elections?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced Rollout Techniques: Custom Strategies for Stateful Apps in Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16626</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/kube-stateful-rollouts/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T07:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog post—A Simple Kubernetes Admission Webhook—I discussed the process of creating a Kubernetes webhook without relying on Kubebuilder. At Slack, we use this webhook for various tasks, like helping us support long-lived Pods (see Supporting Long-Lived Pods), and today, I delve once more into the topic of long-lived Pods, focusing on our […]
The post Advanced Rollout Techniques: Custom Strategies for Stateful Apps in Kubernetes appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clément Labbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sixdimensional in "Voyager 1 is back online: NASA spacecraft returns data from all 4 instruments"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40687966</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40687966"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T06:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing this news is a nice tribute to Ed Stone, who was one of the core project scientists for Voyager and recently passed [1] (and all those who work/worked on the program).
I had the pleasure of meeting Dr. Stone at a public NASA event many years ago.  I asked him, perhaps a silly question: "what does it feel like to know you built the furthest man-made known object in the universe?".
He paused for a moment, after which he responded, with a smile: "Pretty darn good".
RIP, Dr. Stone and go Voyager go!
[1] https://www.jpl.nasa.gov/news/ed-stone-former-director-of-jp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sixdimensional</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: US Cryptocurrency as an Offshore Banking Center]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273360</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/michael-hudson-us-cryptocurrency-as-an-offshore-banking-center.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T06:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another cryptocurrency scheme, here for its major use case, tax evasion. But for a good cause, the US dollar!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Must be High or Low]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325502</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/15/it-must-be-high-or-low/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T05:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Cott has written about the meaning of those stories and rhymes we consider to be for children. He has also written about the childlike nature of certain rock and pop songs, especially certain songs by The Beatles and Donovan. He has interviewed artists, musicians, writers and others from Chinua Achebe to John Lennon and many more. His works refer to everyone from Carl Jung to Tony Bennett; Rollo May to the Old Testament; Greg Bateson to Gaston Bachelard. At times, his ability to connect seemingly disparate phenomena is mind-blowing. Other time, one nods their head knowingly at a reference that they might have often considered just to see it verified via Cott’s quotation and argument tying the two things together. Some might consider his considerations too fanciful while others might see them as so simply obvious they wonder why he bothered to even write them down.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post It Must be High or Low appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mk zariel - ambassador of homosexuality]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mk-zariel-ambassador-of-homosexuality?v=1718394609</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mk-zariel-ambassador-of-homosexuality?v=1718394609"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: mk zariel
Title: ambassador of homosexuality
Date: Summer 2024
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 queers like us ache to carve ourselves starring roles in the pageant 
 called gay rights. become picture-perfect 
 assimilated gays who’ve never once had an emotional breakdown 
 queers like us can’t have problems can we? if we do, you will realize 
 your hierarchies spell death for our chosen family 
 so queers like us create the illusion of the normal 
 erase the the way a slur not yet reclaimed 
 burns holes in luminous queer skin, our relatives claiming they don’t think of us as gay 
 and worst of all, we’re free: to be complicit in murder, to marry our oppressors 
 but in three fifths of the country, not all that free fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neltnerb in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683864</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683864"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I do not think it is cynical to assume that Microsoft would sell this to companies as a way to do constant surveillance of their employees with OCR and LLMs used to make it easier for a manager to sift through massive amounts of data.
That's just an actual use case that their true customers would pay for, I think it's awful and should be illegal under any reasonable worker protections but why would they not advertise it this way privately to business customers?
I also don't think it's cynical to think that a manager looking for a reason to get rid of someone will have a much easier time justifying a PIP or just straight up firing someone if they can retroactively have an AI do it for them.
Why wouldn't they be able to ask the system "how much of 's time do they spend doing things on the computer that are not directly related to ?"
Is it technically happening already? Sure, there's nasty nasty spyware being forced on people and it is awful and I hate that those employers are getting away with it. But integrated into the OS, on by default, with a long memory? Just imagine how easy it will be to fire anyone that tries to unionize in an effort to fight against such surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neltnerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Audrid - What makes you think you can govern me?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-what-makes-you-think-you-can-govern-me?v=1718391451</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-what-makes-you-think-you-can-govern-me?v=1718391451"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Audrid
Title: What makes you think you can govern me?
Date: Summer 2024.
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 What makes you think you can govern me? 
 When my mind is about to explode and fling 
 Shrapnel in every direction and into the void 
 For this soul of mine is weeping, while yours gently 
 Blow sleeping in the gaze of protective eyes. 
 Barrage the barricades of your world ‘til they tumble 
 Crumble onto the doorstep of our anarchist utopia? 
 A ticking fission or fusion bomb around the nuclear family - 
 I cannot wait until it disintegrates into ash 
 It never did anything to me - Blood 
 Lines only weave together pain - Choose 
 Your own kind over the abstract confines 
 Of a triple helix with the extra back 
 Bone of suffering. 
 The bigotry ebbs and flows through our collective 
 Memories that we perhaps should forget but cannot 
 Unsee through flashbacks of those who harmed - 
 Us, through bricks at glass and break the institution 
 That hates us - that seeks to eradicate us 
 Yas I may be extreme but was that ever a bad thing - 
 I’ll just shine with the light of a trillion photons 
 Exploding and releasing the energy 
 Of my ungovernable queer self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Audrid - Dear Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-dear-society?v=1718391083</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-dear-society?v=1718391083"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Audrid
Title: Dear Society
Date: Summer 2024.
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 Dear Society, 
 Telling me the way to go - never fit myself into your gender 
 Confines and even in my disruption their compulsion to fit 
 Me into a box flickers behind… shadows. The flames 
 Burning my mind, or am I burning. Fuck. Their stereotypes. 
 You cannot speak up about anything. Be passionate. 
 Rant about ableism and transphobia and they give strange looks 
 And yeah girls can do that, but I’m not one of them… 
 And my identity of being loud… is this just internalized misogyny…? 
 Head and a broken body, too wrong, but I feel no connection to the physical 
 Right…? 
 I guess that’s a lie. Cannot be stoic. Only a fragment. 
 If …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by segasaturn in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683526</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683526"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My takeaway is that Microsoft has been trying to boil the frog, but slipped and turned the temperature up too quickly. They're retreating for now, but make no mistake that Recall will slowly trickle back into Windows under another name. Every major power broker wants something like Recall to become the norm - bosses to spy on their employees, governments to spy on their citizens/enemies, and tech CEO's to collect training data for AI and target more ads at end users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>segasaturn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by digging in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683432</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683432"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is confusing and vague to me, which I believe is exactly the intent. It focuses on security, reiterates that security is their top priority (and we know that this is untrue). What were the security problems? They don't even allude to the existence or detection of any specific security problems.
It sounds to me like they're figuring out a new marketing approach, or they're softening the blow by "listening to users" and then rolling out more slowly, when outrage has died down and people will just accept it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>digging</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free trade frenzy: the hidden costs of South Asia's economic gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Free-trade-frenzy-the-hidden-costs-of-South-Asia-s-economic-gamble</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Free-trade-frenzy-the-hidden-costs-of-South-Asia-s-economic-gamble"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As debt pressures rise, South Asia's economic strategies are increasingly revolving around FTAs. The frenzy, however, is not only reshaping the region's trade dynamics, but also a wide array of national legal frameworks, from labour rights to agriculture policies. 
English

/ 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
South Asia, 
Free Trade/Trade Liberalisation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GRAIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273335</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics; new Covid charts: stay safe out there; Kamala!; sleep and memory ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lina Moe: &ldquo;Hard Work&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hard-work</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hard-work"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T16:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The art of Käthe Kollwitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by benjedwards in "I found a 55 year old bug in the first Lunar Lander game"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40680958</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40680958"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If anyone is curious, in 2009, I discovered that Jim Storer was the author of the first Lunar Lander game and interviewed him about it (and also chronicled the history of the game beyond that). He later provided the source code, which was awesome.
https://technologizer.com/2009/07/19/lunar-lander/index.html
My favorite part is this:
“After leaving high school I never thought about the game again,” says Storer. “Until about a couple of months ago when someone e-mailed me about this, I was completely unaware of any Lunar Lander game other than the one I wrote in high school.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benjedwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Debilitating a Generation”: Expert Warns That Long COVID May Eventually Affect Most Americans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273327</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/debilitating-a-generation-expert-warns-that-long-covid-may-eventually-affect-most-americans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some updates on long Covid make for an indictment of US public health. Not that that should come as a surprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Fed DSGE Model Forecast—June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30360</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/the-new-york-fed-dsge-model-forecast-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post presents an update of the economic forecasts generated by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s dynamic stochastic general equilibrium (DSGE) model. We describe very briefly our forecast and its change since March 2024. As usual, we wish to remind our readers that the DSGE model forecast is not an official New York Fed forecast, but only an input to the Research staff’s overall forecasting process. For more information about the model and variables discussed here, see our DSGE model Q & A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, Ramya Nallamotu, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jacques Rancière: &ldquo;Grand Éditeur&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/grand-editeur</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/grand-editeur"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Hazan (1936-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273309</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our mercurial daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our meaningless modern lives: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45418</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/14/our-meaningless-modern-lives-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog The Most Valuable Kind of Knowledge These lectures aim to provide the reader with knowledge. But what is knowledge? Our lives consist of a small number of infinitely precious moments. What makes it worthwhile to invest these moments in the acquisition of knowledge? Is it the kind of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asad Zaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plain text journaling]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/plain-text-journaling/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/plain-text-journaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T07:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been journalling for a long time now. It's something I don't even think about anymore; just a thing I do. Some people meditate, others pray. I write.
I've published a few essays about how journaling has impacted my life by providing the space for me to reflect on my day. One thing I have never done until this year, however, is read any of my old journals.
This may seem strange, since what is the point of writing if not to be read. But that isn't why I do it. I write as a practice. As a thing that I do. If all my journals were lost in a house fire, I'd be sad, yes. But the documentation of my life isn't what's valuable. That value has already been gleaned through the act itself.
That being said, I tried reading one of my old journals at the beginning of this year and it turns out I can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The edge of extinction]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52771</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/14/the-edge-of-extinction/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T07:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Referring back to this 2002 post defining “neoliberalism”, I find the claim that the “The (UK) Conservative party is hovering on the edge of extinction”. That wasn’t one of my more accurate assessments, and I’m bearing it in mind when I look at suggestions that the party is now “facing a defeat so dramatic it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Way Out in Nuseirat: the Great Hostage Rescue Massacre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325396</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/no-way-out-in-nuseirat-the-great-hostage-rescue-massacre/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T06:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Americans knew. The Americans helped. The Americans provided the bombs, the helicopters, the fighter jets, the bullets and the tank shells. The Americans watched the attack unfold. They watched from Biden's pier. They watched from drones. They watched as the streets filled with blood, bodies and limbs. Afterward, the Americans praised the rescue operation and said nothing about the dead Palestinian children and women. Nothing about the amputees and the eviscerated. Nothing about the three hostages who were also apparently killed in the Israeli attack, including an American citizen.  More
The post No Way Out in Nuseirat: the Great Hostage Rescue Massacre  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Can’t Fix the Immigration System by Banning Asylum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325345</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/biden-cant-fix-the-immigration-system-by-banning-asylum/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden once pledged to adopt more humane immigration policies than his predecessor.  But in practice, as immigrant rights advocates have documented, his administration has escalated the attack on the legal right of people facing life-threatening conditions to seek safety. Even though this right is guaranteed regardless of how asylum seekers enter the country, he has sought to restrict access to ports of entry. More
The post Biden Can’t Fix the Immigration System by Banning Asylum appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanted: a Mass Uprising Against the Neoliberal Matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325303</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/wanted-a-mass-uprising-against-the-neoliberal-matrix/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neoliberalism seems impermeable to the facts. The theory is that markets are efficient, and privatization, deregulation, and liberalization will bring about the best of all possible worlds, so if the facts don’t fit the theory, so much the worse for the facts. The image that has haunted me is one from the movie The Matrix, where human beings are plugged into a system that has them dreaming of a pleasant alternate reality while their bodies are being sucked dry of the nutrients and energy to feed alien beings. More
The post Wanted: a Mass Uprising Against the Neoliberal Matrix appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead Man’s Hand: Betting on Biden and Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325376</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/dead-mans-hand-betting-on-biden-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the current presidential election, the betting odds have Donald Trump as the favorite (-109), which estimates his chances at 52%, while Joe Biden is close but behind at +122, which puts his odds at 45%. (By way of definition, these odds mean anyone who bets $109 on Trump to win will receive, if he does win, $100. By contrast, $100 bet on Biden to win will earn you $122 if he prevails.) More
The post Dead Man’s Hand: Betting on Biden and Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Isolated: Why Some Western Capitals Are Shifting Positions on Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325398</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/america-isolated-why-some-western-capitals-are-shifting-positions-on-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 6, Spain joined South Africa’s case at the United Nations top Court, accusing Israel of genocide. This move followed a decision by Madrid and two other western European capitals – Dublin and Oslo – to recognize the state of Palestine, thus breaking ranks with a long-established US-led western policy. As per American thinking,  More
The post America Isolated: Why Some Western Capitals Are Shifting Positions on Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamonds and Cold Dust: Slaughter at Nuseirat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325291</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/diamonds-and-cold-dust-slaughter-at-nuseirat/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ashes had barely settled on a Rafah tent camp incinerated by an Israeli airstrike before the next, gorged massacre presented itself for posterity’s gloomy archive.  It was intended as a golden operation and had been months in the making.  The rescue of four Israeli hostages, the killing of three others (bound to happen for the expertly inclined), and the massacre of over 274 Palestinians at the Nuseirat refugee camp were the end result.  More
The post Diamonds and Cold Dust: Slaughter at Nuseirat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chomsky & UN Forewarnings Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325382</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/chomsky-un-forewarnings-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently attended a family affair in Upstate NY and was informed that climate change articles, like this one, are too negative, causing close relatives to shutdown and going so far as to ignore articles, too gloomy, too negative, do something more positive. My response: Analyzing the planet’s climate system by studying peer-reviewed scientific publications  More
The post Chomsky & UN Forewarnings Revisited appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A WWII Canadian Soldier Honored for Killing Allied Troops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325292</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/a-wwii-canadian-soldier-honored-for-killing-allied-troops/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Normandy celebrations of the 80th anniversary of D Day commemorated the victory of the Allies against the Axis powers. But a very different recent celebration in Italy paid tribute to a WWII Allied soldier who shot and killed fellow Allied soldiers. The heroics of the young Italian Canadian officer Captain Tony Scotti shooting French  More
The post A WWII Canadian Soldier Honored for Killing Allied Troops appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End the Israeli War on Gaza and Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325463</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/end-the-israeli-war-on-gaza-and-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight months ago, Israel began a genocidal war against Gaza and the further increase of repression in the West Bank including thousands imprisoned, and expansion of the settlements there. Torture is commonplace of Palestinian prisoners in the West Bank and especially of prisoners in Gaza. 90 per cent of the population of Gaza is hungry,  More
The post End the Israeli War on Gaza and Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bohmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False Flag Over Ramapo: a Novella in Legal Pleadings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325427</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/false-flag-over-ramapo-a-novella-in-legal-pleadings/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ramapo, New York is per capita one of the most ultra-Orthodox Jewish communities in the United States.  Split between an ardent pro-Israeli/Zionist community and the Satmar’s -one of the largest and most vocal Hasidic dynasties that recognizes neither the state of Israel nor Zionism as representative of Jewish faith or history- until recently Ramapo tried  More
The post False Flag Over Ramapo: a Novella in Legal Pleadings appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanley L. Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two European Thorns in the Empire’s Side: Rightist Orban and Leftist Fico (and Look What Happened to Him)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325288</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/two-european-thorns-in-the-empires-side-rightist-orban-and-leftist-fico-and-look-what-happened-to-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hungary’s prime minister, Viktor Orban may be a far-right politician, but he also opposes the west’s proxy war in Ukraine and that, much more than his extreme conservatism, is what infuriates imperial henchmen. The European Union is in a constant snit over Orban, because every time that organization turns around, he blocks funds or weapons  More
The post Two European Thorns in the Empire’s Side: Rightist Orban and Leftist Fico (and Look What Happened to Him) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Teamsters Bearing Gifts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325467</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/beware-of-teamsters-bearing-gifts-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Except for a handful of insiders in the Teamsters and the Amazon Labor Union (ALU), few of us were aware that negotiations were being held to affiliate the ALU with Teamsters, until the recent announcement. If anything, most of us stopped paying attention to the ALU, which two years ago had an important breakthrough in winning  More
The post Beware of Teamsters Bearing Gifts appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Crypto Industry Dodges Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325455</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/how-the-crypto-industry-dodges-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent bill passed by the House of Representatives claims to regulate the cryptocurrency industry and protect consumers. But the bill is a Trojan horse designed by an industry flush with cash — the real kind. The Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act is the cryptocurrency industry’s big attempt to win favors from Washington.  More
The post How the Crypto Industry Dodges Regulation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Carss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They’re Arresting the Wrong People Inside of Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325423</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/theyre-arresting-the-wrong-people-inside-of-congress/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was arrested again inside of Congress for speaking out against US-backed genocide. Myself and others were brutally tackled and carried out of the room by Capitol Police. I was charged with “crowding, obstructing, or incommoding” for speaking out and holding a sign as the Secretary of State and the Secretary of Defense testified in Congress for  More
The post They’re Arresting the Wrong People Inside of Congress appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia DiNucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caste and the Colonization of Liberal Souls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325461</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/caste-and-the-colonization-of-liberal-souls/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The imagination!  [John] Brown’s faith in its transformative power was boundless…it gave him license to envision his death as an event that might spur the antislavery world to action…right down to “poor, little, dirty, ragged bare-headed and barefooted Slave Boys and Girls, led by some old grey-headed Slave Mother”  bearing witness to his hanging.    – Amy Godine,  More
The post Caste and the Colonization of Liberal Souls appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing Our Cool in the Twenty-First Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325386</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/losing-our-cool-in-the-twenty-first-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The odds are that the entire continental United States will swelter through a hotter-than-normal summer this year. And no surprise there. It seems as if that’s been the forecast every spring for years now. But this summer promises to eclipse even the summer of 2023, which, in the Northern Hemisphere, was the hottest since at least the year  More
The post Losing Our Cool in the Twenty-First Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you post determines your tribe]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/tribe/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/tribe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you post determines who you attract. Tweets are like prompts to attract fascinating people towards you based on shared context, ideas, interests, taste, knowledge, and expertise - your "context overlap" determines your tribe.
If you do shitposting, people who are here for fun will join (I think most people love shitposting, because even founders sometimes follow me and my mutuals for memes lol). In my experience, shitposting is often authentic. There's a lot of space for improv replying and leads to fun interactions -> good connections. People like to have fun together. Everyone should do it. It's the backbone of Twitter.
Posting about Rust or AI (I love to see there are several students who post ML stuff and then they follow and hype each other) will attract a different cluster, whil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics anon?]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T04:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics enough before indulging in optimization
hacks? Don't tell me you are already watching videos on how to do xyz thing fast instead of focusing on basics.
First step of optimization should be to profile if you are milking the basics enough or not.
Leveling up in anything boils down to a few simple processes. I repeat simple but hard to execute - doing minimum viable research to get started, understanding the basics, doing the thing and focusing.
Minimum viable research - finding the correct resources, enough to get started with, finding a mentor or a teacher. The emphasis is to get enough to get started. This is pretty easy especially for knowledge work given we have internet and chatgpt. The basics are more or less similar across most resources plus as you progress…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Worshipping Power]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-worshipping-power?v=1718332230</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-worshipping-power?v=1718332230"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T02:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Worshipping Power
Subtitle: An Anarchist View of Early State Formation
Date: January 10, 2017

 “And perhaps solving the mystery of the birth of the State might also permit us to clarify the conditions of the possibility […] of its death.” 
 —Pierre Clastres 
 “Acudid los anarquistas 
 empuñando la pistola hasta el morir 
 con petróleo y dinamita 
 toda clase de gobierno 
 a combatir 
 ¡y destruir!” 
 —“Arroja la Bomba” 
 Spanish anarchist song composed in prison in 1932, popularized in the revolution of 1936 
 Dedicated to Harold H. Thompson and Kuwasi Balagoon, who died in the dungeons of the State after decades of confinement, to Matías Catrileo, shot down in the struggle to regain his people’s land, and to all those who continue fighting, inside and out.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jean-Pierre Voyer - An inquiry into the causes and nature of the misery of people]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-an-inquiry-into-the-causes-and-nature-of-the-misery-of-people?v=1718317284</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-an-inquiry-into-the-causes-and-nature-of-the-misery-of-people?v=1718317284"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jean-Pierre Voyer
Title: An inquiry into the causes and nature of the misery of people
Date: 2017
Notes: Translated by Isaac Cronin, Roger Gregoire, and Linda Lanphear. Originally published by Champ Libre, 1976, Paris
Source: Text provided to library by the publisher.

Introduction
The Wicked Ways of This 
Devious World Explained 
An Inquiry into the Nature and Causes 
of the Misery of People
 In the mid 70s in Europe and the United States, the wave of radical revolt had ebbed. In the Bay Area, the Situationist milieu was quietly falling into inglorious disarray with vicious infighting over internal hierarchies based in part on male domination of the network. The New York-based former members of the American Situationist International had largely gone silent, had disappeared from t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jean-Pierre Voyer - It’s Crazy How Many Things Don’t Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-it-s-crazy-how-many-things-don-t-exist?v=1718316915</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-it-s-crazy-how-many-things-don-t-exist?v=1718316915"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jean-Pierre Voyer
Title: It’s Crazy How Many Things Don’t Exist
Subtitle: Selected Writings of Jean-Pierre Voyer
Date: 2015
Notes: Cruel Hospice 2015. “Reich, Mode d’emploi” was translated by Ken Knabb under the title “Reich, How to Use;” the other texts were translated collaboratively by Isaac Cronin, Roger Gregoire, and Linda Lanphear. Little Black Cart.
Source: PDF source provided to library by publisher

Introduction
Who is Jean-Pierre Voyer?
 French social thinkers don’t have the best reputation in America. Typically they are seen as humorless, self-important, elitist intellectuals whose purpose is to tell the world not only what to believe, but what to do with those beliefs. We know Jean-Pierre Voyer, and he is none of those things. He has worked as a cab driver, a plumber an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What about anti-virus apps? On going #IndieOS with Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7810</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-about-anti-virus-apps-on-going-indieos-with-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I wrote a few days ago, I’m in the process of trying out Linux operating systems, specifically Linux Mint. With the release of Windows 11, I think Microsoft has (finally) jumped the shark. Others will probably argue that happened long before Win 11 came along. They’re likely right. I’ve been doing a lot of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you use Vison Pro in a group or social setting?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7807</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/use-vison-pro-group-social-setting/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T20:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or when snuggled up on the sofa, say watching a movie, with your better half? I feel isolated when watching media, and it’s also much harder to snack and get cozy. This is a point — raised by Hacker News/Y Combinator member archagon — and is not something I’d thought of, in regards to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writers not using AI being accused of using AI… by AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7800</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/writers-not-using-ai-accused-using-ai-by-ai-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not anti-AI (well, not too much), but when there’s a one-hundred percent reliance on their abilities, and more crucially, the judgements some AI apps make, then there’s a problem. News that (human) writers and journalists, who have never used AI-powered tools in their work, but are being fired for apparently doing so, because an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On prioritising what you want to learn]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/on-prioritising-what-you-want-to-learn/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/on-prioritising-what-you-want-to-learn/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it's easy to get distracted by the current discourse on what people are learning (or posing to learn).
you need to be careful on prioritising what you want to learn.
somehow these days the meme has been let's do hardware, c is cracked, we will go cuda. it's downstream of what influential figures like karpathy are pursuing.
problem is, mere exposure can make you feel more interested in new things like gpu programming, writing llm in c and unconsciously prioritise the same when let's say you were already trying to learn about the transformer architecture. (shiny object syndrome sort of situation lol)
frequently hopping bandwagons will lead to scattered attention and you don't want that. now i get it, you gotta pursue your intellectual curiosity but you also need to think from your usecase point of view.
what do i require to learn more urgently? what will allow me to build the thing i want to build faster? what is more relevant for me based on my previous understanding? is it worth going this deep in the stack for now?
depending on the time you have, you can pursue more than 2 things in parallel but you gotta stick to what you have decided atleast for a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by the_snooze in "Group chats rule the world"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40673318</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40673318"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>Salons and groups have always existed but why the recent shift to private discourse?
Because the public internet makes it too easy for people to sell you stuff, extract value from you, or harass you. Private chats are human-scale environments where understandable social norms---not commerce, algorithms, or formal rules---drive the interactions. It's an authentic experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>the_snooze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michaelt in "Please maintain eye contact for the duration of the ad"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40672233</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40672233"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T17:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do note that this twitter account is posting fake screenshots of product ideas.
Other posts include "Google Meet option to punish interrupters by sending them to meeting jail" "iOS camera lock if you record too much concert footage" and "Spotify feature to lock Christmas music until after Thanksgiving"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaelt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lxgr in "MLow: Meta's low bitrate audio codec"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40671435</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40671435"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All these new, low-bitrate codecs are amazing, but ironically I suspect that they won't actually be very useful in most of the scenarios Meta is using them:
To keep latency low in real-time communications, the packet rate needs to be relatively high, and at some point the overhead of UDP, IP, and lower layers starts dominating over the actual payload.
As an example, consider (S)RTP (over UDP and IP): RTP adds at least 12 bytes of overhead (let's ignore the SRTP authentication tag for now); UDP adds 8 byte, and IPv4 adds 20, for a total of 40. At at typical packet rate of 50 per second (for a serialization delay of 1/50 = 20ms), that's 16 kbps of overhead alone!
It might still be acceptable to reduce the packet rate to 25 per second, which would cut this in half for an overhead of 8 kbps, but the overhead would still be dominating the total transmission rate.
Where codecs like this can really shine, though, is circuit-switched communication (some satphones use bitrates of around 2 kbps, which currently sound awful!), or protocol-aware VoIP systems that can employ header compression such as that used by LTE and 5G in IMS (most of the 40 bytes per frame are extremely predictable).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lxgr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of unstructured data with RAG]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unstructured data holds valuable information about codebases, organizational best practices, and customer feedback. Here are some ways you can leverage it with RAG, or retrieval-augmented generation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/">Unlocking the power of unstructured data with RAG</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VyseofArcadia in "Microsoft Chose Profit over Security, Whistleblower Says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670667</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670667"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T15:11:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft bribes scandal broke not too long after I had to take the "hey don't do bribes" training at Microsoft.
That event really drove home for me the fact that all of the trainings, emails, processes, etc. are mostly plausible deniability. There are people who care about security at MS. I know, I've met them, but for the most part all of this exists so that Satya can plausibly say in court or in front of congress, "well we told them to do security better. This is clearly the fault of product teams or individual contributors, not Microsoft policy and incentives."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VyseofArcadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by minisooftwin in "Microsoft Chose Profit over Security, Whistleblower Says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670551</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670551"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> “If you’re faced with the tradeoff between security and another priority, your answer is clear: Do security,” the company’s CEO, Satya Nadella, told employees.
Satya's model of making security a priority at Microsoft:
- Cram ads in every nook and corner of Windows. Left, right, centre, back, front, everywhere. What else is an operating system for?
- Install a recorder which records everything you do. For the benefit of users of course - you know, what if a user missed an ad and wants to go back and see what they missed.
- Send a mail to your employees and tell them "Do security". Mission accomplished - Microsoft is now the most secure platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>minisooftwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLow: Meta’s low bitrate audio codec]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21258</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/13/web/mlow-metas-low-bitrate-audio-codec/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we support real-time communication (RTC) for billions of people through our apps, including WhatsApp, Instagram, and Messenger.  We are working to make RTC accessible by providing a high-quality experience for everyone – even those who might not have the fastest connections or the latest phones. As more and more people have relied on [...]
Read More...
The post MLow: Meta’s low bitrate audio codec appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Etheryte in "Indian startup 3D prints rocket engine in 72 hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40669488</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40669488"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T13:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The machine also automatically outputs a report that details any deviations during printing, removing the need for postfabrication qualification.
Anyone who's previously worked with 3D printing knows that this simply does not pass any kind of a sniff test. Both preventing and detecting internal defects is one of the, if not the hardest problem in 3D printing. There are many large companies trying to find ways to reliably solve just this problem alone. Saying that this method doesn't require any checks after production is simply false.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Etheryte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Bickerton: &ldquo;After Euroscepticism&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/after-euroscepticism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/after-euroscepticism"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T10:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The assimilation of the far right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money Is Stored Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/money-is-stored-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/money-is-stored-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most helpful perspective of looking at money is stored time. You can exchange money for time or time for money. It's like a balance. To make money you need to invest time. And you get back time by spending money. That can be time saved by hiring someone to do something for you. Even when buying a nice painting you are buying the stored time of a painter(not to mention the talent).
This perspective is helpful as it gives a clear motivation. You would want to leverage your time to make a lot of money. This can be working efficiently at things where you exchange your time for money like a job or freelance work. But such things only scale linearly. True leverage is owning a piece of something. Something valuable. Something exponential. This can be taking the time to build products that people want, invest or have equity.
On the other side of the equation, you want to make sure you are not doing anything stupid with your time. Let's say you spend 1 hour cooking to save money. Is the value of the saved money less or more than the value of 1 hour of your time? Have you ever thought about it? Cooking for fun or just as a hangout with friends or lack of healthier alternatives is a different value proposition. One that you might be more than happy to make.
Thinking of your time and money as an interchangeable value store gives a framework that you can leverage in your favour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The productivity/pay gap and phony debates]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45414</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/13/the-productivity-pay-gap-and-phony-debates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker New York Times columnist Peter Coy did a piece yesterday questioning the existence of a gap between productivity growth and the typical worker’s pay. This gap was established decades ago by my friends and former colleagues at the Economic Policy Institute (EPI). The fact that it is now being questioned says a lot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by immortan in "Serious Sam handled massive amounts of enemies on 56k modem connections"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40666661</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40666661"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T06:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was one the developers responsible for implementing the netcode on Serious Sam.  We often slept under the desks in the offices at croteam after lurking usenet.  One post in particular described the QuakeWorld prediction system which inspired us.  That night we coded a simplistic mvp as a colleague (hi dan) tested it over an old 486 nix machine acting as a router that we could simulate lag with.  This was well before the actual game was built around it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>immortan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta trains large language models at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21330</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/12/data-infrastructure/training-large-language-models-at-scale-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T22:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we continue to focus our AI research and development on solving increasingly complex problems, one of the most significant and challenging shifts we’ve experienced is the sheer scale of computation required to train large language models (LLMs). Traditionally, our AI model training has involved a training massive number of models that required a comparatively [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta trains large language models at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iron Triangle - Richmond, CA]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/iron-triangle-richmond-ca/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/iron-triangle-richmond-ca/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T21:41:01.432Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ricoh GRIIIx I reserved at the beginning of May finally came in earlier this month. The camera has a bit of a learning curve that I'm still getting used to, but am really enjoying the portability of it. Although I'm used to shooting with a 35mm, I'm still finding myself having to work around a 40mm. I think at the end of the day, this is still better for me than a 28mm (that the GRIII has) since I prefer tighter frames.


Marty's Grill has pretty decent Cheesesteak, although obviously not comparable to an authentic Philly Cheesesteak. LSC also seems to like their burgers.

First post on this platform. It's already a breath of fresh air compared to WP 😮‍💨]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software vendors… supercharge their apps with AI. But why?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7796</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/software-vendors-supercharge-apps-ai-but-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a disturbing trend, vendors of software and apps, in particular those that have been around for years, suddenly introducing AI functionality. Indeed, whose idea was this? What Apple announced looks like more of the same that’s been offered lately. Help writing emails that don’t need to be written, bad generative images that look […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "The GJK Algorithm: A weird and beautiful way to do a simple thing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40663042</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40663042"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T20:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent about a year struggling with GJK back in the 1990s.
It's useful for collision detection in 3D, and it can also be used as a closest-points algorithm. As a closest-points algorithm, it's easy to understand the basics. You have two convex solids. Start with a random point on each, and get the distance between those points. On each solid, try to improve the distance by advancing along each edge from the current point. Pick the new closest point. Repeat.
This stops working when the closest point is no longer a vertex. That's when the "simplex" concept is needed. The closest points can be vertex-vertex, vertex-edge, vertex-face, edge-edge, edge-face (no unique solution) and face-face (no unique solution). The simplex thing is really doing a case analysis of those cases.
Lots of things go wrong in practice. If you are doing a physics engine, objects will often settle into face-face contact. A single-point collision model will then result in vibration or incorrect movement. Also, as positions settle into face-face contact, the GJK algorithm runs into a small difference of large values problem that can result in a complete loss of floating point significance. 
The termination condition can also cause infinite looping.
In theory, this is an elegant solution, but it's a difficult numerical analysis problem.
Despite that, it's probably the fastest approach to the problem. It's O(log N) in normal cases, and O(1) for situations where the positions are closest to the previous positions and you use the last solution as the starting point.
The late Prof. Steven Cameron at Oxford did a lot of work on getting GJK right.
I used GJK in "Falling Bodies", the first commercial 3D ragdoll system, in the late 1990s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Automation for SAP on AWS Operations using Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>eb364b2e48c0d12e84d148bc9bf27c3a87452c88</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-your-automation-for-sap-on-aws-operations-using-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on discussions with several SAP on AWS customers, we have discovered that the number of SAP administration or operational task requirements often exceed the capacity of the available team. Due to lack of time, resources, and heavy focus on operations, strategic initiatives like digital transformations often remain unaddressed. Although 1P and 3P automation solutions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bidwan Baruah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In May, we experienced one incident that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: May 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryandrake in "Star botanist likely made up data about nutritional supplements, new probe finds"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40661641</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40661641"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My pet theory: Nobody wants to go up against a very charismatic phony in what will almost certainly turn into a battle of wits instead of a battle of facts.
Our entire society deifies charismatic phonies. They are the ones that get elevated to the highest positions in politics and the C-level business suite. They're always the heroic Main Character. They build up cult followings. They often look so good, speak so smoothly and have those irresistible Ivy League mannerisms. You're supposed to like them and help elevate them even higher.
Do you want to expose this person? The Main Character? You better be right, and you better be ready to have the full force of his charm, persuasion, and cult following at your throat forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryandrake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining large-scale AI capacity at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21309</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/12/production-engineering/maintaining-large-scale-ai-capacity-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is currently operating many data centers with GPU training clusters across the world. Our data centers are the backbone of our operations, meticulously designed to support the scaling demands of compute and storage. A year ago, however, as the industry reached a critical inflection point due to the rise of artificial intelligence (AI), we [...]
Read More...
The post Maintaining large-scale AI capacity at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by arithmoquine in "The GJK Algorithm: A weird and beautiful way to do a simple thing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40660762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40660762"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I couldn't find any written explanation of the GJK collision detection algorithm which gave good intuition for it, so I spent an afternoon writing one up. Let me know of any ways I could make it more clear & efficient.
And, of course:
Take this with the appropriate amount of salt for a high school sophomore's explanation of anything math related.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>arithmoquine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilv in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40659620</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40659620"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> If a founder cashes out 10% of their position for $500k @ $25M Series A valuation, that de-risks a lot of their personal life. But when the startup ends up selling for $250M, that $500k of 'early' selling would have been worth $5M (less any dilution between rounds) - hard not to regret the choice in that case even if hedging is going to be the correct choice 99% of the time.
IMHO, it's very easy not to regret, with those particular numbers.
I'd take $500K now plus possibly $45M later -- over $0 now and possibly $50M later.
I'd take that deal even if "possibly" were "guaranteed".
(Who might regret that is a founder who was otherwise already wealthy.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental Yoga]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/mental-yoga/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/mental-yoga/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["All of humanity's problems stem from man's inability to sit quietly in a room." — Blaise Pascal
I'm constantly surprised, and, by this point in my life, I shouldn't be, but I am. What of? People who feel the need to constantly be busy or doing this, and that, and, well, the other. Is it something that happened slowly, over night, I wonder? Is it since the advent of smart phones, or maybe TV even? Or was it always there and I just didn't notice it?
Because, I'm of a mind that I really don't feel the need to be constantly doing something, anything, or going somewhere to do something (like sports), whether to participate or watch. I'm not always in front of a screen, or TV. I have a life outside of smart gadgets that involves me walking around a garden, or sitting in a park staring at, well,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macron’s gamble and the myth of the Republican Barrier]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52764</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/12/macrons-gamble-and-the-myth-of-the-republican-barrier/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Macron’s decision to call legislative elections in France, following a strong showing for the extreme-right-wing Rassemblement National of Marine Le Pen constitutes an extreme risk. No doubt he thinks that either the RN will fail to get as many seats as they hope under France’s two-stage election system or he calculates that since he […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deaths of infants and young children in Gaza. A fact-based estimate.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45429</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/12/deaths-of-infants-and-young-children-in-gaza-a-fact-based-estimate/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the death toll of the violence in Gaza, around 15.000 additional deaths of infants and children between 1 and 5 have to be added. This is a rough and, in my opinion, a lower-bound estimate. However, the calculations are based on robust information, and sizeable additional mortality in infants and young children in Gaza […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by coldpie in "Intel is trucking a 916k-pound 'Super Load' across Ohio to its new fab"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40658256</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40658256"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It doesn't happen often, but I always enjoy when I spot oversize equipment making its way across the roads. Enormous construction equipment; wind turbine blades; partial buildings. The kind of stuff that requires multiple lanes, careful route planning, and lead & follow cars. Gives a little glimpse of the immense effort we put in to building, improving, and maintaining our society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coldpie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 years of Project Galileo]]></title>
        <id>6668ec88e955c4000a8b4dd4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrating-10-years-of-project-galileo"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago today, Cloudflare launched Project Galileo, a program which today provides security services, at no cost, to more than 2,600 independent journalists and nonprofit organizations around the world supporting human rights, democracy, and local communities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by koalaman in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656921</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656921"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:40:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently left a long career in FANG to roll the dice on an early startup.  I was pretty surprised by the uneven terms between founders and early employees.  From what I could tell the early employees takes more risk than the founders because they don't get that magic token dollar turning into their share of the founding equity event and have to pay the fictional valuation of the seed to convert their options. Depending on how hot your startup is that can be a lot of money.
Anyway that ended in tears, but I got what I was looking for from it. A look under the covers of the hot VC backed startup roller coaster.  I may be getting old and cynical, but it looked considerably more exploitative than what I saw at Google.  Obviously depends on the character of the founders and leaders, but the structure seems to be setup for toxicity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>koalaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lrvick in "Raspberry Pi is now a public company"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656761</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656761"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only ever bought Pis because it was a mission focused company.
Now that they are in stock-price-go-up mode, I am inclined to buy and promote cheap clones, and I expect most will feel the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lrvick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doodda in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656617</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656617"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post has managed to piss off everyone: employees who didn't realize founders were getting liquidity events while they're still sitting on their more-often-than-not valueless equity, and founders who feel they've earned it and don't like the implication they haven't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doodda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Paul Wolfowitz (2005-2007) to Ajay Banga (2023-...): the US President's men control the World Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/From-Paul-Wolfowitz-2005-2007-to-David-Malpass-2019-the-US-President-s-men</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/From-Paul-Wolfowitz-2005-2007-to-David-Malpass-2019-the-US-President-s-men"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmward01 in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654725</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654725"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T05:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was mentally, physically and emotionally worn out when I left my previous startup after being an early employee. Despite that I really wanted to stay and be part of what my friends and I were building. Had I had the chance to 'de-risk my life' with some equity to replenish my empty bank account, which was empty from taking an early employee salary, I may have been able to stay but in the end I had to get out.
Getting out for an early employee after funding rounds is expensive because buying options can hit you with massive tax bills on top of the cost of buying the options. Worse, the stats aren't great for a chance on return. Your lotto ticket gets expensive and risky as soon as you decide to leave.
Articles like this one hammer home more and more to me how little VCs actually value early employees. Paying out founders to stay is a strategic move. Keeping them is worth it because they are the face of the company and turmoil at that level hurts their payout. Burning out early employees is not a concern because you can just swap them without drama. In fact, with the way options are structured and the 'industry wisdom' to hold off purchasing, it feels like a strategic move to burn out early employees since many employees that are forced out often can't even buy their options. They are left with nothing after all that work and risk. From a purely cynical view this is a great thing for VCs since now the company got all the benefit of an early employee and just lost all the costs.
I don't know about the other three points, but I can guarantee you point 1 of 'right sizing perceptions' is wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmward01</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Finbarr in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654678</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654678"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secondary at Series A is very rare. Part of the reason more early employees don't get included in secondary sales is because of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 14e-2. If you have more than 10 sellers involved, the transaction can be considered a tender offer, which triggers additional regulatory requirements and disclosures.
> As of 4 months ago I left a very successful stealth startup (which grew to 40M in ARR in two years) to become a founder and that is when it clicked - I expected to feel stressed, pressured, and the weight of all of the risk I was taking.
Please let us all know how that's working out for you in 5-10 years. 4 months in and no stress? Must be easy riding from here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Finbarr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kneath in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654402"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have seen a lot of companies, a lot of rounds. I have known zero founders who have turned down an option to take money off the table (and zero A raises that offered that to employees). I love the idea of your universe, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kneath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by josh2600 in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654349</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654349"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best startups have a concept which is summed up thusly:
“We all go to the pay window at the same time.”
It’s ok for founders to take a little bit of money off of the table if they extend that to their employees as well. Asymmetry is where things get weird.
I’ve seen many founders who got deep into the fundraising cycles without ever realizing they could take a cent out. VCs will constantly tell you to let it all ride, and sometimes that works out, but for most people, having a little bit of financial security while you’re trying to change the world is necessary.
The best startups figure out how to manage liquidity through financing in a way that aligns incentives, keeps the goalposts at the mission, while allowing their teams to thrive.
It’s about alignment. If everyone is pulling in the same direction you’re going to execute the vision. Whether you win in the startup lottery is up to the threads of fate, but alignment is the straightest path towards a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>josh2600</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>8da48ee2807e1e4e56d1d5e36b5355877d24b331</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-region-in-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T03:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing that a new AWS Region will be coming to Taiwan by early 2025. The new AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region will consist of three Availability Zones at launch, and will give AWS customers in Taiwan the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in Taiwan. Each of the Availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini - International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini
Title: International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/01/05/ccf_int_net>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 “Solidarity is a constant attack against the system and society, an act where the words fabrication, innocent, guilty, do not fit. Because as revolutionaries it is our duty to always be guilty for this system, always dangerous and always proud of our choices. We are not persecuted for our ideas, but because it seemed poor to us to not transubstantiate them into actions.” 
 (Gerasimos Tsakalos member of the prisoners cell of C.C.F.). 
 Real solidarity between revolutionary consciences and groups of comrades is what the dominators fear most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - 2008’s communiques]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: 2008’s communiques
Date: December 1, 2010
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3269>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Communique on the arson against the French press agency (Athens, 3/12/2008)
 While the peaceful citizens where enjoying the coffee break of their inexistance in the paved street of Kolonaki, we set ourselves for once again under the “services” of destruction and prepared a new gift out of idyllic ashes. With these, we send our revolutionary greetings to the French comrades that selected to attack the network of the high speed trains, sabotaging the routes of everyday hurry and anxiety, of a determined pre-set life imposed by the bio-authority to its subjects. 
 Striking at the ordinary flaw of the system, using aggres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Post-anarchism Today]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-post-anarchism-today?v=1718149008</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-post-anarchism-today?v=1718149008"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T23:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Post-anarchism Today
Date: 2014-01-12
Source: <journals.uvic.ca/index.php/adcs/issue/view/1258>

Editorial — Post-anarchism Today
 Lewis Call{1}
 Welcome to Post-anarchism Today. This is certainly not USA Today, et ce n’est certainement pas Aujourd’hui en France. Indeed, it is a refreshing antidote to all such discourses of modern state capitalism. During its short but colourful existence, post-anarchism has always been libertarian and socialist in its basic philosophical outlook: that’s the anarchism part. But post-@ has also maintained its independence from modern rationalism and modern concepts of subjectivity: that’s the post- part. As I survey post-anarchism today, I find to my surprise and delight that both parts are stronger than ever. It’s now clear t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 9, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well-built furniture should last centuries, not a couple of years]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7793</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/well-built-furniture-should-last-centuries-not-couple-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Bray: When Lauren was pregnant with a child who’s now turning 25, we purchased a comfy dark-brown leather sofa which fits our living room nicely. What with kids and relatives and employees and cats and Standards Comittees and friends and book clubs and socials, the butt-support cushions had, a quarter century later, worn out. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we improved push processing on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Pushing code to GitHub is one of the most fundamental interactions that developers have with GitHub every day. Read how we have significantly improved the ability of our monolith to correctly and fully process pushes from our users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/">How we improved push processing on GitHub</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticker Anxiety and the Idea of Permanence]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to LOVE collecting stickers, and in some ways, I still do. Every time I traveled or visited some place, if they had stickers, I would get at least one. They were my souvenirs from all the places I visited, each sticker told some kind of story or memory.
Over the years, I started facing a dilemma that I never truly faced when I was collecting other things like magnets or keychains: where do I put them? The idea of permanence gave me some unneeded anxiety. On one hand, I loved the idea of decorating my laptop with the stickers, but the thought of losing those stickers when my laptop died (because they all inevitable do), made me super sad. This hesitation led to a growing collection of stickers sitting unused, each waiting for that perfect place that never seemed to come.
The crazy th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21299</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/11/core-infra/mobileconfig-meta-mixed-reality-mr/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MobileConfig enables developers to centrally manage a mobile app’s configuration parameters in our data centers. Once a parameter value is changed on our central server, billions of app devices automatically fetch and apply the new value without app updates. These remotely managed configuration parameters serve various purposes such as A/B testing, feature rollout, and app [...]
Read More...
The post Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Audit Manager extends generative AI best practices framework to Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>f0f3c70728357d6ed187ea0df993809736f41c25</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-audit-manager-extends-generative-ai-best-practices-framework-to-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain comprehensive visibility with the AWS Audit Manager generative AI best practices framework v2, which now includes Amazon SageMaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify AWS CloudTrail log analysis with natural language query generation in CloudTrail Lake (preview)]]></title>
        <id>24bdb2fd2e9ad8e57868d4acc1da126f35a18e52</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-aws-cloudtrail-log-analysis-with-natural-language-query-generation-in-cloudtrail-lake-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline compliance and security analysis using natural language query generation. Ask questions like "What errors occurred last month?" and get ready-to-run SQL queries tailored to your needs – no technical expertise required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon GuardDuty Malware Protection for Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>dd44be812e425caecd4fb1915afa474d215f2431</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-guardduty-malware-protection-for-amazon-s3/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty expands malware scanning to secure S3 uploads, enabling continuous monitoring and isolation of malicious files without infrastructure overhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM Access Analyzer Update: Extending custom policy checks & guided revocation]]></title>
        <id>940b08797e1a3df84f46252ee98dfbdd72457eea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/iam-access-analyzer-update-extending-custom-policy-checks-guided-revocation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New custom policy checks for critical resources, public access detection, and guided revocation to remove unused permissions - proactively securing AWS environments with tailored analysis and actionable insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS adds passkey multi-factor authentication (MFA) for root and IAM users]]></title>
        <id>21e15c1e7596eeb37b7d4390f7e9925a4b0eb8aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-adds-passkey-multi-factor-authentication-mfa-for-root-and-iam-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortify your AWS account security with new passkey MFA and mandatory root user MFA. Experience seamless authentication while bolstering protection against unauthorized access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Student protests and academic freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52754</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/11/on-student-protests-and-academic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier post (here), prompted by some writings by Jacob T. Levy, I defended the idea that student protests can fall under academic freedom. My argument for this starts from the fact that while many universities can have mission specific interpretations of the latitude and constraints on how they interpret academic freedom (non-trivially constrained […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perinomics: a yet to exist discipline]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45410</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/11/perinomics-a-yet-to-exist-discipline/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Edward Fullbrook Humankind urgently needs a new discipline.  Our very survival may depend on it.  Natural science tells us that the economy now threatens humanity with calamity and potentially with extinction; and the daily news tells us that the economy’s forty-year upward redistribution of wealth, income and power threatens democracy and social order.  But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Fullbrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call to support Australia’s most at-risk entities]]></title>
        <id>6650a29807441c000a06ea10</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/heeding-the-call-to-support-australias-most-at-risk-entities"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call for industry to step up support of Australia's most at-risk entities, Cloudflare and CI-ISAC are teaming up to help protect Australia’s General Practitioner clinics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Ramsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just enough social media]]></title>
        <id>https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:50:21.615Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve had this paragraph on the home page of my personal website for a while now:
Disconnected from social media, but will always answer an email.
My retreat from social media was gradual and uneventful. I left Facebook so long ago that I barely remember what I used it for. I left Instagram well before it became the weird jumble of videos, shorts and occasionally photos it is today. People trying to be brands, brands posing as people. Twitter broke my heart - it connected me to many cool people, helped me find an audience as a musician, and led to lifelong friendships. And then it all went to shit - though honestly, it had been going to shit for a while.
It was a clean break. For the most part, I haven’t missed social media. I’ve kept in touch with friends in other ways, from the ubiquitous…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Linux, farewell to toxic Windows operating systems]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7787</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/hello-linux-farewell-toxic-windows-operating-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve read a stack of articles recently about Windows 11 (11), the successor operating system (OS) to Windows 10 (10), and am not liking a single thing I’ve seen. Microsoft (MS) will soon begin forcing users to install Windows 11, whether they like it or not. If that’s not toxic behaviour on Microsoft’s part, what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>