<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-04-03T06:26:47.805Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-04-03T06:26:47.805Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax Day and War Resistance, Philip Berrigan Style]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317688</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/tax-day-and-war-resistance-philip-berrigan-style/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T06:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In fiscal year 2023, the Pentagon received $858 billion for the preparation of war. This doesn’t include hidden costs for intelligence services, veterans' benefits, Homeland Security, or the Department of Energy which oversees the nation’s nuclear arsenal. All totaled, over $1 trillion a year is allotted for warmaking. One way to register resistance to this profligate spending on warmaking is that of renowned peace activist and Catholic priest Philip Berrigan.  During the Vietnam war, Phil initiated the destruction of U.S. military draft files in Baltimore and Catonsville, Maryland to save the lives of both Vietnamese and Americans, actions for which he received lengthy prison sentences. More
The post Tax Day and War Resistance, Philip Berrigan Style appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brad Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banks Won’t Save Nuclear Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317679</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/banks-wont-save-nuclear-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T06:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NuScale, the company whose small modular reactor project collapsed so spectacularly last November, is “burning cash at the rate of $185 million per year”. On March 22, the company’s CEO, John Hopkins, sold 59,768 of his shares in the company. This is the same CEO who declared NuScale’s SMR project, aptly named VOYGR, “a dead horse.” It’s clearly on a journey to nowhere. More
The post Banks Won’t Save Nuclear Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Pentz Gunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unjust Wars and a Just Peace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317675</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/unjust-wars-and-a-just-peace/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three major wars or conflicts that are ongoing today demonstrate the volatility of the intersection between the local and the global. In the Hamas-Israeli conflict, we see how the maintenance of the Israeli settler-colonial state is intertwined with the preservation of the global hegemony of the United States. In the war in Ukraine, a  More
The post Unjust Wars and a Just Peace appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State-Level Marijuana Legalization Has Been a Stunning Success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317834</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/state-level-marijuana-legalization-has-been-a-stunning-success/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been over a decade since Colorado and Washington became the first two states to legalize marijuana for adults. With the benefit of hindsight, it’s fair to ask: Has this policy been successful? Absolutely. A policy of legalization, regulation, and education is preferable to a policy of criminalization, stigmatization, and incarceration. Let’s be clear. Legalization  More
The post State-Level Marijuana Legalization Has Been a Stunning Success appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Armentano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest Huge Transfer of 2,000-Pound Bombs from U.S. to Israel Not Newsworthy to the New York Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317837</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/latest-huge-transfer-of-2000-pound-bombs-from-u-s-to-israel-not-newsworthy-to-the-new-york-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the Washington Post revealed Friday afternoon that “the Biden administration in recent days quietly authorized the transfer of billions of dollars in bombs and fighter jets to Israel,” a lot of people cared. Readers of the story posted more than 10,000 comments on its webpage. A leading progressive site for breaking news, Common Dreams,  More
The post Latest Huge Transfer of 2,000-Pound Bombs from U.S. to Israel Not Newsworthy to the New York Times appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Uber Overcharges Riders and Underpays Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317831</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/how-uber-overcharges-riders-and-underpays-drivers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve taken an Uber ride recently, you’ve probably noticed it cost a lot more than a few years ago. Why is that? PowerSwitch Action, my organization, conducted the largest-ever study of rideshare fares to find out. We discovered a story of gaslighting and greed that squeezes drivers and riders alike — while funneling our  More
The post How Uber Overcharges Riders and Underpays Drivers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mariah Montgomery</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Federal Tax Dollars Meant to Fight Climate Change Could End Up Boosting Louisiana’s Fossil Fuel Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317676</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/03/how-federal-tax-dollars-meant-to-fight-climate-change-could-end-up-boosting-louisianas-fossil-fuel-production/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louisiana accounted for nearly one-sixth of the nation’s oil-refining capacity and shipped 63% of its liquefied natural gas exports in 2022. Adbar/Wikimedia, CC BY Billions of federal tax dollars will soon be pouring into Louisiana to fight climate change, yet the projects they’re supporting may actually boost fossil fuels – the very products warming the  More
The post How Federal Tax Dollars Meant to Fight Climate Change Could End Up Boosting Louisiana’s Fossil Fuel Production appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ned Randolph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full EU chat control proposal attack on digital privacy and encryption]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913946</id>
        <link href="https://www.patrick-breyer.de/en/full-chat-control-proposal-leaked-attack-on-digital-privacy-of-correspondence-and-secure-encryption/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.patrick-breyer.de/en/full-chat-control-proposal-leaked-attack-on-digital-privacy-of-correspondence-and-secure-encryption/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913946
Points: 23
# Comments: 3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>walterbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octopus v2: On-device language model for super agent]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913807</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2404.01744"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T05:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://arxiv.org/abs/2404.01744
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913807
Points: 10
# Comments: 0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lawrencechen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Junta in Niger Tells the United States to Pack Up Its War and Go Home]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269378</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/the-new-junta-in-niger-tells-the-united-states-to-pack-up-its-war-and-go-home.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T04:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US is being run out of Niger. A lot of our "hegemon forever" spending is going down the drain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tackle complex reasoning tasks with Mistral Large, now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>4fd909902bf32ca8c7a2918978932b571fc7fc18</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/tackle-complex-reasoning-tasks-with-mistral-large-now-available-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T04:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, we announced the availability of two high-performing Mistral AI models, Mistral 7B and Mixtral 8x7B on Amazon Bedrock. Mistral 7B, as the ﬁrst foundation model of Mistral, supports English text generation tasks with natural coding capabilities. Mixtral 8x7B is a popular, high-quality, sparse Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) model, that is ideal for text summarization, question […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise and Fall of 3M's Floppy Disk]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913505</id>
        <link href="https://spectrum.ieee.org/3m-floppy"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T04:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://spectrum.ieee.org/3m-floppy
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39913505
Points: 53
# Comments: 42]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stratoscope</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel discloses $7B operating loss for chip-making unit]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912854</id>
        <link href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-discloses-financials-foundry-business-2024-04-02/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T01:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.reuters.com/technology/intel-discloses-financials-foundry-business-2024-04-02/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912854
Points: 116
# Comments: 59]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmc414</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Threat of Discontinued Software (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912771</id>
        <link href="https://almy.us/softwaredeath.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T01:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://almy.us/softwaredeath.html
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912771
Points: 35
# Comments: 28]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iyeaton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navies are obsolete, but no one will admit it]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52559</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/03/navies-are-obsolete-but-no-one-will-admit-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T00:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last year, three of the four most powerful navies[1] in the world have suffered humiliating defeats at the hands of opponents with no navy at all. First, there’s Russia’s Black Sea Fleet. Until the invasion of Ukraine in February 2022, it was regularly touted as a decisive factor in any conflict, capable not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7.4 earthquake in Taiwan, 34km depth]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912330</id>
        <link href="https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/map/?extent=16.34123,-246.42334&amp;extent=28.51697,-223.43994"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T00:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/map/?extent=16.34123,-246.42334&extent=28.51697,-223.43994
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39912330
Points: 371
# Comments: 122]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway598</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Windows Operational Readiness Specification]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/03/intro-windows-ops-readiness/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/03/intro-windows-ops-readiness/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Jay Vyas (Tesla), Amim Knabben (Broadcom), and Tatenda Zifudzi (AWS)
Since Windows support graduated to stable
with Kubernetes 1.14 in 2019, the capability to run Windows workloads has been much
appreciated by the end user community. The level of and availability of Windows workload
support has consistently been a major differentiator for Kubernetes distributions used by
large enterprises. However, with more Windows workloads being migrated to Kubernetes
and new Windows features being continuously released, it became challenging to test
Windows worker nodes in an effective and standardized way.
The Kubernetes project values the ability to certify conformance without requiring a
closed-source license for a certified distribution or service that has no intention
of offering Windows.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Terraform CI/CD and testing on AWS with the new Terraform Test Framework]]></title>
        <id>20587d8a6b5c4ce6e32930afb4205da1159ed595</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/terraform-ci-cd-and-testing-on-aws-with-the-new-terraform-test-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T23:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will show you how to validate Terraform modules and how to automate the process using a Continuous Integration/Continuous Deployment (CI/CD) pipeline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevon Mayers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ReALM: Reference Resolution as Language Modeling]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911961</id>
        <link href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2403.20329"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T23:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://arxiv.org/abs/2403.20329
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911961
Points: 64
# Comments: 10]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mfiguiere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by madeofpalk in "Amazon ditches 'just walk out' checkouts at its grocery stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911573</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911573"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T22:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Though it seemed completely automated, Just Walk Out relied on more than 1,000 people in India watching and labeling videos to ensure accurate checkouts. The cashiers were simply moved off-site, and they watched you as you shopped.
Wow - I did not know this. This makes it all a whole lot less impressive and interesting that it was just people off shore watching you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madeofpalk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Johnny555 in "Amazon ditches 'just walk out' checkouts at its grocery stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911470</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911470"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T22:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of services would be phenomenal when you can offload much of the cost to run them to cheap offshore labor.
Remember how great Uber and Doordash were when much of the cost of operating was offset by underpaid workers and VC funds? Now that they don't have unlimited piles of money and cities/states are making them pay more fair wages, the cost-benefit of those services has diminished. I was ok paying $5 for $20 of food to be delivered, but now it's more like $10 - $15 in fees/tip, plus fees hidden in menu prices making that $20 food cost $27.50.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johnny555</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Science fiction and the death of the sun]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911155</id>
        <link href="https://www.typebarmagazine.com/2024/03/24/science-fiction-and-the-death-of-the-sun/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.typebarmagazine.com/2024/03/24/science-fiction-and-the-death-of-the-sun/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911155
Points: 60
# Comments: 56]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ohjeez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bilalq in "Amazon ditches 'just walk out' checkouts at its grocery stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911139</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39911139"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is pretty sad to read. Before Covid, the Amazon Go store experience was phenomenal. All the convenience of a 7-Eleven but with the pricing of a normal grocery store. The food options were really good and the BlueApron style meal-kits were amazing. The Alexa integration was also nice for being able to just verbally ask what's the next step on a recipe while you're busy stirring or chopping things.
When it rolled out to Amazon Fresh stores, it was a breadth of fresh air. The painful clunkiness of self-checkout was gone. The slow and pointless exercise of unloading and reloading your cart was gone. You could just bring your reusable shopping bags, throw stuff in, and walk home. By far the most hassle-free shopping experience to be had.
Scan as you shop is a big step backwards and feels like you've got the annoying self-checkout experience looming over you the entire time you're there.
The selection and operating hours both took a hit during covid and never recovered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bilalq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Platform Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7037</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/04/data-platform-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As engineers working at Spotify, we frequently find ourselves explaining our robust data platform to fellow professionals who are contemplating [...]
The post Data Platform Explained appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roe AI (YC W24) Is Hiring]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910806</id>
        <link href="https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/roe-ai/jobs/NZDmSo9-founding-engineer"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/roe-ai/jobs/NZDmSo9-founding-engineer
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910806
Points: 0
# Comments: 0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zswzs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brazilian special-forces unit fighting to save the Amazon]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910383</id>
        <link href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2024/04/08/the-brazilian-special-forces-unit-fighting-to-save-the-amazon"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T20:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2024/04/08/the-brazilian-special-forces-unit-fighting-to-save-the-amazon
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910383
Points: 51
# Comments: 2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mitchbob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous public voicemail inbox]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910119</id>
        <link href="https://afterthebeep.tel/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T19:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://afterthebeep.tel/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39910119
Points: 268
# Comments: 76]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>unixispower</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A rudimentary simulation of the three-body problem]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39909123</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/achristmascarl/three_body"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://github.com/achristmascarl/three_body
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39909123
Points: 144
# Comments: 78]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>achristmascarl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calling Haskell from Swift]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908891</id>
        <link href="https://alt-romes.github.io/posts/2024-04-02-calling-haskell-from-swift.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:05:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://alt-romes.github.io/posts/2024-04-02-calling-haskell-from-swift.html
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908891
Points: 71
# Comments: 12]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>romes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 4/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269379</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/200pm-water-cooler-4-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics and pandemics, plus Trump posts his bond, Kennedy's "paranoid style," and more detail on Shanahan. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study uses wearables to show that physical activity lengthens REM latency]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908798</id>
        <link href="https://news.utexas.edu/2024/04/01/move-more-sleep-better-ut-study-finds/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://news.utexas.edu/2024/04/01/move-more-sleep-better-ut-study-finds/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908798
Points: 127
# Comments: 72]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gmays</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by speff in "Amazon ditches 'just walk out' checkouts at its grocery stores"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908722</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908722"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Though it seemed completely automated, Just Walk Out relied on more than 1,000 people in India watching and labeling videos to ensure accurate checkouts.
That line was unintentionally hilarious to me. Like looking inside a TV and finding a bunch of fast-working little people drawing images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>speff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Artificio de Juanelo]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908660</id>
        <link href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificio_de_Juanelo"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificio_de_Juanelo
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908660
Points: 76
# Comments: 9]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benbreen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Konrad Zuse (1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908629</id>
        <link href="http://www.xn--plankalkl-x9a.de/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: http://www.xn--plankalkl-x9a.de
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908629
Points: 63
# Comments: 30]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tmalsburg2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon ditches 'just walk out' checkouts at its grocery stores]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908579</id>
        <link href="https://gizmodo.com/amazon-reportedly-ditches-just-walk-out-grocery-stores-1851381116"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://gizmodo.com/amazon-reportedly-ditches-just-walk-out-grocery-stores-1851381116
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908579
Points: 383
# Comments: 509]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>walterbell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Competitive Bass Fishing Cheaters (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908561</id>
        <link href="https://grantland.com/features/bass-fishing-cheaters/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://grantland.com/features/bass-fishing-cheaters/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908561
Points: 55
# Comments: 61]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EndXA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS Deadline Cloud: Set up a cloud-based render farm in minutes]]></title>
        <id>a63b7ed0cfc557e50341fc8a679e5cb5c3c53dda</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-aws-deadline-cloud-set-up-a-cloud-based-render-farm-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers in industries such as architecture, engineering, & construction (AEC) and media & entertainment (M&E) generate the final frames for film, TV, games, industrial design visualizations, and other digital media with a process called rendering, which takes 2D/3D digital content data and computes an output, such as an image or video file. Rendering also requires […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I know about SSDs (2019)]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908146</id>
        <link href="https://kcall.co.uk/ssd/index.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://kcall.co.uk/ssd/index.html
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39908146
Points: 149
# Comments: 42]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fagnerbrack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing our work with CISA and the Joint Cyber Defense Collaborative to keep vulnerable communities secure online]]></title>
        <id>6605db16a5fcdf000a08ef1f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cisa-cyber-defense-keep-vulnerable-communities-secure-online"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Along with CISA and the Joint Cyber Defense Collaborative, we are spotlighting threats to civil society, best practices for online protection, and new resources specifically for these vulnerable communities. Find out more about our latest initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CityGaussian: Real-time high-quality large-scale scene rendering with Gaussians]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39907876</id>
        <link href="https://dekuliutesla.github.io/citygs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article URL: https://dekuliutesla.github.io/citygs/
Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39907876
Points: 378
# Comments: 102]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smusamashah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by blackhawkC17 in "Canoo spent double its annual revenue on the CEO's private jet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39907380</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39907380"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the reimbursements were solely for corporate travel, it might not be a concern.
The CEO here sold his previous company for $6.5 billion [1], so he already owned the jet before starting Canoo. The company reimburses him for corporate travel on it.
What's concerning is that Canoo is stacking big losses and living on the edge...it seems like excessive spending for a company that hasn't even made a dime of profit.
But hold on, this same CEO has spent over $230 million(!) buying Canoo stock from his personal funds [2], so he is significantly in the red no matter how much he gets reimbursed for air travel.
Always dig into the details and avoid getting suckered by clickbait...
1- https://www.reuters.com/article/idUSL1N11J0PS/
2- https://www.secform4.com/insider-trading/1399053.htm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blackhawkC17</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LangSmith: Production Monitoring & Automations]]></title>
        <id>660acb04241009000105c2fa</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/langsmith-production-logging-automations/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T15:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Links:

YouTube Walkthrough
Sign up for LangSmith here

If 2023 was a breakthrough year for LLMs, then 2024 is shaping up to be the year that a significant amount of LLM-powered applications make their way into production. From the Elastic AI Assistant to CommandBar's Copilot User Assistant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankush Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overexposure Distorted the Science of Mirror Neurons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=136784</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/overexposure-distorted-the-science-of-mirror-neurons-20240402/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a decade out of the spotlight, the brain cells once alleged to explain empathy, autism and theory of mind are being refined and redefined.            
The post Overexposure Distorted the Science of Mirror Neurons first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan Willcoxon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yanis Varoufakis: Greece, EU Elections, Palestine & the International Order – JACOBIN Interview with David Broder]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269373</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/yanis-varoufakis-greece-eu-elections-palestine-the-international-order-jacobin-interview-with-david-broder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Varoufakis weighs in on topics of keen interest: the looting of Greece, then and now, the European left, and Palestine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aurornis in "Timeline of the xz open source attack"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905631</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905631"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attackers will leverage any culture that helps them accomplish their goals.
If being rude and pushy doesn’t work, the next round will be kind and helpful. Don’t read too much into the cultural techniques used, because the cultural techniques will mirror the culture at the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurornis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bitexploder in "You won't find a technical co-founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905545</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905545"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve Jobs has a great quote about this, from The Lost Interview:
“… it's the disease of thinking that a really great idea is 90% of the work, and if you just tell all these other people "here's this great idea" then of course they can go off and make it happen.
And the problem with that is that there is just a tremendous amount of craftsmanship in between a great idea and a great product.  And as you evolve that great idea it changes and grows. It never comes out like it starts because you learn a lot more as you get in the subtleties of it.
And you also find there's tremendous trade-offs that you have to make. There are just certain things you can't make electrons do. There are certain things you can't make plastic do or glass do. Or factories do, or robots do.
And as you get in to all these things, designing a product is keeping 5000 things in your brain, these concepts. And fitting them all together and kind of continuing to push to fit them together in new and different ways to get what you want. And every day you discover something new that is a new problem or a new opportunity to fit these things together a little differently.
It's that process that is the magic."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bitexploder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running fine-tuned models on Workers AI with LoRAs]]></title>
        <id>660aeacca5fcdf000a08f351</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/fine-tuned-inference-with-loras"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers AI now supports fine-tuned models using LoRAs. But what is a LoRA and how does it work? In this post, we dive into fine-tuning, LoRAs and even some math to share the details of how it all works under the hood]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveling up Workers AI: General Availability and more new capabilities]]></title>
        <id>660ab7c3a5fcdf000a08f29a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-ai-ga-huggingface-loras-python-support"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to make a series of announcements, including Workers AI, Cloudflare’s inference platform becoming GA and support for fine-tuned models with LoRAs and one-click deploys from HuggingFace. Cloudflare Workers now supports the Python programming language, and more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing Python to Workers using Pyodide and WebAssembly]]></title>
        <id>660ad435a5fcdf000a08f2aa</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/python-workers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Cloudflare Workers in Python, now in open beta! We've revamped our systems to support Python, from the runtime to deployment. Learn about Python Worker's lifecycle, dynamic linking, and memory snapshots in this post]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hood Chatham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rwmj in "Timeline of the xz open source attack"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905189</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905189"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missing the whole Fedora timeline.  I was emailed by "Jia Tan" between Feb 27 and Mar 27, in a partially successful attempt to get the new xz into Fedora 40 & 41.  Edit: I emailed Russ with the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rwmj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pc86 in "You won't find a technical co-founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905163</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39905163"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2010 or so I had a series of meetings with someone about being a technical cofounder for them. I wasn't super passionate about the domain (don't even remember what it was at this point) but it was interesting enough and I had just enough technical experience at the time to think I could pull it off. We had everything figured out in broad strokes until we realized that of the 80/20 equity split, we both thought we were getting the 80. His exact words were "I just gave you this great idea why would I only get 20%?"
Anyone who sees themselves as an "ideas person" as if that is a defining or valuable characteristic is a cancer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pc86</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bastawhiz in "You won't find a technical co-founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904923</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904923"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:24:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> sees themselves as the ideas person
More importantly, most businesses don't need an "ideas person". They need someone who knows how to run a business. You need a total of one decent idea to start and run a business. You need tens of thousands of little hard choices, emails, and sales calls to keep the business successful, and that means getting your hands dirty. Ideas are not valuable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bastawhiz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JCM9 in "You won't find a technical co-founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904830</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904830"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main problems I see in 99% of the cases of a founder looking for a technical co-founder are:
1. The founder sees themselves as the ideas person but doesn’t have the situational awareness to recognize that their ideas aren’t that unique.
2. The founder doesn’t understand that the value in a startup isn’t the idea but the ability to execute and build on that idea. For every very successful startup in X space there were 10x more with the same general idea but that failed to execute. The founder wants someone to built it for them but wants credit/equity for having the idea. In 99% of cases the value is created by the builders (technical cofounder) which instantly creates awkwardness of the founder wanting far more equity, credit, and control than their contributions warrant
For the above reasons I’d avoid 99% of asks for a technical co-founder like the plague.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JCM9</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lukaslalinsky in "Timeline of the xz open source attack"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904721</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904721"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The social side of this is really haunting me over the last days. It's surprisingly easy to pressure people to giving up control. I've been there myself. I can't even imagine how devastating this must be to the original author of XZ, especially if he is dealing with other personal issues as well. I hope at least this will serve a strong example to other open source people, to never allow others to pressure them into something they are not comfortable with.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lukaslalinsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by altdataseller in "You won't find a technical co-founder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904704</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39904704"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want me as a technical cofounder, you are going to tick most of these boxes:
1. You have at least 8-10 years of experience in that domain with some of it in a leadership position (ie product manager)
2. You already have a huge following or audience. Especially important if this is a SaaS product or b2c. Not as important if this is hard tech (ie biotech).
But if you’re doing a HR startup, show me your 10,000 engaged HR followers on LinkedIn. If you’re doing a martech startup, show me your Substack with 10k marketing subscribers.
3. You already have talked to at least 25 people about this, and gotten feedback about their pain points, initial reaction to your solution, etc. These conversations are documented and easily shared with me
4. You preferably have at least 1 successful exit/company under your belt, or a couple of failed ones is OK too (but I would need references to make sure they failed for legitimate reasons) the worse is 0 years of experience starting a company.
5. You are a cold email/call/outreach junkie. Because you will OWN sales in the early days. I want to see your 100 send emails or 100 daily calls or 100 sent DMs everyday asking potential customers for feedback or validation conversations or to sign up for your beta]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>altdataseller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 4/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269277</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/links-4-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bodacious daily links: Classic April Fools' Day, new Everest poop rules, Covid vax spike worries, oil giant admits to greenwashing, TikTok backfire? moar Israel hits on Gaza relief workers, Iran top general killed, Imran Kahn freed, no Western Plan B for Ukraine, Trump gagged again, Hunter tax charge hit, US economy stats]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brussels Begins to Mobilise Its Mass Censorship Regime for Upcoming EU Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269034</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/brussels-begins-to-mobilise-its-mass-censorship-regime-for-upcoming-eu-elections.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the culmination of a process that began at least a decade ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Electric War Is Redrawing the Ukraine Map – In Black]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269350</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/how-the-electric-war-is-redrawing-the-ukraine-map-in-black.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:20:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like so many things, the electric war has developed not necessarily to Ukraine's advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by skrebbel in "XZ: Repo maintainer Lasse Collin responding on LKML"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39903798</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39903798"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T09:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Points for Collin for letting his holiday take precedence over this mess.
Don’t forget that he made xz for free, as a hobby project, and likely got duped by “Jia Tan” same as everybody else did. He’s not obligated to solve this on any particular timeline.
Xz is not a business, so if your business got in trouble because a single solo hobby dev was a bit too trustful, it’s your job, and not his, to mitigate the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skrebbel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Desultory Analytic (Or How I Was Peter Turchin’d Into Perdition) by “I lost my harmonica albrt”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269298</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/a-simple-desultory-analytic-or-how-i-was-peter-turchind-into-perdition-by-i-lost-my-harmonica-albrt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T06:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of Peter Turchin’s End Times: Elites Counter-Elites, and the Path of Political Disintegration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post Believes U.S. & Israel “Can Get Back on the Same Page”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317723</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/washington-post-believes-u-s-israel-can-get-back-on-the-same-page/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T06:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a bizarre, even obtuse, lead editorial on March 31, the Washington Post outlined a scheme for the United States and Israel to “get back on the same page.”  The Post editorial suffers from the conventional misperception that ignores today’s fundamentalist and separatist Israel, which is so different from Israel’s long ago standing as a secular and social democratic society that replicated many West European countries.  The Post ignores the fact that Ashkenazi Jews from Europe are no longer in control, and the political and social influence of Orthodox Jewry, the Haredim, who play a central role in the government of Benjamin Netanyahu.  These misperceptions are apparent throughout the mainstream media. More
The post Washington Post Believes U.S. & Israel “Can Get Back on the Same Page” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Kuffiyehs and Watermelon – Revealing the Meaning of Palestinian Symbols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317694</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/on-kuffiyehs-and-watermelon-revealing-the-meaning-of-palestinian-symbols/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those who admonish Palestinian Resistance, armed or otherwise, have little understanding of the psychological ramifications of resistance, such as a sense of collective empowerment, honor and hope. But resistance is not just a rifle, a rocket launcher. The latter are but one manifestation in resistance and, if not backed by strong popular support, they hardly  More
The post On Kuffiyehs and Watermelon – Revealing the Meaning of Palestinian Symbols  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud - Romana Rubeo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shouldn’t Every American Enjoy the Luxury of a Roof?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317450</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/shouldnt-every-american-enjoy-the-luxury-of-a-roof/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America, a new report details, is minting millionaires at a record pace. Some 37 percent of the world’s millionaires, analysts at the wealth advisory firm Henley & Partners calculate, now call the United States home. And these analysts are talking real millionaires, not those Americans who rate as “millionaires” only because they’re living in homes  More
The post Shouldn’t Every American Enjoy the Luxury of a Roof? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rafah is Netanyahu’s Last Fig Leaf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317729</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/rafah-is-netanyahus-last-fig-leaf/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rafah is not a military base, nor does it have any geopolitical significance. It is, however, Netanyahu’s last chance for political survival and exoneration from criminal charges. Rafah’s only symbolic importance is being a potential gateway to forcibly exile Palestinians from Gaza. Thus, Netanyahu’s vision of “total victory” entails the complete occupation and then the  More
The post Rafah is Netanyahu’s Last Fig Leaf appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kategate: From Conspiracy to Contrition Extraction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317708</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/kategate-from-conspiracy-to-contrition-extraction/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cancer is a stomping bugger of a disease.  It seeks the worm-ridden end, a thief finding its way into your body unasked and willingly helping itself.  This cellular mass army will, in a most tribal way, make off with your remains chance permitting. So, it’s understandable that people speak about it.  Blog, discuss, worry, grieve and gather in  More
The post Kategate: From Conspiracy to Contrition Extraction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time to Stop Playing Politics With Immigrant Lives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317713</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/its-time-to-stop-playing-politics-with-immigrant-lives/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When President Biden was campaigning in 2020, he pledged to strengthen our country by supporting and welcoming immigrants. Early in his presidency, he began taking steps in that direction. On his first day in office, Biden proclaimed an end to his predecessor’s “Muslim ban,” which summarily banned migration from several Muslim-majority countries. And In February 2021,  More
The post It’s Time to Stop Playing Politics With Immigrant Lives appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Carlos Gomez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thailand Leads Southeast Asia: Parliament Approves Landmark Same-Sex Marriage Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317706</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/thailand-leads-southeast-asia-parliament-approves-landmark-same-sex-marriage-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legislators in Thailand’s lower house of Parliament have decisively endorsed a marriage equality bill, marking a historic step towards becoming the first Southeast Asian nation to legalize equal marriage rights for all people. On March 27, 2024, 400 out of 415 attending lawmakers voted in favor of the bill. “This is the beginning of equality.  More
The post Thailand Leads Southeast Asia: Parliament Approves Landmark Same-Sex Marriage Bill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Meddles in Another Nation’s Elections, Once Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317444</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/us-meddles-in-another-nations-elections-once-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Insanity is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results.” – Albert Einstein The USA is stuck in the recurring folly of trying to dictate the political life of Venezuela, including by trying to discredit their elections. They cannot grasp the fact that Venezuela is a sovereign nation, that it has  More
The post US Meddles in Another Nation’s Elections, Once Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Paez Victor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Carbon Footprint of March Madness?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317437</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/whats-the-carbon-footprint-of-march-madness/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:21:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CC BY-ND March Madness means 68 teams vying to become champion, Cinderella runs for a few underdogs and big business for the NCAA, which earns 85% of its annual operating budget during the men’s basketball tournament. But all of that comes at a tremendous cost: An estimated 463 million pounds (210 million kilograms) of carbon  More
The post What’s the Carbon Footprint of March Madness? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian P. McCullough</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the World Needs Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317691</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/02/what-the-world-needs-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am looking at a photograph I have just received from Argentina. It is from old friend (we have been friends for more than 70 years) holding his wife’s hand, who suffered a stroke and has been in a coma for weeks. One word can describe that photograph: compassion. I cannot shake that image out  More
The post What the World Needs Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by greenavocado in "Banning open weight models would be a disaster"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39902606</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39902606"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember when the world freaked out over encryption, thinking every coded message was a digital skeleton key to anarchy? Yeah, the 90s were wild with the whole PGP (Pretty Good Privacy) encryption fight. The government basically treated encryption like it was some kind of wizardry that only "good guys" should have. Fast forward to today, and it's like we're stuck on repeat with open model weights.
Just like code was the battleground back then, open model weights are the new frontier. Think about it—code is just a bunch of instructions, right? Well, model weights are pretty much the same; they're the brains behind AI, telling it how to think and learn. Saying "nah, you can't share those" is like trying to put a genie back in its bottle after it's shown you it can grant wishes.
The whole dea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>greenavocado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the use of economics?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45263</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/02/whats-the-use-of-economics-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T04:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The simple question that was raised during a recent conference … was to what extent has — or should — the teaching of economics be modified … The simple answer is that the economics profession is unlikely to change. Why would economists be willing to give up much of their human capital, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Author Correction: SARS-CoV-2 neutralizing antibody structures inform therapeutic strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07344-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07344-w"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nature - Author Correction: SARS-CoV-2 neutralizing antibody structures inform therapeutic strategies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher O. Barnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t dismiss carbon credits that aim to avoid future emissions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00972-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00972-2"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Mitchard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Right- or left-handed? Protein in embryo cells might help decide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00977-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00977-x"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gene that codes for structural protein could determine the dominant side of the human brain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumeet Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hand-operated front brakes were set to be the future of motoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00918-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00918-8"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Snippets from Nature’s past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nature</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopt universal standards for study adaptation to boost health, education and social-science research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00970-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00970-4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dragos Iliescu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How can we make PhD training fit for the modern world? Broaden its philosophical foundations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00969-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00969-x"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Alagarasan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allow researchers with caring responsibilities ‘promotion pauses’ to make research more equitable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00971-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00971-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel H. Lowenstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long COVID still has no cure — so these patients are turning to research]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00901-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00901-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With key long COVID trials yet to yield results, people with the condition are trying to change how clinical trials are done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rachel Fairbank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research assessments are still not fit for purpose — here’s how to change things]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00899-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00899-8"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A move away from narrow assessment metrics such as high-impact publications is welcome, but a lack of planning and consultation mean the replacements are often no better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Cobey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Maybe I was never meant to be in science’: how imposter syndrome seizes scientist mothers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00953-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00953-5"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian biologist Fernanda Staniscuaski saw career opportunities diminish after returning from parental leave, prompting her to take action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Gould</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A 2023 hurricane caught Mexico off guard: we must work together to prepare better]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00904-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00904-0"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Otis yields lessons for researchers and policymakers on how to reduce risks in the face of inequality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gian C. Delgado-Ramos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Mini liver’ will grow in person’s own lymph node in bold new trial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00975-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00975-z"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biotechnology firm LyGenesis has injected donor cells into a person with liver failure for the first time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Africa’s postdoc workforce is on the rise — but at what cost?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00980-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00980-2"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will a growth in postdoctoral positions across Africa cause bottlenecks, replicating the career-progression challenges faced by scientists elsewhere?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Nordling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cosmologist Claudia de Rham on falling for gravity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00903-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00903-1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aspiring astronaut turned theoretical physicist talks travelling, the accelerating expansion of the Universe, thinking beyond three dimensions and detecting gravitational waves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Davide Castelvecchi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gut bacteria break down cholesterol — hinting at probiotic treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00955-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00955-3"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Species in the human microbiome have enzymes that can metabolize a potentially dangerous lipid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian  Nowogrodzki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is IVF at risk in the US? Scientists fear for the fertility treatment’s future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00830-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00830-1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Alabama court ruling that human embryos outside the uterus should be regarded as children has raised concerns among doctors and scientists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mariana Lenharo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilv in "The Wi-Fi only works when it's raining"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39900247</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39900247"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:40:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite story kinda of this nature, of an expert as alien intelligence, was Feynmann's calculations about computer architecture of the Connection Machine:
https://longnow.org/essays/richard-feynman-connection-machin...
It's a few paragraphs, maybe too much to quote, but the bulk of it starts with:
> By the end of that summer of 1983, Richard had completed his analysis of the behavior of the router, and much to our surprise and amusement, he presented his answer in the form of a set of partial differential equations.  To a physicist this may seem natural, but to a computer designer, treating a set of boolean circuits as a continuous, differentiable system is a bit strange. [...] Our discrete analysis said we needed seven buffers per chip; Feynman's equations suggested that we only needed five. We decided to play it safe and ignore Feynman.
Guess who was right.
The whole essay is worth reading, if you haven't yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[London Stock Exchange Group uses chaos engineering on AWS to improve resilience]]></title>
        <id>345ba3f0d8c5ac648ee210aecd44afc75b663028</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/london-stock-exchange-group-uses-chaos-engineering-on-aws-to-improve-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T20:43:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Luke Sudgen, Lead DevOps Engineer Post Trade, and Padraig Murphy, Solutions Architect Post Trade, from London Stock Exchange Group. In this post, we’ll discuss some failure scenarios that were tested by London Stock Exchange Group (LSEG) Post Trade Technology teams during a chaos engineering event supported by AWS. Chaos engineering […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elias Bedmar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Ensh*ttification”: A General Theory for the Life Cycle of the Firm?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269302</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/enshttification-a-general-theory-for-the-life-cycle-of-the-firm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T20:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It is the people that distinguish one company from another."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eli in "Xzbot: Notes, honeypot, and exploit demo for the xz backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39898419</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39898419"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More to the point it prevents your enemies from using the exploit against friendly targets.
The tradeoff is that, once you find it, it's very clearly a backdoor. No way you can pretend this was an innocent bug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS-Optimized Amazon Linux 2023 AMIs Now Available]]></title>
        <id>a410d9b329bc9e36892be6cb10663b49849ddd61</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-optimized-amazon-linux-2023-amis-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:08:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction We are excited to announce general availability of Amazon Linux 2023 (AL2023) on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). AL2023 is the next generation of Amazon Linux from Amazon Web Services (AWS) and is designed to provide a secure, stable, high-performance environment to develop and run your cloud applications. The standard AL2023-based EKS-optimized Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Premal Tailor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 4/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269308</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/200pm-water-cooler-4-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — AWS Chips Taste Test, generative AI updates, Community Days, and more — April 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>29a22a04939e0190f624818d8958fa5f905572fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-chips-taste-test-generative-ai-updates-community-days-and-more-april-1-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is April Fool’s Day. About 10 years ago, some tech companies would joke about an idea that was thought to be fun and unfeasible on April 1st, to the delight of readers. Jeff Barr has also posted seemingly far-fetched ideas on this blog in the past, and some of these have surprisingly come true! […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jordigh in "The Wi-Fi only works when it's raining"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896826</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896826"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let me see if I'm the first one to link to that classic story in the same series, "I cannot send email further than 500 miles"
http://www.ibiblio.org/harris/500milemail.html
Or the Magic/More Magic switch
http://www.catb.org/jargon/html/magic-story.html
It's fun when physical reality meets the abstract models that we have built in our heads of these machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jordigh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by haswell in "Xzbot: Notes, honeypot, and exploit demo for the xz backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896392</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896392"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I suspect the original rationale is about preserving the longevity of the backdoor. If you blow a hole wide open that anyone can enter, it’s going to be found and shut down quickly.
If this hadn’t had the performance impact that brought it quickly to the surface, it’s possible that this would have lived quietly for a long time exactly because it’s not widely exploitable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>haswell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indiana’s DEI Law]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52531</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/01/indianas-dei-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here in the U.S., my home state of Indiana has a new state-mandated DEI initiative: The law specifies that: “Each board of trustees [of a public college] shall establish a policy that provides that a faculty member may not be granted tenure or a promotion by the institution if, based on past performance or other […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gina Schouten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asveikau in "Xzbot: Notes, honeypot, and exploit demo for the xz backdoor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896221</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39896221"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's pretty interesting that they didn't just introduce an RCE that anyone can exploit, it requires the attacker's private key. It's ironically a very security conscious vulnerability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asveikau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mysterydip in "Error Handling in Baby Toys"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39895942</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39895942"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Related but a nod from a toy engineer to parents: my daughter had a toy baby gamepad when she was little. The D-pad and four buttons made different sounds when pressed. I decided to try the konami code (up up down down left right left right b a) and it went through a special sound sequence then said, "you win!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mysterydip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devolution and the Decline in Operational Capacity and Elite/Managerial Competence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=269301</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/04/devolution-and-the-decline-in-operational-capacity-and-elite-managerial-competence.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has devolution, as in technologies that increase output at the cost of skill,  contributed to the decline in operational capability?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merging Fields, Mathematicians Go the Distance on Old Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=136723</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/merging-fields-mathematicians-go-the-distance-on-old-problem-20240401/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mathematicians have illuminated what sets of points can look like if the distances between them are all whole numbers.            
The post Merging Fields, Mathematicians Go the Distance on Old Problem first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Klarreich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building D1: a Global Database]]></title>
        <id>660605bfa5fcdf000a08ef79</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-d1-a-global-database"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[D1, Cloudflare’s SQL database, is now generally available. With new support for 10GB databases, data export, and enhanced query debugging, we empower developers to build production-ready applications with D1 to meet all their relational SQL needs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vy Ton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Workers environment variables contain live objects]]></title>
        <id>66061348a5fcdf000a08f052</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-environment-live-object-bindings"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bindings don't just reduce boilerplate. They are a core design feature of the Workers platform which simultaneously improve developer experience and application security in several ways. Usually these two goals are in opposition to each other, but bindings elegantly solve for both at the same time]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenton Varda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making state easy with D1 GA, Hyperdrive, Queues and Workers Analytics Engine updates]]></title>
        <id>66060ca6a5fcdf000a08efd4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/making-full-stack-easier-d1-ga-hyperdrive-queues"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We kick off the week with announcements that help developers build stateful applications on top of Cloudflare, including making D1, our SQL database and Hyperdrive, our database accelerating service, generally available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rita Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 4bpp in "LLaMA now goes faster on CPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39893444</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39893444"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T12:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would be good to see some independent verification of this claim. HN has previously [1] fallen for a claim by the same author to have reduced llama.cpp memory usage for a dense model way below the size of the model, which should have failed a basic smell test and indeed was debunked shortly after. Justine Tunney appears to enjoy extreme superstar status here, and it's hard to overstate the degree of social pressure that needed to be overcome at the time for the skeptic position to reach fixation (to begin with, what other LLM developments even hit upvote numbers like the +1300ish there or the +712 here at the time of writing?).
[1] https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35393284]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>4bpp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning by Bouncing: Overdraft Experience and Salience]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28692</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/learning-by-bouncing-overdraft-experience-and-salience/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overdraft credit, when banks and credit unions allow customers to spend more than their checking account holds, has many critics. One fundamental concern is whether overdrafts are salient—whether account holders know how often they overdraw and how much it costs them. To shed light on this question, we asked participants in the New York Fed’s Survey of Consumer Expectations about their experience with and knowledge of their banks’ overdraft programs. The large majority knew how often they overdrew their account and by how much. Their overdraft experience, we find, begets knowledge; of respondents who overdrew their account in the previous year, 84 percent knew the fee they were charged, roughly twice the share for other respondents. However, even experienced overdrafters were relatively unaware of other overdraft terms and practices, such as the maximum overdraft allowed or whether their financial institution processed larger transactions first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donald P. Morgan and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four parking places and a car. Let’s make that a stellar charged wedding.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45249</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/01/four-parking-places-and-a-car-lets-make-that-a-stellar-charged-wedding/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T10:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summary: parking places are a woefully inefficient use of space. And ugly. Cars are a woefully inefficient use of machinery. Using them, in combination with bi-directional charging of cars, to produce solar can amend this. Doing this the right way, parking places can be beautified, costs will go down and life will be more pleasant. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Germany as Collateral Damage in America’s New Cold War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317457</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/germany-as-collateral-damage-in-americas-new-cold-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dismantling of German industry since 2022 is collateral damage in America’s geopolitical war to isolate China, Russia and allied countries whose rising prosperity and self-sufficiency is viewed as an unacceptable challenge to U.S. hegemony. To prepare for what promises to be a long and costly fight, U.S. strategists made a pre-emptive move in 2022 to turn Europe away from its trade and investment relations with Russia. In effect, they asked Germany to commit industrial suicide and become a U.S. dependency. That made Germany the first and most immediate target in America’s New Cold War. More
The post Germany as Collateral Damage in America’s New Cold War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starvation in Gaza: The World Court’s Latest Intervention]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317443</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/starvation-in-gaza-the-world-courts-latest-intervention/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rarely has the International Court of Justice been so constantly exercised by one topic during a short span of time.  On January 26, the World Court, considering a filing made the previous December by South Africa, accepted Pretoria’s argument that the Convention on the Prevention and Punishment of the Crime of Genocide was applicable to the conflict in so far as Israel was bound to observe it in its military operations against Hamas in Gaza.  More
The post Starvation in Gaza: The World Court’s Latest Intervention appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate Profiteering Destroyed the Baltimore Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317449</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/corporate-profiteering-destroyed-the-baltimore-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, the U.S. Department of Labor investigated a complaint against Maersk and concluded that the company had violated the Seaman’s Protection Act by retaliating against a whistleblower employee. At stake was the fact that, as per the Labor Department, “Reporting Policy requires seamen to report safety concerns to the company and allow it time to abate the conditions before reporting to the [U.S. Coast Guard] or other regulatory agencies.” In other words, Maersk, which is one of the world’s top shipping companies, tried to protect itself from government regulators. More
The post Corporate Profiteering Destroyed the Baltimore Bridge appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Narratives]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317452</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/ukraine-narratives/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It all depends on the story one tells.  When the Russians invaded Ukraine, many observers saw Putin as attempting to crush Ukraine, acquire territory and recreate a new Soviet empire.  Some Eastern European countries feared that Russia might invade their borders.  U.S. President Joe Biden saw the invasion as a threat to democracy. As the war shifted southeastward,  More
The post Ukraine Narratives appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bomber Biden Doesn’t Wage Peace, Save Civilians or Listen to American Antiwar Crimes Advocates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317496</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/bomber-biden-doesnt-wage-peace-save-civilians-or-listen-to-american-antiwar-crimes-advocates/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe Biden has long had a problem with PEACE – as in “ceasefires,” “serious peace negotiations,” and conditioning the transfer or sale of major weapons systems as required by five U.S. criminal statutes. From one side of his mouth, Biden urges futilely Israeli compliance with international law while on the other side he supports the  More
The post Bomber Biden Doesn’t Wage Peace, Save Civilians or Listen to American Antiwar Crimes Advocates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU Is Marching Toward an Independent and Integrated Military]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/the-eu-is-marching-toward-an-independent-and-integrated-military/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the European Defense Agency’s annual conference in November 2023, President of the European Commission Ursula von der Leyen warned member states from buying too much equipment from abroad and called for a European Defense Union. While the defense union is yet to materialize, the first-ever European Defense Industrial Strategy signed in early March 2024 marked another significant  More
The post The EU Is Marching Toward an Independent and Integrated Military appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan Election Laws are Designed to Guarantee Democracy Despite Personal Ambitions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317484</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/venezuelan-election-laws-are-designed-to-guarantee-democracy-despite-personal-ambitions/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuela has one of the most progressive constitutions in the world spearheaded by former president Hugo Chavez in 1999. Article 1 sets the tone: “The Republic of Venezuela is forever and irrevocably free and independent from any domination or protection by a foreign power.” This is binding to everyone in Venezuela. The constitution is supported by a  More
The post Venezuelan Election Laws are Designed to Guarantee Democracy Despite Personal Ambitions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nino Pagliccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kudos to Montana Supreme Court for Defending Democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317481</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/kudos-to-montana-supreme-court-for-defending-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Montanans who believe our democracy is founded on the right of people to vote in free and fair elections owe a huge debt of gratitude to Montana’s recent Supreme Court decision overturning four laws passed by the Republican-dominated 2021 legislature as unconstitutional.  Those bogus bills were signed into law by Republican Gov. Greg Gianforte and defended by  More
The post Kudos to Montana Supreme Court for Defending Democracy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Profits Are Still Rising, Why Is the Fed Worried About Wage Growth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317448</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/profits-are-still-rising-why-is-the-fed-worried-about-wage-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was more than a bit surprised to see the profit data this morning. I really did believe that the profit surge during the pandemic was a one-off, associated with supply-chain issues. We can argue about how much of this increase was a predictable story, where profits rise due to shortages, and how much was  More
The post Profits Are Still Rising, Why Is the Fed Worried About Wage Growth? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of Generosity: My Collaboration with Mark Roskill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317491</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/04/01/in-praise-of-generosity-my-collaboration-with-mark-roskill/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you make the transition from being a well-trained graduate student to becoming a successful productive scholar? Sometimes that is not easy, for the distance between graduate school training and original writing can be enormous. Nowadays normally academics go to graduate school, pass the classes, take exams, and then struggle while teaching to come  More
The post In Praise of Generosity: My Collaboration with Mark Roskill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fragmede in "LLaMA now goes faster on CPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39891030</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39891030"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T04:52:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The other reason is to find out what a detuned model is capable of. The canonical example is how to make cocaine, which ChatGPT will admonish you for even asking, while llama2-uncensored will happily describe the process which is only really interesting if you're an amateur chemist and want to be Scarface-that-knocks. (the recipe is relatively easy, it's getting access to the raw ingredients that's the hard part, same as with nukes.)
if you accidentally use the word"hack" when trying to get ChatGPT to write some code for you. it'll stop and tell you that hacking is bad, and not a colloquial expression, and refuse to go further.
privacy reasons are another reason to try a local LLM. for the extremely paranoid (justified or not), a local LLM gives users a place to ask questions without the text being fed to a server somewhere for later lawsuit discovery (Google searches are routinely subpoenaed, it's only a matter of time until ChatGPT chats are as well.)
There's an uncensored model for vision available as well. The censored vision models won't play the shallow game of hot or not with you.
There are uncensored image generation models as well, but, ah, those are NSFW and not for polite company. (As well as there's multiple thesis' worth of content on what that'll do to society.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fragmede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "LLaMA now goes faster on CPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39890656</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39890656"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T03:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I strongly recommend that people run LLMs locally for a different reason.
The ones you can run on your own machine tend to be bad - really bad. They hallucinate wildly and fail at all sorts of tasks that the larger hosted ones succeed at.
This makes them a fantastic tool for learning more about how LLMs work and what they're useful for. Interacting with a weak-but-functional LLM that runs on your own computer is a great way to get a much more solid mental model for what these things actually are.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bottlepalm in "LLaMA now goes faster on CPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39890454</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39890454"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T02:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it's a good idea for everyone to download and be able to run a LLM locally, even if you have the minimum of requirements. As a pseudo-backup of a large chunk of human knowledge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bottlepalm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Free shipping isn’t really free (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39889598</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39889598"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article is trying to paint baking in the shipping cost into the item's sale price as some diabolical anti-consumer ploy but in reality that's exactly what customers want. Yes I know free shipping isn't actually "free", just like how free returns aren't free and customer service isn't free and the warranty isn't free and the credit card transaction isn't free... But I still don't care. Tell me ONE price — inclusive of everything — up front, and I'll decide if I want to buy your product or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Complexity of avian evolution revealed by family-level genomes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07323-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07323-1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nature - Complexity of avian evolution revealed by family-level genomes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josefin Stiller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green space near home has an antidepressant effect]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00968-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00968-y"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People who had the most vegetation near their residences were the least likely to report depression and anxiety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nature</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I use tide gauges to develop geospatial maps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00908-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00908-w"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geographer Muh Aris Marfai collects reference data for Indonesia’s coastal areas to prepare for the impacts of climate change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikki Forrester</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How scientists are making the most of Reddit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00906-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00906-y"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As X wanes, researchers are turning to Reddit for insights and data, and to better connect with the public.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hannah Docter-Loeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How synthetic biologists are building better biofactories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00907-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00907-x"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial electron donors and acceptors expand researchers’ metabolic engineering options — if only cells would cooperate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sara Reardon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by roenxi in "Documentation for the AMD 7900XTX"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39889198</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39889198"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T23:24:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So for reference, this geohot is George Hotz who has a company Tiny Corp [0] in the space. Among a long list of things, he had a moment in the spotlight recently for a long rant [1] where he "gave up on AMD" because their drivers sucked more than he expected. The situation is reasonably complex - AMD have some programmers working on ROCm who seemed to be operating at standard fare when that is really not what AMD needs right now (I personally, suspect there is/was a PM in a key position who didn't "get it", although I am not sure what it is either). As far as I know it got the attention of Lisa Su.
I'm cheering him on, even though his complaints were a little melodramatic. My experience is the driver technically supports everything I could possibly want. The problem is if I spend an evening trying to do anything with OpenCL or ROCm the kernel hard-locks and I go to bed early. If the problem inside is what it looks like from the outside (repeating myself, a key manager somewhere just doesn't get the space) they really need some pressure from grumpy customers like George to realign their software development process.
That context might be related to this particular case. I see a suspicious folder called "crash" in this repo.
[0] https://tinygrad.org/
[1] https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mr0rWJhv9jU - as I recall he ran the demo suite and it crashed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>roenxi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by itsjustme2 in "A proposal to add signals to JavaScript"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39887549</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39887549"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T20:03:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Am I the only one that thinks the vanilla js example is actually easier to read and work with?
- "The setup is noise and boilerplate heavy." Actually the signals example looks just as noisy and boilerplate heavy to me. And it introduces new boilerplate concepts which are hard for beginners to understand.
- "If the counter changes but parity does not (e.g. counter goes from 2 to 4), then we do unnecessary computation of the parity and unnecessary rendering." - Sounds like they want premature memoization.
- "What if another part of our UI just wants to render when the counter updates?" Then I agree the strawman example is probably not what you want. At that point you might want to handle the state using signals, event handling, central state store (e.g. redux-like tools), or some other method. I think this is also what they meant by "The counter state is tightly coupled to the rendering system."? Some of this document feels a little repetitive.
- "What if another part of our UI is dependent on isEven or parity alone?" Sure, you could change your entire approach because of this if that's a really central part of your app, but most often it's not. And "The render function, which is only dependent on parity must instead "know" that it actually needs to subscribe to counter." is often not an unreasonable obligation. I mean, that's one of the nice things about pure computed functions- it's easy to spot their inputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>itsjustme2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Films of 2024:Q1]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874771481/0/themoneyillusion~Films-of-Q/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874771481/0/themoneyillusion~Films-of-Q/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T18:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read another Gene Wolfe trilogy, this one about ancient Greece. Not as good as the three &#8220;Sun&#8221; series, but still enjoyable. Stefan Zweig&#8217;s The World of Yesterday was another highlight, a brilliant work of social science masquerading as a memoir. Benjamin Moser&#8217;s The Upside Down World is an excellent study of Dutch painting, and [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874771481/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874771481/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-31-at-1.29.42-PM-909x1024.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874771481/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874771481/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874771481/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comment-6802445">econmist manque sumner is running out of movies to review, or ...</a> <i>by agrippa postumus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comment-6802351">“indispensable.”   Likewise for your comments.</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comment-6802348">“In the Court of the Crimson King”   I didn't know this ...</a> <i>by anon/portly</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comment-6802322">“It’s good to know that someone finds this stuff useful.” ...</a> <i>by anon/portly</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comment-6802287">Thanks Rick. It's good to know that someone finds this stuff ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/films-of-2024q1/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Developer Week 2024]]></title>
        <id>66087d34a5fcdf000a08f160</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/welcome-to-developer-week-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T17:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re kicking off 2024’s Developer Week, and we’re excited to welcome you to the week and give you a small preview of what to expect, and how we’re thinking about the future of our platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rita Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mo_42 in "How to graduate your PhD when you have no hope"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39884431</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39884431"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T14:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From my experience, I strongly do not recommended You and Your Research.
When I started my PhD I read this text as well. Of course I was very motivated of doing only important research. After some time I even found a nice research topic and worked on it for over two years. Even my advisor pointed out that it was a very novel and foundational idea.
At the same time, a colleague published three papers in top conferences. Their approach was basically to look at publications from the previous conference, apply some delta that they had an advantage over other teams and publish this in the next round.
Reviewers were happy because their publications already got cited and they understood the topic well.
Whereas my topic used an algorithm from the seventies that reviewers had to revisit. My topic didn't fit so well into the overall conference trend and so I still have way less citations than those incremental works.
When someone asks me if it's worth doing a PhD I tend to say that you need to like the direction in which science is going. If you don't like it and are rather rebellious, it's better to start a company.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mo_42</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sunshine_reggae in "Tell HN: Reddit now blocks VPN access via browser, 'old' subdomain included"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39884349</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39884349"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T14:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, same here.
Let's just QUIT using Reddit. Enough is enough. If we tolerate corrupt behavior, we support corrupt behavior.
And quite honestly, it's become such a pile of trash, anyway. Also, it's become so obvious that submissions and comments are being manipulated and pushed by tons of bots and industry interests, it's just a bad joke at this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sunshine_reggae</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Canal Saint-Martin, Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52550</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/31/sunday-photoblogging-canal-saint-martin-paris/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T07:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Banality of Sir Keir Starmer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/31/the-banality-of-sir-keir-starmer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T06:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secretary Antony J. Blinken meets with British Labour Party leader Keir Starmer in Munich, Germany, February 17, 2024. (Official State Department photo by Chuck Kennedy)
What is remarkable about Sir Keir Starmer, however, is that he has not a single, discernible positive quality.    If he got lost in Tesco, and his mum put out his description on the tannoy, there would be no possible chance of him being tracked down.  He is not a good speaker, his nasal voice drones on and on, a lulling invitation to the most pronounced meaninglessness.   When asked about his vision for the future, he says things like this:‘Changing the things that need changing … that is the change I will bring about!’
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Banality of Sir Keir Starmer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s War Psychosis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317435</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/31/israels-war-psychosis/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T05:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bomb-shattered buildings in Gaza. Photo: Tasnim News Agency, CC BY-SA 4.0.
The October 7 Hamas-led attack on Israelis followed by the extremely disproportionate IDF assault on Gaza has been accompanied by a slew of racist invective by Israeli leaders. Dan Gillerman, the former Israeli ambassador to the UN referred to Palestinians as “horrible inhuman animals.” Israel’s defense minister, Yoav Gallant, used the same hate expression. Netanyahu called Gaza a “city of evil,” summoning the Old Testament tale of Sodom and Gomorrah, in which the Israeli government now gets to play God.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Israel’s War Psychosis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerald Sussman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who’ll Stop the Rain?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=317401</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/03/30/wholl-stop-the-rain/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T12:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ The UN has been used to start many wars, but has it ever stopped one? The Security Council’s ceasefire resolution, temporary as it is, was completely ignored by Israel. Will any of the Council’s members (China? Russia?) use their considerable power to enforce it?
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Who’ll Stop the Rain? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty EC2 Runtime Monitoring is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>d4d25eead84d8e9e4dca3d48a430a61aa73e18dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-ec2-runtime-monitoring-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T20:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty is a machine learning (ML)-based security monitoring and intelligent threat detection service that analyzes and processes various AWS data sources, continuously monitors your AWS accounts and workloads for malicious activity, and delivers detailed security findings for visibility and remediation. I love the feature of GuardDuty Runtime Monitoring that analyzes operating system (OS)-level, network, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed is clumsy]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675130/0/themoneyillusion~The-Fed-is-clumsy/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675130/0/themoneyillusion~The-Fed-is-clumsy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fed should not be targeting interest rates. But if it insists on doing so, then the most efficient regime would adjust the fed funds rate target by basis points (i.e., 0.01%), not quarter point increments. In addition, the rate should be adjusted daily based on the median vote of the FOMC. It should move [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874675130/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874675130/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874675130/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874675130/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874675130/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comment-6802284">To what do you attribute the economics profession desire to ...</a> <i>by Effem</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comment-6802121">Scott,   Thesis:   The Fed cares less about inflation (let ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comment-6801785">Bobster, Sure, it's possible.   Jeff, Of course rates can fall ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comment-6801770">If NGDP growth remains high, the inflation will persist.   Yep ...</a> <i>by SK</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comment-6801686">“Highly consequential” seems to be a reference not just to ...</a> <i>by Jeff</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-fed-is-clumsy/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A question for critics of democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675133/0/themoneyillusion~A-question-for-critics-of-democracy/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675133/0/themoneyillusion~A-question-for-critics-of-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There&#8217;s a certain type of person that doesn&#8217;t trust democracy. On the left, there&#8217;s a perception that difficult issues must be left to the experts. On the right, a fear that &#8220;the mob&#8221; will try to extract wealth from the rich. These people have trouble explaining Switzerland, by far the most democratic country on Earth. [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874675133/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874675133/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874675133/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874675133/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874675133/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comment-6802120">Scott,   I think you are misrepresenting the view of the ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comment-6801822">I agree that democracies make better decisions than ...</a> <i>by Carl</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comment-6801550">Carl, If you are saying that democracies often make bad ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comment-6801531">Another explanation is that people by and large actually do ...</a> <i>by Jeff</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comment-6801507">Is this what you expected?   Let's see. The vote turnout was ...</a> <i>by Jim Glass</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/a-question-for-critics-of-democracy/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What do you mean by &#8220;you&#8221;?]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675136/0/themoneyillusion~What-do-you-mean-by-%e2%80%9cyou%e2%80%9d/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874675136/0/themoneyillusion~What-do-you-mean-by-%e2%80%9cyou%e2%80%9d/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T16:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People ask me: &#8220;What do you think about X?&#8221; It might be the path of interest rates or stock prices or the rate of inflation. I might respond &#8220;Well, the market is predicting . . . &#8221; They respond; &#8220;No, what do YOU think about X.&#8221; I can only respond, what do you mean by [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874675136/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874675136/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874675136/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874675136/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874675136/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comment-6802060">An entity with an IQ of 250 be capable of discerning objective ...</a> <i>by Philo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comment-6801552">Sean, I'm not talking about people like Sam Altman (who I don't ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comment-6801368">Only the very extreme right tail is smarter than you by any ...</a> <i>by Sean</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comment-6800919">The weighted average of experts believed that DDT was harmless. ...</a> <i>by Sara</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comment-6800881">Yep, Objective truth is just a myth.   2+2 doesn't equal 4. It ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/what-do-you-mean-by-you/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s Applied AI Research]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/c34b8a1569e4</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-ones-applied-ai-research-c34b8a1569e4?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T14:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about how Capital One’s Applied AI Research is fueling the frontier of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimizing on-call burnout through alerts observability]]></title>
        <id>66032966a5fcdf000a08e732</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/alerts-observability"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Cloudflare used open-source tools to enhance alert observability, leading to increased resilience and improved on-call team well-being]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Monika Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Kahneman has died]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52539</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/29/daniel-kahneman-has-died/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T04:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Kahneman, who was, along with Elinor Ostrom, one of the very few non-economists to win the Economics Nobel award, has died aged 90. There are lots of obituaries out there, so I won’t try to summarise his work. Rather, I’ll talk about how it influenced my own academic career. When I was an undergraduate, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The great rewiring: is social media really behind an epidemic of teenage mental illness?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00902-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00902-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evidence is equivocal on whether screen time is to blame for rising levels of teen depression and anxiety — and rising hysteria could distract us from tackling the real causes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Candice L. Odgers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting your Amazon EKS web apps with AWS WAF]]></title>
        <id>257507f474fb2b9e42ef9eb8c686959d172d720d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/protecting-your-amazon-eks-web-apps-with-aws-waf/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze the traffic patterns on any public-facing website or web app, and you’ll notice connection requests from all over the world. Apart from the intended traffic, a typical web application responds to requests from bots, health checks, and various attempts to circumvent security and gain unauthorized access. In addition to impacting your customer’s experience, these […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elamaran Shanmugam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LangFriend: a Journal with Long-Term Memory]]></title>
        <id>65fa3a289333bd00014c371f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/langfriend/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the concepts we are most interested in at LangChain is memory. Whenever we are interested in a concept, we like to build an example app showing off that concept. For memory, we decided to build a journaling app! We're hosting a version of it that anyone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Social Benefits of Getting Our Brains in Sync]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=136671</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-social-benefits-of-getting-our-brains-in-sync-20240328/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T13:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our brain waves can align when we work and play closely together. The phenomenon, known as interbrain synchrony, suggests that collaboration is biological.            
The post The Social Benefits of Getting Our Brains in Sync first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marta Zaraska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Is Flocking Like Computing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=136659</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/how-is-flocking-like-computing-20240328/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Birds flock. Locusts swarm. Fish school. From chaotic assemblies of life, order somehow emerges. In this episode, co-host Steven Strogatz interviews the evolutionary ecologist Iain Couzin about how and why collective behaviors arise.            
The post How Is Flocking Like Computing? first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Strogatz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Copper-catalyzed dehydrogenation or lactonization of C(sp<sup>3</sup>)−H bonds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07341-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07341-z"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nature - Copper-catalyzed dehydrogenation or lactonization of C(sp3)−H bonds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shupeng Zhou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists made a six-legged mouse embryo — here’s why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00943-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00943-7"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A rodent with two extra limbs instead of genitals shows the crucial role of a gene pathway in determining the fate of a primordial structure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sara Reardon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a spreadsheet helped me to land my dream job]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00950-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00950-8"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A shared spreadsheet, passed from generation to generation, helps graduate students in management navigate the academic job market. Whatever your field of study, you can make one, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvia  Sanasi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The corpse of an exploded star and more — March’s best science images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00941-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00941-9"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The month’s sharpest science shots, selected by Nature’s photo team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emma Stoye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sam Bankman-Fried sentencing: crypto-funded researchers grapple with FTX collapse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00960-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00960-6"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations who received funds from FTX face pressure to return the money at significant operational cost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan O'Callaghan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This super-Earth is the first planet confirmed to have a permanent dark side]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00414-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00414-z"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Convincing evidence of 1:1 tidal locking has been absent until a new analysis of the exoplanet LHS 3855b.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Howlett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming low vision to prove my abilities under pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00957-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00957-1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A genetic eye condition pushed biochemist Kamini Govender to develop coping strategies that serve her well in the lab and help her to avoid burnout.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lesley Evans Ogden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How papers with doctored images can affect scientific reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00875-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00875-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists compiling a review scan more than 1,000 papers and find troubling images in nearly 20%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumeet Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[new issue of Real-World Economics Review]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45236</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/27/new-issue-of-real-world-economics-review-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T17:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please click here to support this open-access journal and the WEA   real-world economic review issue no. 106 download whole issue   How entropy drives us towards degrowth Crelis Rammelt 2 “It is much too soon to act “ – Economists and the climate change Giandomenico Scarpelli 8 Addressing the climate and inequality crises: An emergency […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Researcher Who Explores Computation by Conjuring New Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.quantamagazine.org/?p=136607</id>
        <link href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-researcher-who-explores-computation-by-conjuring-new-worlds-20240327/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T14:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russell Impagliazzo studies hard problems, the limits of cryptography, the nature of randomness and more.            
The post The Researcher Who Explores Computation by Conjuring New Worlds first appeared on Quanta Magazine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Brubaker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deposits and the March 2023 Banking Crisis—A Retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28971</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/deposits-and-the-march-2023-banking-crisis-a-retrospective/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we evaluate how deposits have evolved over the latter portion of the current monetary policy tightening cycle. We find that while deposit betas have continued to rise, they did not accelerate following the bank runs in March 2023. In addition, while overall deposit funding has remained stable, we find that the banks most affected by the March 2023 events are offering higher deposit rates and are growing their deposit funding relative to the broader banking industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephan Luck and Matthew Plosser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tweeting your research paper boosts engagement but not citations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00922-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00922-y"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analysis of a random selection of papers shared on social media showed no causative link between posting and citations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bianca Nogrady</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video: Cancer-busting vaccines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00842-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00842-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treatments that could train the immune system to identify and destroy cancer cells are on the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nature</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cancer-vaccine trials give reasons for optimism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00840-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00840-z"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Therapeutic vaccines could provide a transformative shot in the arm for cancer treatment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Liam Drew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No sweat: Moisture-wicking device keeps wearable-tech dry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00945-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00945-5"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Breathable patch could allow for comfortable and multifunctional wearable electronics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A global timekeeping problem postponed by global warming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07170-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07170-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increased melting of ice in Greenland and Antarctica, measured by satellite gravity, has decreased the angular velocity of Earth more rapidly than before and has already affected global timekeeping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Duncan Carr Agnew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CGRP sensory neurons promote tissue healing via neutrophils and macrophages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07237-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07237-y"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experiments in mouse models show that NaV1.8+ nociceptors innervate sites of injury and provide wound repair signals to immune cells by releasing calcitonin gene-related peptide (CGRP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yen-Zhen Lu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formation of memory assemblies through the DNA-sensing TLR9 pathway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07220-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07220-7"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning results in persistent double-stranded DNA breaks, nuclear rupture and release of DNA fragments and histones within hippocampal CA1 neurons that, following TLR9-mediated DNA damage repair, results in their recruitment to memory circuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladimir Jovasevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The HEAT repeat protein HPO-27 is a lysosome fission factor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07249-8</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07249-8"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conserved HEAT repeat protein HPO-27 is identified as a lysosome scission factor in Caenorhabditis elegans, and the human homologue MROH1 also serves the same function to maintain lysosomal homeostasis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Letao Li</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five million years of Antarctic Circumpolar Current strength variability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07143-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07143-3"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The strength of the Antarctic Circumpolar Current, as traced in sediment cores from the Pacific Southern Ocean, shows no linear long-term trend over the past 5.3 Myr; instead, the strongest flow occurs consistently in warmer-than-present intervals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Lamy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optomechanical realization of the&#xa0;bosonic Kitaev chain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07174-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07174-w"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We report the experimental realization of a bosonic Kitaev chain in a nano-optomechanical network.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jesse J. Slim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TRBC1-targeting antibody–drug conjugates for the treatment of T cell cancers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07233-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07233-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-TRBC1 antibody–drug conjugates may offer a more potent T cell cancer therapy by bypassing the fratricide that may be limiting the efficacy of anti-TRBC1 CAR T cells in the clinical trial for patients with T cell cancers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tushar D. Nichakawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Depleting myeloid-biased haematopoietic stem cells rejuvenates aged immunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07238-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07238-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antibody-mediated depletion of myeloid-biased haematopoietic stem cells in aged mice restores characteristic features of a more youthful immune system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason B. Ross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structural basis of exoribonuclease-mediated mRNA transcription termination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07240-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07240-3"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A study presents two cryo-EM structures of yeast Pol II pre-termination transcription complexes bound to Rat1–Rai1, and provides the mechanisms for termination of mRNA transcription in yeast and other eukaryotes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yuan Zeng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-fidelity spin qubit operation and algorithmic initialization above 1 K]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07160-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07160-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Initialization and operation of spin qubits in silicon above 1 K reach fidelities sufficient for fault-tolerant operations at these temperatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Y. Huang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controlling the helicity of light by electrical magnetization switching]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07125-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07125-5"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The helicity of light from a light-emitting diode can be electrically controlled by spin–orbit torque effects, enabling a seamless integration of magnetization dynamics with photonics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pambiang Abel Dainone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graphene nanoribbons grown in hBN stacks for high-performance electronics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07243-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07243-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A strategy for the transfer-free direct growth of ultralong, high-quality graphene nanoribbons, which have desirable electronic properties, between layers of a boron nitride insulator is reported.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bosai Lyu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A figure of merit for efficiency roll-off in TADF-based organic LEDs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07149-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07149-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiency roll-off in a wide range of TADF OLEDs is analysed and a figure of merit proposed for materials design to improve efficiency at high brightness, potentially expanding the range of applications of TADF materials.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>S. Diesing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The complex polyploid genome architecture of sugarcane]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07231-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07231-4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We build a polyploid reference genome for hybrid sugarcane cultivar R570, improving on its current ‘mosaic monoploid’ representation, enabling fine-grain description of genome architecture and the exploration of candidate genes underlying the Bru1 brown rust resistance locus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>A. L. Healey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Targeting DCAF5 suppresses <i>SMARCB1</i>-mutant cancer by stabilizing SWI/SNF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07250-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07250-1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DCAF5 has a quality-control function for SWI/SNF complexes and promotes the degradation of incompletely assembled SWI/SNF complexes in the absence of SMARCB1.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandi Radko-Juettner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate velocities and species tracking in global mountain regions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07264-9</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07264-9"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of the rate at which isotherms are shifting in mountain regions worldwide identifies 17 key regions with particularly high vertical isotherm shift velocities, and provides insight into how these shifts affect species ranges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wei-Ping Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revealing uncertainty in the status of biodiversity change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07236-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07236-z"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This study presents an approach to deal with spatial, temporal and phylogenetic non-independence in large-scale analyses of biodiversity change, improving trend estimation and inference across scales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>T. F. Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The complex circumstellar environment of supernova 2023ixf]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07116-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07116-6"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using ultraviolet data as well as a comprehensive set of further multiwavelength observations of the supernova 2023ixf, a reliable bolometric light curve is derived that indicates the heating nature of the early emission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>E. A. Zimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Single-cell multiplex chromatin and RNA interactions in ageing human brain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07239-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07239-w"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We introduce multinucleic acid interaction mapping in single cells (MUSIC), for concurrent profiling of multiplex chromatin interactions, gene expression and RNA–chromatin associations within individual nuclei, as a tool for exploring chromatin architecture and transcription.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xingzhao Wen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heat and desiccation tolerances predict bee abundance under climate change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07241-2</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07241-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 16-year dataset of abundance patterns of a diverse assemblage of bees in New Mexico, USA predicts declines for many bee species and indicates that drought-tolerant taxa will prevail in a warming and drying climate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie R. Kazenel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A three-dimensional liquid diode for soft, integrated permeable electronics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07161-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07161-1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incorporation of a ‘liquid diode’ into a wearable electronic platform enhances comfort and stability by shunting away sweat as it accumulates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binbin Zhang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interchain-expanded extra-large-pore zeolites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07194-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07194-6"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We report a strategy that yields thermally and hydrothermally stable silicates by expansion of a one-dimensional silicate chain with an intercalated silylating agent that separates and connects the chains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zihao Rei Gao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence for chiral graviton modes in fractional quantum Hall liquids]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07201-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07201-w"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Through inelastic light scattering chiral spin-2 long-wavelength magnetorotons are observed, revealing chiral graviton modes in fractional quantum Hall states and aiding in understanding the quantum metric impacts in topological correlated systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jiehui Liang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-threshold and low-overhead fault-tolerant quantum memory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07107-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07107-7"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An end-to-end quantum error correction protocol that implements fault-tolerant memory on the basis of a family of low-density parity-check codes shows the possibility of low-overhead fault-tolerant quantum memory within the reach of near-term quantum processors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergey Bravyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brainstem–hypothalamus neuronal circuit reduces feeding upon heat exposure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07232-3</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07232-3"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to acute thermal challenge, thermosensing glutamatergic neurons of the parabrachial nucleus in mouse brain activate tanycytes, which reduce the excitability of Flt1-expressing dopamine and agouti-related peptide-containing neurons, thus suppressing appetite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Benevento</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thermonuclear explosions on neutron stars reveal the speed of their jets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07133-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-07133-5"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Relativistic jets observed from transient neutron stars throughout the Universe produce bright flares for minutes after each X-ray burst, helping to determine the role individual system properties have on the speed and revealing the dominant launching mechanism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas D. Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily briefing: Tweeting about your paper doesn’t boost citations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00958-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00958-0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posting about a paper on X seems to boost engagement but not citations. Plus, researchers pinpoint humans’ first home outside Africa and what the science says about the Baltimore bridge collapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Flora Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Journal editors are resigning en masse: what do these group exits achieve?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00887-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00887-y"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editorial rebellions seem to be on the rise, as researchers seek more control over scholarly communication.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katharine Sanderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electrons flip a switch on optical communications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00663-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00663-y"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Light controlled by electrically induced change in magnetization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Satoshi Hiura</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The real time-travel paradox was the friends we made along the way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00897-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00897-w"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life at the cutting edge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Culagovski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change has slowed Earth’s rotation — and could affect how we keep time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00932-w</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00932-w"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The effect of melting polar ice could delay the need for a ‘leap second’ by three years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Gibney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Divisive Sun-dimming study at Harvard cancelled: what’s next?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00876-1</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00876-1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the climate crisis rages on, advocacy for testing controversial solar geoengineering technology is ramping up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Tollefson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising history of the Southern Ocean’s super current]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00678-5</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00678-5"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reconstructions of the strength of the Antarctic circumpolar current.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie J. Burls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-ageing antibodies revive the immune system]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00680-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00680-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rejuvenating an aged immune system with antibody therapy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yasar Arfat T. Kasu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maple-scented cacti and pom-pom cats: how pranking at work can lift lab spirits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00951-7</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00951-7"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether for April Fools’ Day or year-round, practical jokes allow scientists to tap into creative thinking while building group camaraderie.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Heidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The wearable electronic patch that’s impervious to sweat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00789-z</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00789-z"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A flexible liquid diode for protecting wearable devices from moisture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yifan Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make an old immune system young again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00871-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00871-6"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antibodies that target blood stem cells can rejuvenate immune responses in mice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heidi Ledford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mouse brains respond differently to observed threat and direct danger]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00051-6</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00051-6"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danger is interpreted by a specific brain region, but direct and observed dangers are processed differently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nature</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memories are made by breaking DNA — and fixing it]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00930-y</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00930-y"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nerve cells form long-term memories with the help of an inflammatory response, study in mice finds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Max Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melting ice solves leap-second problem — for now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00850-x</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00850-x"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two perspectives on how climate change is affecting timekeeping.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrizia Tavella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Innate immunity in neurons makes memories persist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00679-4</id>
        <link href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00679-4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pathway of the immune system has a surprising role in memory formation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin A. Kelvington</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing HDR photo support to Instagram and Threads]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21166</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/26/android/instagram-threads-hdr-photos/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T16:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s family of apps serves trillions of image download requests every day. And if you’re into high-quality images, you’ve probably noticed that Instagram and Threads have added support for high dynamic range (HDR) photos. Now people on Threads and Instagram can upload and share images that are more true-to-life, with the full color and range [...]
Read More...
The post Bringing HDR photo support to Instagram and Threads appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Extraction Service]]></title>
        <id>660225b35ea622000149efd0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/open-source-extraction-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T15:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this month we announced our most recent OSS use-case accelerant: a service for extracting structured data from unstructured sources, such as text and PDF documents. Today we are exposing a hosted version of the service with a simple front end. The application is free to use, but is not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From .com to .beauty: The evolving threat landscape of unwanted email]]></title>
        <id>65fb5e94a5fcdf000a08dd78</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/top-level-domains-email-phishing-threats"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this 2023-early 2024 email analysis, we examine how certain generic Top-Level Domains (TLDs) are primarily used for spam and phishing, and their evolution over a year. There are many trends in email threats to examine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uber, but for Human Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52535</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/26/52535/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T11:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You open the app and immediately the algorithm shows you what you want. All the drivers in the world—and the algorithm someone finds the one who will get you where you want to go, as cheaply as possible! Uber makes it harder to sustain the myth of “the algorithm.” As I wrote in Mother Jones last month, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happens to U.S. Activity and Inflation if China’s Property Sector Leads to a Crisis?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28575</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/what-happens-to-u-s-activity-and-inflation-if-chinas-property-sector-leads-to-a-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previous post explored the potential implications for U.S. growth and inflation of a manufacturing-led boom in China. This post considers spillovers to the U.S. from a downside scenario, one in which China’s ongoing property sector slump takes another leg down and precipitates an economic hard landing and financial crisis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ozge Akinci, Hunter Clark, Jeff Dawson, Matthew Higgins, Silvia Miranda-Agrippino, Ethan Nourbash, and Ramya Nallamotu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run large-scale simulations with AWS Batch multi-container jobs]]></title>
        <id>27d6439952116d198c3da93cd6bf74a07643e13e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/run-large-scale-simulations-with-aws-batch-multi-container-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T19:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industries like automotive, robotics, and finance are increasingly implementing computational workloads like simulations, machine learning (ML) model training, and big data analytics to improve their products. For example, automakers rely on simulations to test autonomous driving features, robotics companies train ML algorithms to enhance robot perception capabilities, and financial firms run in-depth analyses to better […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GitHub Copilot in your IDE: Tips, tricks, and best practices]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-25-how-to-use-github-copilot-in-your-ide-tips-tricks-and-best-practices/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-25-how-to-use-github-copilot-in-your-ide-tips-tricks-and-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T17:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Copilot is a powerful AI assistant. Learn practical strategies to get the most out of GitHub Copilot to generate the most relevant and useful code suggestions in your editor.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-25-how-to-use-github-copilot-in-your-ide-tips-tricks-and-best-practices/">Using GitHub Copilot in your IDE: Tips, tricks, and best practices</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Savings Plans, Amazon DynamoDB, AWS CodeArtifact, and more — March 25, 2024]]></title>
        <id>88f54ca0364687eda69fa3466dbc6f9799c85ef7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-savings-plans-amazon-dynamodb-aws-codeartifact-and-more-march-25-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T16:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is starting! I’m happy I will meet our customers, partners, and the press next week at the AWS Summit Paris and the week after at the AWS Summit Amsterdam. I’ll show you how mobile application developers can use generative artificial intelligence (AI) to boost their productivity. Be sure to stop by and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism Is Dead – Long Live Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52527</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/25/capitalism-is-dead-long-live-capital/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T14:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his latest book, Technofeudalism, the maverick academic-turned unlikely Minister of Finance-turned enfant terrible of European politics Yanis Varoufakis argues that capitalism has ended. It has not, however, been destroyed by the workers of the world – it has been killed by capital itself. The idea, in a nutshell, is the following. As a response […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Ronzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous hardware diagnostics and recovery at scale]]></title>
        <id>65fdd779a5fcdf000a08def9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/autonomous-hardware-diagnostics-and-recovery-at-scale"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operating hardware in 310 cities in 120 countries means that hardware can break anywhere and anytime. Detecting and managing server failure at scale requires automation. Here's how we automated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jet Mariscal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What if China Manufactures a Sugar High?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28589</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/what-if-china-manufactures-a-sugar-high/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the slump in China’s property sector has been steep, Chinese policymakers have responded to the falloff in property activity with policies designed to spur activity in the manufacturing sector. The apparent hope is that a pivot toward production-intensive growth can help lift the Chinese economy out of its current doldrums, which include weak household demand, high levels of debt, and demographic and political headwinds to growth. In a series of posts, we consider the implications of two alternative Chinese policy scenarios for the risks to the U.S. outlook for real activity and inflation over the next two years. Here, we consider the impact of a scenario in which a credit-fueled boom in manufacturing activity produces higher-than-expected economic growth in China. A key finding is that such a boom would put meaningful upward pressure on U.S. inflation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ozge Akinci, Hunter Clark, Jeff Dawson, Matthew Higgins, Silvia Miranda-Agrippino, Ethan Nourbash, and Ramya Nallamotu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: the Musée Albert Kahn]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52523</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/24/sunday-photoblogging-the-musee-albert-kahn/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T08:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A wonderful few days in Paris where, among other things, we visited the Musée Albert Kahn in Boulogne-Billancourt, which was closed for a long time for “travaux”, but is now refurbished. I’ve wanted to visit the MAK for years to see the collection of autochromes that are the fruit of the expeditions that Kahn financed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Read – Is Bitcoin more energy intensive than mainstream finance?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45225</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/23/long-read-is-bitcoin-more-energy-intensive-than-mainstream-finance/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-23T22:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Blair Fix When it comes to Bitcoin, there’s one thing that almost everyone agrees on: the network sucks up a tremendous amount of energy. But from there, disagreement is the rule. For critics, Bitcoin’s thirst for energy is self-evidently bad — the equivalent of pouring gasoline in a hole and setting it on fire. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Week of 3/18] LangChain Release Notes]]></title>
        <id>65fdb8815ea622000149ecaf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/week-of-3-18-langchain-release-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T17:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🤓 Using Feedback to Improve Your Application: Self Learning GPT
Everyone is trying to figure out how to get better quality LLM-applications. And for us, prompt optimization is top of mind. We’ve been experimenting with if we can take all the data and feedback that we collect in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving Development Forward: How the PGA TOUR speeds up Development with the AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>82d907b0980888d73db747c8af7693c84de03db9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/driving-development-forward-how-the-pga-tour-speeds-up-development-with-the-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is written by Jeff Kammerer, Senior Solutions Architect. The PGA TOUR is the world’s premier membership organization for touring professional golfers, co-sanctioning tournaments on the PGA TOUR along with several other developmental, senior, and international tournament series. The PGA TOUR is passionate about bringing its fans closer to the players, tournaments, and courses. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evgeny Karasik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Fed DSGE Model Forecast—March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28780</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/the-new-york-fed-dsge-model-forecast-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post presents an update of the economic forecasts generated by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s dynamic stochastic general equilibrium (DSGE) model. We describe very briefly our forecast and its change since December 2023. As usual, we wish to remind our readers that the DSGE model forecast is not an official New York Fed forecast, but only an input to the Research staff’s overall forecasting process. For more information about the model and variables discussed here, see our DSGE model Q & A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, Ramya Nallamotu, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Academic Freedom and Institutional Neutrality]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52519</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/22/on-academic-freedom-and-institutional-neutrality/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T07:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago Jacob Levy (McGill)  published a lengthy Op-Ed, “Campus culture wars are a teachable moment in how freedom of speech and academic freedom differ,” in the Globe and Mail. It offered a salutary account on the nature of academic freedom in the aftermath of the “Dec. 5 U.S. House of Representatives committee […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Price indices: constant utility or constant quantity?]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130828/0/themoneyillusion~Price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130828/0/themoneyillusion~Price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T00:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Josh Hendrickson argues that an ideal price index should include asset prices. I am not going to address that issue, as I&#8217;m not sure what an ideal price index is. But it&#8217;s a good post&#8212;worth reading if you are interested in price indices. Instead, I&#8217;d like to focus on a less controversial claim in the [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874130828/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874130828/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-21-at-9.59.09-AM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874130828/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874130828/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874130828/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comment-6802314">Scott, I agree it's subjective but I think a price index will ...</a> <i>by Justin</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comment-6802310">It all depends on what is the purpose of the price index. Thus ...</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comment-6802307">There is an inconsistency with how cars and houses are treated ...</a> <i>by Justin</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comment-6802306">Justin, I used to use the example of the 1986 Acura Legend, ...</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comment-6802299">I'm a bit late to this, but this is a very good post.   I've ...</a> <i>by Justin</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/price-indices-constant-utility-or-constant-quantity/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasure for pleasure]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130831/0/themoneyillusion~Treasure-for-pleasure/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130831/0/themoneyillusion~Treasure-for-pleasure/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T00:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Readers trying to avoid sugar for health reasons may want to skip this post.] My basement recently flooded, and I was forced to knock out some drywall to prevent mold. At one point, I discovered a secret compartment that was completely walled in. It contained several boxes. Here I should digress and mention that I&#8217;ve [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874130831/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874130831/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-18-at-8.03.22-PM-1024x984.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874130831/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874130831/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874130831/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comment-6799630">Everyone, Put “ivermectin” in the search box for this blog ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comment-6798468">Remember when Sumner said republicans were killing people ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comment-6797503">“In the 1960’s, before Nixon closed the Gold window, ...</a> <i>by Jim Glass</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comment-6797360">I can understand how one might find more pleasure in finding ...</a> <i>by Michael Rulle</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comment-6797328">In the 1960's, before Nixon closed the Gold window, Americans ...</a> <i>by Sara</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/treasure-for-pleasure/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break with Trump?]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130834/0/themoneyillusion~Break-with-Trump/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/874130834/0/themoneyillusion~Break-with-Trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T00:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw the following headline in the National Review: What It Took for Republicans to Break with Trump The article discussed the overwhelming vote to force a TikTok sale, which Trump &#8220;opposes&#8221;. This is supposedly in contrast to their kowtowing to Trump in voting against a border control bill, which Trump also &#8220;opposes&#8221;. Why do [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/874130834/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/874130834/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-17-at-4.07.02-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/874130834/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/874130834/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/874130834/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comment-6797985">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comment-6797958">Michael Sandifer,   Well he says he forgave trump but Jan 6 but ...</a> <i>by Bobster34</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comment-6797884">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comment-6797550">“Of course by “RINO” I mean true Republicans.”   What ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comment-6797469">Peter, You said:   “The problem is Trump, like anyone else ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/break-with-trump/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve the security of your software supply chain with Amazon CodeArtifact package group configuration]]></title>
        <id>12a0bd4942e2dfeef23cb1085e292736de05ca58</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-the-security-of-your-software-supply-chain-with-amazon-codeartifact-package-group-configuration/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T22:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, administrators of package repositories can manage the configuration of multiple packages in one single place with the new AWS CodeArtifact package group configuration capability. A package group allows you to define how packages are updated by internal developers or from upstream repositories. You can now allow or block internal developers to publish packages […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threads has entered the fediverse]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=20984</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/21/networking-traffic/threads-has-entered-the-fediverse/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T18:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threads has entered the fediverse! As part of our beta experience, now available in a few countries, Threads users aged 18+ with public profiles can now choose to share their Threads posts to other ActivityPub-compliant servers. People on those servers can now follow federated Threads profiles and see, like, reply to, and repost posts from [...]
Read More...
The post Threads has entered the fediverse appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify document search at scale with intelligent search bot on AWS]]></title>
        <id>985391c98bb111a75f7e5eacb6c10c1bd3ac0a39</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/simplify-document-search-at-scale-with-intelligent-search-bot-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T16:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise document management systems (EDMS) manage the lifecycle and distribution of documents. They often rely on keyword-based search functionality. However, it increasingly becomes hard to discover documents as such repositories grow to tens of thousands of items. In this blog, we discuss how Amazon Web Services (AWS) built an intelligent search bot on top of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rostislav Markov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing RTC bandwidth estimation with machine learning]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21117</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/20/networking-traffic/optimizing-rtc-bandwidth-estimation-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T21:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bandwidth estimation (BWE) and congestion control play an important role in delivering high-quality real-time communication (RTC) across Meta’s family of apps. We’ve adopted a machine learning (ML)-based approach that allows us to solve networking problems holistically across cross-layers such as BWE, network resiliency, and transport. We’re sharing our experiment results from this approach, some of [...]
Read More...
The post Optimizing RTC bandwidth estimation with machine learning appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better video for mobile RTC with AV1 and HD]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21105</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/20/video-engineering/mobile-rtc-video-av1-hd/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T19:40:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we support real-time communication (RTC) for billions of people through our apps, including Messenger, Instagram, and WhatsApp. We’ve seen significant benefits by adopting the AV1 codec for RTC. Here’s how we are improving the RTC video quality for our apps with tools like the AV1 codec, the challenges we face, and how we [...]
Read More...
The post Better video for mobile RTC with AV1 and HD appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering video content with fractional GPUs in containers on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>a24470174dc3de2f62b0578fea92c263ef738e9c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/delivering-video-content-with-fractional-gpus-in-containers-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T18:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Video encoding and transcoding are critical workloads for media and entertainment companies. Delivering high-quality video content to viewers across devices and networks needs efficient and scalable encoding infrastructure. As video resolutions continue to increase to 4K and 8K, GPU acceleration is essential to real-time encoding workflows where parallel encoding tasks are necessary. Although encoding on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Hart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Feedback to Improve Your Application: Self Learning GPTs]]></title>
        <id>65fa4ef29333bd00014c374e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/self-learning-gpts/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T16:38:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We built and hosted a simple demo app to show how applications can learn and improve from feedback over time. The app is called "Self Learning GPTs" and it uses LangSmith to gather feedback and then automatically use that feedback to improve over time. It does this by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankush Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing WARP Connector: paving the path to any-to-any connectivity]]></title>
        <id>65fa39e3a5fcdf000a08d932</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-warp-connector-paving-the-path-to-any-to-any-connectivity-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, Zero Trust administrators can deploy our new WARP Connector for simplified any-to-any connectivity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abe Carryl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redefining fleet management at Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>65f89e45a5fcdf000a08d386</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/redefining-fleet-management-at-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing pains were inevitable given the sheer pace of Cloudflare’s growth. Processes around server provisioning, maintenance windows, repairs, and diagnostics reporting were reaching their limits]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan De Lap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LangChain Integrates NVIDIA NIM for GPU-optimized LLM Inference in RAG]]></title>
        <id>65f882d39333bd00014c35fc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/nvidia-nim/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T22:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roughly a year and a half ago, OpenAI launched ChatGPT and the generative AI era really kicked off. Since then we’ve seen rapid growth and widespread adoption by all types of industries and all types of enterprises. As enterprises turn their attention from prototyping LLM applications to productionizing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Claude 3 Haiku in Amazon Bedrock, AWS CloudFormation optimizations, and more — March 18, 2024]]></title>
        <id>958f9e9fef9ae1609e5461db386c9603ffcc5732</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-haiku-in-amazon-bedrock-aws-cloudformation-optimizations-and-more-march-18-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T18:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Storage, storage, storage! Last week, we celebrated 18 years of innovation on Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) at AWS Pi Day 2024. Amazon S3 mascot Buckets joined the celebrations and had a ton of fun! The 4-hour live stream was packed with puns, pie recipes powered by PartyRock, demos, code, and discussions about generative […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logarithm: A logging engine for AI training workflows and services]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21074</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/18/data-infrastructure/logarithm-logging-engine-ai-training-workflows-services-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T16:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systems and application logs play a key role in operations, observability, and debugging workflows at Meta. Logarithm is a hosted, serverless, multitenant service, used only internally at Meta, that consumes and indexes these logs and provides an interactive query interface to retrieve and view logs. In this post, we present the design behind Logarithm, and [...]
Read More...
The post Logarithm: A logging engine for AI training workflows and services appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Justice and the Biodiversity Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52505</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/18/global-justice-and-the-biodiversity-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T14:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My new book is out this week (in the UK at least – but those elsewhere can read it right now online). I very much hope it will stimulate debate and discussion. Something that’s really struck me over recent years is that whereas a really rich literature exists on the global justice dimensions of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequential Testing Keeps the World Streaming Netflix Part 2: Counting Processes]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/da6805341642</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/sequential-testing-keeps-the-world-streaming-netflix-part-2-counting-processes-da6805341642?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Lindon, Chris Sanden, Vache Shirikian, Yanjun Liu, Minal Mishra, Martin Tingley]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: starling]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52502</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/17/sunday-photoblogging-starling/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T13:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another Sunday rolls around, and I haven’t written anything substantial here in ages. But here’s a starling:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper:  When Armor Met Lips]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52491</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/16/occasional-paper-when-armor-met-lips/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T15:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So about five hundred million years ago, give or take, there was this little creature called Plectronoceras.  It was about 2 cm long — just under an inch — and it had a conical shell with a bunch of tentacles sticking out.  It was a cephalopod, an early member of the group that includes octopuses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read – The trouble with words]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45218</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/16/weekend-read-the-trouble-with-words/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T01:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Words are not ideas.  They are our means to capture ideas and make them tangible.  The problem is that words are a porous net that inevitably lets some accuracy slip away, but sometimes captures irrelevant detail that shines brightly in the moment and then dulls in the light of later thought. Trying […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing RAG-based application accuracy by constructing and leveraging knowledge graphs]]></title>
        <id>65f47e0330d5eb0001dd5b1e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/enhancing-rag-based-applications-accuracy-by-constructing-and-leveraging-knowledge-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T18:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to constructing and retrieving information from knowledge graphs in RAG applications with Neo4j and LangChain
Editor's Note: the following is a guest blog post from Tomaz Bratanic, who focuses on Graph ML and GenAI research at Neo4j. Neo4j is a graph database and analytics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One and Columbia U partner to drive responsible AI]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fef35d05b83b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-one-and-columbia-u-partner-to-drive-responsible-ai-fef35d05b83b?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T15:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One & Columbia University announce a new partnership to establish the Center for AI and Responsible Financial Innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking Query Analysis in High Cardinality Situations]]></title>
        <id>65f3773530d5eb0001dd5a90</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/high-cardinality/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T15:15:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several key use cases for LLMs involve returning data in a structured format. Extraction is one such use case - we recently highlighted this with updated documentation and a dedicated repo. Query analysis is another - we’ve also updated our documentation around this recently. When returning information in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Cloudflare Workers testing via Vitest and workerd]]></title>
        <id>65f2fe96a5fcdf000a08cb50</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-vitest-integration"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T14:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re excited to announce a new Workers Vitest integration - allowing you to write unit and integration tests via the popular testing framework, Vitest, that execute directly in our runtime, workerd]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Coll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run and manage open source InfluxDB databases with Amazon Timestream]]></title>
        <id>3a184bf9dfd95467e0bd27737c7d220b8539ab2b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/run-and-manage-open-source-influxdb-databases-with-amazon-timestream/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T01:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting today, you can use InfluxDB as a database engine in Amazon Timestream. This support makes it easy for you to run near real-time time-series applications using InfluxDB and open source APIs, including open source Telegraf agents that collect time-series observations. Now you have two database engines to choose in Timestream: Timestream for LiveAnalytics and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The decline of economics]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873647717/0/themoneyillusion~The-decline-of-economics/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873647717/0/themoneyillusion~The-decline-of-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T23:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, I&#8217;ve been bemoaning a new &#8220;dark age of macroeconomics&#8221;. I know less about current trends in micro, and thus was interested in these comments by Steven Levitt (from an interview by Jon Hartley): Steve: &#8220;Yeah, yeah, sort of everywhere. Every macro department feels a lot like heavily influenced by Chicago. And I [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873647717/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873647717/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873647717/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873647717/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873647717/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comment-6795940">Lawrence K. Roos, Past President, Federal Reserve Bank of St. ...</a> <i>by spencer</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comment-6795933">I don't think everyone agrees with the Chicago Price Theory, to ...</a> <i>by spencer</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comment-6794916">Mankiwsmom, Yes, I saw that. I guess he's in a better position ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comment-6794853">Anup Malani has an interesting thread on twitter that disagrees ...</a> <i>by mankiwsmom</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comment-6794797">Scott, Funny. People have looked at correlations between local ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-decline-of-economics/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In a free market, drugs are cheap, government-granted patent monopolies make them expensive]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45222</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/14/in-a-free-market-drugs-are-cheap-government-granted-patent-monopolies-make-them-expensive/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker This simple point was left out of a Washington Post article on the legal battle surrounding the Biden Administration’s efforts to negotiate lower prices for drugs purchased by Medicare. This point is important because the drug companies are definitely not trying to get the government out of the market, as the industry claims. The industry is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undersea cable failures cause Internet disruptions for multiple African countries]]></title>
        <id>65f3356da5fcdf000a08cda5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/undersea-cable-failures-cause-internet-disruptions-across-africa-march-14-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T18:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet connectivity in several African countries was disrupted on March 14, 2024, beginning at approximately 05:00 UTC. Based on published reports and social media posts from impacted network providers, the disruption is believed to be due to multiple undersea cable failures in the region]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Pi Day 2024: Use your data to power generative AI]]></title>
        <id>e27aadba159a82a8421a846f45b7aa39ba3dae67</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-pi-day-2024-use-your-data-to-power-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T15:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updated 20 March: I added a phrase in the original text to mention that the AWS SDKs for Rust and Kotlin now support Amazon S3 Express One Zone. Today is AWS Pi Day! Join us live on Twitch, starting at 1 PM Pacific time. On this day 18 years ago, a West Coast retail company […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wage inflation in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873608627/0/themoneyillusion~Wage-inflation-in-Japan/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873608627/0/themoneyillusion~Wage-inflation-in-Japan/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is evidence that nominal wages in Japan are finally starting to rise: Toyota Motor Corp.&#160;met its labor union&#8217;s demands for increases in salary and bonuses in full for the fourth straight year, in another sign that a sustainable wage-price cycle may be taking hold in Japan&#8217;s economy as the central bank considers the timing [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873608627/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873608627/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-02-28-at-4.02.23-PM-1024x593.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873608627/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873608627/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873608627/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comment-6795082">Scott,   You're right.</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comment-6794800">dtoh, Just the opposite. The long duration makes it help even ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comment-6794063">Scott,   Not as much as you would expect because the duration ...</a> <i>by dtoh</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comment-6793881">dtoh, Yes, but it would help a bit with the fiscal situation. ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comment-6793710">Agree that BOJ should err on the side of not raising rates too ...</a> <i>by Mike M.</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/wage-inflation-in-japan/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Random observations]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873608630/0/themoneyillusion~Random-observations/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/873608630/0/themoneyillusion~Random-observations/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. This confused me: Renewed efforts by Congress to force TikTok to sell or face a ban in the US have the backing of the White House, even as President Joe Biden&#8217;s reelection campaign has started to use the platform to reach younger voters. I&#8217;m confused. If using Tiktok endangers national security, then why is [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/873608630/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/873608630/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f03%2fScreen-Shot-2024-03-08-at-8.24.05-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/873608630/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/873608630/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/873608630/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comment-6792426">By: Lorenzo from Oz		</a> <i>by Lorenzo from Oz <a href="https://www.lorenzofromoz.net/">https://www.lorenzofromoz.net/</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comment-6792274">Scott- I am believer in pendulum effects. I dont think it is ...</a> <i>by steve</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comment-6792078">steve, #6 Here's another recent example, from New Zealand: ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comment-6792067">#6- Maybe a better sign is that some of the left of center ...</a> <i>by steve</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comment-6792061">Jensen, I see you are new here. Keep lying and you'll soon be ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/random-observations-4/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Let’s Encrypt certificate chain change and impact for Cloudflare customers]]></title>
        <id>65f23f4ba5fcdf000a08ca3f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/upcoming-lets-encrypt-certificate-chain-change-and-impact-for-cloudflare-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Encrypt’s cross-signed chain will be expiring in September. To prepare for the change, after May 15th, 2024, Cloudflare will start issuing certs from Let’s Encrypt’s ISRG X1 chain. This change will impact legacy devices with outdated trust stores (Android versions 7.1.1 or older)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitigating a token-length side-channel attack in our AI products]]></title>
        <id>65f1fb96a5fcdf000a08c9fb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-side-channel-attack-mitigated"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T12:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Workers AI and AI Gateway team recently collaborated closely with security researchers at Ben Gurion University regarding a report submitted through our Public Bug Bounty program. Through this process, we discovered and fully patched a vulnerability affecting all LLM providers. Here’s the story]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Celso Martinho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Haiku model is now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>f82acaea0917cce965212856bcf2ac6a924f9e78</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-haiku-model-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T22:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Anthropic announced their Claude 3 foundation model family. The family includes three models: Claude 3 Haiku, the fastest and most compact model for near-instant responsiveness; Claude 3 Sonnet, the ideal balanced model between skills and speed; and Claude 3 Opus, the most intelligent offering for top-level performance on highly complex tasks. AWS also […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I heard there’s some good shit on TV tonight …]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45213</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/13/i-heard-theres-some-good-shit-on-tv-tonight/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T21:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Time is a scarce resource on television. However, if one still — as is so often the case nowadays — uses precious airtime for trivial matters and meaningless ‘entertainment,’ there must be a reason. Television is — still — for a large part of the population one of the primary sources of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi Needle in a Haystack]]></title>
        <id>65ecab5a84261200016670a5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/multi-needle-in-a-haystack/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T16:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key Links

Video
Code

Overview
Interest in long context LLMs is surging as context windows expand to 1M tokens. One of the most popular and cited benchmarks for long context LLM retrieval is Greg Kamradt's Needle in A Haystack: a fact (needle) is injected into a (haystack) of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankush Gola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infrastructure as Code development with Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>1af365523512cdc2dbdbb4fee1e1e897cdd97d9a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/infrastructure-as-code-development-with-amazon-codewhisperer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At re:Invent in 2023, AWS announced Infrastructure as Code (IaC) support for Amazon CodeWhisperer. CodeWhisperer is an AI-powered productivity tool for the IDE and command line that helps software developers to quickly and efficiently create cloud applications to run on AWS. Languages currently supported for IaC are YAML and JSON for AWS CloudFormation, Typescript and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Z. Beard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Meta’s GenAI Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21038</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/12/data-center-engineering/building-metas-genai-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marking a major investment in Meta’s AI future, we are announcing two 24k GPU clusters. We are sharing details on the hardware, network, storage, design, performance, and software that help us extract high throughput and reliability for various AI workloads. We use this cluster design for Llama 3 training. We are strongly committed to open [...]
Read More...
The post Building Meta’s GenAI Infrastructure appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Peek at Kubernetes v1.30]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/12/kubernetes-1-30-upcoming-changes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/12/kubernetes-1-30-upcoming-changes/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authors: Amit Dsouza, Frederick Kautz, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, Natali Vlatko
A quick look: exciting changes in Kubernetes v1.30
It's a new year and a new Kubernetes release. We're halfway through the release cycle and
have quite a few interesting and exciting enhancements coming in v1.30. From brand new features
in alpha, to established features graduating to stable, to long-awaited improvements, this release
has something for everyone to pay attention to!
To tide you over until the official release, here's a sneak peek of the enhancements we're most
excited about in this cycle!
Major changes for Kubernetes v1.30
Structured parameters for dynamic resource allocation (KEP-4381)
Dynamic resource allocation was
added to Kubernetes as an alpha feature in v1.26. It defines an alternat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Physics on AWS: Optimizing wind turbine performance using OpenFAST in a digital twin]]></title>
        <id>15b43805eef7a9a28f3253f162528f28d1cfd790</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/physics-on-aws-optimizing-wind-turbine-performance-using-openfast-in-a-digital-twin/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T22:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wind energy plays a crucial role in global decarbonization efforts by generating emission-free power from an abundant resource. In 2022, wind energy produced 2100 terawatt-hours (TWh) globally, or over 7% of global electricity, with expectations to reach 7400 TWh by 2030. Despite its potential, several challenges must be addressed to help meet grid decarbonization targets. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Masciola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sped up AWS CloudFormation deployments with optimistic stabilization]]></title>
        <id>aca9fd3bf0ae74d5710c89512f26c242d6e97df7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-we-sped-up-aws-cloudformation-deployments-with-optimistic-stabilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction AWS CloudFormation customers often inquire about the behind-the-scenes process of provisioning resources and why certain resources or stacks take longer to provision compared to the AWS Management Console or AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI). In this post, we will delve into the various factors affecting resource provisioning in CloudFormation, specifically focusing on resource stabilization, which allows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bhavani Kanneganti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup — Claude 3 Sonnet support in Bedrock, new instances, and more — March 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>1ac173b1e82d4b67e6ec4044be26f6b60a2f29dc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-sonnet-support-in-bedrock-new-instances-and-more-march-11-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T16:05:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday was International Women’s Day (IWD), and I want to take a moment to appreciate the amazing ladies in the cloud computing space that are breaking the glass ceiling by reaching technical leadership positions and inspiring others to go and build, as our CTO Werner Vogels says. Last week’s launches Here are some launches […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcia Villalba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iterating Towards LLM Reliability with Evaluation Driven Development]]></title>
        <id>65ef1def8426120001667414</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/iterating-towards-llm-reliability-with-evaluation-driven-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:11:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor's Note: the following is a guest blog post from the Devin Stein, CEO of Dosu. Dosu is an engineering teammate that helps you develop, maintain, and support software.
It’s well known at this point that building production-grade LLM products is hard. Reliability is critical for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is “greedflation” over?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45202</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/11/is-greedflation-over/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker Peter Coy used his column yesterday to beg President Biden not to use the term “greedflation” to explain the runup in inflation since the pandemic. I am sympathetic to much of his argument, most importantly, the idea that corporations suddenly turned greedy is a bit far out. As Coy notes, corporations are always greedy. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Week 2024 wrap up]]></title>
        <id>65eea293a5fcdf000a08b807</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/security-week-2024-wrap-up"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A summary of the blog posts and product announcements released during Security Week 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniele Molteni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: blue tit]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52485</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/10/sunday-photoblogging-blue-tit/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T07:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Week of 3/4] LangChain Release Notes]]></title>
        <id>65eb45458426120001666f8e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/week-of-3-04-langchain-release-notes/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T17:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[✂️ Extraction Use Case
One of the main use cases for LLMs is extracting structured data from unstructured text. We've added a lot of functionality to LangChain to best support this, as well as more high level end-to-end guides for this use case!

We've added]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Log Explorer: monitor security events without third-party storage]]></title>
        <id>65e9e84ca5fcdf000a08aaa8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/log-explorer"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the combined power of Security Analytics + Log Explorer, security teams can analyze, investigate, and monitor for security attacks natively within Cloudflare, reducing time to resolution and overall cost of ownership for customers by eliminating the need to forward logs to third-party SIEMs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Sells</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launching email security insights on Cloudflare Radar]]></title>
        <id>65e9e88ca5fcdf000a08aabc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/email-security-insights-on-cloudflare-radar"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Email Security section on Cloudflare Radar provides insights into the latest trends around threats found in malicious email, sources of spam and malicious email, and the adoption of technologies designed to prevent abuse of email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol detection with Cloudflare Gateway]]></title>
        <id>65e9e87aa5fcdf000a08aab4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/gatway-protocol-detection"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Gateway, our secure web gateway (SWG), now supports the detection, logging, and filtering of network protocols using packet payloads without the need for inspection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Aggarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network performance update: Security Week 2024]]></title>
        <id>65e9e852a5fcdf000a08aaac</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-performance-update-security-week-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is the fastest provider in 44% of networks around the world for 95th percentile connection time. Let’s dig into the data and talk about how we do it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Tuber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harnessing chaos in Cloudflare offices]]></title>
        <id>65e9e891a5fcdf000a08aac0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/harnessing-office-chaos"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post will cover the new sources of “chaos” that have been added to LavaRand and how you can make use of that harnessed chaos in your next application]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cefan Daniel Rubin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Requests for Information (RFIs) and Priority Intelligence Requirements (PIRs) for threat intelligence teams]]></title>
        <id>65e7cdc8a5fcdf000a089ddc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/threat-intel-rfi-pir"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Security Center now houses Requests for Information (RFIs) and Priority Intelligence Requirements (PIRs). These features are available via API as well and Cloudforce One customers can start leveraging them today for enhanced security analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Javier Castro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s URL Scanner, new features, and the story of how we built it]]></title>
        <id>65e9e85aa5fcdf000a08aab0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-urlscanner"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the enhanced URL Scanner API: Now with direct access from the Security Center Investigate Portal, enjoy unlisted scans, multi-device screenshots, and seamless integration within the Cloudflare ecosystem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sofia Cardita</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stablecoins and Crypto Shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28471</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/stablecoins-and-crypto-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous post, we described the rapid growth of the stablecoin market over the past few years and then discussed the TerraUSD stablecoin run of May 2022. The TerraUSD run, however, is not the only episode of instability experienced by a stablecoin. Other noteworthy incidents include the June 2021 run on IRON and, more recently, the de-pegging of USD Coin’s secondary market price from $1.00 to $0.88 upon the failure of Silicon Valley Bank in March 2023. In this post, based on our recent staff report, we consider the following questions: Do stablecoin investors react to broad-based shocks in the crypto asset industry? Do the investors run from the entire stablecoin industry, or do they engage in a flight to safer stablecoins? We conclude with some high-level discussion points on potential regulations of stablecoins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenechukwu Anadu, Pablo D. Azar, Marco Cipriani, Thomas Eisenbach, Catherine Huang, Mattia Landoni, Gabriele La Spada, Marco Macchiavelli, Antoine Malfroy-Camine, and J. Christina Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional Paper: The Iron Snow Beneath Your Feet]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52332</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/08/occasional-paper-the-iron-snow-beneath-your-feet/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T11:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay so, we all know how the Earth ends, right? In six billion years or so, the Sun swells up into a red giant, and the Earth gets melted. Pretty straightforward. But it turns out that /life/ on Earth will end long before that. There are reasons to think that the biosphere will collapse about […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale your Amazon ECS using different AWS native services!]]></title>
        <id>70b136257100414015f3edd9d302efd1f3639888</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/scale-your-amazon-ecs-using-different-aws-native-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers accelerate application development and enhance deployment consistency across environments, thus enabling organizations to improve productivity and agility. AWS container services such as Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) make it easier to manage your application so you can focus on innovation and your business needs. Customer experience is the most important yardstick by which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Chandapillai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why and how economics must change]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45195</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/08/why-and-how-economics-must-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T01:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Jayati Ghosh Economics needs greater humility, a better sense of history, and more diversity The need for drastic change in the economics discipline has never been so urgent. Humanity faces existential crises, with planetary health and environmental challenges becoming major concerns. The global economy was already limping and fragile before the pandemic; the subsequent […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Diverse ML Systems at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d2e6b6d205d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/supporting-diverse-ml-systems-at-netflix-2d2e6b6d205d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T18:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David J. Berg, Romain Cledat, Kayla Seeley, Shashank Srikanth, Chaoying Wang, Darin Yu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While AI revolutionizes software development, it still relies on developers to pilot its use. In this blog, we’ll cover the skills that developers need to have for navigating this new AI-powered coding frontier. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-07-hard-and-soft-skills-for-developers-coding-in-the-age-of-ai/">Hard and soft skills for developers coding in the age of AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Moderation in Wage Growth Continue?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28480</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/will-the-moderation-in-wage-growth-continue/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wage growth has moderated notably following its post-pandemic surge, but it remains strong compared to the wage growth prevailing during the low-inflation pre-COVID years. Will the moderation continue, or will it stall? And what does it say about the current state of the labor market? In this post, we use our own measure of wage growth persistence – called Trend Wage Inflation (TWIn in short) – to look at these questions. Our main finding is that, after a rapid decline from 7 percent at its peak in late 2021 to around 5 percent in early 2023, TWin has changed little in recent months, indicating that the moderation in nominal wage growth may have stalled. We also show that our measure of trend wage inflation and labor market tightness comove very closely. Hence, the recent behavior of TWIn is consistent with a still-tight labor market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Almuzara, Richard Audoly, Augustin Belin, and Davide Melcangi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRI-O: Applying seccomp profiles from OCI registries]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/03/07/cri-o-seccomp-oci-artifacts/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Grunert
Seccomp stands for secure computing mode and has been a feature of the Linux
kernel since version 2.6.12. It can be used to sandbox the privileges of a
process, restricting the calls it is able to make from userspace into the
kernel. Kubernetes lets you automatically apply seccomp profiles loaded onto a
node to your Pods and containers.
But distributing those seccomp profiles is a major challenge in Kubernetes,
because the JSON files have to be available on all nodes where a workload can
possibly run. Projects like the Security Profiles
Operator solve that problem by
running as a daemon within the cluster, which makes me wonder which part of that
distribution could be done by the container
runtime.
Runtimes usually apply the profiles from a local path, for example:
a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The Political Economy of COVID-19”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45176</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/03/06/the-political-economy-of-covid-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New book from WEA Books At the beginning of 2020, the outbreak of Covid-19 and the lockdown practices imposed worldwide generated a global economic crisis that challenges the traditional explanations of economic downturns .  Like the economic crisis of 2008, the Covid-19 pandemic crisis was systemic and global, and this collection of essays examines it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS now supports io2 Block Express volumes for mission-critical database workloads]]></title>
        <id>e1f154044ec7ddbc580e087aadbcf76d2131d2a0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-now-supports-io2-block-express-volumes-for-mission-critical-database-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[March 7, 2024: Post updated to change GB to GiB. March 8, 2024: Post updated to reflect correct region availability. Today, I am pleased to announce the availability of Provisioned IOPS (PIOPS) io2 Block Express storage volumes for all database engines in Amazon Relational Database Service (Amazon RDS). Amazon RDS provides you the flexibility to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the newest Heroes of the year – March 2024]]></title>
        <id>1c28a1aa7d172c4f3ef6f586d0d873794d1f054c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-newest-heroes-of-the-year-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Heroes are inspirational thought leaders who go above and beyond to knowledge share in a variety of ways. You can find them speaking at local meetups, AWS Community Days, or even at re:Invent. And these technical experts are never done learning—they’re passionate about solving problems and creating content to enable the community to build […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Case Accelerant: Extraction Service]]></title>
        <id>65e8ab66ee362e00014c854a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.langchain.dev/use-case-accelerant-extraction-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re excited to announce our newest OSS use-case accelerant: an extraction service. LLMs are a powerful tool for extracting structured data from unstructured sources. We've improved our support for data extraction in the open source LangChain library over the past few releases, and now we&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LangChain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CRaC to reduce Java startup times on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>26b1f9ab0d42d8e039ae489d79cbced9ed8430e2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-crac-to-reduce-java-startup-times-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application modernization is a focus area for organizations of different sizes and across industries to achieve business objectives such as reduced time to market, improved cost efficiency, and better customer experience. Containers and container orchestration platforms have been one of the key enablers for these modernization initiatives. Many customers standardize on Kubernetes as a containers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Islam Mahgoub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Bezzle]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52474</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/06/the-bezzle/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently read Cory Doctorow’s new novel, The Bezzle. (FYI his publisher sent me a copy.) It’s the follow-up (and in the story’s own timeline, a prequel) to Cory’s excellent tech-themed thriller, Red Team Blues. The hero of Red Team Blues is Marty Hench, a forensic accountant who loves barbecuing, whiskey, and exposing elaborate financial […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making messaging interoperability with third parties safe for users in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=20955</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/03/06/security/whatsapp-messenger-messaging-interoperability-eu/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T09:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To comply with a new EU law, the Digital Markets Act (DMA), which comes into force on March 7th, we’ve made major changes to WhatsApp and Messenger to enable interoperability with third-party messaging services.  We’re sharing how we enabled third-party interoperability (interop) while maintaining end-to-end encryption (E2EE) and other privacy guarantees in our services as [...]
Read More...
The post Making messaging interoperability with third parties safe for users in Europe appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Old]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52470</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/03/06/old/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a few days time, I’ll be lining up in the 65-69 category for the Mooloolaba Olympic triathlon (1500m swim, 40km cycle, 10km run)[1]. People in this age category are commonly described as “aging”, “older”, “seniors”, “elders” and, worst of all, “elderly” (though this mostly kicks in at 70). The one thing we are never […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bending pause times to your will with Generational ZGC]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/256629c9386b</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/bending-pause-times-to-your-will-with-generational-zgc-256629c9386b?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surprising and not so surprising benefits of generations in the Z Garbage Collector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows authentication with gMSA on Linux containers on Amazon ECS with AWS Fargate]]></title>
        <id>4ec2c9e4d9ddbea5e7b461fc9fa5c45c03eaa037</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/windows-authentication-with-gmsa-on-linux-containers-on-amazon-ecs-with-aws-fargate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T21:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today, we are announcing the availability of Credentials Fetcher integration with AWS Fargate on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS). With this launch, you have the option of running Linux containers that depend on Windows authentication on Amazon ECS using both the Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) launch type, as well as with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cristobal Espinosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risk-Aware Product Decisions in A/B Tests with Multiple Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7002</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/03/risk-aware-product-decisions-in-a-b-tests-with-multiple-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T18:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR We summarize the findings in our recent paper, Schultzberg, Ankargren, and Frånberg (2024), where we explain how Spotify’s decision-making [...]
The post Risk-Aware Product Decisions in A/B Tests with Multiple Metrics appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community matters: Four open source trends in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6f1d879983d6</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/community-matters-four-open-source-trends-in-2024-6f1d879983d6?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking ahead at open source trends and technology in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free data transfer out to internet when moving out of AWS]]></title>
        <id>75d716af79fb6ef0c02f33b4b7ca18cfd5dd4743</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/free-data-transfer-out-to-internet-when-moving-out-of-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You told us one of the primary reasons to adopt Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the broad choice of services we offer, enabling you to innovate, build, deploy, and monitor your workloads. AWS has continuously expanded its services to support virtually any cloud workload. It now offers over 200 fully featured services for compute, storage, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expectations and the Final Mile of Disinflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28517</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/03/expectations-and-the-final-mile-of-disinflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, the U.S. economy experienced a swift recovery accompanied by a sharp rise in inflation. Inflation has been gradually declining since 2022 without a notable slowdown in the labor market. Nonetheless, inflation remains above the Federal Reserve's 2 percent target and the path of the so-called final mile remains uncertain, as emphasized by Chair Powell during his press conference in January. In this post, we examine the unemployment-inflation trade-off over the past few years through the lens of a New Keynesian Phillips curve, based on our recent paper. We also provide model-based forecasts for 2024 and 2025 under various labor market scenarios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard K. Crump, Stefano Eusepi, and Ayşegül Şahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>