<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-30T06:35:02.447Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-30T06:35:02.447Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI boom in electricity demand: a multiply recycled myth]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53456</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/30/the-ai-boom-in-electricity-demand-a-multiply-recycled-myth/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-30T03:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I posted this piece in RenewEconomy a couple of months ago. It didn’t convince the commenters then, and I don’t expect it to be any different here, but I’m putting it on the record anyway. AI won’t use as much electricity as we are told, and it’s not a reason to slow transition to renewables […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283069</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T19:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Did it really take $500,000 to make Al Sharpton "friendly"? Sanders on the Four Freedoms  (and Norman Rockwell); Another day, another Boeing airworthiness directive. ALso, COMAC ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Landmark climate hearings set at UN court + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/landmark-climate-hearings-set-at-un-court-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/landmark-climate-hearings-set-at-un-court-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T18:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 100 countries join ICJ for climate hearings; Germany plans a $25 billion hydrogen network;]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM International network condemns the cowardice of Northern governments in response to the climate emergency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-International-network-condemns-the-cowardice-of-Northern-governments</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-International-network-condemns-the-cowardice-of-Northern-governments"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T14:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The COP29 was another farce. The CADTM International network denounces an event that was riddled from the start by fossil fuel lobbies and by the Azerbaijan government that never had any intention to even start an ecological transition. The CADTM International network denounces the hypocrisy of Northern governments that still refuse to commit themselves to compensate for the damage they are historically responsible for and help countries of the South to face climate change and initiate (...)
Press releases

/ 
International Institutions, 
Ecological debt, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your PR Process Is Killing Morale and Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://blackentropy.com/your-pr-process-is-killing-morale-and-productivity/</id>
        <link href="https://blackentropy.com/your-pr-process-is-killing-morale-and-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T13:12:09.318Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code reviews are supposed to be about improving code quality and sharing knowledge, but when PR comments start hitting the hundreds, something is very wrong. I’ve recently come across a discussion where a new developer joined a team and faced over 300 PR comments on their first contribution. Most of it was stylistic nitpicking. This isn’t just unproductive, it’s outright toxic.
Why This Happens
You’re Not Using Linters or Auto-Formatters
Prettier, ESLint, or Black exist for a reason. Not automating this is borderline malpractice in modern development.
Your Team Has a "Style Over Substance" Obsession
Metrics Gone Wild
Toxic Culture
What Needs to Change
Automate the Trivial Stuff
Focus on What Matters
Define (and Stick To) a Style Guide
Measure the Right Things
Stop Wasting Everyone’s Time
Hundreds of comments on a PR are a red flag, not a badge of honor. It means your process is broken. Fix the culture, fix the tooling, and focus on what actually matters: shipping high-quality, maintainable software. Anything else is just noise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283023</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T11:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our salacious daily links: Mayflower survivors, 2024 big heat mystery, China Baltic ship hostage? Kerkala, German crisis, Romania election pushback, UK euthanasia, Israel continues Lebanon attacks, whither NATO? Trump abortion options, Mexico says no tariffs, Thanksgiving cost propaganda,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Example from Switzerland: Neuchâtel Becomes Second Canton to Enshrine Right to “Offline Life” in Constitution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283035</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/food-for-thought-swiss-canton-enshrines-right-to-offline-life-in-its-constitution.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T11:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It is a question of having access to all the services of the State without having a computer, smartphone or tablet."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Inside Job? Phishing for Government ID]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283056</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/amazon-inside-job-phishing-for-government-id.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T10:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are Amazon insiders trying to defraud customers? It's hard to come up with another explanation for a recent attempt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland election: its economic model under threat?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Ireland-election-its-economic-model-under-threat</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Ireland-election-its-economic-model-under-threat"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T10:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Repubic of Ireland (this excludes the northern Ireland enclave which is still part of Britain) holds a general election today. Ireland has just 5m people and is part of the European Union and the Eurozone, contributing just 1% of EU27 and 3% of EU GDP. 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Ireland, 
Inequality, 
Tax Justice]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seattle Diary: 25 Years After]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345290</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/seattle-diary-25-years-after/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T07:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-five years ago this week, the streets of Seattle erupted into the kind of militant protest rarely seen in the US. Over the course of five days, thousands of street activists counterpunched the global managers of neoliberalism in the face at their own confab, humiliated Bill Clinton and took the ruling class entirely off guard. The battle in Seattle became a kind of operational template for the popular protests of the both the right and left that followed in its wake: Code Pink's anti-Iraq war demos, the Occupy Movement, the Tea Party, Black Lives Matter and, even, MAGA. The populist right certainly absorbed more lessons from the Battle of Seattle than the liberal elites of the Democratic Party–to their peril and ultimate doom. More
The post Seattle Diary: 25 Years After appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get the Hell Out of My Way]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/get-the-hell-out-of-my-way/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:58:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Right now, a multi-billionaire regime is being set up by electing just one man, and this done by popular vote, by those Rand would call masses of mud. You need only scan those President-Elect Donald Trump has given key governmental positions: Private Predators, on and offline, with an animus to laws and the bureaucracy that enforces them. This subjugation of the many by the few comes as no surprise as such has always been part of “winning” in “The American Dream” as well as the force behind “American Exceptionalism.” Egalitarianism has always been the soft and fuzzy dream of useful idiots, in the eyes of the Winners. More
The post Get the Hell Out of My Way appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emergency Summit Regarding Antarctic Meltdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345327</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/emergency-summit-regarding-antarctic-meltdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Runaway ice loss causing rapid and catastrophic sea level rise is possible within our lifetimes.” (Source: Our Science, Your Future: Next Generation of Antarctic Scientists Call for Collaborative Action, Australian Antarctic Research Conference, November 22, 2024) Hundreds of scientists gathered in Australia for an “emergency summit” within the auspices of the inaugural Australian Antarctic Research  More
The post Emergency Summit Regarding Antarctic Meltdown appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Win for Renters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345167</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/a-win-for-renters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With over 2,300,000 renters in New York City, it’s a good bet most of them had to pay exorbitant brokers’ fees to land their apartments. Those brokers charged a fortune – natch, because with a 2023 city rental vacancy rate of 1.41 percent, they could set their fees sky high. But on November 13, the city council approved a new law with a veto-proof majority to make landlords fork over those fees. According to the New York Times that day, “the fee is typically more than one month’s rent, and right now the median rent is roughly $3,4000.” So up-front costs to get a new place in Gotham were often over $10,000. How ‘bout them apples? More
The post A Win for Renters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Animal Agriculture Threatens Freshwater Supplies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345192</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/how-animal-agriculture-threatens-freshwater-supplies/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agricultural runoff from barnyards, feedlots, and cropland carries pollutants like manure, fertilizers, ammonia, pesticides, livestock waste, toxins from farm equipment, soil, and sediment to local water sources. According to a February 2022 article by the Public Interest Research Groups, the factory farming industry is one of the leading causes of water pollution in the United States. The animal agriculture industry is also a front-runner for water risk, which makes it an environmentally unsustainable practice. More
The post How Animal Agriculture Threatens Freshwater Supplies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vicky Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Already Rewarding Fossil Fuel Executives for Funding His Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345266</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/trumps-already-rewarding-fossil-fuel-executives-for-funding-his-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his campaign, Donald Trump publicly promised to reward oil and gas executives handsomely in exchange for funding his campaign. Within weeks of winning the election, he’s making good on his promise by tapping oil and gas executive Chris Wright to lead the Department of Energy. Wright has zero experience in running a federal agency.  More
The post Trump’s Already Rewarding Fossil Fuel Executives for Funding His Campaign appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Great Trump Escape By Night Trains to Armenia: Across the Alps to Vienna]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345398</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/a-great-trump-escape-by-night-trains-to-armenia-across-the-alps-to-vienna/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part in a series about riding night trains across Europe and the Near East to Armenia — to spend some time in worlds beyond the pathological obsessions of President-elect Donald Trump. (This week his appointee as Secretary of Defense is trying to dodge rape allegations.) The dining cars on Austrian trains  More
The post A Great Trump Escape By Night Trains to Armenia: Across the Alps to Vienna appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK Jr. Praises Wacky Wellness Gurus, Blames Fauci for Everything From Bad Breath to Jock Itch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345182</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/rfk-jr-praises-wacky-wellness-gurus-blames-fauci-for-everything-from-bad-breath-to-jock-itch/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[” . . . slimy, dishonest, [a] stunning display of ignorance . . . [A] god-awful book.” —–Molecular biologist Dan Wilson reviewing RFK Jr.’s “The Real Anthony Fauci” Son of the late Senator Robert F. Kennedy, RFK Jr. graduated from Harvard in 1976, later earning a law degree from the University of Virginia. He established  More
The post RFK Jr. Praises Wacky Wellness Gurus, Blames Fauci for Everything From Bad Breath to Jock Itch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael K. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ironic Dependency: Russian Uranium and the US Energy Market]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345329</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/ironic-dependency-russian-uranium-and-the-us-energy-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be careful who you condemn and ostracise.  They just might be supplying you with a special need.  While the United States security establishment deems Russia the devil incarnate helped along by aspiring, mischief-making China, that devil continues supplying the US energy market with enriched uranium. This dependency has irked the self-sufficiency patriots in Washington, especially those keen  More
The post Ironic Dependency: Russian Uranium and the US Energy Market appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greater Energy Levels by GOP Produce Victories Over Democrats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345338</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/greater-energy-levels-by-gop-produce-victories-over-democrats/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over thirty years ago, Republican historian and political analyst, Kevin Phillips, remarked that the “Republicans go for the jugular while the Democrats go for the capillaries.” This serious disparity in political energy levels is rarely taken into account to explain election turnouts. The voluntary enfeebling of the Democratic Party started long ago. In 1970, writing  More
The post Greater Energy Levels by GOP Produce Victories Over Democrats appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Whitelash Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345356</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/another-whitelash-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with high turnout, endorsements from top Republicans and former Trump aides, and outspending the Trump-Vance ticket by nearly $460 million, Democrats still lost the White House, as well as both Houses of Congress. What happened? Many are speculating what Democrats could have done differently. Some political pundits blame Joe Biden for not stepping down sooner, while others blame the  More
The post Another Whitelash Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tracey L. Rogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Kamala Harris Thumbed Her Nose at Arab American and Muslim Voters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345170</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/how-kamala-harris-thumbed-her-nose-at-arab-american-and-muslim-voters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vice President Kamala Harris made many mistakes during her run for the White House. One that stood out was Harris’ callous disregard for Muslim and Arab American voters. Harris won a miniscule 20% of Muslim voters according to an exit poll commissioned by the Council on American-Islamic Relations (CAIR). The same poll showed former president  More
The post How Kamala Harris Thumbed Her Nose at Arab American and Muslim Voters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charles Pierson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promise and Contradictions Emerge From Celebration of Cuba’s Latin American School of Medicine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345349</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/promise-and-contradictions-emerge-from-celebration-of-cubas-latin-american-school-of-medicine/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Latin American School of Medicine (ELAM for its Spanish language initials) is a masterpiece of Cuba’s remarkable healthcare system. A conference of ELAM graduates took place in Havana from November 11 to November 15; two sets of them attended. The gathering marked the 25th anniversary of ELAM’s founding in 1999. What happened and what was  More
The post Promise and Contradictions Emerge From Celebration of Cuba’s Latin American School of Medicine  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If the Chief Business of the American People is Business, the Chief Business of the American Government is to Govern]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345251</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/if-the-chief-business-of-the-american-people-is-business-the-chief-business-of-the-american-government-is-to-govern/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The chief business of the American people is business,” President Calvin Coolidge declared in 1925. Whether or not that phrase is applicable today, it is evident that the new Trump administration believes that the U.S. government should be business-like. How else to understand the new Department of Government Efficiency (DOGE), a planned presidential advisory commission  to be led by  More
The post If the Chief Business of the American People is Business, the Chief Business of the American Government is to Govern appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No More ‘Deals’ – What Palestinians Want and Will Fight to Achieve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345345</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/no-more-deals-what-palestinians-want-and-will-fight-to-achieve/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A major problem in American thinking in the Middle East is the utter rejection of the notion that Palestinian rights are fundamental, if at all relevant, to the coveted peace and stability. Long before Donald Trump’s first ‘Deal of the Century’ was officially revealed on January 28, 2020, successive US administrations attempted to ‘stabilize’ the  More
The post No More ‘Deals’ – What Palestinians Want and Will Fight to Achieve  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Desertions Over Radiation Could End the War in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345368</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/mass-desertions-over-radiation-could-end-the-war-in-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NATO leaders have been dithering about Russia’s recent retaliation against Ukraine’s lofting one of Lockheed’s long-range missiles deep into its interior. Their emergency huddle was about Putin’s new multi-missile (“Oreshnik “) which traveled 10 times the speed of sound (range: 310-3,400 miles) to hit a former ICBM factory . So far, either side seems to  More
The post Mass Desertions Over Radiation Could End the War in Ukraine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barbara G. Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Digging Up the Roots of Human Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345333</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/digging-up-the-roots-of-human-culture/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What led humans on the unique path of cultural development? And can we do anything useful with newly reconstructed histories of this process? Culture is central to defining humanity. Throughout history, many definitions have been proposed to describe what we mean when we talk about culture, leading to considerable confusion. The word “culture” was once reserved  More
The post Digging Up the Roots of Human Culture appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deborah Barsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Want More Young People to Join the Military? Spend Less on It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345353</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/want-more-young-people-to-join-the-military-spend-less-on-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The military is concerned about a growing recruitment crisis. Survey after survey reveals young people just aren’t inspired by military service. Ironically, decades of sky-high military spending — and the endless war it enabled — may have much to do with that. And reversing that trend is critical to making Americans safer. An 18-year-old today will  More
The post Want More Young People to Join the Military? Spend Less on It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lindsay Koshgarian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Carbon Soil Opportunity: Organic Farming Helps Counter Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345331</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/the-carbon-soil-opportunity-organic-farming-helps-counter-climate-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change is no longer an abstraction. I can literally see it at my front door. My figs ripened in October 2024, which has never happened before as it was never warm enough during that month. In my home state of Oregon, wildfires set new records this year, with almost 2 million acres burned. Meanwhile, in my  More
The post The Carbon Soil Opportunity: Organic Farming Helps Counter Climate Change appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teamster President Sean O’Brien’s Wager: Did He Win?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345257</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/teamster-president-sean-obriens-wager-did-he-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2024, Teamster President Sean O’Brien made a wager. He bet that if he flattered and fawned over Donald Trump, the former president would make the union leader his fair-haired boy. So, O’Brien visited Trump at Mar-a-Lago, invited Trump to Teamster headquarters in Washington to meet with union members, and then, breaking  More
The post Teamster President Sean O’Brien’s Wager: Did He Win? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan La Botz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Invest in Families, Project 2025 Wants the Opposite]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345357</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/we-need-to-invest-in-families-project-2025-wants-the-opposite/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I teach my children to be kind and respectful and not to judge others — we’re all in this life together. Yet families like ours are often stigmatized when we need assistance to make ends meet. My husband and I work hard for our four boys. We live above the official federal poverty line, but  More
The post We Need to Invest in Families, Project 2025 Wants the Opposite appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chloe Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Something in the ‘We Gotta Do Something’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/the-something-in-the-we-gotta-do-something/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“You can’t fight something with nothing, you have to have an alternative vision…Trump had a vision…he had an explanation. To my view, Democrats really did not” – Bernie Sanders, in “Bernie Sanders says Democrats have lost their way”, 11/15/24, New York Times Podcast Since our most recent disastrous election, I have seen many variations of  More
The post The Something in the ‘We Gotta Do Something’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Rynn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Degrees of Complicity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345262</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/on-degrees-of-complicity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“…good deeds can be shortly stated but where wrong is done a wealth of language is needed to veil its deformity.” ― Thucydides “We have a responsibility to act for good when we have the power to do so.” –Proverbs 3:27 IF Hajj Amin al-Husseini – the Palestinian leader during the 1940s – had been  More
The post On Degrees of Complicity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Shahid Alam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu to Biden: “Well, You Dropped the Atom Bomb.”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345343</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/netanyahu-to-biden-well-you-dropped-the-atom-bomb/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s ghastly genocidal destruction of Gaza drags on and is horrifyingly clear for all to see. The Israeli Defense Forces’ criminal mass murder is so blatant and unabashed that in December last year, even U.S. President Joe Biden challenged Israel’s President Netanyahu. Speaking to an audience of campaign donors in Washington, D.C. including a former  More
The post Netanyahu to Biden: “Well, You Dropped the Atom Bomb.” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In a ‘Free’ Country Should Not Every Vote Be of Conscience? Or,  the “Mystery of Iniquity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345387</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/in-a-free-country-should-not-every-vote-be-of-conscience-or-the-mystery-of-iniquity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Men like Master-at-Arms Claggart] are madmen of the most dangerous sort…for their lunacy is…occasional;…it is self-contained so that…it is to the average mind indistinguishable from sanity [because] whatever the aims may be…the method and the outward proceeding are always perfectly rational. …such an one was Claggart, in whom was “a depravity according to nature.” Dark  More
The post In a ‘Free’ Country Should Not Every Vote Be of Conscience? Or,  the “Mystery of Iniquity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I No Longer Wish to Write About American Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345150</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/why-i-no-longer-wish-to-write-about-american-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There comes a time to quit something one has long been pursuing and even something one is good at. I feel like it’s time to quit political writing, at least of a particular kind that deals with the daily ups and downs in America, because it’s filling up headspace that takes away from crucial other  More
The post Why I No Longer Wish to Write About American Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ANIS SHIVANI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGill Admin Battles its Pro-Palestinian Students]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345340</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/mcgill-admin-battles-its-pro-palestinian-students/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Harvard of the North has been the site of an increasingly intense battle linking Justin Trudeau, Roger Waters, a government handbook marginalizing Palestinians and a historic student strike for Palestine. The alma mater of the prime minister and a disproportionate share of Justin Trudeau’s cabinet is aggressively repressing a movement to divest from apartheid  More
The post McGill Admin Battles its Pro-Palestinian Students appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Cheers for Maurizio Cattelan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345144</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/two-cheers-for-maurizio-cattelan/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For H.B. Just now I see in the news that a previously little known, rarely seen portrait by Caravaggio has reappeared in Italy. Because I am very interested in him, having written about his art repeatedly and read some of the vast literature about him, I would love to see this work. Maybe, indeed, it’s  More
The post Two Cheers for Maurizio Cattelan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report from a Campfire of the Resistance, San Francisco 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345157</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/report-from-a-campfire-of-the-resistance-san-francisco-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dust had not yet settled around the White House and the foul air had not yet cleared from above the nation’s capital, but the campfires of the resistance were already burning brightly. They were burning brightly on a recent night at City Lights Bookstore in San Francisco’s North Beach, where UCSC Professor Emerita Dana  More
The post Report from a Campfire of the Resistance, San Francisco 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Natural Capital or Natural Commonwealth?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345214</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/29/natural-capital-or-natural-commonwealth/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T06:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We are subject today to a barrage of neoliberal attempts to commodify what was previously seldom or never appropriated for private sale — the human body, water, hospitals.” —Immanuel Wallerstein, “New Revolts Against the System” Enabled by digital media, we humans are constantly convening ourselves: for protests and truck rallies; for funerals and football games;  More
The post Natural Capital or Natural Commonwealth? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Paur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "Engineers do not get to make startup mistakes when they build ledgers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42270266</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42270266"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T02:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tell that to Synapse customers. Many millions of dollars are missing.
Banks have to follow strict rules to account for where all the money goes. But the way fintechs work, they usually just have one or a couple underlying "FBO" accounts where all the pooled money is held, but then the fintech builds a ledger on top of this (and, as the article points out, to varying levels of engineering competence) to track each individual customer's balance within this big pool of money. In Synapse's case, their ledger said the total amount of all of their individual customer balances ended up being much more than the actual funds held in the underlying FBO accounts. Lots of folks are assuming fraud but I'm willing to put money that it was just a shitty, buggy ledger.
FWIW, after seeing "how the sausage is made", I would never put money into a fintech depository account. Use a real bank. Fintechs also often put out the fake promise that deposits are FDIC insured, but this only protects you if the underlying bank goes belly up, not if the fintech loses track of your money.
See https://www.forbes.com/sites/zennonkapron/2024/11/08/what-th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by revscat in "Send someone you appreciate an official 'Continue and Persist' Letter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42269718</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42269718"/>
        <updated>2024-11-29T00:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who is coming to increasingly believe that 99% of the world problems are caused by powers seeking to intentionally divide us one from the other, I cannot tell you how much joy this brings me to see. I wish you great success in this effort, however small it might appear to be in the scheme of things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>revscat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threads to allow users to select following feed as their default]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8903</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/threads-allow-users-select-following-feed-default/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This to finally spare us the time-wasting, sometimes totally irrelevant, tyranny of the “for you” tab. Chris Welch, writing for The Verge, says Meta has started testing a feature allowing users to select their preferred feed, be it “for you”, “following”, or even one custom made, as the stream they’ll see all the time. It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/thanksgicing-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/thanksgicing-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year's Thanksgiving has a special flavor. My son, who lives far away in Austin, Texas, is here for a visit. I still live in the house where he grew up, and he enjoys these nostalgic returns. After we got home from the airport yesterday, he went for a run. He came home to report that he'd passed the homes of old friends, the middle school he attended, and various spots where he's committed various teenage sins in his wayward youth.
A little later, we went to the train station to pick up his daughter, our granddaughter, who was traveling to meet us from Virginia, where she attends school. We all went out for a sushi feast before coming home to hang out, telling stories, and making each other laugh.
I get up early, and as I sit here writing, I have that wonderful protective parental feel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More ´Natural rate of unemployment´ busting, bad measurement edition.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45894</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/28/more-natural-rate-of-unemployment-busting-bad-measurement-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T15:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ´natural rate of unemployment´, also called ´Non-Accelerating Inflation Rate of Unemployment´ (NAIRU) or ´Non-Accelerating Wage Rate of Unemployment´ (NAWRU), is as, on this blog, Lars Syll states (here and here), a dangerous tool. According to NAIRU/NAWRU theory, a) When unemployment falls below a certain threshold, an inexorable increase in inflation will start. This is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/28/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283001</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T11:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turkey day links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inflation Re-Accelerates Despite Plunging Gasoline Prices as “Core Services” PCE Price Index Hits 7-Month High]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283008</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/inflation-re-accelerates-despite-plunging-gasoline-prices-as-core-services-pce-price-index-hits-7-month-high.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T10:21:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Core services inflation is the  biggie and going the wrong way. The Fed is already talking down the pace of rate cuts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Desalination Quench Agriculture’s Thirst?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282998</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/can-desalination-quench-agricultures-thirst.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T07:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small decentralized desalination plants hold the promise of low enough cost to use on brackish agricultural water.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Of Mongeese And Men]]></title>
        <id>6747319d139b5b0001851e3e</id>
        <link href="https://indi.ca/of-mongeese-and-men/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-28T06:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How America infected Ukraine, 'Israel', and Taiwan and made them rabid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>indi.ca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alexwasserman in "London's 850-year-old food markets to close"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42260795</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42260795"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T23:20:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statement from the City of London Corporation which is closing them down:
> Chris Hayward, policy chairman of the City of London Corporation, said the
> decision represented a "positive new chapter" for the markets as it "empowers
> traders to build a sustainable future in premises that align with their
> long-term business goals".
This is a great statement. Like firing people to free them up to find jobs that better align with their desire for employment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alexwasserman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Busting the ‘natural rate of unemployment’ myth]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45890</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/27/busting-the-natural-rate-of-unemployment-myth-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T23:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Sixty years ago Milton Friedman wrote an (in)famous article arguing that (1) the natural rate of unemployment was independent of monetary policy and that (2) trying to keep the unemployment rate below the natural rate would only give rise to higher and higher inflation. The hypothesis has always been controversial, and much […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autograd - in C, Zig, Rust and PyCodon]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/autograd-in-c-zig-rust-and-pycodon/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/autograd-in-c-zig-rust-and-pycodon/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T22:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
So...I'm supposed to be on my DevOps arc, but here I am writing a piece on Low Level programming! The pull to this path is too strong, I can't fight it..I'll get back to DevOps by the end of the week, I promise!
Autograd
There are great references on Autograd:
Pytorch Autograd: text and video.
Medium article
Taken from Pytorch's website:
PyTorch’s Autograd feature is part of what make PyTorch flexible and fast for building machine learning projects. It allows for the rapid and easy computation of multiple partial derivatives (also referred to as gradients) over a complex computation. This operation is central to backpropagation-based neural network learning.
Machine Learning in general use case.
Machine Learning has been proven to be highly useful in variety of sectors:
Health…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Lustre increases throughput to GPU instances by up to 12x]]></title>
        <id>2b2f34f261d66fc71bf826f5410519524152023d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-lustre-unlocks-full-network-bandwidth-and-gpu-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T22:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Lustre now features Elastic Fabric Adapter and NVIDIA GPUDirect Storage for up to 12x higher throughput to GPUs, unlocking new possibilities in deep learning, autonomous vehicles, and HPC workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 24, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241127</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241127"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 542458 in "Malware can turn off webcam LED and record video, demonstrated on ThinkPad X230"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42259659</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42259659"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T20:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are hardwired on Macbooks. From Daring Fireball, quoting an email from an Apple engineer.
> All cameras after [2008] were different: The hardware team tied the LED to a hardware signal from the sensor: If the (I believe) vertical sync was active, the LED would light up. There is NO firmware control to disable/enable the LED. The actual firmware is indeed flashable, but the part is not a generic part and there are mechanisms in place to verify the image being flashed. […]
> So, no, I don’t believe that malware could be installed to enable the camera without lighting the LED. My concern would be a situation where a frame is captured so the LED is lit only for a very brief period of time.
https://daringfireball.net/2019/02/on_covering_webcams]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>542458</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sbarre in "Malware can turn off webcam LED and record video, demonstrated on ThinkPad X230"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42259395</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42259395"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T20:27:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I thought the whole point of these camera LEDs was to have them wired to/through the power to the camera, so they are always on when the camera is getting power, no matter what.
Having the LED control exposed through the firmware completely defeats this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sbarre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wow! signal, sun-like stars, and an abundance of hydrogen]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8890</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wow-signal-sun-like-stars-abundance-hydrogen/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T20:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did an extra-terrestrial intelligence attempt to message us in the distant past? Or did an Earth based radio telescope, nicknamed Big Ear, inadvertently eavesdrop in on a snippet of a conversation between two other alien civilisations? These are among some of the many explanations advanced to understand the so-called Wow! signal, a suspected narrowband radio […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Melissa Lucashenko wins 2024 Mark and Evette Moran Nib award]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8895</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/melissa-lucashenko-wins-2024-mark-evette-moran-nib-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T19:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goorie/South East Australian author Melissa Lucashenko has won the 2024 Mark and Evette Moran Nib literary award, with her 2023 novel Edenglassie. A work of historical fiction, Edenglassie, which links the past with the present, also won this year’s ARA Historical Novel Prize, Indie Book Awards, and the fiction category of the Victorian Premier’s Literary […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage powerful generative-AI capabilities for Java development in the Eclipse IDE public preview]]></title>
        <id>7e4cb886f0c6e225870947705dc35910b3a68575</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-eclipse-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T19:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks an exciting milestone for Eclipse developers everywhere: we’re thrilled to announce the public preview of Amazon Q Developer in the Eclipse IDE. This integration brings the power of AI-driven development directly into one of the most popular development environments. In this blog post, we’ll explore some of its game-changing features, and show you […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vinicius Senger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282973</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-27-2024-html.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T19:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Blame cannons thunder  after Kamala campaign team podcast; Investigation into attempts to assassinate Trump  seem curiously silent; Boeing delivery, layoff woes ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[kirby vs. this blog post]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/kirby-vs-this-blog-post/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/kirby-vs-this-blog-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T16:28:43.327Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[:root{--inhale-duration:1000ms;--inhale-easing:cubic-bezier(0.25, 0.1, 0.25, 1)}.content{display:flex;align-items:flex-start;position:relative;width:100%}.kirby{min-width: 0;box-shadow:none;width:50px;height:50px;image-rendering:pixelated;position:absolute;left:0;top:0;z-index:10;transition:transform 0.3s ease}#text-to-inhale{padding-left:40px;position:relative;width:100%}.character{display:inline-block;transition:transform var(--inhale-duration) var(--inhale-easing),opacity var(--inhale-duration) var(--inhale-easing);position:relative;z-index:1}.character.inhaling{position:absolute;will-change:transform,opacity}.character.inhaled{opacity:0;transform:scale(.1) rotate(360deg);width:0;margin:0;padding:0}.credits{position:absolute;right:0;font-size:90%;top:20px;color:var(--sub-color);opacity:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV  购买和使用不完全指北]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/my-apple-tv-life/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/my-apple-tv-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[/ 本文会持续更新
版本
  更新时间
  更新内容




  1.0
  20241127
  初版




此文就是记录从我调研到购买和使用的一系列功课的汇总，如果你也桌备购入，希望能够帮助到你。
购前
🤔 如果你要使用 Apple TV 就意味着……
在中国大陆地区，想要使用 Apple TV 还是需要一些技巧的，这里作为前提先列出来：
一个 Apple ID（为了体验最大化，并不推荐使用中国大陆地区的 Apple ID）；
一台电视或一台显示器；
流畅的网络环境（为了体验最大化，最好是比较科学的网络条件）；
一条 HDMI2.0/2.1 连接线（随包装不会附赠）；
接下来，我会逐一讲解上述因素。
🍎 Apple ID
使用 Apple 设备和服务的基础因素。这里需要注意的是，由于Apple TV 并没有正式在中国大陆地区销售，并不推荐你使用中国大陆地区的 Apple ID 进行登录和使用，因为体验会收到最大程度的折损。
使用中国大陆地区的 Apple ID 登录时，Apple TV 将没有 App Store ，无法下载新的 App。同时预装的 Apple Music 也不会显示，即使该 Apple ID 已经订阅了中国大陆地区的 Apple Music 亦无法使用相关功能。但是，若先用其他地区的 Apple ID 登录，并在 APP Store 下载第三方 APP，再切换回中国大陆地区的 Apple ID，则已下载的第三方 APP 仍会保留。
所以，如果你想要正常体验 Apple TV 的原生各项服务，下载并享受其他第三方 App，请使用非大陆地区 Apple ID，我个人推荐使用美区 Apple ID。
📺 显示器/电视
最推荐的当然是一台电视，如果你有足够大的空间的话。否则，一台合适尺寸的显示器也是可以的。比较理想的是一台支持杜比视界的 4k 电视/显…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Agrees to Ceasefire in Lebanon After Ground Invasion Fails]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282964</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/israel-agrees-to-ceasefire-in-lebanon-after-ground-invasion-fails.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T14:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An initial look at the ceasefire between Israel and Lebanon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/27/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282954</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-27-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T11:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank/IMF have clearly failed. An alternative policy is needed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-IMF-have-clearly-failed-An-alternative-policy-is-needed</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-IMF-have-clearly-failed-An-alternative-policy-is-needed"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T10:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forced to upgrade]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/forced-to-upgrade/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/forced-to-upgrade/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been happily using an iPhone 8 for the last 7 years. It has been, and still is, a perfect smartphone. I've never bumped up against the limitations of the hardware (gaming on a phone is a bit of a mystery to me), and all of my photos and videos are synced to the cloud, so I've never even run out of the 64gb of storage space.
About a year ago the battery wasn't making it through a full day. So I replaced the battery and breathed new life into my phone. It felt brand new.
But then this year,  it started happening. Certain apps become unavailable, requiring iOS 17 or later. The iPhone 8 will never support iOS 17 since Apple only provides software updates for 6 years after the device's release date1. So I'm stuck at 16.7.10 in perpetuity.
And now I feel quite bitter. I have a perfectly fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by geuis in "I Stopped Using Kubernetes. Our DevOps Team Is Happier Than Ever"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42253354</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42253354"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T05:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh boy. Please, please stop using Medium for anything. I have lost count of how many potentially interesting or informative articles are published behind the Medium sign-in wall. At least for me, if you aren't publishing blog articles in public then what's the point of me trying to read them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>geuis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tombert in "I Didn't Need Kubernetes, and You Probably Don't Either"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42253231</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42253231"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T05:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve come to the conclusion that I hate “cloud shit”, and a small part of me is convinced that literally no one actually likes it, and everyone is playing a joke on me.
I have set up about a dozen rack mount servers in my life, installing basically every flavor of Unix and Linux and message busses under the sun in the process, but I still get confused by all the Kubectl commands and GCP integration with it.
I might just be stupid, but it feels like all I ever do with Kubernetes is update and break YAML files, and then spend a day fixing them by copy-pasting increasingly-convoluted things on stackexchange.  I cannot imagine how anyone goes to work and actually enjoys working in Kubernetes, though I guess someone must in terms of “law of large numbers”.
If I ever start a company, I am going to work my damndest to avoid “cloud integration crap” as possible.  Just have a VM or a physical server and let me install everything myself.  If I get to tens of millions of users, maybe I’ll worry about it then.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tombert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming Istio into an enterprise-ready service mesh for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>de2fd3b7da33ab9ea64af38d12aae1e6afd237fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/transforming-istio-into-an-enterprise-ready-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T01:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is authored by John Howard(Senior Architect, Solo.io), Petr McAllister(Engineer on the Partner Team, Solo.io), Christian Posta(VP, Global Field CTO, Solo.io) and Jooyoung Kim (Senior Containers Specialist Solutions Architect, AWS). Introduction Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) is a fully managed service that streamlines the deployment, management, and scaling of containerized applications. Although Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jooyoung Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grateful for more time with Cocoa after GDV]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/grateful-for-more-time-with-cocoa-after-gdv/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/grateful-for-more-time-with-cocoa-after-gdv/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T22:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In answering my own WeblogPoMoAMA Question: What are you thankful for?
Well... I would be remiss if I didn’t talk about an important life event.
Yesterday marked Cocoa’s 2nd year of life— not her 2nd birthday, but the 2-year anniversary of when the universe (or choose your own higher being) gave us more time with her.
Let’s rewind a bit.
Thanksgiving 2022. We just finished eating Thanksgiving dinner and were relaxing, watching TV. Cocoa was lying on the couch when she suddenly started dry heaving, as if trying to throw up but with nothing to expel.
Strange.
We took her outside. She was on and off dry heaving. Nothing was coming out. Maybe she wanted to go use the bathroom. She walked very slowly, something clearly off. We brought her back inside, her little body feeling so tender.
She wasn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time-based snapshot copy for Amazon EBS]]></title>
        <id>2780add382124234bd566eba632030da9555e3b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/time-based-snapshot-copy-for-amazon-ebs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T22:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With time-based copying, critical EBS snapshots and AMIs can now meet crucial RPOs by specifying exact completion durations from 15 minutes to 48 hours for disaster recovery, testing, development, and operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gail Jones wins Creative Australia Award for Lifetime Achievement in Literature]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8886</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/gail-jones-wins-creative-australia-award-lifetime-achievement-literature/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based Western Australian author Gail Jones was last week presented with the Creative Australia Lifetime Achievement in Literature award. Jones’ books have won the ARA Historical Novel Prize, Barbara Ramsden Award, and Western Australian Premier’s Book Awards. They have also been included on the long and short lists of numerous literary awards, including the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s sessions and speakers at AWS re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/098ea5265b56</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-ones-sessions-and-speakers-at-aws-re-invent-2024-098ea5265b56?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud forward, data powered, AI ascendant. That’s how we stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by phil21 in "California's most neglected group of students: the gifted ones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247816</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247816"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Killing truly progressive programs for the purpose of virtue signaling is a loss for society
It's not just a loss for society.  It's society-killing.
Taking resources away from those who move society forward and spending them on those who are unlikely to "pay it back" is a way your culture dies.  Conquerers in the past used this strategy to win massive empires for themselves.  It's a ridiculous self-own.
This is perhaps the sole political topic I will die on a hill for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phil21</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by csa in "California's most neglected group of students: the gifted ones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247695</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247695"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not just California, but California may be one of the more egregious state neglecters.
The push at the state level for policies that focus on equality of outcomes over equality of opportunities will not end well for the gifted and talented communities.
Whenever I hear these people talk about their policies, I can’t help but recall Harrison Bergeron.
Focusing on equality of outcomes in a society that structurally does not afford equality of opportunities is a fool’s game that ends with Bergeron-esque levels of absurdity.
Imho, the only viable/main solution is to acknowledge that we all aren’t equal, we don’t all have access to the same opportunities, but as a country we can implement policies that lessen the imbalance.
Head Start is a good example.
Well-run gifted and talented programs in schools are also good examples.
Killing truly progressive programs for the purpose of virtue signaling is a loss for society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing your AWS Cost Explorer data with Amazon Q Developer: Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>677db6e38f74e929dcdd46ad8d92b84fe21e3332</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/analyzing-your-aws-cost-explorer-data-with-amazon-q-developer-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the general availability of the cost analysis capability in Amazon Q Developer. This powerful feature integrates Q Developer’s natural language processing capabilities with AWS Cost Explorer, revolutionizing how you analyze and understand your AWS costs. Initially launched in preview on April 30, 2024, the Amazon Q cost analysis capability now offers enhanced […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riya Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Benefits with Bottlerocket: A Purpose-Built Container OS]]></title>
        <id>7fd5d2aa425994eb182752ee6f7b22bfd45719d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/benefiting-from-bottlerocket-an-open-source-container-optimized-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post updated on Nov 26, 2024. This post discusses Bottlerocket, a Linux-based open source operating system that is purpose-built for running containers. We will walk through fleet management at scale and how users can benefit from it. We will also share the key pillars that support Bottlerocket’s development plan. The challenges of fleet management with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Charan Teja Gopaluni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare incident on November 14, 2024, resulting in lost logs]]></title>
        <id>3SNSdDbbVziSrdGxDq4AzH</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-november-14-2024-resulting-in-lost-logs"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 14, 2024, Cloudflare experienced a Cloudflare Logs outage, impacting the majority of customers using these products. During the ~3.5 hours that these services were impacted, about 55% of the logs we normally send to customers were not sent and were lost. The details of what went wrong and why are interesting both for customers and practitioners.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Herre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How SmugMug Increased Data Modeling Productivity with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>60be41c2505f5225f2f910fd21a76bb690d633ff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-smugmug-increased-data-modeling-productivity-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-written with Dr. Geoff Ryder, Manager, at SmugMug. Introduction SmugMug operates two very large online photo platforms: SmugMug and Flickr. These platforms enable more than 100 million customers to safely store, search, share, and sell tens of billions of photos every day. However, the data science and engineering team at SmugMug and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Matos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok in Romania]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53447</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/26/tiktok-in-romania/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ownership and control of social media platforms is a first-order concern for both domestic politics and international conflict. The most important battleground in the Russia-Ukraine war is elections in NATO member states. And there, Russia is clearly winning. Trump, obviously, but yesterday saw the stunning success of formerly fringe right-wing candidate C?lin Georgescu. In an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近通勤路上的习惯变化]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/20241126/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/20241126/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我的公司距离我的家有 17km 距离，所以我每天会花单程 30-40mins 的时间开车通勤。今天简单说说我怎么度过这每天一个多小时的时间。
🎵 听音乐
通勤时间总是无聊的，我最早的时候是听歌。但是我这个人有一个毛病，很难听得进去新歌，但是我的收藏列表我又听烂了。所以现在通勤路上听音乐的频率较少，也会，但不多。
📻 听播客
我个人很喜欢听播客，不光在通勤的时候会听。但是我又很挑，对于信息和内容输出质量很低的播客我极少收听。所以我有一个白名单，一旦白名单的播客更新，我才会考虑听。所以，不会每天有一个小时的可收听量。
📚 听书
这个是我最近半个月养成的新习惯，起因是我在一些播客中听到过一些书籍的分享，但是我又没有很好的建立起读新书的习惯，所以我就瞅准了通勤这段时间。恰好微信读书又有听书模式，如果你是付费会员，可以想听歌一样的听书。这简直是一举多得，解决了我通勤路上恰好收听内容不足的隐患，又拓展了「阅读量」，还能完成微信读书的任务。

▲ 阅读了 13 天的成果
关于微信读书我准备后面找时间专门写一篇有趣的观察和思考，作为产品分析吧。
💬 总结
综上所述，我现在通勤路上依然会听歌和听播客，听歌比较少，听播客比听音乐稍多。这两者的区别在于听歌可以随时开播，听播客我需要提前甄选一下听的内容。如果两者都不想实施，我使用了微信读书的听书来补齐，这样又可以在这个通勤的时间段内拓展出一个内容输入的渠道。可喜可贺。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by stackghost in "Cybertruck's Many Recalls"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42243288</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42243288"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T07:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>I wonder if you exclude "recalls" resolved by software updates, for all cars, where it would rank then?
Why have you put "recalls" in quotes?  It gives the impression you think this makes it somehow lesser.  The cybertruck, for example, was subject to a recall because the rearview camera wouldn't come up, but the mirrors are insufficient to back the vehicle up safely without the camera.
That's a safety issue, irrespective of whether or not the fix was in software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stackghost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stack Overflow Does Not Want To Help You]]></title>
        <id>https://stackoverflow-makes-me-sad.bearblog.dev/stack-overflow-does-not-want-to-help-you/</id>
        <link href="https://stackoverflow-makes-me-sad.bearblog.dev/stack-overflow-does-not-want-to-help-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T22:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stack Overflow's traffic has been in decline, and the convenient narrative is to blame it on LLMs.
However, I think developers were already looking for reasons to stop interacting with Stack Overflow. LLMs have massive blind spots. New framework releases, yesterday's OS update, and niche languages are not in LLM training data. These are the problems where Stack Overflow should shine over AI. Yet traffic is declining even in these areas.
I recently found myself caught between these two worlds, trying to solve a problem too new for LLMs, but running into the exact community issues driving people away from Stack Overflow. My experience might shed some light on why developers are leaving, even when AI can't help them.
My Problem
The remote SSH plugin for VSCode stopped working. Like many devel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Enough for Snow by Jessica Au being adapted to film]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8884</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/cold-enough-for-snow-jessica-au-film/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian author Jessica Au’s multi-award winning 2022 novel, Cold Enough for Snow, is being made into a film, says publisher Giramondo. No word yet as to who the lead actors will be, but production is scheduled to commence in 2025, and will be the debut feature of Jemima James. Fingers crossed this is a faithful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing future-dated Amazon EC2 On-Demand Capacity Reservations]]></title>
        <id>c82766052a1eefeefa0411b4276a70ec3f98023b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-future-dated-amazon-ec2-on-demand-capacity-reservations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS EC2 Capacity Reservations empowers you to secure compute capacity for critical future workloads up to 120 days ahead, ensuring seamless performance during peak demand events like product launches or seasonal sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[imza hücresi ve diğerleri]]></title>
        <id>https://vitriolpodcast.blog/imza-hucresi-ve-digerleri/</id>
        <link href="https://vitriolpodcast.blog/imza-hucresi-ve-digerleri/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[geçtiğimiz hafta sonu, sevgili üstadım seda bağcan’ın “imza hücresi şifası birinci seviye eğitimi”nde, artık ben de bir eğitmen olduğum için, asistan olarak bulundum. birçok son derece kuvvetli şifacının el almasına tanık oldum, ben de el verme onuruna eriştim.
detaylara inmeden evvel, bu el verme olayını, diğer isimleriyle inisiyasyon veya erginlenme, biraz kendi cümlelerimle açmak istiyorum.
elbette birçok şekilde anlatılabilir, eski hayata ölmek ve yeni hayata doğmak, ki bu yeni hayat kişinin olması gerektiği kişi olmasına sıçramasıdır, yeni bir bilginin alınması ve içselleştirmeye başlanması süreci, zaten titreşimlerden oluşan atomlardan oluşan insan bedeninin, ki bu bedenler (en az) dört tanedir ve fiziksel beden bunların içinden titreşimi en düşük veya en az süptil olanıdır (diğerler…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking down CPU speed: How utilization impacts performance]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Performance Engineering team at GitHub assessed how CPU performance degrades as utilization increases and how this relates to capacity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/">Breaking down CPU speed: How utilization impacts performance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: multiple new launches, AI training partnership with Anthropic, and join AWS re:Invent virtually (Nov 25, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>1534a75f44b8d95651046b97d6cd9b1d87d12a92</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-multiple-new-launches-ai-training-partnership-with-anthropic-and-join-aws-reinvent-virtually-nov-25-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T16:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I saw an astonishing number of new feature and service launches from AWS. This means we are getting closer to AWS re:Invent 2024! Our News Blog team is also finalizing blog posts for re:Invent to introduce some awesome launches from service teams for your reading pleasure. The most interesting news is that we’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving back to Japan - countryside]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/moving-back-to-japan-countryside/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/moving-back-to-japan-countryside/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:46:14.158Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a two-month writing hiatus, I'm back to share my recent adventure: moving back to Japan.
Two weeks ago, I left my croupier job in Estonia, moved back to Japan and already achieved one of my long-standing dreams – settling into a charming two-story house with a garden. My plan is to transform this outdoor space into a green haven, with lemon trees and herb-filled pots(Yes I love lemon trees a lot and fortunately there are lemon trees everywhere around my neighborhood). The house was completely empty when I moved in, so I'm gradually acquiring basic appliances to make it feel like home.
Transportation here presented an interesting challenge. While a car is essential in the countryside, my current financial situation – thanks to the loans I took for this journey – means I've opted for a bicycle. I purchased a Giant Escape for around 70,000 yen and will be commuting 5km each way, a distance familiar from my university days.
This isn't my first time in Japan, but living in the countryside as a foreigner feels like a unique privilege. The locals are incredibly welcoming. While I'm visibly different – a bearded foreigner in a small Japanese city – I've been pleasantly surprised by the warm interactions. Elders, children, and dog owners are particularly friendly, often greeting me with enthusiastic "konnichiwa"s.
My ability to speak Japanese fluently is making a big difference, of course. In this small city, encountering a Turk who speaks Japanese at an advanced level is not something locals experience everyday. Whenever I need assistance, people go out of their way to help me, which I deeply appreciate.
My professional journey is just beginning. Starting December 2nd, I'll join a new workplace where I've already met most of my colleagues. Contrary to stereotypes about Japanese companies, my new team is quite supportive and genuinely interested in making me feel comfortable. I'm aware that I'm really lucky to have found such an environment, and I'm hopeful about building a long-term community here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka's People Have Kicked Out the Old Political Class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-People-Have-Kicked-Out-the-Old-Political-Class</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-People-Have-Kicked-Out-the-Old-Political-Class"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The progressive alliance that backs Sri Lanka's new president, Anura Kumara Dissanayake, won a landslide victory in last week's parliamentary election. The government has a clear mandate for change but now faces many obstacles to its reform agenda. 
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Corruption / financial criminality, 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Recipients of the 2024 Spotify FOSS Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7274</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/11/congratulations-to-the-recipients-of-the-2024-spotify-foss-fund/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Spotify FOSS Fund is back again! We created the Spotify FOSS Fund in 2022 to help support the [...]
The post Congratulations to the Recipients of the 2024 Spotify FOSS Fund appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alexandrawei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is everyone here a CS major?]]></title>
        <id>https://wyverian.bearblog.dev/is-everyone-here-a-cs-major/</id>
        <link href="https://wyverian.bearblog.dev/is-everyone-here-a-cs-major/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like whenever I browse bear blog its mostly posts about coding and or being a computer science major? Not that that's a bad thing, I'm just observing a theme on here. Sometimes I can feel out of my depth here with it all, I only know basic html and although I do code, it's in R (woo lets go statistics). Just sometimes I can feel a bit lonely on here browsing etc because none of my hobbies or pursuits have been reflected on here as of yet :0. Any other earth science ppl out there ?Maybe this is a nothing burger post but whatever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? Bank Runs Versus Solvency]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32467</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-bank-runs-versus-solvency/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence from a 160-year-long panel of U.S. banks suggests that the ultimate cause of bank failures and banking crises is almost always a deterioration of bank fundamentals that leads to insolvency. As described in our previous post, bank failures—including those that involve bank runs—are typically preceded by a slow deterioration of bank fundamentals and are hence remarkably predictable. In this final post of our three-part series, we relate the findings discussed previously to theories of bank failures, and we discuss the policy implications of our findings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The political economy of estimating productivity.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45871</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/25/the-political-economy-of-estimating-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T10:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who decides what statistical offices measure and how they measure it? And what are the implicit values embedded in these decisions? Recently, the ILO issued a new manual on measuring productivity. Below, I´ll discuss the questions posed. But for starters, it is essential to realize that economists measure monetary productivity, not physical productivity, which leads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/daily/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/daily/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[{{ posts|tag:daily }}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Follow Up to: Adding a Little Friction to My Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/a-follow-up-to-adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/a-follow-up-to-adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T05:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I wrote a post about how I wanted to add a friction between myself and getting online. I was curious to see how it would affect my mental health as well the amount of time I spend online. Things didn’t exactly go to plan, but I did come away with some interesting take aways and some ideas on how I want to proceed in the future.
The first two days, I didn’t log on to the internet at all. My laptop remained off, my tablet had the wi-fi turned off, and my phone was restricted to just a few apps. I forgot to turn off my email notifications (the only notifications I have on), so I saw some emails on my phone and that was fine. I didn’t respond to any, because I prefer to type on a real keyboard, but it helped me keep track of some Amazon orders as well as a few other things I had goi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warm Embrace of Coffee and Quiet Ambition]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/the-warm-embrace-of-coffee-and-quiet-ambition/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/the-warm-embrace-of-coffee-and-quiet-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I strolled through yet another city on a mid-week trip, I came across a cozy-looking coffee shop. Looking through the window, I saw a variety of people sitting inside. Most of them were looking at their laptops: reading, typing, and occasionally writing something down on a physical notepad. Other people were just enjoying today's newspaper.
I had my own laptop with me, tucked away in my backpack, and that made me curious. I knew people were working in places like these, but it never really appealed to me to try the same thing. Probably due to the fact that I've always had a full-time job, working out of an office and without the need or time to work anywhere else. But now that I was here, on a little holiday and with some time on my hands, I felt a force that tried to drag me inside.
An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jeroenhd in "RFC 35140: HTTP Do-Not-Stab (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232991</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232991"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T03:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important to note that the Do-Not-Stab header has been deprecated because one browser engine switched it on by default and requiring users to opt into stabbing hurt the bottom line of the stabbing industry, so it's no longer respected. Luckily someone came up with General Assault Control, a non-standard alternative, which also only has one value, so you can set Sec-GAC to 1 to request websites not to assault you. By design, this header cannot be extended, so it cannot be used to distinguish brutal stabbings from a comedic pie to the face in the future.
Because of legal requirements, the General Assault Control header may not be enabled by default, as American states like Colorado require explicit opt-out (rather than explicit opt-in). This protects Colorado's thriving stabbing and shooting industry as most users will never want to opt into being stabbed.
Despite the feature being forced to be disabled by default, the organisation behind the spec is pushing hard for customers to download fringe browsers  that implement the feature (though you may need about:config to enable it). Because of the small user base, the request not to be assaulted can be used by websites not willing to follow the standard to make their stabbings and shootings more precise. End users can request a JSON file from the web server containing the supposed support for the GAC header, but requesting this URL may be used to kick the user in the teeth by non compliant servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeroenhd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by saurik in "The two factions of C++"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232183</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232183"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T01:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I compile a lot of C++ code from a lot of places, and the only time I run into code that somehow simply doesn't work on newer versions of C++ and where the developers aren't even sure if they will accept any patches to fix the issue as they claim it "isn't supported" to use a newer version of C++--even for the public headers of a library--is, you guessed it: code from Google.
Meanwhile, most of the C++ code from Google seems to be written in some mishmash of different ideas, always at some halfway point along a migration between something ancient and something passable... but never anything I would ever dare to call "modern", and thereby tends to be riddled with state machines and manual weak pointers that lead to memory corruption.
So... I really am not sure I buy the entire premise of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saurik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JacobJeppesen in "Denmark will plant 1B trees and convert 10% of farmland into forest"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42231053</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42231053"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T22:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've seen a bit of confusion regarding this. First, it's 10% of Denmark's total land area, which is roughly equivalent to 15% of farmland area. Second, the conversion of farmland area into nature and forests is mainly for improving water quality, as excess nitrogen from agriculture has essentially killed the rivers and coastal waters through oxygen depletion from algae.
Regarding global warming and CO2, the area conversion of peatlands will help, but the major change here is the introduction of a carbon tax for the entire agricultural industry. And to end confusion regarding other emissions than CO2, it's actually a CO2-equivalent (CO2e) tax, which includes a range of other gasses. E.g., 1kg of methane is 25kg CO2e.
If you'd like to read more, see the two PDF documents below, which are the main official documents. They're in Danish, but upload them to Claude or ChatGPT, and you'll have a much better source of information if you'd like to know more about the specifics and how the actual implementation is planned.
[1] https://www.regeringen.dk/media/13261/aftale-om-et-groent-da...
[2] https://mgtp.dk/media/iinpdy3w/aftale_om_implementering_af_e...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JacobJeppesen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pfraze in "This website is hosted on Bluesky"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42230689</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42230689"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T21:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Appreciated Daniel reaching out to the team about this! Hosting blobs is one of those things that will inevitably go through iterations as we understand the abuse vectors more and more, but for now it's really fun to see this kind of usage in action. The PDS is meant to be a database host in the same sense that a webserver is a website host.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pfraze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Substack, no alternative to independent websites and blogs]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8877</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/substack-no-alternative-independent-websites-blogs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T20:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online publishing platform Substack, founded in 2017, was all anyone could talk about by 2022. Writers were scrambling to jump on the bandwagon, having heard tales of six-figure revenues being earned by some publishers. Even though we’ve heard those sorts of stories before. I even joined up myself, to see what the fuss was about. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Responce to ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot, or the Necessity to Write Our Own Histories’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/responce-to-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-write-our-own-histories?v=1732477766</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/responce-to-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-write-our-own-histories?v=1732477766"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T19:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Responce to ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot, or the Necessity to Write Our Own Histories’
Notes: This essay is a response to Yintah film review: Anarchists in the blind spot, or the necessity to write our own histories which was posted to BC Counter Info on Nov 9th, 2024.
Source: Retrieved from https://bccounterinfo.org/2024/11/17/review-of-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-get-an-editor/

 ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot’ has the posture of a disappointed lover who didn’t make it into their songwriter ex’s latest LP. None of the songs are about them, so they leave a scathing review. 
 The anonymous author argues that Yintah should have included the history of anarchist participation in the Wet’suwet’en struggle. I agree that the film is incomplete witho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can businesses flourish in a world with a cap on personal wealth?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53415</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/can-businesses-flourish-in-a-world-with-a-cap-on-personal-wealth/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T18:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Rutger Claassen and Ingrid Robeyns Let’s establish an upper limit on the personal wealth any individual can possess. This is the core principle behind ‘limitarianism’. Limitarianism represents one of the more radical proposals in the debate on wealth inequality. Over the past few years, one of us has developed the philosophy of limitarianism (first […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan and Romania join a very special club]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53421</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/taiwan-and-romania-join-a-very-special-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T17:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So in the last three years or so — since COVID, basically — Romania and Taiwan have both joined a very special club of countries. There are not a lot of countries in this club. If you’re very generous, you could include perhaps a dozen or so. But to my way of thinking, there are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by equestria in "A career-ending mistake"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42228934</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42228934"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T17:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the thing about the average career in big tech: five years after you leave, almost no one will remember you were there. Most of your old team mates will leave for other other jobs. Your code will get refactored or rewritten. Docs will be superseded, then lost in some CMS migration. Before long, it will be as if you have never worked there.
I know it sounds preposterous, but ask anyone over the age of 55 or 60: except for folks who built their own companies or made truly exceptional contributions to their field, most will say that hobbies, friends, and family mattered a lot more.
So, there is this fundamental contradiction in this article: you can engineer a very neat career, but for most techies, the most useful goal is to make money fast in a way that doesn't drain your life energy. And most of the time, this means responding to opportunities, not sticking to your guns. For example, a lifetime IC job may be ultimately worth less than a management job that gets you to VP level in a decade. You don't need to dream about being a manager; you just need to be reasonably good at it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>equestria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[重新开始记录每一天]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/20241125/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/20241125/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[重新开始公开写日记。
Why
前一段时间发现自己在浑噩过日子，并不是像一具行尸走肉，而是缺少自律的可持续的沉淀过程。熟悉我的朋友可能知道，我运营了一个名叫不求甚解的 Telegram 频道，这是我的得意之作，也是我的心头之痛。为什么这么讲，得意的是因为我在运营这个介质的同时获得了诸多关注和肯定，难过的是我经常缺少更新它的动力。
但是我经常思考。是的，作为一个 INTJ-A，我是非常喜欢思考，人生经历了 30 多年，到达了现在的阶段，我已经养成了时刻思考的能力和习惯，但是我缺少系统化沉淀的动作。
所以，我准备开启我人生的新阶段 ———— 养成自律的思考到沉淀的链路。
How
我准备按照时间周期的维度产出一些内容：
[Daily] 每天在这里写日记，哪怕是流水账；
[Weekly] Telegram 频道一周至少 3 更；
[Monthly] 召集思想同频的小伙伴录制播客。
Specially
需要说明几点，以上产出的内容，都是为了我自己，如果能帮助到此刻正在看的你，我很荣幸，但这不是我的职责以及初心。
最后，除了上面那些看起来很高大上的原因外，另外一个让我开始想要系统化记录自己生活的原因，是因为我看到了我的朋友 61 正在这么做，能够通过他的内容中感受到他对生活的热爱以及快乐，我也同样需要这些。
以上，祝各位都好。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nations pledge $300 billion for climate aid + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nations-pledge-300-billion-for-climate-aid-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nations-pledge-300-billion-for-climate-aid-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T15:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan's president plans South Pacific tour for stronger ties; UN talks result in $300 billion climate funding for developing nations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zug_zug in "Dear friend, you have built a Kubernetes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42227960</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42227960"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T14:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For what it's worth, I've worked at multiple places that ran shell scripts just fine for their deploys.
- One had only 2 services [php] and ran over 1 billion requests a day. Deploy was trivial, ssh some new files to the server and run a migration, 0 downtime.
- One was in an industry that didn't need "Webscale" (retirement accounts). Prod deploys were just docker commands run by jenkins. We ran two servers per service from the day I joined the day I left 4 years later (3x growth), and ultimately removed one service and one database during all that growth.
Another outstanding thing about both of these places was that we had all the testing environments you need, on-demand, in minutes.
The place I'm at now is trying to do kubernetes and is failing miserably (ongoing nightmare 4 months in and probably at least 8 to go, when it was allegedly supposed to only take 3 total). It has one shared test environment that it takes 3-hours to see your changes in.
I don't fault kubernetes directly, I fault the overall complexity. But at the end of the day kubernetes feels like complexity trying to abstract over complexity, and often I find that's less successful that removing complexity in the first place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zug_zug</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't buy me a coffee... yet]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/dont-buy-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/dont-buy-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A contradictory title from someone who lives in a country that is among the world's largest coffee consumers, and who loves a Swedish fika.
The title, of course, refers to the "Buy Me a Coffee" buttons that you see on every other blog. Today, it's often easier to find a donation button than a link to the RSS feed or a contact page.
I tried it myself when launching the Bearming Theme. It lasted for a day; then I removed it. It simply doesn't feel right—at least not at the moment.
I don’t think I offer anything that justifies a call to donate money. I write some blog posts and let others use my theme. That’s it!
Maybe it's a matter of background and culture. Maybe it has to do with the typically Scandinavian "jantelagen" (Law of Jante). I don't know.
I don't blame anyone who chooses to use these buttons. Some may see it as a way to put some pressure on themselves to deliver. Some may see it as a way for others to show appreciation.
Personally, I blog almost daily anyway, and I think it's nice to know that I don't "have to." And when it comes to appreciation from others, a short email or a guestbook entry feels much more valuable to me.
But hey, if you're ever in Sweden and feel like buying me a real cup of coffee, I'll gladly accept your fika invitation any day of the week. ☕️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peak babies has been. Young men are not expendable, anymore.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45847</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/24/peak-babies-has-been-young-men-are-not-expendable-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T09:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peak Babies was in 2012. At this moment, we´re back to the level of forty years ago (and the most recent data may well be an overestimate). For the first time in centuries, cohorts entering the global labour market will soon be smaller than the cohorts preceding them. Even when there are significant differences in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Handy Mini-Market]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53422</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/sunday-photoblogging-handy-mini-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T09:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by NAHWheatCracker in "How to give a senior leader feedback without getting fired"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42224244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42224244"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T21:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree with you that's how it should be, but experience tells me that everyone is insecure and it's hardly correlated with position and job security.
People lower down the chain are insecure because they could legitimately be let go at any time for any reason.
People higher up the chain are insecure because any loss of face is debilitating. Especially having failings pointed out by someone "below" them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NAHWheatCracker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lijok in "How to give a senior leader feedback without getting fired"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223920</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223920"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T21:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astonishing. Completely backwards. This article describes how to give feedback to your subordinates, not to your superiors. If your superiors are unable to process no-fluff information, regardless of whether it's feedback or updates, they have no business lording over anyone and will sink whatever function they have oversight of. If you find yourself working under such people, don't bother giving feedback, start polishing your resume.
The reason you fluff up feedback to your subordinates is because lower down the chain they tend to be insecure and don't yet have the experience to distinguish between actionable impartial feedback, and threats to their job security.
The reason you don't fluff feedback, or any information for that matter to your superiors, is described in basically every handbook on highly effective communication in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lijok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gary_0 in "The tech utopia fantasy is over"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223132</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223132"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T19:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In retrospect it was extremely arrogant of us 90's nerds to think that the bullies and autocrats and sleazebags of the world were too stupid to figure out how to use the Internet to their own ends, and overwhelm the incumbent minority. Once you could use a sleek, trendy iPhone instead of a clunky desktop computer to get online, the writing was on the wall.
Technology changes, people don't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gary_0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>