<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-13T01:43:42.703Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-13T01:43:42.703Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The website song: everyone is free to write websites, an IndieWeb anthem]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8271</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/website-song-everyone-free-write-websites-indieweb-anthem/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody’s Free (To Write Websites), by Robb Knight, and Keenan. Spectacularly riffing off Australian filmmaker Baz Luhrmann’s 1999 video, the Sunscreen Song, this is for the graduating Indie Web class of whenever. There is an abundance of sage advice here. If I could offer you only one tip for the future, coding would be it. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate jargon alternatives by Matt Watson]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8267</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/corporate-jargon-alternatives-matt-watson/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American web developer Matt Watson has re-written many latter-day, jarring, corporate-speak terms, with words and phrases from long past times. For instance, instead of “circle back”, say “bring word again”. Or, replace “open communication” with the surely eye-brow raising “regular intercourse”. In other examples, ASAP becomes “betimes”, change agent (what?) becomes “efficient cause”, while lean […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by danShumway in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228545</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228545"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T19:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another point that Patreon isn't really emphasizing here that seems relevant to any conversations about "fairness" is that Apple's fees on Patreon subscriptions in-app are now higher than Patreon's fees.
It's important to recognize any time that we're talking about the market that services charge what they can, not what is fair. The market does not have a concept of fairness, only competition. This is why there is no such thing as a benevolent monopoly that charges fair prices - because fairness does not exist in the market, only competition.
BUT... since fairness gets so often brought into conversations about Apple's fees, often with the implicit suggestion that Apple "deserves" to be compensated for all of the work they're putting into hosting and curating apps and for (in heavy quotes) "creating" a market that they supposedly also don't have duopoly control over: does anybody want to argue that Apple hosting the Patreon app on iOS provides more value to Patreon subscribers and creators than the existence of Patreon itself does?
Like, if we're going to talk about what's egregious and what's not egregious, charging higher fees per-transaction than the platforms you are hosting seems like it might be a good indicator that things have gotten out of control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danShumway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexandrB in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41227566</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41227566"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has quietly been one of the biggest culprits in the proliferation of subscription software. They still don't support upgrades/upgrade pricing. Subscriptions are also the easiest way to implement a software demo or trial in the App Store. Finally they use their control of the App Store to coerce anyone doing something different than monthly/yearly subscriptions into that model (as we see here).
It sucks big time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexandrB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276592</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Kamala on the cover of Time; Trump files suit against DOJ for political persecution; Thomas Frank on liberals; Front Porch Forum in Vermont ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize your .NET application using AWS App2Container and AWS Toolkit for .NET]]></title>
        <id>320801e855cd9287d2d4d32d6e3f92c93b03b8c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/replatform-and-refactor-your-workload-to-aws-using-aws-app2container-and-aws-toolkit-for-net-refactoring-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview As businesses increasingly embrace cloud computing, many organizations are seeking to migrate their existing .NET applications from on-premises data centers to AWS. However, the transition of these workloads can often be complex and time-consuming. To simplify this process, AWS App2Container(A2C) is a robust command-line tool that assists users in lifting and shifting their on-premises […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yleisradio enhances digital services with Amazon EKS and IPv6 Adoption]]></title>
        <id>94c09e9e264ea0f58ded29d7f22edf19a693faf4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/yleisradio-enhances-digital-services-with-amazon-eks-and-ipv6-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yleisradio is a Finnish broadcasting company running most of its online and mobile services – which roughly 2.1 million Finns use every day – on AWS. Like many organizations, they use IP Address Management (IPAM) systems to allocate IP addresses across their AWS environment to make sure routing works, even between AWS and their on-premises […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Asuja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Getir optimized their Amazon EKS compute using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>c830c70b5a62c96358f60beae8c9ec9b409b72ff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-getir-optimized-their-amazon-eks-compute-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Getir is the pioneer of ultrafast grocery delivery. Getir was founded in 2015 and revolutionized last-mile delivery with its grocery in-minutes delivery proposition. Today, Getir is a conglomerate incorporating nine verticals under the same brand. Challenge Getir uses Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) to host applications on AWS. One of the foremost challenges […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tunahan Yediel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Mithra, Amazon Titan Image Generator v2, AWS GenAI Lofts, and more (August 12, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3760f7c717826e880f11a584dc886851e903659a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-mithra-amazon-titan-image-generator-v2-aws-genai-lofts-and-more-august-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Dr. Swami Sivasubramanian, VP of AI and Data, was an intern at Amazon in 2005, Dr. Werner Vogels, CTO of Amazon, was his first manager. Nineteen years later, the two shared a stage at the VivaTech Conference to reflect on Amazon’s history of innovation—from pioneering the pay-as-you-go model with Amazon Web Services (AWS) to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bkraz in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41226460</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41226460"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a longtime YouTube creator who uses Patreon for financial support, the news is terrible: Patreon informed me that all creators must switch to a monthly subscription schedule instead of the per-creation schedule that I and many other currently use. The whole point of per-creation is that it allows me to take time off, and only charge people when I release something, thus incentivizing me, and being fair to my supporters. I'm really annoyed by this change, and will start pushing back, but if it happens as planned, I may be forced to switch to another platform, or come up with some other solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bkraz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whywhywhywhy in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225827</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225827"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world where Apple is just completely fine with Apple users paying $13 instead of $10 for a subscription if they do it through an app is an interesting one.
Obviously this makes a lot of money for them but when you think about it they must think very little of their customers treating them with disrespect like this. This is how 'Tim Cook's Apple' should be remembered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whywhywhywhy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jprete in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225668</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225668"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember reading that per-creation billing is a very important feature for Patreon creators, because it removes the moral obligation to produce content just to justify a subscription.
If Patreon really doesn't want to kill the feature itself, but is just responding to Apple's enforcement, then it seems like a really clear illustration of monopoly power - pushing unrelated markets to change their own structure and products just to fit Apple's preferred billing flow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jprete</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i miss who i used to be]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/i-miss-who-i-used-to-be/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/i-miss-who-i-used-to-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some people reminisce about their exes when they hear sad, wistful songs. I reminisce about who I used to be (in a gifted kid burnout way, not a narcissistic way). The ghost of Valentine past, if you will.
I'm listening to NIKI's new album Buzz while working on my planned projects for one of my college organizations. It's taking me right back to high school, when I was stepping into my very first "real" leadership position in an executive committee.
Isn't it funny how things that were so serious to you get so much less so over time? I remember tripping over my words that day, feeling the heat crawl up my neck and ears when it was my turn to speak. Little fifteen-year-old me, surrounded by older girls I looked up to. I wanted so badly to impress them. When our director messaged me after the meeting to tell me I did great, I sagged with relief.
Now that I'm older than she was back then, I see how I must've looked to her: just a girl trying so hard to seem like she had it all under control. She must've known how important her encouragement was to me.
I loved what I did there. I stayed until I graduated high school. But when I started college, I wanted to leave it all behind me. I was tired and burned out, and it didn't seem like it having extracurriculars would help. Whether it was good instinct or a self-fulfilling prophecy, I was right. I changed in a bad way. I messed up everything I touched.
I've come a long way now from my disastrous freshman year. I've pulled up my grades. I've made a few good friends. My extracurriculars are starting to look up again—the entire catalyst of this post was the project presentation I was putting together. But I can't help it. I still miss who I used to be before all this, even though I know it's just my memories polishing themselves brighter than they really were. Nostalgia really is one hell of a drug.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deirdre McCloskey’s shallow and misleading rhetoric]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45535</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/12/deirdre-mccloskeys-shallow-and-misleading-rhetoric/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll This is not new to most of you of course. You are already steeped in McCloskey’s Rhetoric. Or you ought to be. After all economists are simply telling stories about the economy. Sometimes we are taken in. Sometimes we are not. Unfortunately McCloskey herself gets a little too caught up in her […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Effect of AI Adoption on Jobs: Evidence from US Commuting Zones]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276569</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-effect-of-ai-adoption-on-jobs-evidence-from-us-commuting-zones.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T13:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using data across US commuting zones over the period 2000-2020, this column presents evidence that AI adoption has reduced employment, except in high-paying occupations and those requiring a degree in STEM disciplines]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing Threat Intelligence: JA4 fingerprints and inter-request signals]]></title>
        <id>667deb80a4598c000bd706b4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ja4-signals"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T13:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Cloudflare's JA4 fingerprinting and inter-request signals provide robust and scalable insights for advanced web security and threat detection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reallocating Liquidity to Resolve a Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30992</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/reallocating-liquidity-to-resolve-a-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) in March 2023, a consortium of eleven large U.S. financial institutions deposited $30 billion into First Republic Bank to bolster its liquidity and assuage panic among uninsured depositors. In the end, however, First Republic Bank did not survive, raising the question of whether a reallocation of liquidity among financial institutions can ever reduce the need for central bank balance sheet expansion in the fight against bank runs. We explore this question in this post, based on a recent working paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kinda Hachem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276559</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our forward-looking daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lina Khan’s FTC Gears Up to Go After Algorithmic Black Boxes Governing Workers’ Lives, but It Might Be Running Out of Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276547</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/lina-khans-ftc-gears-up-to-go-after-algorithmic-black-boxes-governing-workers-lives-but-it-might-be-running-out-of-time.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A closer look at “algorithmic wage discrimination” used at gig companies (and increasingly across all industries), one potential tool to stop it, and how the FTC is zeroing in on the practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forty Percent of Biden IRA Manufacturing Projects Behind Schedule or Paused]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276552</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/forty-percent-of-biden-ira-manufacturing-projects-behind-schedule-or-paused.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T09:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new study by the Financial Times on the early results from Biden Administration IRA spending raises as many questions as it answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lewis Lapham, a Prince of American Letters and Traitor to His Class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330605</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/lewis-lapham-a-prince-of-american-letters-and-traitor-to-his-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T06:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lewis Lapham, who passed away at 89 last month, was a prince of American letters. To say that Lapham was well put together would be an understatement.  Lapham's prose was as elegant and sharply cut as his bespoke City of London suits. Like Twain, he was a quintessential American specimen, a distinctly New World literary product grounded in centuries of Old World cultivation. More
The post Lewis Lapham, a Prince of American Letters and Traitor to His Class appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Medish</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Spy Bases: Rumors, Speculation and Bad Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330544</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/china-spy-bases-rumors-speculation-and-bad-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest iteration of the “China spy base” story was revived last month when the Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS), a prominent D.C. think tank, released a report entitled “Secret Signals: Decoding China’s Intelligence Activities in Cuba.” The report was created by CSIS’s Hidden Reach program, which focuses on revealing China’s influence around the world. More
The post China Spy Bases: Rumors, Speculation and Bad Analysis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Lindsay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boiling The Judicial Frog]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330600</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/boiling-the-judicial-frog/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us have heard the story about boiling the frog.  Drop a frog in boiling water, and he’ll jump right out. But, drop the frog in cool water, and then increase the temperature of the water slowly, and the frog won’t notice.  Soon he’ll be cooked. That’s exactly what is happening to state courts around the  More
The post Boiling The Judicial Frog appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James C. Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AUKUS Revamped: The Complete Militarisation of Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330598</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/aukus-revamped-the-complete-militarisation-of-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is much to loathe about the AUKUS security agreement between Canberra, Washington and London.  Of the three conspirators against stability in the Indo and Asia Pacific, one stands out as the shouldering platform, the sustaining force, the political and military stuffing.  But Australian propagandists and proselytisers of the US credo of power prefer to see it  More
The post AUKUS Revamped: The Complete Militarisation of Australia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Media Coverage of Venezuela’s Presidential Election Normalizes US Interference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330602</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/media-coverage-of-venezuelas-presidential-election-normalizes-us-interference/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate media’s coverage of Venezuela’s July 28 presidential election is akin to an investigation of a homicide that is focused not with identifying the murderer but with an unpaid parking ticket of the victim. Likewise, the media has shifted the narrative into the minutia of electoral procedures, ignoring the much larger issue of US interference in  More
The post Media Coverage of Venezuela’s Presidential Election Normalizes US Interference  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger D. Harris and Peter Bolton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De-escalation vs Self-defense: Double Standards or Racism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330516</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/de-escalation-vs-self-defense-double-standards-or-racism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the evening of July 30, an Israeli drone targeted a residential building in South Beirut, killing a woman and two children, and injuring 74 civilians. Israel claimed the attack was aimed at an officer of the Lebanese resistance. Targeting residential infrastructures outside a war zone is part of the Israeli army’s Artificial Intelligence (AI)  More
The post De-escalation vs Self-defense: Double Standards or Racism? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criticism of Gaza Genocide is off of the Table]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330541</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/criticism-of-gaza-genocide-is-off-of-the-table/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The media blitz in favor of first Kamala Harris, and then Tim Walz, has been deafening. From someone growing up in the 1950s and early 1960s, it was like finding the toy in a box of Crackerjacks, or the gum that came along with some loaves of sliced bread. The “gifts” that came along with  More
The post Criticism of Gaza Genocide is off of the Table appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is a Crime?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330514</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/what-is-a-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As another anniversary of Hiroshima and Nagasaki passes and the survivors dwindle down, have we come any closer to moving beyond the nuclear age? No we have not. The risk of these weapons being used again against civilians is greater than ever. Former FBI Director Robert Mueller gave a speech in 2011 where he asserted  More
The post What Is a Crime? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Winslow Myers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time Farce, Second Time Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330629</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/first-time-farce-second-time-dangerous/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When the Clock Broke: Con Men, Conspiracists, and How America Cracked Up in the Early 1990s.” My reading has gotten ahead of my ability (mostly not having the spare time) to write proper book reviews, so I was going to write a few posts plugging a couple of books. I really liked John Ganz’s “When  More
The post First Time Farce, Second Time Dangerous appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025: Authoritarian Rule and Foreign Policy Mayhem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330592</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/12/project-2025-authoritarian-rule-and-foreign-policy-mayhem/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T05:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Far-Right Conspiracy in the Open Project 2025, the far-right’s ambitious policy planning guide published as Mandate for Leadership, is designed to dismantle the “Deep State” and install a president and proven loyalists who will carry out Donald Trump’s authoritarian agenda. Now the Project supposedly is no more—but not really. Trump’s campaign, concerned about the bad  More
The post Project 2025: Authoritarian Rule and Foreign Policy Mayhem appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Myanmar Mess]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276522</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-myanmar-mess.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T04:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those of you, like me, who have grievous little understanding of Myanmar, this presentation provides a history, particularly of British misrule and the major ethnic groups, discusses the interests and actions of the major powers, and reviews the recent fighting and the prospects for Myanmar. The look of this video is a bit homespun, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The internet is different now]]></title>
        <id>https://reedybear.bearblog.dev/the-internet-is-different-now/</id>
        <link href="https://reedybear.bearblog.dev/the-internet-is-different-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T04:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was born in the early 1990s. I got my first computer when I was, maybe, 6-8 years old.
I wasn't online much until my teens. I enjoyed yahoo pool, AOL Instant Messenger (AIM) among other chats.
I killed time on 4chan, Stumbled Upon (i.e. StumbleUpon.com) many random websites (incredibox; some mood-based music player;idr what else), and had an early MySpace account.
MySpace was configurable - custom CSS & even HTML if I remember correctly. We'd list our Top Friends (this was an AWFUL feature that never should have existed) and stressed about where we'd be on our friends' lists. (I would anyway)
Digg.com was a love of mine. Things felt different.
I've had a Facebook since sophomore year high school, and I'm in my early 30s now. It changed from a little place to share stuff with my friends. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mild case of the sunday scaries]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/mild-case-of-the-sunday-scaries/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/mild-case-of-the-sunday-scaries/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T02:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's Sunday night. I finished East of Eden (what a book!) and am now sitting on the couch thinking about going into the office tomorrow.
While introducing myself in a meeting last week I caught myself saying that I'd only been working for a month. In reality I've just hit the 2 month mark this week. It feels unreal that time has passed so quickly; looking back the days are a blur. Los días pasan volando.
Some of the new job luster is starting to fade from this role (as it has with teaching as well). There is still much I'm grateful for: a boss I can talk to, helpful coworkers, hybrid flexibility, a nice office a short commute away. But once I look past those (as one does with time) I find different questions staring me in the face. Is this it? What's next?
I've never had to face these ques…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Feature Gates to Client-Go: Enhancing Flexibility and Control]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/12/feature-gates-in-client-go/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/12/feature-gates-in-client-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes components use on-off switches called feature gates to manage the risk of adding a new feature.
The feature gate mechanism is what enables incremental graduation of a feature through the stages Alpha, Beta, and GA.
Kubernetes components, such as kube-controller-manager and kube-scheduler, use the client-go library to interact with the API.
The same library is used across the Kubernetes ecosystem to build controllers, tools, webhooks, and more. client-go now includes
its own feature gating mechanism, giving developers and cluster administrators more control over how they adopt client features.
To learn more about feature gates in Kubernetes, visit Feature Gates.
Motivation
In the absence of client-go feature gates, each new feature separated feature availability from enablement i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark and Evette Moran Nib Literary Nib Award 2024 longlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8264</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mark-evette-moran-nib-literary-nib-award-2024-longlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seventeen books have been included on the recently announced Mark and Evette Moran Nib Literary Nib Award 2024 longlist. Also known as the “Nib”, the literary award celebrates excellence in Australian literary research, and as such works of any genre, including fiction, non-fiction, and autobiography, are eligible for inclusion. A Very Secret Trade, by Cassandra […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing about Kissing by Kathryn Lomer wins 2024 Furphy literary award]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8259</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/nothing-about-kissing-kathryn-lomer-wins-2024-literary-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T20:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hobart based Australian poet, and young adult writer, Kathryn Lomer, has been named winner of the 2024 Furphy literary award for short stories, with her work Nothing about Kissing (PDF). Set in Tasmania’s Museum of Old and New Art (Mona), also in Hobart, Nothing about Kissing, is the story of an unnamed museum cleaner, who’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mask Bans Slowly Spread [cough, cough] in States and Localities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276523</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/mask-bans-slowly-spread-cough-cough-in-states-and-localities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T20:25:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mask bans passed in North Carolina and Nassau County, NY; mask bans considered in New York State, Chicago, IL, and Los Angeles, CA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by addicted in "CrowdStrike accepting the PwnieAwards for "most epic fail" at defcon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41218426</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41218426"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T18:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only reason this could be funny is because the software industry has found a way to excuse itself from any liability.
There is no other industry where someone could cause so much damage and laugh about it. Least of all because the liability itself would have led to its collapse.
Can you imagine a company hired to reinforce a bridge to protect it from damage from a ship instead causes its collapse.
How long is that company gonna last? Even if no one dies or is injured it will be run out of business.
Only in Tech can such a company not only survive but laugh about it.
And that’s even before we get to how amateurish the mistake these guys made was.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>addicted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[small but certain happiness - vintage camera!]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/small-but-certain-happiness-vintage-camera/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/small-but-certain-happiness-vintage-camera/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I have garnered a strange fascination with cameras, particularly those with a vintage, grainy feel to their lens. I've been on a hunt for an old vintage camera, in antique marketplaces and local online stores. I thought I would experiment with something relatively affordable, belonging to a previous owner, test the waters, then upgrade to another camera.
After futile searches, I finally obtained a vintage camera of a Fujifilm Z200fd model, whose previous owner purchased almost 15 years ago. I have been carrying it with me all the time, crossbody in a small, black pouch. In a way, the act makes me feel like a real photographer.

There is something indubitably alluring about the tangible nature of film photography that our contemporary phones simply cannot capture. I was thinking about this today - where did my interest abruptly surge from? I realized I was seeking change from the clinically ideal picture of the modern phone, the high resolution perfection.
Maybe this is a hobby I am merely dabbling with, but I think film photography is a medium that invites a slower, more intentional approach, offering me an emotional connection through their grainy lens and lower resolution pictures.
My camera has also given me motivation to leave the house. My depression makes me spend too much time inside, makes my days blur into one, that sometimes I can't identify one day from another. This week, I decided I would spend more time outside to capture the beauty of this world through my Fujifilm. I look forward to sharing some pictures in the future, along with my notes and observations from my adventures with you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh : Who is Muhammad Yunus, the new prime minister ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-Who-is-Muhammad-Yunus-the-new-primer-minister</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-Who-is-Muhammad-Yunus-the-new-primer-minister"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM welcomes the departure of Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina as a victory for the courageous student movement, which has been in July-August 2024 the victim of a terrible repression that left over 400 people dead. Nevertheless, given the social and economic orientation of the new Prime Minister, Muhammad Yunus, we can only fear that the neo-liberal capitalist extractivist export model will continue and that the debt system will also continue. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Bangladesh, 
Capitalism, 
South, 
Microcredit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM, Denise Comanne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/silent-sunday/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/silent-sunday/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things I've seen around Mastodon is the concept of Silent Sundays on... Sundays. I've never participated in it and don't really know the history behind it. I have noticed that most people post a simple photo that projects a peaceful vibe, and for the most part... silent.
The past couple of days was a lot of socializing due to a friend staying with us. My social battery is a bit depleted, so for today, I will also practice some sort of Silent Sunday.
Anyways, here you go. A photo from yesterday for #SilentSunday. Context later.

Taken with the CampSnap Camera.
Not my usual type of post, but I kind of like it. Until tomorrow.
11/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Interests]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/importance-interests/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/importance-interests/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T14:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the weekend, I sat and fiddled with a new theme for Bear blog.
I'm not a professional designer and have no ambition to become one. I just think it's very fun and interesting to tinker with. Time slips away in an almost meditative state as small snippets of text magically transform the canvas.
Regardless of what we like or do for work, I think it's extremely important to have personal interests. Unfortunately, these are often the first things to go when we're struggling.
I've been in the darkest of places myself. One by one, I abandoned my interests. Not because I'd lost interest, but because I thought it would fix what was broken.
A fruitless attempt, of course, to try to fix the inside by messing with the outside. A downward spiral that accelerated into the bottomless depths with each interest I let go. In the end, they were all gone – and I felt worse than ever.
Fortunately, I got the help I needed. Slowly but surely, I began to climb out of the grave I'd dug for myself. As time passed, I started to reintroduce my interests, slowly and cautiously: designing, photography, movies…
It wasn’t a quick fix, that’s for sure, and not the only change I had to make. But things were heading in the right direction.
Now I feel better than in a long, long time –although it’s still like being on a crab fishing boat on the Bering Sea, not knowing when the next storm will hit.
If it weren't for rediscovering my love of my interests and letting them illuminate my life, I'd still be lost in the dark. My interests are lighthouses on the rough sea of life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grandizo Munis - Unions Against Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/grandizo-munis-unions-against-revolution?v=1723388029</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/grandizo-munis-unions-against-revolution?v=1723388029"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T14:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Grandizo Munis
Title: Unions Against Revolution
Date: 1960
Notes: Unions Against Revolution is a translation of a work by G. Munis written in 1960 and reprinted in France after the events of May 1968. The English version appearing here is from Internationalism No. 3. Black and Red, Detroit
Source: Retrieved on August 11, 2024 from Black and Red Press PDF

 No contradiction can exist between the economic and the political aspects of a revolutionary conception, even supposing the clearest organic and functional demarcation between them. The same is true for any reactionary conception. Hence the present interpenetration, the agreement and collaboration between unions—economic organs —and political parties—ideological organs—gives us the key to understanding both, from whichever side o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by erlend_sh in "Verso – Web browser built on top of the Servo web engine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41216030</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41216030"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In other exciting Servo-browser news, Servo and Redox OS have submitted a joint proposal to fund the porting of SpiderMonkey and WebRender to Redox: https://www.redox-os.org/news/this-month-240731/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>erlend_sh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[write for no one but yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/write-for-no-one-but-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/write-for-no-one-but-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You should write for no one but yourself.
I came to this thought the more posts I write. The fact that I'm writing for my own enjoyment rather than to show anyone makes it so rewarding and satisfying because I don't have to deal with any pressures or expectations from others. It's not some technical documentation that has to be comprehensible or an academic thesis that needs to be written to the highest degree. It's my blog, and I can write whatever I want. It's so freeing to just let my mind flow across the page and have my consciousness translated into intelligible language.
I write to write, whether it's about a topic I'm interested in or a post or quote that I found cool and wanted to share. All my writings are simply words on a page that have originated from my imagination. Writing is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by smallstepforman in "Firefox Browser Ported to HaikuOS"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41215573</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41215573"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T11:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some history about Firefox and BeOS. Before Firefox, there was Mozilla, which had a BeOS port (called Bezilla). Bezilla was bloated and slow. So the BeOS community tried to make a stripped version of Mozilla with only the browser (minus all the bloat). This project became an inspiration to do the same for Mozilla, and that product became Firebug (or something similar - edit phoenix, then firebird), which due to trademark conflicts got renamed to Firefox that we all know today. So in a round-a-bout way, we have come full circle after 20 years, Firefox is finally ported to the platform that inspired its creation.
Kind of poetic. We should write a 3-5-3 Haiku about this journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smallstepforman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276512</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tentacular daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Between Optimism and Despair: The Messy Middle Paths Through Climate Breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276519</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/between-optimism-and-despair-the-messy-middle-paths-through-climate-breakdown.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mindset at the root of the ecological crisis will continue to drive destructive patterns, until we are forced to confront it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Cranes]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52970</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/11/sunday-photoblogging-cranes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Transfer Agreement: Nazi Support for a Jewish State in Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330264</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/11/the-transfer-agreement-nazi-support-for-a-jewish-state-in-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T06:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Karsten Winegeart.
From 1933 to 1939, Hitler provided the future government of Israel with the assets of German Jews in exchange for aid undermining an international anti-Nazi boycott.
On March 19, 1933 — less than three months after Adolph Hitler had been elected chancellor of Germany — flags of the reigning National Socialist German Workers’ Party bearing black swastikas against blood-red fields were unfurled from the German consulates in Jerusalem and Jaffa, both then part of British-controlled Palestine. Already aware of the Nazi’s rabid anti-Semitism, the residents of nearby Tel Aviv, one of the relatively few Jewish settlements in Palestine at the time, prepared to tear down and burn the swastikas. But before they could storm the consulates, the erstwhile anti-fascists were halted by a combination of forces: the colonial authorities of the British, who were still in the mode of appeasing Hitler, and more surprisingly, the leadership of the Zionist movement, which sought a Jewish state in Palestine. While the British were fearful of igniting what would inevitably become World War II, the Zionists looked to preserve their own organizing and fundraising activities in Germany, then home to more than half a million Jews.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Transfer Agreement: Nazi Support for a Jewish State in Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Soul of Detroit, 1985]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330536</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/11/the-soul-of-detroit-1985/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T05:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing Donald Trump aggress top Black journalists at the National Association of Black Journalists (NABJ) made for uncomfortable viewing. The gasps of disgust, even from Harris Faulkner, were unsurprising. Trump’s unskilled wordplay actually reminded me of a cab ride made in Detroit just under forty years ago, including the redeeming nature of what happened afterwards. […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Soul of Detroit, 1985 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roderick McMillan - Can Stoicism Be Reconciled With Anarchy?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/roderick-mcmillan-how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with-anarchy?v=1723312426</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/roderick-mcmillan-how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with-anarchy?v=1723312426"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roderick McMillan
Title: Can Stoicism Be Reconciled With Anarchy?
Subtitle: A comparative examination of Anarcho-Stoicism
Date: 10th August 2024
Source: Retrieved on August 10, 2024 from https://morewretchthansage.substack.com/p/how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with

How can Stoicism, a philosophy that has largely come down to us from the hierarchical, centralised, statist, Roman Empire and whose most famous adherent was an absolute Monarch, be reconciled with Anarchy?
 At first consideration Anarchy and Stoicism seem unlikely bedfellows. Much of Stoicism has come down to us through the Roman' Late Stoa' of Seneca, Epictetus, and Marcus Aurelius. Seneca was a Billionaire slave-owner politician, and Marcus Aurelius was an absolute monarch… but Epictetus was a disabled enslaved person,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Torture Archipelago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330434</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/10/israels-torture-archipelago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For about the 30th time since last October, we’re being asked to believe that Biden has reached his limit with Netanhayu. Two spoke by phone last week, after Israel’s dual assassination strikes in Beirut and Tehran. Supposedly Biden said during the call that the assassination of Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh in Iran was “poorly timed,” […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Israel’s Torture Archipelago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem with Pronatalism: Pushing Baby Booms to Boost Economic Growth Amounts to a Ponzi Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276504</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-problem-with-pronatalism-pushing-baby-booms-to-boost-economic-growth-amounts-to-a-ponzi-scheme.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schemes to boost birth rates to bolster growth are generally ineffective and more important, miss the real problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Hangover]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/social-hangover/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/social-hangover/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["We are all different" – a phrase thrown around quite often. And thankfully, it's true. Some adore winter, others summer; some thrive in nature, while others prefer the city.
But there's one area where this diversity seems absent: socializing.
The first to leave a party is branded a bore. Anyone declining a gathering is deemed a weirdo. Going to the movies alone marks you as strange.
Why is this? Why does socializing always trump solitude? It's as if loneliness is automatically equated with something being wrong.
There's a lot of talk about the importance of online privacy, but when it comes to wanting some privacy in the physical world, it's a different story. We're expected to be "online" by default, 24/7. If we go "offline," it's treated as a malfunction — a 404 page.
People often tell me I'm a social person. Sure, I enjoy listening to others, asking questions, and reflecting on their experiences in light of my own. But it comes with a price...
After two or three hours, I'm exhausted. I experience a "social hangover." Everyone seems to be talking endlessly about nothing, as if there's a collective fear of silence and stillness.
Why is solitude taboo?
I don't have the answers, but I've gotten better at announcing my early departure. It still feels odd to do so, and occasionally, I'm met with confusion. But honestly, I don't care — I'm too old for that, and it feels incredibly liberating.
Mentions
Flips]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicola Gai - Declaration at the trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nicola-gai-declaration-at-the-trial?v=1723294215</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nicola-gai-declaration-at-the-trial?v=1723294215"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T12:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nicola Gai
Title: Declaration at the trial
Date: November 11, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15519>. Retrieved on 19/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Declaration at the trial (October 30 2013) for the wounding of Ansaldo Nucleare managing director Roberto Adinolfi
 ‘Nobody can judge me 
 Not even you 
 The truth hurts you, I know.’ 
 C. Caselli 
 A few words to make a few simple points before the ‘truth’ is pronounced by the court; just in case it’s not clear, I am using the word ‘truth’ ironically as I don’t recognize any tribunal other than my own conscience. The only ones responsible for what happened in Genoa on May 7 2012 are Alfredo and myself. None of our friends or comrades knew what we were planning and then carried out. No matter how far you dig into our lives and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mistercow in "A wonderful coincidence or an expected connection: why π² ≈ g"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41209068</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41209068"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T12:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is interesting, but I have to quibble with this:
> If you express this value in any other units, the magic immediately disappears. So, this is no coincidence
Ordinarily, this would be extremely indicative of a coincidence. If you’re looking for a heuristic for non-coincidences, “sticks around when you change units” is the one you want. This is just an unusual case where that heuristic fails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mistercow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fascist violence and the imaginative failure of the Labour government]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52963</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/10/fascist-violence-and-the-imaginative-failure-of-the-labour-government/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T07:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often on a Friday evening, we order a curry from our local “Indian” takeaway. They deliver, but it is easier and quicker for me to walk round and collect, and, anyway, I enjoy chatting to the guy behind the counter. He’s a Man United fan, I’m Liverpool, so we have some banter with a bit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lchengify in "Susan Wojcicki has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207918</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207918"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T07:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was shocked to hear this news. I worked for Google years ago but I was in the NYC office, so we didn't run into the YouTube folks much.
Opinions about YouTube may be mixed here on HN, but it is objectively one of the most successful businesses in tech or media to emerge in the past 15 years. If it weren't buried inside Alphabet, Youtube would be worth on the order of $400 billion, more than Disney and Comcast combined. It's a weird mix of a huge creator monetization network, a music channel, an education platform, a forever-store of niche content, and a utility.
It's also not a business that rested on it's laurels. It's easy to forget how novel creator monetization was when YouTube adopted it. They do a lot of active work to manage their creators, and now have grown into a music and podcast platform that is challenging Apple. To top it off, YouTube TV, despite costing just as much as cable, is objectively a good product.
Few products have the brand, the reach, monetization, and the endurance that YouTube has had within Google. And I know for a fact that this is in no small part due to the way it was managed.
I've probably watched tens of thousands of hours of YouTube at this point. Some of it sublime, some of it absurd, some of it critical for my work or my degree. I couldn't imagine a world without it.
RIP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lchengify</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yyyfb in "Susan Wojcicki has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207776</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207776"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T06:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next time you're thinking "I wish I was the one who had made a billion dollars with my startup idea", remember that only health and family matter, and to have fun while you're alive. RIP.
Edit: some people misinterpreted my comment. I'm just one anonymous  voice on the Internet, but am deeply saddened by the passing of Susan Wojcicki, who meant a lot to me as one of the many people who crossed paths with her professionally. I wish her family strength in a very trying moment. She did not deserve this. I've not met another business leader demonstrate everyday kindness to the degree that she did.
Her untimely passing is also a reminder to those of us who sometimes look up to such successful businesspeople that we should all appreciate our luck to be alive and enjoy it to the fullest, as I hope that she did as well, and as I'm sure that she'd prefer we did. RIP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yyyfb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus - A Letter to the Libertarian Left]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left?v=1723265632</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left?v=1723265632"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus
Title: A Letter to the Libertarian Left
Date: 8/8/2024
Source: Retrieved on 8/8/2024 from https://dsa-lsc.org/2024/08/08/a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left/

 “The idea is like grass. It craves light, likes crowds, thrives on crossbreeding, grows better for being stepped on.” 
 - The Dispossessed, Ursula K. Le Guin 
 We in the Libertarian Socialist Caucus (LSC) of the Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) recognize that our formation has dual obligations, both to the development of the socialist movement in the United States and to the broader libertarian socialist movement that exists outside of DSA. While much of our caucus’ focus thus far has been on DSA’s internal politics, we believe in cross-pollination with the broader libertarian left via an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gorgoiler in "Rivian reduced electrical wiring by 1.6 miles and 44 pounds"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207331"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The before/after ECU layout diagram is very instructional.
I like to imagine some kind of engineering “meet cute” whereby, one random day, the headlights engineer and the parking radar engineer happen to be working on the front of the car together.  Their eyes meet:
“hey, I’m John — I didn’t know you had an ECU here!”,
“hi, I’m Claire — wow, you have an ECU right up front too?  It’s, like, right next to mine and we never knew!”
“I know, crazy right?!  Hey this is going to sound really forward and I don’t normally do this but I’m only running at 70% compute capacity.  I don’t suppose you need any real-time budget this evening?”
“So funny you should ask, I was just about to run a whole bunch of heavy new wiring to…”
And in a story as old as time they get ECU married and raise their control loops in the same front-of-vehicle ECU together instead of living their separate, lonely, ECU-right-next-to-each-other-and-they-didn’t-know-it lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gorgoiler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oefrha in "Building a highly-available web service without a database"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207172</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207172"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T03:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seems weird to start with “not talking about using something like SQLite where your data is still serialized”, then end up with a home grown transaction log that requires serialization and needs to be replicated, which is how databases are replicated anyway.
If your load fits entirely on one server, then just run the database on that damn server and forget about “special architectures to reduce round-trips to your database”. If your data fits entirely in RAM, then use a ramdisk for the database if you want, and replicate it to permanent storage with standard tools. Now that’s actually simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oefrha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asveikau in "Daily marijuana use linked to increased risk of deadly head and neck cancers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41206823</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41206823"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T02:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People tend to get defensive at even the most vague insinuation that cannabis may have potential negative health effects. Comment section already has evidence of this.
Edit just to clarify: I'm generally in favor of legalization and I don't believe in restricting responsible use by adults. I've just noticed really strong reactions to this kind of discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asveikau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BessS in "Jake Seliger has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41206550</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41206550"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T00:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,
This is Bess, Jake's wife. I just want to say how deeply touched I am to see how much Jake and his writing are appreciated here on HN. The intellectual online community which made up a big piece of his life for so long was important to him, as was having a positive influence on others, and it would have meant so much to him- as it does to me- to see the impact he made. Thank you for the people who reached out while he was still alive to make sure he knew just how large that impact was.
I've lost the love of my life, as well as my thinking and writing partner, and everything is strange and disorienting right now. It's a comfort when nothing feels comfortable to know how appreciated he was and still is. As soon as I'm able, and for anyone who is interested in joining the efforts, I promised him I'd continue the push for FDA reform, and to try to find ways to improve agency for cancer patients so that other people in his position might suffer less than he did. I've never known a braver person. I'll miss him forever, but won't stop trying to keep his legacy alive.
Please feel free to reach out anytime (I'm at drbstillman@gmail.com). Thank you also for all the well wishes for myself and Athena, who I hope will be just like her Dad.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BessS</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Jewish Artists for Palestine: Sophia Sobko and Steph Kudisch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330467</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/california-jewish-artists-for-palestine-sophia-sobko-and-steph-kudisch/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T22:41:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Rebecca Maria Goldschmidt talks with fellow members of California Jewish Artists for Palestine Sophia Sobko and Steph Kudisch, about their collective decision to submit and withdraw explicitly anti-Zionist artworks to an open call for Jewish artists at the Contemporary Jewish Museum in San Francisco. They discuss the process of pulling their works out of the exhibition; the importance of the academic and cultural boycott of Israel (PACBI); and what it means to be Jewish artists publicly confronting Jewish arts institutions that receive Zionist funding and are struggling to address the ongoing genocide of the Palestinian people.
Steph Kudisch is a trans genderfluid artist whose work uses mutated intertidal aesthetics and personal storytelling to dwell in in-betweens. They work as a teaching artist on Lisjan Ohlone land, also known as the San Francisco Bay Area. Kudisch and their collaborator Kate Laster form Clear as Schmutz Press as well as the collective Hevra Kadisha in which they create site-specific works across the mediums of printmaking, sculpture, performance, and sound.
Sophia Sobko (she/they) is an artist, educator & researcher born in Moscow, USSR & based on Lisjan Ohlone Land in Oakland, CA. They are excited about collaborative learning, participatory art, and co-creating a more liberatory world. Sophia is founder/co-steward of two queer post-Soviet Jewish collectives: Kolektiv Goluboy Vagon and Krivoy Kolektiv.
Get in touch with CJAFP at cajewishartists4palestine[@]proton.me More
The post California Jewish Artists for Palestine: Sophia Sobko and Steph Kudisch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 8organicbits in ".INTERNAL is now reserved for private-use applications"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41205729</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41205729"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T22:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My biggest frustration with .internal is that it requires a private certificate authority. Lots of organizations struggle to fully set up trust for the private CA on all internal systems. When you add BYOD or contractor systems, it's a mess.
Using a publicly valid domain offers a number of benefits, like being able to use a free public CA like Lets Encrypt. Every machine will trust your internal certificates out of the box, so there is minimal toil.
Last year I built getlocalcert [1] as a free way to automate this approach. It allows you to register a subdomain, publish TXT records for ACME DNS certificate validation, and use your own internal DNS server for all private use.
[1] https://www.getlocalcert.net/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>8organicbits</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rseliger in "Jake Seliger has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41205326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41205326"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T20:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is Jake’s sister. He was reading and replying to as much as he could up until the end. He loved this community and would in turn be touched by this entire thread. Thank you all who supported him and read and shared his writing. He said it was bittersweet to go out on top.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rseliger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amateur Guide to Some BearBlog Extra Features]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/amateur-guide-to-some-bear-blog-extra-features/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/amateur-guide-to-some-bear-blog-extra-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amateur Guide to Some BearBlog Extra Features
I'm in no way a web designer, but i am curious about how folks get certain features to work on BearBlog, so I've done some reading and experimenting. Someone asked me to share what I've learned and I am always willing to do that.
Header
Under Settings>Header and Footer Directives > Header, I have some code copied from the website SearchMySite that allows my blog to be searchable in their IndyWeb search engine. It's not visible when you are looking at one of my blog posts.
Footer
Under Settings>Header and Footer Directives > Footer, I have links to:
Letterbird email form
A Gateway Theme page from Micro,blog listing where you can find me on all the socials, You can make a page like that on Gravatar.
My account on Mastodon
A free guestbook on Smar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dredmorbius in "Jake Seliger has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41203548</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41203548"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jake posted as jseliger on HN:  https://news.ycombinator.com/user?id=jseliger
He blogged at https://jakeseliger.com/>, and numerous of his blog articles were submitted to HN:  https://news.ycombinator.com/from?site=jakeseliger.com>.  That includes numerous topics, over the past year or so his experience with cancer, often concerning frustrations with the process and mechanism.
His essay on agenticness especially strikes me as hugely insightful and underappreciated.  It was submitted several times to HN but saw little discussion:
https://jakeseliger.com/2024/07/29/more-isnt-always-better-d...>
Jake's wife, now widow, Bess, blogs at Everything is an Emergency:  https://bessstillman.substack.com>.  That also details the cancer / caregiving experience, from the point of view of a wife, caregiver, expectant mother, and emergency-room doctor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dredmorbius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Community Echoes]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/implementing-community-echoes/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/implementing-community-echoes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been seeing a lot of Reply posts, or just posts in general with bloggers playing off of each other’s blog posts and think it’s absolutely fantastic.
During my Wordpress days, I took for granted the automatic pingbacks (is that still a thing?) when my post gets mentioned somewhere, and I know that Webmentions exist, but now I’m doing things a little bit more manual.
Earlier last month, around the time I posted To Blogroll, or to not?, I added a section at the bottom of my posts (when it applies) titled 💬 COMMUNITY ECHOES. In this section, I add posts I run across that is either a response to that post, or references the post in some way.
Some examples from my recent posts where you can see this section:
Video Games I've Owned and Played
The Plan to Not Have a Plan
When Every Day Feels the Same
Adding references to other posts that have been written on similar subjects allows readers to click through to see other people’s takes on that specific subject. I know that I personally enjoy reading other people’s blogs, and then finding a link to another blog that talks about the same thing, especially if it’s the same subject with a different (or same) perspective. It’s also (selfishly) nice for me to keep track of posts that mention mine for my own personal documentation.
I welcome you all to go down the rabbit hole of posts with me.
Also, if there is a blog post of yours where mine is referenced that I missed, feel free to let me know, so that I can add it.
Happy reading!
9/31 - Blaugust
💬 Community Echoes
by Forking Mad
Echoing the Community by Alexandra
Webnotes: a simple replacement for comments, pingbacks, and webmentions by rscottjones
#1 Changelog news by Bearly Significant
Sunday Review (08-11-24) by Brandon (WNDR)
Pingbacks, Webmentions, and IndieAuth on WordPress by kgadams
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Loved Your Post, but I Can’t Tell You That]]></title>
        <id>https://matanabudy.com/i-loved-your-post-but-i-cant-tell-you-that/</id>
        <link href="https://matanabudy.com/i-loved-your-post-but-i-cant-tell-you-that/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:29:09.223Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indie Web is a great place. Ever since I started writing on this website, I've received the most heartwarming reactions—from plain old emails to guestbook comments, and in some cases, even reply posts that can spark discussions in what might otherwise feel like posting into the void.
A reply post like this was RE: Why Are Shoes Treated Differently Than Shirts by Marisabel, which really made me think about stuff I wrote in my original post. I loved that! She mentioned me on Mastodon, and I thanked her for the reply, it really made my day back then.
Last week, I discovered another reply through the analytics page of my bear blog, which had a referrer I wasn’t familiar with—mgx. I visited the website and found a reply post to my bat incident! It had a short poem about it, which made me laugh and brightened my day, especially since I was feeling quite sick after the vaccine.
I wanted to thank mgx for the reply, but I couldn’t find a way to contact on the website. Obviously, not everyone wants to be approachable, and I understand that, but I still wanted to acknowledge the reply—so here we are!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how bearblog makes me a better writer]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/how-bearblog-makes-me-a-better-writer-new/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/how-bearblog-makes-me-a-better-writer-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T14:50:37.489Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe consistent Bearblogging has made me a better writer, but not in the way you might think. I don't mean it has drastically perked my English grammar or refined my sentence structure (though these have definitely been a bonus). Instead, it makes me write more, and, subjectively, that is my definition of a good writer: someone who writes.
Before Bearblog, I had a penchant for perfectionism with writing, which made me avoid it for years. For my first blogpost, I was rusty from the lack of practice, and I faced difficulty expressing my internal chaos of thoughts & ideas into coherent phrasing. I was practically forcing out words. That paid off, though, because regular Bearblogging has made my words come more naturally now. I easily phrase whatever crosses my mind, writing as I go along…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Clarity: Enhancing Code Understanding and Efficiency with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>f383bcb9ec048b73375bec51ac8752a5b1290f19</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/code-clarity-enhancing-code-understanding-and-efficiency-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“All code will become legacy”. This saying, widely recognized amongst software developers, highlights the reality of their day-to-day activities. While writing new code is an integral part of a developer’s role, a significant portion of their time is dedicated to refactoring and maintaining existing codebases. Developers typically encounter numerous challenges when attempting to understand and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jehu Gray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud 2024 Autumn MVP Application Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d29c26909580</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/alibaba-cloud-2024-autumn-mvp-application-now-open-d29c26909580?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T09:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest batch of Alibaba Cloud MVP applications is now open! Apply before 10 September, 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0xEF in "USPS text scammers duped his wife, so he hacked their operation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41199904</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41199904"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T08:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate that it kicks off with "DISCLAIMER: This is not my work. I would never and don't condone illegal hacking of scammers"
You know what? I do. We all should. These scammers are awful people and deserve to be attacked. I am tired of toothless authorities like CISA and the alphabet agencies in the US doing next to nothing about it unless some YouTube scam baiter does the work for them. Scammers destroy people, not just financially, but emotionally as well, even driving some victims to suicide. As far as I am concerned,  any wannabe hacker out there should be using these scammers for target practice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0xEF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building RAG Services on Compute Nest with Alibaba Cloud Model Studio and AnalyticDB for…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8f26bee20273</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/building-rag-services-on-compute-nest-with-alibaba-cloud-model-studio-and-analyticdb-for-8f26bee20273?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article guides the setting up of a RAG service using Alibaba Cloud Model Studio, Compute Nest, and AnalyticDB for PostgreSQL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mainstream Media’s Leading Warmonger: NYT Columnist Bret Stephens]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330380</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/mainstream-medias-leading-warmonger-nyt-columnist-bret-stephens/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times has always favored Israel in its editorial writings, but no Times’ columnist compares to Bret Stephens, whose writings are chauvinistic and bellicose.,  Stephens, a former editor of the Jerusalem Post and a supporter of all Israeli policies, left the Wall Street Journal to join the Times in 2017 because he believed Israel was not getting a fair hearing in the mainstream media.  In doing so, he joined other Jewish columnists at the Times (Thomas Friedman, David Brooks, Paul Krugman, and Roger Cohen).  However, these men brought some objectivity to America’s Israel problem.  Stephens has no limits in his support of Israel. More
The post Mainstream Media’s Leading Warmonger: NYT Columnist Bret Stephens appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism’s Unequal Distribution Deprives You of True Freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330270</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/capitalisms-unequal-distribution-deprives-you-of-true-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the French economist Thomas Piketty most recently exposed, capitalism, across time and space, has always tended to produce ever-greater economic inequality. Oxfam, a global charity, reported that 2022’s 10 richest men together had six times more wealth than the poorest 3.1 billion people on earth. The lack of democracy inside workplaces or enterprises is both a cause and an effect of capitalism’s unequal distribution of income and wealth. More
The post Capitalism’s Unequal Distribution Deprives You of True Freedom appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conscience of the Blues: How Howlin’ Wolf Got Caged in Oregon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/conscience-of-the-blues-how-howlin-wolf-got-caged-in-oregon/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From his locked room, Chester Burnett could hear the trains rattling up the tracks, one every half hour. They reminded him of home, back on Dockery Plantation, when he played on the porches of old shacks with Charley Patton, blowing his harmonica to the rhythm of those big wheels rolling along the rails. Those northbound  More
The post Conscience of the Blues: How Howlin’ Wolf Got Caged in Oregon appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Racism Shouldn’t Get a Pass in America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330245</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/israeli-racism-shouldnt-get-a-pass-in-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, 2023, blatantly racist statements by Israeli leaders have been widely reported. Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu likened Palestinians to Amalekites, an ancient tribe in Old Testament lore whom Yahweh told the Israelites to destroy—men, women, children, infants, and cattle. Israeli Defense Minister Yoav Gallant referred to Israel’s assault on Gaza as a fight against “human animals.” Other Israeli officials called for erasing Gaza from the face of the earth, claiming that no Palestinian civilians are innocent. More
The post Israeli Racism Shouldn’t Get a Pass in America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Schwalbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unfulfilled promises of microcredit: some new evidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-unfulfilled-promises-of-microcredit-some-new-evidence</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-unfulfilled-promises-of-microcredit-some-new-evidence"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The student movement in Bangladesh ousted Sheikh Hasina last Monday, August 5, 2024. A new interim government has been formed to restore order, end repression, and hold a fair election to facilitate a democratic transition of power. Nobel laureate Muhammad Yunus has been sworn in as the interim government's chief adviser, and many civil society activists and student leaders who have led the rebellion are included in the advisory group. There is a widespread hope that Prof. Yunus, the (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Bangladesh, 
Third World Debt, 
Private debt, 
Microcredit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM, Stéphanie Jacquemont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Gov. Tim Walz Failed the Indigenous-led Movement to Stop the Line 3 Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330353</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/how-gov-tim-walz-failed-indigenous-led-movement-to-stop-the-line-3-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Originally published August 16, 2021 in Rampant When we wrote this article in August 2021, many of us in the movement to stop Line 3 were hopeful that we might make the governor of Minnesota listen to our demands to respect treaty rights and recognize that building Line 3 would mean, in the words of  More
The post How Gov. Tim Walz Failed the Indigenous-led Movement to Stop the Line 3 Pipeline appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Medley - Erik Wallenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fossil-Fuelized Colonialism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330428</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/fossil-fuelized-colonialism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 9, 2001, in Colombia, riot police and private security forces from the Cerrejón coal mine — one of the largest open-pit coal mines in the world — surrounded the remote community of Tabaco. They then dragged residents out of their homes and bulldozed what remained of that town’s structures. There was, after all,  More
The post Fossil-Fuelized Colonialism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aviva Chomsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’s Delayed Coronation Streets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330416</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/harriss-delayed-coronation-streets/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe Donald Trump’s revelations to that colosseum of rapturous Christians were on point? Maybe we don’t need to vote after all? Maybe voting is so 1960s—when senators such as Robert Kennedy (the Camelot father, not the bear-dumping son) or Eugene McCarthy tried to turn out the vote by quoting from Aeschylus or George Bernard Shaw  More
The post Harris’s Delayed Coronation Streets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism on the Brink: The Gaza War Beyond Netanyahu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330336</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/zionism-on-the-brink-the-gaza-war-beyond-netanyahu/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea that the war on Gaza is essentially waged and sustained by and for Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has, for long, dominated political analyses on the subject. The notion is often kept alive by public opinion inside Israel. Most polls produced since the start of the Israeli genocide on Gaza suggest that an  More
The post Zionism on the Brink: The Gaza War Beyond Netanyahu  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enough of the Creepy Obsession with Fertility, Menstruation, Labia and Boobs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330284</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/enough-of-the-creepy-obsession-with-fertility-menstruation-labia-and-boobs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How’s that for a title? I’m guessing we just lost several men right there. That’s okay, for those of you still here—let’s discuss this incredibly disgusting obsession that men of the reactionary right seem to have in regard to the very normal and what should be mundane, workings and plumbing of the female body. We’ve  More
The post Enough of the Creepy Obsession with Fertility, Menstruation, Labia and Boobs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times has Identified Wall Street’s Most Dangerous Enemy: Billionaire-Backed Millionaire JD Vance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330154</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/the-new-york-times-has-identified-wall-streets-most-dangerous-enemy-billionaire-backed-millionaire-jd-vance/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea that the GOP has been taken over by radical anti-capitalists out to destroy the American Way of Life will surely come as a surprise to Trump backers such as Blackstone Group CEO Stephen Schwarzman, Shaun Maguire and Doug Leone of Sequoia Capital, venture capitalist David Sacks, who spoke at the convention two nights before Vance, and Elon Musk, who recently pledged to donate $45 million a month to a Super PAC that’s working to elect the former president. More
The post The New York Times has Identified Wall Street’s Most Dangerous Enemy: Billionaire-Backed Millionaire JD Vance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Silverstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Conundrums of Bangladeshi Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330247</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/the-conundrums-of-bangladeshi-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Monday, August 5, former Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina boarded a Bangladesh Air Force C-130J military transport in a hurry and fled to Hindon Air Force base, outside Delhi. Her plane was refueled and reports said that she intended to fly on either to the United Kingdom (her niece, Tulip Siddiq is a minister in  More
The post The Conundrums of Bangladeshi Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Supreme Court to the Homeless: Drop Dead!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330248</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/the-supreme-court-to-the-homeless-drop-dead/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So income from your three jobs won’t cover your rent increase. There are no beds at the shelter and public housing has a waiting list decades long. You buy a tent and sleeping bag and move into a town park. This would have worked until June 28, when the Supreme Court essentially ruled that municipalities  More
The post The Supreme Court to the Homeless: Drop Dead! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midwinter Antarctica 50°F Above Average]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330332</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/midwinter-antarctica-50f-above-average/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temperatures for the entire month of July in Antarctica were 50°F above average, but it also experienced days when temperatures spiked up to 82°F above average. Yes, Antarctica is the world’s deepfreeze, and it is the dead of winter. What does this portend? For starters, according to Michael Dukes, director of forecasting at MetDesk: “In  More
The post Midwinter Antarctica 50°F Above Average appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MAGA and the Fear of Being Eaten]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330414</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/maga-and-the-fear-of-being-eaten/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be a Trump Republican is to live in a horror film. Fears abound. The fear of immigrants, the fear of Woke (a euphemism for Black culture), a fear of books, a fear of cat ladies, a fear of being replaced, a fear of George Soros, and now Anthropophagophobia, the fear of being eaten. In  More
The post MAGA and the Fear of Being Eaten appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishmael Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK Riots: Racism And Islamophobia Meets Community Unity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330347</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/uk-riots-racism-and-islamophobia-meets-community-unity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The legacy left by the Conservatives after 14 years in government is not just economic stagnation, and the destruction of public services, it is social division, far right extremism and anger. Violence, racism and hate are the common language of far-right groups/individuals the world over, all of which has been writ large on the streets  More
The post UK Riots: Racism And Islamophobia Meets Community Unity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graham Peebles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mass Deportations Would be a Nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330377</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/09/mass-deportations-would-be-a-nightmare/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s an image that’s stayed with me for weeks: A sea of people holding up “Mass Deportation Now” signs at the Republican National Convention. Since then, I’ve been plagued with nightmares of mass raids by the military and police across the country. I see millions of families being torn apart, including families with citizen children.  More
The post Mass Deportations Would be a Nightmare appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alliyah Lusuegro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by chocolatkey in "USPS text scammers duped his wife, so he hacked their operation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41198724</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41198724"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T04:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the original posts themselves, probably more interesting to people here:
https://blog.smithsecurity.biz/hacking-the-scammers
https://blog.smithsecurity.biz/systematic-destruction-hackin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chocolatkey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cordial’s journey implementing Bottlerocket and Karpenter in Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>ac084886fb841ea3e723373170666aa3ce78fc34</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/cordials-journey-implementing-bottlerocket-and-karpenter-in-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T23:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Cordial is a cross-channel marketing platform that offers tools to fully automate marketing strategies. By automating marketing execution, Cordial liberates technology teams to focus on their core strengths: building and creativity. It empowers technology teams to delegate data access and management to marketers, using Cordial’s robust platform to migrate, transform, and deliver complex data […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Charan Teja Gopaluni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A review of Dan Davies’ book]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45530</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/08/a-review-of-dan-davies-book/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T21:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford – a critique of the absurdity of economics I finally read “The Accountability Machine”, the book by Dan Davies.  It’s worth the effort.  You can read it in a number of ways.  As a peon to cybernetics and Stafford Beer.  As a critique of the absurdity of economics.  As a summary of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jessetemp in "Do quests, not goals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41196363</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41196363"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T21:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think what’s going on behind the verbal sleight of hand here, is focusing on the process (quest) instead of the outcome (goal). It’s the difference between doing a thing and having done a thing. I might enjoy having written a book, but I don’t think I would enjoy writing a book. And I don’t think calling it a quest instead of a goal would make much difference]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jessetemp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More price rises are on the way for coffee drinkers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8224</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/more-coffee-price-rises-on-the-way/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad weather continues to hit coffee growers in Brazil and Vietnam, forcing Australian coffee suppliers to warn of shortages, and more price increases. It’s been a tough few years for coffee producers. When I wrote about production problems almost three years ago, droughts in Brazil were impacting harvest yields, causing a reduction in supply. Labour […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by solatic in "How we migrated onto K8s in less than 12 months"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41195709</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41195709"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T20:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't get the hate for Kubernetes in this thread. TFA is from Figma. You can talk all day long about how early startups just don't need the kind of management benefits that Kubernetes offers, but the article isn't written by someone working for a startup, it's written by a company that nearly got sold to Adobe for $20 billion.
Y'all really don't think a company like Figma stands to benefit from the flexibility that Kubernetes offers?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>solatic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by davedx in "Ask HN: Should we bring software dev in-house?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41194744</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41194744"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T18:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IME what works best getting new projects kick started is hiring a very small team of senior freelancers, making one of them lead, and letting them loose. I worked on such a team once and it was really excellent. The advantage of this strategy is if the experiment doesn't work out, terminating freelancers is much easier than permanent (I noted you're based in Europe).
Contrary to what other people said, I wouldn't try find a CTO straightaway. It's a hard role to hire for, especially at the start. I think you're better off unleashing a small, excellent team of builders then hire management later to help build out the team if the initial effort succeeds.
Happy to chat more about my experiences with this strategy, davedx@gmail.com (I'm in Europe too)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davedx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Retr0id in "Firefox Sidebar and Vertical tabs: try them out"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41193140</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41193140"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T16:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to be a tree-style-tabs power user but at some point I went back to regular tabs. I find that the amount of horizontal tab space is pretty close to the actual number of things I can usefully have open at once. Seeing the tabs get "squished" is my reminder to close the ones I no longer need.
I was using the tab-state as a sort of short-term working memory and I don't think it was doing me any favours, particularly in terms of focus.
Now when I'm working on a project, I keep a list of relevant URLs in a text file (i.e. bookmarks but checked into source control).
I also use two browser windows, a regular one for "stateful" browsing, and a private-mode one for "stateless" browsing. Quick queries and exploratory research happens in the "stateless" session, with the understanding that I can close any of these tabs (or nuke the whole session) at any time without losing anything important. If I do come across something important, it gets noted down elsewhere.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Retr0id</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: Finding my Blogging Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/finding-blogging-voice/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/finding-blogging-voice/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello fellow blogger,
I found your blog and the "Finding my Blogging Voice" post through Bear's 'Most Recent' feed and felt like writing a reply.
It's wonderful to see that you got your first post out there. A good and interesting one too, that many bloggers can relate to. Now that you're up and running, the hardest part is over.
I've been in a similar situation myself and understand how you feel. My advice is to not overthink it and just keep writing and posting, writing and posting, writing and posting...
I always find myself thinking I could do better, write better, be better.
We can all do better, and the only way to achieve it is by consistently publishing content. Plus, what we consider our "best writing" today, will be replaced by "even better" soon. Looking back at what I thought was my "best writing ever" five years ago, I wouldn't even publish it today.
Besides, we're terrible at being our own critics. We'll post texts we believe are outstanding, only to see them go by unnoticed. And we'll post texts we hesitate to share, which end up being our most read ever.
Blogging is like a school without final exams, that’s what makes it so valuable and rewarding.
Just keep on blogging and never skip class.
Good luck!
Update
The original post by "Thoughtless Ramblings" made ripples in cyberspace. Another great example of the beauty of blogging. A first post was all it took...
Blog posts
Bearly Significant
You?
Mastodon
I had a hard time finding my voice. I always felt like I needed to perform for someone with my writing. Took me a while to feel comfortable just writing for myself and to get stuff out of my head. And I think the way I see it now is like I'm doing an impromptu presentation and some people might stop and listen. — Juan Villela]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laundering Carbon—The Gulf's ‘New Scramble for Africa']]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Laundering-Carbon-The-Gulf-s-New-Scramble-for-Africa</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Laundering-Carbon-The-Gulf-s-New-Scramble-for-Africa"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:13:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early November 2023, shortly before the COP28 summit opened in Dubai, a hitherto obscure UAE firm attracted significant media attention around news of their prospective land deals in Africa. 
 Reports suggested that Blue Carbon—a company privately owned by Sheikh Ahmed al-Maktoum, a member of Dubai's ruling family—had signed deals—a land grab enacted in the name of climate change mitigation. In response, Blue Carbon insisted the discussions were merely exploratory and would require (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Africa, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Hanieh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Automatic SSL/TLS: securing and simplifying origin connectivity]]></title>
        <id>66b406ef4a25d6000ae1ca70</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-automatic-ssl-tls-securing-and-simplifying-origin-connectivity"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new Automatic SSL/TLS setting will maximize and simplify the encryption modes Cloudflare uses to communicate with origin servers by using the SSL/TLS Recommender]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Krivit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating one year of Project Cybersafe Schools]]></title>
        <id>66b360254a25d6000ae1c9cb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrating-one-year-of-project-cybersafe-schools"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 8, 2024, marks the first anniversary of Project Cybersafe Schools, Cloudflare’s initiative to provide small K-12 public school districts in the United States with a package of Zero Trust cybersecurity solutions – for free, and with no time limit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaid Zaid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how to love yourself]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/how-to-love-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/how-to-love-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mikasacus recently made a video titled "how to actually love yourself"1 in which he details his own journey towards discovering self-love:
I learned that self-love means giving yourself acceptance for your very being, accepting your flaws, quirks, and failures as a part of you and choosing to respect yourself despite your perceived shortcomings. It means treating yourself with the same respect you would treat anyone else with. You wouldn't tell someone something even half as cruel as the things you tell yourself. So why would you tell yourself those things?
His overall message comes down to self-love being something not about vanity but about developing a deep sense of self-assurance, acceptance, and trust with yourself. True self-love involves treating oneself with kindness, respect, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by diffeomorphism in "The Story of Samsung's failed deal with iFixit, as told by iFixit's CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41190527</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41190527"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T11:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would argue the opposite. They are not aiming to be a neutral arbiter but an active advocate for better repairability. For that they should have for-profit business relationships with basically all companies manufacturing such devices. In particular, that would allow them to pressure or drop any one misbehaving company.
> Providing consumers with information on where to find reputable companies selling repair parts would be a much more palatable alternative to selling them yourself.
That does not really make sense. They are a repair company and the only company selling specialized parts is, of course, the manufacturer.
> also stands in the way of advocating for consumers.
That is much too bleak. They made a deal happen in the first place, which is large progress even if it did not quite work out, and compromises are a fact of life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>diffeomorphism</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Persistence of Global Capitalism's Long Depression]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Persistence-of-Global-Capitalism-s-Long-Depression</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Persistence-of-Global-Capitalism-s-Long-Depression"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T10:49:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Biden administration and its liberal apologists crow about the economic recovery, in reality US capitalism, and indeed global capitalism, remain stuck in a slump with seemingly no end in sight. Spectre's Ashley Smith interviews Michael Roberts about the state of the US and world economy, the reasons for what he calls the Long Depression, and how it is driving political polarization within countries and imperial rivalries between the globe's dominant and rising powers. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Capitalism, 
Financial crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith, Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by a2128 in "Google and Meta struck secret ads deal to target teenagers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41189252</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41189252"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T08:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This reads like a tragic story. Once you've collected enough data on every internet user out there to group them into different advertising cohorts, the remaining ungrouped users, by process of elimination (due to privacy or targeted advertising laws), are children; and now they can be targeted just as easily.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>a2128</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by somenameforme in "NASA says Boeing Starliner astronauts may fly home on SpaceX in 2025"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41189189</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41189189"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T08:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think many might not be aware of Starliner's sordid history. It has failed essentially every qualification test in various ways. Their pad abort test (where you simulate a launch abort while on the launch pad) resulted in only 2 of the 3 parachutes deploying in beyond optimal conditions. NASA considered that such a resounding success that they let them completely skip the far more challenging in-flight abort test. Their first automated mission to the ISS completely failed and did not make it to the station. NASA finally required a redo from Boeing and their second one did make it to the ISS, but only after experiencing widespread leaks and thruster failures literally identical to the ones that have now left these astronauts stranded.
If SpaceX or another company had remotely similar results, they would never have been greenlit. For instance in spite of a flawless pad abort test, NASA required SpaceX also carry out an in-flight abort. And that's completely reasonable - you don't simply skip tests, even with optimal performance. Skipping tests following suboptimal performance is simply unjustifiable. And so I think we're largely looking at another Challenger type disaster caused by a disconnect between management (and likely political appointees) versus engineering staff, rather than inherent risk. But this is not a vessel that should have ever had a single human anywhere near it, and so their official comments (and even actions) on the situation are going to be heavily biased due to their own behaviors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>somenameforme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dongobread in "GPT-4 LLM simulates people well enough to replicate social science experiments"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41187239</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41187239"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T01:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm very skeptical on this, the paper they linked is not convincing. It says that GPT-4 is correct at predicting the experiment outcome direction 69% of the time versus 66% of the time for human forecasters. But this is a silly benchmark because people are not trusting human forecasters in the first place, that's the whole purpose for why the experiment is run. Knowing that GPT-4 is slightly better at predicting experiments than some human guessing doesn't make it a useful substitute for the actual experiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dongobread</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The not-so-strange shortage of conservative professors]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52960</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/08/the-not-so-strange-shortage-of-conservative-professors/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T00:24:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a letter in The Chronicle of Higher Education responding to Steven Teles’ call for more conservative college professors. It’s a shortened version of a longer piece I wrote, which I’m posting here. The fact that conservatives are thin in the humanities and social sciences departments of US college campuses is well known. A […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GMoromisato in "NASA says Boeing Starliner astronauts may fly home on SpaceX in 2025"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41185845</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41185845"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T21:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I listened to the whole conference and here's my impression:
1. NASA manager Steve Stich said there's a relatively wide "band of uncertainty" in how risky a Starliner return is. Some (many?) NASA engineers are at the high end of the band and are advocating a return on Dragon instead. Boeing is obviously at the low end of the band and thinks it is a low risk.
The problem is, the data doesn't rule out either side of the band. So they are trying to get more data to narrow the uncertainty (in either or both directions). [Interestingly enough, the data from the White Sands testing made them more worried because it revealed the Teflon seal deformation.]
But my sense is that if they don't narrow the uncertainty (i.e., convince the NASA engineers) then they will very likely choose a Dragon return.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GMoromisato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ledge, a new thriller/whodunit by Christian White]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8162</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-ledge-new-thriller-whodunit-christian-white/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ledge is the fourth novel by Victoria based Australian writer, and master of twists that will leave you breathless and dumbfounded: Christian White. When human remains are discovered in a forest, police are baffled, the locals are shocked and one group of old friends starts to panic. Their long-held secret is about to be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Was a Simple Man, a film by Christopher Makoto Yogi, with Steve Iwamoto]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8203</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-i-was-a-simple-man-christopher-makoto-yogi-steve-iwamoto/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T20:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Made in 2021, I Was a Simple Man, trailer, is the third feature of American writer and filmmaker Christopher Makoto Yogi, who also wrote the screenplay. Masao Matsuyoshi (Steve Iwamoto), an elderly man who has spent most of his life in Hawaii, is terminally ill, and has months to live. As he nears death, he […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generating Accurate Git Commit Messages with Amazon Q Developer CLI Context Modifiers]]></title>
        <id>48429d91a938bbf293ffce211846060b22069209</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/generating-accurate-git-commit-messages-with-amazon-q-developer-cli-context-modifiers/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T19:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing clear and concise Git commit messages is crucial for effective version control and collaboration. However, when working with complex projects or codebases, providing additional context can be challenging. In this blog post, we’ll explore how to leverage Amazon Q Developer to analyze our code changes for us and produce meaningful commit messages for Git. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Yanchuleff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Identity-Aware Sessions with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>3c406d6b6643e9f7cd3259f269265514c76240a2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/implementing-identity-aware-sessions-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T18:58:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.” -Oscar Wilde In the real world as in the world of technology and authentication, the ability to understand who we are is important on many levels. In this blog post, we’ll look at how the ability to uniquely identify ourselves in the AWS console can lead to a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Yanchuleff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending August 04, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240807</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240807"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Davidson (1930-2024) In Memoriam]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45523</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/07/paul-davidson-1930-2024-in-memoriam/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T18:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Paul Davidson, the co-founder of the Journal of Post Keynesian Economics (JPKE) and a leading Post Keynesian economist, died on June 20, 2024, in Chicago. He was born in Brooklyn, NY, on October 23, 1930, about a year after the Great Crash of 1929. He was a staunch defender of the importance […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tenant portability: Move tenants across tiers in a SaaS application]]></title>
        <id>4c0d6017f7c1386a5b4dec794fa1e21422e9c2fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/tenant-portability-move-tenants-across-tiers-in-a-saas-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T17:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s fast-paced software as a service (SaaS) landscape, tenant portability is a critical capability for SaaS providers seeking to stay competitive. By enabling seamless movement between tiers, tenant portability allows businesses to adapt to changing needs. However, manual orchestration of portability requests can be a significant bottleneck, hindering scalability and requiring substantial resources. As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aman Lal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Muse That Keeps Getting Away]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-muse-that-keeps-getting-away/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-muse-that-keeps-getting-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T16:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways I come up with blog post topics to publish. Most days, I sit down in front of my computer (or phone) and allow myself to just type, see what comes out, and then refine. Other times, I write intentional posts about topics that I have been ruminating on. Then there are moments when my emotions run so strong that I have to express them before I explode. I guess such was the case yesterday.
Of course, there are other ways. I have a list of topics I want to get to one day, but those have been mostly ignored. They overwhelm me too much.
Anyways, that's not the intention of this post.
The best topics come to me in the most inopportune times, and so half the time, they never see the light of day. I often find myself coming up with things I want to write about in that space betw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by refibrillator in "How French Drains Work"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41182936</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41182936"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T16:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve built quite a few french drains in residential settings, some lasting longer than others - I’ll share a few hard earned lessons here:
Soil migration is the number one failure mode. This is mentioned but perhaps a bit understated in the video.
To prevent soil migration you absolutely need commercial grade geotextile fabric wrapping the gravel and pipe.
You can buy pipe with much bigger and more numerous holes than the tiny slits depicted in the video. That also obviates the need to decide what orientation the holes should be.
Void space is the most critical factor when choosing gravel. You need a lot of space between the rocks to support fast drainage. Do not use playground pebbles or anything similar. Pay close attention to the type of aggregate you’re buying.
Calculate how much water you actually need to drain. You can use the “100 year flood” values for your locale to get an upper bound on rainfall, then multiple by drainage area. This is especially important if your roof is part of the watershed.
https://www.usgs.gov/special-topics/water-science-school/sci...
Sometimes there is insufficient gradient to move the water anywhere, ie the land is too flat. In this case you may be better off building a drywell, which is constructed very similarly.
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dry_well]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>refibrillator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Amazon Q Developer to deploy a Serverless web application with AWS CDK]]></title>
        <id>60c3228f9cecdd1129746426fa63b39e04be4a39</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-to-use-amazon-q-developer-to-deploy-a-serverless-web-application-with-aws-cdk/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T15:26:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that Amazon Q Developer, a new type of Generative AI-powered (GenAI) assistant, can help developers and DevOps engineers accelerate Infrastructure as Code (IaC) development using the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)? IaC is a practice where infrastructure components such as servers, networks, and cloud resources are defined and managed using code. Instead […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riya Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anatomy of Labor Demand Pre‑ and Post‑COVID]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31057</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/the-anatomy-of-labor-demand-pre-and-post-covid/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has labor demand changed since the COVID-19 pandemic? In this post, we leverage detailed data on the universe of U.S. online job listings to study the dynamics of labor demand pre- and post-COVID. We find that there has been a significant shift in listings out of the central cities and into the “fringe” portion of large metro areas, smaller metro areas, and rural areas. We also find a substantial decline in job listings in computer and mathematical and business and financial operations occupations, and a corresponding increase in job openings in sales, office and administrative support, food preparation, and especially healthcare occupations. These patterns (by geography and by occupation) are interconnected: the biggest declines in job listings by occupation occurred in the largest and densest geographies, and the strongest increases in job listings by occupation occurred in the smaller and less populated geographies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Audoly, Miles Guerin, Giorgio Topa, and Roshie Xing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG API Machinery]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/07/sig-api-machinery-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/07/sig-api-machinery-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently talked with Federico Bongiovanni (Google) and David
Eads (Red Hat), Chairs of SIG API Machinery, to know a bit more about
this Kubernetes Special Interest Group.
Introductions
Frederico (FSM): Hello, and thank your for your time. To start with, could you tell us about
yourselves and how you got involved in Kubernetes?
David: I started working on
OpenShift (the Red Hat
distribution of Kubernetes) in the fall of 2014 and got involved pretty quickly in API Machinery. My
first PRs were fixing kube-apiserver error messages and from there I branched out to kubectl
(kubeconfigs are my fault!), auth (RBAC and *Review APIs are ports
from OpenShift), apps (workqueues and sharedinformers for example). Don’t tell the others,
but API Machinery is still my favorite :)
Federico: I was not as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actually listening to 10cc.]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52956</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/06/52956/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you know my age my musical tastes as a teenager are very easy to guess. Obviously Dylan, Mitchell, the Kinks and the Beatles – equally obviously not the Stones or the Who. Richard Thompson, Sandy Denny, Fairport, Steeleye Span, Roy Harper, The Watersons, Carthy, etc, etc and more than any of them, Kevin Coyne. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who needs LinkedIn when you can network at music festivals?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8159</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/who-needs-linkedin-network-music-festivals/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking tips for music festivals, by Harry Carr: Don’t make the mistake that most people make and switch off as soon as you reach Paddington. Maximise your train journey by reaching out to your extended network, to see if they are going to Glastonbury Music Festival. If there’s a speaker or business guru you admire […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dense Discovery notches three hundred editions, opens reader community]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8193</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dense-discovery-three-hundred-editions-reader-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne based Australian designer and publisher Kai Brach’s weekly publication, Dense Discovery (DD), is one of the few newsletters I subscribe to. If you have an interest in, well, everything, then DD is for you. First published in September 2018, the three-hundredth edition was posted yesterday. And to mark this most impressive of milestones, Brach […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding my Blogging Voice]]></title>
        <id>https://hiddenperson.bearblog.dev/finding-my-blogging-voice/</id>
        <link href="https://hiddenperson.bearblog.dev/finding-my-blogging-voice/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T19:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to blog but have never posted. I start a draft and work on it for hours and days, but I never think it's good enough. I always think that I could do better, write better, be better. For so long all I've written is essays and official memos, I find it hard to let down my standards and be natural.
My recent resume is working against me; four years of college with essays and lab reports, and a year at a corporate job with professional communications. Writing off the cuff to a casual audience doesn't come as easy to me as it once did. Somehow I need to undo the last five years of training and relearn simplicity and sincerity.
This is my first post and I don't expect it to make a splash, but rather just a drop in the sea of writers online. My real goal with this post and others are to find my "blogging voice", a version of myself who can write freely without worrying so much about the particulars.
I'm afraid this post will join the myriad others on BearBlog in the "meta-blogging" category; blogging about blogging. While that may be true for this first entry, I'm hoping to expand my writing in the coming months, I just hope someone will join me on that journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Image Generator v2 is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>2d71dc91ba8d25a9634204389216e742e9917a1e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-titan-image-generator-v2-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T19:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Image Generator v2 provides unprecedented creative capabilities: image conditioning, color control, background removal, and subject preservation via fine-tuning for brand consistency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in the Everyday]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/lost-everyday/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/lost-everyday/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the houses I visited at work today had an absolutely stunning view of the sea. I could have easily stayed there all day.
When I mentioned how amazing the location was, the owner of the house replied, "Yeah, but you don't think about it after a while."
It should be illegal to live like that if you don't even appreciate it, I thought as I walked back to my car. I started driving away and caught myself...
But what about me? I'm basically the same.
I don't live in a house with a sea view, but I have an apartment with a window overlooking a beautiful courtyard. And every morning when I walk to my car, I pass amazing old buildings.
How often do I think about it? Hardly ever.
Yet, it's something I once marveled at for its beauty. Where did that awareness go? I looked out the window now and it still looks absolutely wonderful, of course.
Okay, it's never going to be like "the first high" again, but that doesn't matter. Just a tenth of the first experience is still immensely precious and rewarding.
A tiny bit of awareness is all it takes to start observing and appreciating our surroundings. Let's remind ourselves of the beauty of the mundane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortgage Lock‑In Spurs Recent HELOC Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31202</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/mortgage-lock-in-spurs-recent-heloc-demand/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mortgage balances, the largest component of U.S. household debt, grew by only $77 billion (0.6 percent) in the second quarter of 2024, according to the latest Quarterly Report on Household Debt and Credit from the New York Fed’s Center for Microeconomic Data. This modest increase reflects a substantial slowdown in mortgage origination; only $374 billion was originated during the second quarter, compared to an average of about $1 trillion per quarter between 2021 and 2022. Meanwhile, after nearly thirteen years of decline, balances on home equity lines of credit (HELOC) have begun to rebound, gaining 20 percent since bottoming out at the end of 2021. In this post, we consider the factors behind this upswing, finding that HELOCs have likely become an attractive alternative to cash-out refinancings amid higher interest rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle W. Scally, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>