<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-21T01:32:32.715Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-21T01:32:32.715Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by anon373839 in "Statement from Scarlett Johansson on the OpenAI "Sky" voice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421564</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40421564"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, that statement lays out a damning timeline:
- OpenAI approached Scarlett last fall, and she refused.
- Two days before the GPT-4o launch, they contacted her agent and asked that she reconsider. (Two days! This means they already had everything they needed to ship  the product with Scarlett’s  cloned voice.)
- Not receiving a response, OpenAI demos the product anyway, with Sam tweeting “her” in reference to Scarlett’s film.
- When Scarlett’s counsel asked for an explanation of how the “Sky” voice was created, OpenAI yanked the voice from their product line.
Perhaps Sam’s next tweet should read “red-handed”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anon373839</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The health benefits of giving up drinking coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/health-benefits-giving-up-drinking-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with many things we consume, the science on coffee can be conflicted. One decade caffeine consumption is a no-no, the next it seems coffee is quite beneficial. Regular readers will know I’m a coffee drinker, but in — what I consider to be — moderation: two (large serve) cups per day. But some people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "ICC prosecutor seeks arrest warrants against Sinwar and Netanyahu for war crimes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418956</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418956"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:05:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: if you're going to comment in this thread, please review the site guidelines (https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html). Make sure that your comment is following them, and that you are posting in the intended spirit: intellectually curious, respectful conversation.
"Respectful" here means respectful to the people who are wrong (in your view) and most respectful to the people who are most wrong (in your view). If you can't do that, that's ok, but please don't post until you can. Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive - https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html.
Hellish flamewars in deep subthreads are not ok. I'm going to lower the bar for banning accounts that do this, so please don't do this. If you're hotly indignant, step away from the keyboard until that changes. Nobody 'wins' on the internet anyway, and it's not worth destroying this community for. Not to mention your heart.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by isoprophlex in "Introducing Copilot+ PCs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418816</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40418816"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Their "copilot" brand is so weird and... muddled.
There's the AI code assistant thing that github actually started, there's the horrible chatbot maker GUI demoware, there's AI stuff you might be able to do with your sharepoint (if only you could get hold of the right ms sales rep to take your money), there's an app that does genai things on your personal MS account... And now there's a Surface rebrand?
That org chart meme about Microsoft being little fiefdoms pointing guns at eachother never stops being relevant.
[1] https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-copilot/microsoft-...
[2] https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2023/05/0...
[3] https://copilot.microsoft.com/
And [4] the meme itself, as you really can't convince me the above is the result of a coherent company-wide strategy https://i.insider.com/51dfec8469bedd5e19000017]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>isoprophlex</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271932</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics, wastewater data debacle as Bionbot ends its wasterwater visualization, Michael Cohen stole $30,000 from Trump, interviews with Kennedy voters, small beer ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;A Reprieve for Assange&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism as ‘espionage’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Application Load Balancer IPv6, Amazon S3 pricing update, Amazon EC2 Flex instances, and more (May 20, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3ec4a6e752f974d277f95d9da7228e9f5bba4ba4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-application-load-balancer-ipv6-amazon-s3-pricing-update-amazon-ec2-flex-instances-and-more-may-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is in full swing around the world, with last week’s events in Bengaluru, Berlin, and  Seoul, where my blog colleague Channy delivered one of the keynotes. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon S3 will no longer charge for several HTTP error codes – A customer reported […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the ICC’s Announcement of Arrest Warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant and Hamas’ Leadership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323355</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/on-the-iccs-announcement-of-arrest-warrants-for-netanyahu-gallant-and-hamas-leadership/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision to announce these applications for arrest warrants prior to their formal approval may have been motivated by a sense that the conditions under which the people of Gaza are striving to survive are deteriorating so rapidly and horrifically that there is no time to waste and by a hope that announcing the applications now might have a positive impact on the decisions of relevant decision-makers for whom arrest warrants are not yet being sought but could be sought later. More
The post On the ICC’s Announcement of Arrest Warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant and Hamas’ Leadership appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Whitbeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruptions Have Eased, But Remain a Concern]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30028</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/supply-chain-disruptions-have-eased-but-remain-a-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain disruptions became a major headache for businesses in the aftermath of the pandemic. Indeed, in October 2021, nearly all firms in our regional business surveys reported at least some difficulty obtaining the supplies they needed. These supply chain disruptions were a key contributor to the surge in inflation that occurred as the economy recovered from the pandemic recession. In this post, we present new measures of supply availability from our Business Leaders Survey and Empire State Manufacturing Survey that closely track the New York Fed’s Global Supply Chain Pressure Index (GSCPI). We will begin publishing these data on a monthly basis starting in June. These indexes indicate that supply availability had generally been improving since early 2023, but over the past couple of months, improvement has stalled. This trend is concerning since our May Supplemental Survey indicates that between a third and a half of businesses in the region are experiencing difficulties obtaining supplies, and many are reducing operations and raising prices to compensate, though to a lesser extent than a few years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel and Richard Deitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Godfrey Wood: &ldquo;Battle Machine&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrospectives on Podemos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271903</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our buzzy daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review: The Untapped Knowledge of Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271919</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/book-review-the-untapped-knowledge-of-animals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In “The Internet of Animals,” Martin Wikelski highlights what insights humans can learn from creatures great and small.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by drpotato in "Migrating Uber's ledger data from DynamoDB to LedgerStore"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40414124</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40414124"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original[1][2] articles are a better read IMO. The link is just a summary of the two with added spelling and grammatical errors that materially impact the meaning.
1. https://www.uber.com/blog/how-ledgerstore-supports-trillions...
2. https://www.uber.com/blog/migrating-from-dynamodb-to-ledgers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>drpotato</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Trade Desperation: Trump Insider Robert Lightheizer Recommends Third-World Capital Controls to Achieve Balanced Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271901</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/us-trade-desperation-trump-insider-robert-lightheizer-recommends-third-world-capital-controls-to-achieve-balanced-trade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New desperate ideas to fix chronic US trade imbalances, like capital controls, are getting a hearing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassination Attempt on Slovak PM Highlights Dangers of Constant EU Demonization of Project Ukraine Opponents and Hypocrisy of ‘Misinformation’ Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271777</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/wheres-the-uproar-over-corporate-medias-history-of-spreading-hate-and-misinformation-about-slovak-pm-who-just-survived-assassination-attempt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T07:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will there be any self reflection among mainstream media and Atlanticist politicians for relentlessly going after Slovakian PM for the crime of opposing Project Ukraine while also silencing counter arguments? Don't hold your breath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMass Arrests: What Would Daniel Ellsberg Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/umass-arrests-what-would-daniel-ellsberg-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a history professor at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst for twenty years. On May 7, I was one of a handful of faculty members arrested for standing in support of hundreds of students who were engaged in nonviolent protest of university complicity in the ongoing slaughter and suffering of Palestinians in Gaza. They want the school to divest from companies profiting from the carnage. More
The post UMass Arrests: What Would Daniel Ellsberg Do? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian G. Appy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323147</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/why-corporations-choose-lawlessness-to-fight-unions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers in Towson, Maryland, have earned the distinction of becoming the first Apple retail workers in the nation to vote to strike over failed union negotiations with their employer. The approximately 100 Apple workers were also the first in the nation to successfully form a union. They did so in 2022, as the Coalition of Organized Retail Employees (CORE), joining the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM). Two-thirds of the store’s workers voted to join the union, a resounding success at a company that has long staved off union activity. More
The post Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Toughest Job Today’s Richest Ever Face?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/the-toughest-job-todays-richest-ever-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York currently hosts, researchers at the London-based Henley & Partners have just reported, more centi-millionaires than any other city on Earth. And if hosting centi-millionaires ever became an Olympic sport, the Henley stats show, the USA would be bringing home gold, silver, and bronze. The San Francisco Bay Area — now teeming with 675 centi-millionaires — rates as the world’s second-most-popular home to fortunes worth over $100 million. Los Angeles sits third with 496. More
The post The Toughest Job Today’s Richest Ever Face? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Procter & Gamble, Mondelēz, and Nestlé Are Among 10 of the Leading Consumer Brands Driving Global Deforestation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323295</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/procter-gamble-mondelez-and-nestle-are-among-10-of-the-leading-consumer-brands-driving-global-deforestation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the turn of the century, there has been a consistent average annual loss of 3 to 4 million hectares (7.4 to 9.9 million acres) of tropical forest globally. This puts us far from reaching the goal of zero deforestation by 2030, a target embraced in 2021 by 145 countries during the COP26 climate summit in Glasgow. Besides  More
The post Procter & Gamble, Mondelēz, and Nestlé Are Among 10 of the Leading Consumer Brands Driving Global Deforestation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurel Sutherlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bluelining Leaves Climate Vulnerable Communities Without Home Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323312</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/how-bluelining-leaves-climate-vulnerable-communities-without-home-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era of climate disasters, Americans in vulnerable regions will need to rely more than ever on their home insurance. But as floods, wildfires, and severe storms become more common, a troubling practice known as “bluelining” threatens to leave many communities unable to afford insurance — or obtain it at any price. Bluelining is  More
The post How Bluelining Leaves Climate Vulnerable Communities Without Home Insurance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promising the Impossible: Blinken’s Out of Tune Performance in Kyiv]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323293</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/promising-the-impossible-blinkens-out-of-tune-performance-in-kyiv/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are looking dire for the Ukrainian war effort.  Promises of victory are becoming even hollower than they were last summer, when US President Joe Biden could state with breathtaking obliviousness that Russia had “already lost the war”.   The worst offender in this regard remains the United States, which has been the most vocal proponent of fanciful victory over  More
The post Promising the Impossible: Blinken’s Out of Tune Performance in Kyiv appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statement of ICC Prosecutor Karim A.A. Khan KC: Applications for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323359</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/statement-of-icc-prosecutor-karim-a-a-khan-kc-applications-for-arrest-warrants-in-the-situation-in-the-state-of-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICC Prosecutor Khan on application for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine Today I am filing applications for warrants of arrest before Pre-Trial Chamber I of the International Criminal Court in the Situation in the State of Palestine. Yahya Sinwar, Mohammed Diab Ibrahim Al-Masri (Deif), Ismail Haniyeh On the basis of  More
The post Statement of ICC Prosecutor Karim A.A. Khan KC: Applications for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuval Noah Harari’s Odyssey into a Parallel Zionist Universe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323162</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/yuval-noah-hararis-odyssey-into-a-parallel-zionist-universe/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast expanse of the intellectual cosmos, there exists a luminary whose brilliance outshines even the brightest stars. Professor Yuval Noah Harari, a name whispered with reverence among the learned denizens of the galaxy, is a beacon of knowledge, whose canon traverses the celestial planes of history, philosophy, human psychology and beyond. Informed by  More
The post Yuval Noah Harari’s Odyssey into a Parallel Zionist Universe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tapping Into the Vast Safety Potential of “Loss Prevention” by the Insurance Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323160</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/tapping-into-the-vast-safety-potential-of-loss-prevention-by-the-insurance-industry/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent newspaper article reports that GEICO, one of the largest auto insurers in the U.S., has amassed a staggering $189 billion in cash, apart from the reserves required by law to insure the volume of potential claims by its policyholders. Angry consumers have cried out about auto insurance premiums going up as the prices  More
The post Tapping Into the Vast Safety Potential of “Loss Prevention” by the Insurance Industry appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Eat the Fish: The Astounding Failure of Our Regulatory Agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323258</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/dont-eat-the-fish-the-astounding-failure-of-our-regulatory-agencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when state and federal agencies refuse to adequately regulate industries and activities that produce pollution and release it into the environment?  Well, as reported by the Daily Montanan, a recent study by the Department of Fish, Wildlife and Parks has found the Clark Fork, Bitterroot and Blackfoot Rivers to be much more polluted with highly  More
The post Don’t Eat the Fish: The Astounding Failure of Our Regulatory Agencies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preying on White Fears Worked for Georgia’s Lester Maddox in the ’60s and is Working There for Trump Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323144</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/preying-on-white-fears-worked-for-georgias-lester-maddox-in-the-60s-and-is-working-there-for-trump-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 1967, after a gubernatorial election that saw neither candidate gain enough votes to win, the Georgia Legislature was faced with a vital decision: the selection of the state’s 75th governor during the height of the Civil Rights Movement. Legislators chose the candidate who earned the least number of votes and was an ardent  More
The post Preying on White Fears Worked for Georgia’s Lester Maddox in the ’60s and is Working There for Trump Today appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Cason</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renting Your Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271870</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/renting-your-life.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T04:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More on the further erosion of ownership and property rights via required renting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Package Deal Full of Holes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323276</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/a-package-deal-full-of-holes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T04:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden administration has been working on a package deal with Saudi Arabia that would guarantee a path to a Palestinian state in return for a permanent cease-fire and establishment of Saudi-Israel relations. But the Saudis want more for themselves: a U.S.-Saudi mutual defense pact and cooperation on a civilian nuclear program in the kingdom.  More
The post A Package Deal Full of Holes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSGE models — a total waste of time]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45375</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/20/dsge-models-a-total-waste-of-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll While one can understand that some of the elements in DSGE models seem to appeal to Keynesians at first sight, after closer examination, these models are in fundamental contradiction to Post-Keynesian and even traditional Keynesian thinking. The DSGE model is a model in which output is determined in the labour market as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Completing the largest migration in Kubernetes history]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since as early as Kubernetes v1.7, the Kubernetes project has pursued the ambitious goal of removing built-in cloud provider integrations (KEP-2395).
While these integrations were instrumental in Kubernetes' early development and growth, their removal was driven by two key factors:
the growing complexity of maintaining native support for every cloud provider across millions of lines of Go code, and the desire to establish
Kubernetes as a truly vendor-neutral platform.
After many releases, we're thrilled to announce that all cloud provider integrations have been successfully migrated from the core Kubernetes repository to external plugins.
In addition to achieving our initial objectives, we've also significantly streamlined Kubernetes by removing roughly 1.5 million lines of code and reduci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by miki123211 in "Llama3 implemented from scratch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40410017</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40410017"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you like this, it's also worth looking at llama2.c[1], an implementation of the Llama 2 architecture in about 1000 lines of plain, dependency-free C, tokenizer and all. THe fact that this 960-line file and a somewhat modern C compiler is all you really need to run a state-of-the-art language model is really surprising to many.
Of course, this is not all there is to a modern LLM, it would probably take another thousand lines or two to implement training, and many more than that to make it fast on all the major CPU and GPU architectures. If you want a flexible framework that lets a developer define any model you want and still goes as fast as it can, the complexity spirals.
Most programmers have an intuition that duplicating a large software project from scratch, like Linux or Chromium for example, would require incredible amounts of expertise, manpower and time. It's not something that a small team can achieve in a few months. You're limited by talent, not hardware.
LLMs are very different. THe code isn't that complicated, you could probably implement training and inference for a single model architecture, from scratch, on a single kind of GPU, with reasonable performance, as an individual with a background in programming and who still remembers their calculus and linear algebra, with a year or so of self study. What makes LLMs difficult is getting access to all the hardware to train them, getting the data, and being able to preprocess that data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miki123211</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What has happened to cover versions of popular songs?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7624</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-happened-cover-versions-popular-songs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, Australian radio station Triple J, invites a band or musician to record a cover of a song, for their Like A Version show. Anything goes here. About two years ago, Sydney based Australian DJ Dave Winnel performed a cover of Africa, by Toto, not the sort of music you’d usually hear on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Word of the Day: Don’t Say “Covid Pandemic.” Say “Covid Syndemic”!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271878</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/word-of-the-day-dont-say-covid-pandemic-say-covid-syndemic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T20:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["'Tis a mystery," except not!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xivzgrev in "Ask HN: Video streaming is expensive yet YouTube "seems" to do it for free. How?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40409320</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40409320"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T19:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: I used to work at a live video streaming company as a financial analyst so quite familiar with this
The biggest cost is as you imagine the streaming - getting the video to the viewer.  It was a large part of our variable cost and we had a (literal) mad genius dev ops person holed up in his own office cave that managed the whole operation.
Ive long forgotten the special optimizations he did but he would keep finding ways to improve margin / efficiency.
Encoding is a cost but I don’t recall it being significant
Storage isnt generally expensive. Think about how cheap you as a consumer can go get 2 TB of storage, and extrapolate.
The other big expense - people!  All those engineers to build back and front end systems. That’s what ruined us - too many people were needed and not enough money coming in so we were burning cash.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xivzgrev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World, I guess?]]></title>
        <id>https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/</id>
        <link href="https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:28:15.910Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay... exhales
Here we go.
Hi, I'm Meï ! And welcome to this blog. Or this attempt at a blog.
It's been a few weeks since I felt a lot of nostalgia for the Internet of old, the one I discovered as a lil' kid, on my tenth birthday, circa 2007.
A friend, Seeker, began working on his own blog a few months back. I really liked his articles about DIY and Game Dev, and on a whim asked him his tech stack with the intent of setting something up for myself.
I used to write quite a bit a few years ago. Especially when I got to the big city after high school. Welcome to Fucktopia1 was a small series detailing my new life far from the countryside.
As of late, I've been trying to get back into writing. Essays to recommend some games, some small fictions, and lore for TTRPGs, I've been slowly but surely getting back into it. But I didn't really manage to find a public, even for the essays in places (well, Discord servers in this case) dedicated to the exact IP I was trying to promote.
This built up as a bit of frustration, and is another of the reasons I felt like doing a blog. I wanted to be more open to the world, able to write in a place anyone could read if they stumble on the place.
So once again, here we go!
1. As a note, the "Fucktopia" is a reference to Souillon's comic book "Hello Fucktopia". Couldn't find a listing in English, sorry! It's available in French & Spanish, at least..
My small rules of writing
Try to write regularly. Not necessarily everyday, but I should strive for a post per week at least.
Focus! I'm super prone to tangents and often stray off-topic. A post should be on a single subject, unless this is a post consciously made for tangents and chaos.
No stressing over this. I already stress over too much, let's keep this place as my comfy Internet place.
Let's hope it goes well. And I hope you'll enjoy this blog and its topics.
Fan-art of Cyberpunk Bartender Action: VA-11 HALL-A, by rnna_7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271855</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T10:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our stellar daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why One New York Health System Stopped Suing Its Patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271867</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/why-one-new-york-health-system-stopped-suing-its-patients.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T10:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American hospital officials often insist that lawsuits and other aggressive collections, though unsavory, are necessary to protect health systems’ finances and deter freeloading. But at Rochester Regional, ditching these collection tactics hasn’t hurt the bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Pézenas]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52709</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/19/sunday-photoblogging-pezenas-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T07:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fallen Angel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322548</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/19/fallen-angel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[llustration from the frontispiece of the 1831 edition of Mary Shelley’s Frankenstein by Theodor Von Holst. Public Domain.
When I was a young child, I would sometimes stay a weekend in the summer holidays with my cousins – who were of a similar age – on their farm.   I grew up in north London: all concrete and cars, and fumes and arcades, and long black railings and grey school playgrounds, and rising tower blocks and rushing roads.   Looking back, the farm of my uncle and aunt couldn’t have been more than a thirty- or forty-minute drive from where I lived in the city; the farm itself was situated only a few fields away from the motorway you would need to traverse to get there. Hardly the back and beyond.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Fallen Angel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Resignation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321754</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/19/the-great-resignation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T05:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Jon Tyson.
I am beyond tired of writing and reading about Trump, his minions Stephen Miller and Steve Bannon, and the evils they plan to inflict upon the world. Reading or watching the news is a daily exercise in dread, self-torment, and exhaustion. The return of spring notwithstanding, things are grim these days. The Trumpist menace seems of a piece with a far-right axis on the march in India, Russia, Israel, China, and Hungary. Of course, it’s futile to wring one’s hands and lament Trumpian aspirations to authoritarianism without taking concrete action to prevent them. Yet despite nearly eight years of experience confronting the Trumpian specter, the answer to the traditional, eminently practical leftist question “What is to be done?” remains elusive, and the sense of burnout and political defeat—with the concomitant, complicated welter of emotions —is a specter difficult to vanquish.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Great Resignation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Remer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by why_at in "Riven"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40404460</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40404460"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T05:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Favorite piece of Riven trivia:
If you've played the game you might remember the one spot where there's a giant sword sticking out of the ground. Since this place also appears in one of the game's FMV cutscenes they had to use a real giant sword prop for filming. The person that made the giant sword prop was Adam Savage from Mythbusters.
https://youtu.be/gcDCZ2TmTck?si=8J8A4ja1vRGDC9c6&t=150]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>why_at</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Hayvok in "I organized a 20-acre game of Capture the Flag"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40400813</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40400813"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T18:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We did night CTF (~9 pm) at our local grade school campus. Easily 40-50 kids. We just rode our bikes to the gathering. Similar rules to what this article had, except no out of bounds. We had kids making huge circuits around a nearby corn field to evade detection.
It was indeed someone of my best childhood memories.
Unfortunately it was all brought to an end because people kept calling the cops. They’d see kids after dark at the school and just assume we were up to no good. No property was ever damaged, the principal knew what we were up to, etc. Wholesome fun.
After the fifth time of coming home with a “the cops showed up” story, our well-meaning parents asked us to please find another game to play.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayvok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The War on Humanitarians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323013</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/18/the-war-on-humanitarians/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T14:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ilan Pappé is 70 years old. He’s Jewish. His parents fled persecution in Hitler’s Germany. He’s an Israeli and served in the IDF. He hasn’t been radicalized by TikTok. He is, in fact, one of Israel’s most celebrated historians. None of that stopped Pappé from being detained by Biden’s TSA in Detroit, interrogated by the agents from the Department of Homeland Security about whether he’s a supporter of Hamas, and having his phone data copied. This crackdown isn’t about protecting Jews or  Israelis or preserving the exceptional nature of the Holocaust.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The War on Humanitarians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crocal in "Cyber Security: A pre-war reality check"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40398331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40398331"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T12:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I cannot agree more with the author’s point of view. As an illustration, many people want to use GPS for the safe positioning of trains in the European Train Control Systems. This makes the space sector happy because it justifies the expenditures incurred for putting things like Galileo in orbit. However, in a pre-war check exercise, one immediately come to the conclusion that all European trains would crawl to a stop in case the GPS is jammed or interfered with. We were not very listened to… until Ukraine.
Critical infrastructures should not depend from things that are located in space or on the other side of the planet. These are one of those things were market logic should be anticipated with regulations (we can’t wait for the next Titanic). Another point touched by the article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crocal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/18/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271701</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-18-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T10:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our far-seeing daily links: animal music, anti-sex bed, Powell's Covid, China real estate rescue, Europe youth hearts far right, Israel poor prospects, pier promo, decoding Kharkiv, China-Russia monster meeting, Garland sanction progresses. Trump wants Biden drug test, Assange, union vote wins and losses]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by smt88 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396533"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T04:56:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look at Sam Altman's career and tweets. He's a clown at best, and at worst he's a manipulative crook who only cares about his own enrichment and uses pro-social ideas to give himself a veneer of trustworthiness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smt88</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mwigdahl in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396395</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396395"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T04:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best approach to circumventing the nondisclosure agreement is for the affected employees to get together, write out everything they want to say about OpenAI, train an LLM on that text, and then release it.
Based on these companies' arguments that copyrighted material is not actually reproduced by these models, and that any seemingly-infringing use is the responsibility of the user of the model rather than those who produced it, anyone could freely generate an infinite number of high-truthiness OpenAI anecdotes, freshly laundered by the inference engine, that couldn't be used against the original authors without OpenAI invalidating their own legal stance with respect to their own models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mwigdahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by throwaway598 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396209</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40396209"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T03:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That OpenAI are institutionally unethical. That such a young company can be become rotten so quickly can only be due to leadership instruction or leadership failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>throwaway598</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Buttons840 in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395918</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395918"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So part of their compensation for working is equity, and when they leave thay have to sign an additional agreement in order to keep their previously earned compensation? How is this legal? Mine as well tell them they have to give all their money back too.
What's the consideration for this contract?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Buttons840</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by modeless in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395842"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of the brouhaha about OpenAI is silly, I think. But this is gross. Forcing employees to sign a perpetual non-disparagement agreement under threat of clawing back the large majority of their already earned compensation should not be legal. Honestly it probably isn't, but it'll take someone brave enough to sue to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>modeless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jay-barronville in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395702</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395702"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T01:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It probably would be better to switch the link from the X post to the Vox article [0].
From the article:
“““
It turns out there’s a very clear reason for [why no one who had once worked at OpenAI was talking]. I have seen the extremely restrictive off-boarding agreement that contains nondisclosure and non-disparagement provisions former OpenAI employees are subject to. It forbids them, for the rest of their lives, from criticizing their former employer. Even acknowledging that the NDA exists is a violation of it.
If a departing employee declines to sign the document, or if they violate it, they can lose all vested equity they earned during their time at the company, which is likely worth millions of dollars. One former employee, Daniel Kokotajlo, who posted that he quit OpenAI “due to losing confidence that it would behave responsibly around the time of AGI,” has confirmed publicly that he had to surrender what would have likely turned out to be a huge sum of money in order to quit without signing the document.
”””
[0]: https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2024/5/17/24158478/openai...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jay-barronville</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fragmede in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395483</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395483"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T00:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's time to find a lawyer. I'm not one but  there's an intersection with California SB 331, also known as “The Silenced No More Act”. while it is focused more on sexual harrasment, it's not limited to that, and these contracts may run afoul of that.
https://silencednomore.org/the-silenced-no-more-act]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fragmede</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thorum in "OpenAI departures: Why can’t former employees talk?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395018</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40395018"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T23:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extra respect is due to Jan Leike, then:
https://x.com/janleike/status/1791498174659715494]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thorum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by phire in "Ubershaders: A Ridiculous Solution to an Impossible Problem (2017)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394442</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394442"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T21:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has it really been 9 years since I started working on Ubershaders?
I'm a little surprised no better solution has come along. Vulkan didn't even exist back then (and DirectX 12 had only just released) but instead of making things better, it digs it's feet even deeper into the assumption that all shaders will be known ahead of time (resulting in long "shader recompilation" dialogs on startup on many games).
I've been tempted to build my own fast shader compiler into Dolphin for many common GPU architectures. Hell, it wouldn't even be a proper compiler, more of a templated emitter as all shaders fit a pattern. Register allocation and scheduling could all be pre-calculated.
But that would be even more insane than ubershaders, as it would be one backend per gpu arch. And some drivers (like Nvidia) don't provide a way to inject pre-compiled shader binaries.
On the positive side, ubershaders do solve the problem, and modern GPU drivers do a much better job at accepting ubershaders than they did 9 years ago. Though that's primarily because (as far as I'm aware) examples of Dolphin's ubershader have made their way into every single shader compiler test suite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phire</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ttul in "Thinking out loud about 2nd-gen email"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394319</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40394319"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T21:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I run one of the largest email sending services on the internet. I have been living the “mess” of internet email for over 20 years.
Here’s the thing: despite the internet’s email system being complex and confusing and riddled with problems, it is universally adopted and interoperable. No other open communication tool can boast of email’s massive interoperability.
Any new system will face the impossible burden of winning hearts and minds while the old system continues to chug along with billions of annual R&D spending and dozens of conferences full of smart people working on solving problems.
Even if “MX2” can peacefully coexist in the DNS, why would anyone spend the millions of dollars in engineering effort to move while their teams are busy building the latest layer that’s been invented to patch over the current system?
By all means if you want to propose a new email system, show up at IETF or M3AAWG and make a bold proposal. Someone will buy you a beer while they explain why you are much better off getting into the mud pit with the rest of us and working on the next pragmatic fix to keep things rolling along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ttul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To my Sunflower]]></title>
        <id>https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/</id>
        <link href="https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:26:07.405Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little bird came to see me,
What’s you name? - I asked.
And he chirped the following words:
Leave a comment or Stay in touch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what makes for a good video essay?]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/what-makes-for-a-good-video-essay/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/what-makes-for-a-good-video-essay/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:46:01.832Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i've been a long-time fan of video essays for a while now, my first watches of the medium date back to my freshman year of high school with videos like Born Sexy Yesterday by Pop Culture Detective and Whiplash vs. Black Swan -- The Anatomy of the Obsessed Artist. I recall posting the links to these on my twitter and tumblr raving about how good and eye-opening they are, recommending them to my friends and mutuals, and soon thereafter reading their thoughts about the essays too. video essays became a sort of internet cultural phenomenon around this time, spurred on by those very videos, the former now holding 11 million views and the former with just a bit under 6 million. but what is so captivating about these videos? what about a video can make millions not only tune in for the first time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CorrectingYou in "Bend: a high-level language that runs on GPUs (via HVM2)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40393253</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40393253"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OP comes around with some of the coolest things posted in HN recently, and all he gets is extensive criticism, when it is clear that this is an early version :/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CorrectingYou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zero_k in "Computer scientists invent an efficient new way to count"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40392831</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40392831"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T18:25:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was involved with implementing the DNF volume counting version of this with the authors. You can see my blog post of it here:
https://www.msoos.org/2023/09/pepin-our-probabilistic-approx...
And the code here: https://github.com/meelgroup/pepin
Often, 30% of the time is spent in IO of reading the file, that's how incredibly fast this algorithm is. Crazy stuff.
BTW, Knuth contributed to the algo, Knuths' notes: https://cs.stanford.edu/~knuth/papers/cvm-note.pdf
He actually took time off (a whole month) from TAOCP to do this. Also, he is exactly as crazy good as you'd imagine. Just mind-blowing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zero_k</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jcims in "A Trial HIV Vaccine Triggered Elusive and Essential Antibodies in Humans"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40391864</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40391864"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T16:54:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation of how HIV infects a single T-cell
https://vimeo.com/260291607]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jcims</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[don't skip the openings]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:35:12.065Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the absolute worst thing someone can tell me about their anime viewing preferences has nothing to do with the kind of show they watch but how they watch it.
image from director nakayama ryū's chainsaw man (2022).
skipping openings just because you're on a binge can so easily rob you of what i'd argue are the best narrative and collective highs a series can offer.1
from a purely functional standpoint, they give us time to breathe and process what exactly we're watching. take, for example, the three versions of shippuden's penultimate opening— blood circulator. each variant denotes which point of the story you're at, and primes you for what's to come. (if you pay attention, you'll notice they lead into each other seamlessly! so neat.)
sometimes it's instinctual and more about building antici…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[traversing across a rainbow bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:27:15.392Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we lost our second dog today.
sherlock, my aunt’s darling boy, passed at 4:20 in the morning. at 3am, she knocked on my door saying the fateful words—i think sherlock’s dying. it was like my whole world came to a stop.
he died in her arms.
10 and a half beautiful years of his company. our kind, kind sherlock who sometimes snapped at us when we kissed him too much. our darling, darling boy who was great at finding toys we’d hide from him; who liked to eat the cheese crackers my grandma fed him when no one was looking.
he had chronic heart failure. we were counting down the months, really, but nothing could’ve ever prepared me for that 3am knock, his fading heartbeat, and his little eyes that wouldn’t close.
ten years ago today, my aunt’s dog quli—a botched attempt of naming him 去来, a dog wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DaiPlusPlus in "Non-Euclidean Doom: what happens to a game when pi is not 3.14159 (2022) [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40390195</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40390195"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T14:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens is the graphics and movement get glitchy and eventually unplayable - I wouldn’t call this “non-Euclidean Doom” - just “consequences of messing with the constants of the universe” - whereas I’d expect an actual non-Euclidean Doom to be like this: https://youtu.be/kEB11PQ9Eo8?si=0HNlpGFBii2AIK1n]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DaiPlusPlus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[even the dustiest of streets has a place in memory]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:09:35.956Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is our last day at the grandparents’ house. Tomorrow we take a taxi to the city we flew into and we’ll spend the day and night there before departing in the morning.
Mom is in her parents’ bedroom with Grandma and Grandpa. She’s sharing photos of us to Grandma and showing her how to download them to her tablet. I laugh as Mom gets frustrated with Grandma’s technological ineptitude. It’s her turn to teach technology to a Boomer.
Earlier I mustered up the courage to wander a little further from home than normal. I walked all the way to the train station and park in the center of town. I’m glad I did, because I saw a lot of things I hadn’t before.
As the sun dips below the horizon vendors set up tables in front of the supermarket. They sell a wide assortment of wares. Cages with corgis,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Zerzan - He Means it — Do you?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Zerzan
Title: He Means it — Do you?
Date: 2002
Source: Retrieved on May 2024 from archive.org

 Today opposition is anarchist or it is non-existent. This is the barest minimum coherence in the struggle against an engulfing totality. 
 And while ten years ago the milieu generally called anti-authoritarian was largely syndicalist, those leftist residues are fading out altogether. Very few now find a vista of work and production at all liberatory. 
 As the smell of this false and rotting order rises to the heavens, registering an unprecedented toll on all living beings, faith in the whole modern world evaporates. Industrialism and its ensemble looks like it has been a very bad idea, sort of a wrong turn begun still earlier. Civilization itself, with its logic of domestication and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sph in "The Downfall of DeviantArt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387452</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387452"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> This had consequences for deviantArt's revenue. It meant that we could not run ads from the "reputable" ad networks
Advertising: perhaps the best and most effective involuntary ally of the Puritan movement.
It is a shame that the Internet that we have created depends pretty much solely on that form of revenue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by earthnail in "Deutsche Bahn introduces "MetaWindow""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387373</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387373"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love this. I read so much criticism here, but noise pollution is a main issue when it comes to railroads in residential zones.
Yes, punctuality is an issue with Deutsche Bahn. No, this doesn’t fix that instantly. But as an organisation you can work on two things at the same time.
This invention is spectacular. I wish more people would work on noise pollution. It makes a huge difference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>earthnail</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pixelmonkey in "Computer scientists invent an efficient new way to count"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387154</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40387154"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This algorithm seems to resemble HyperLogLog (and all its variants), which is also cited in the research paper. Using the same insight of the estimation value of tracking whether we've hit a "run" of heads or tails, but flipping the idea on its head (heh), it leads to the simpler algorithm described, which is about discarding memorized values on the basis of runs of heads/tails.
This also works especially well (that is, efficiently) in the streaming case, allowing you to keep something resembling a "counter" for the distinct elements, albeit with a error rate.
The benefit of HyperLogLog is that it behaves similarly to a hash set in some respects -- you can add items, count distinct them, and, importantly, merge two HLLs together (union), all the while keeping memory fixed to mere kilobytes even for billion-item sets. In distributed data stores, this is the trick behind Elasticsearch/OpenSearch cardinality agg, as well as behind Redis/Redict with its PFADD/PFMERGE/PFCOUNT.
I am not exactly sure how this CVM algorithm compares to HLL, but they got Knuth to review it, and they claim an undergrad can implement it easily, so it must be pretty good!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pixelmonkey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re: the fear of audience expectations, by gabby]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:07:27.208Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This open letter is inspired by a post I read yesterday by Gabby of woolgathering fame.)
Dear Gabby,
It’s not just you: getting over the fear of expectations is hard. I still struggle with it, after 300 something posts. I have a feeling I’ll never get completely over it, but here’s what’s helped me so far.
Posting a lot helps. I’ve posted so much nonsense on this blog that these days there’s not much I can do that will be worse than something I’ve written before. Somehow, I still have regular readers. Realizing that there are people out there still interested in what I have to say after all the good and not so good is a great comfort. From what you write, you seem to have discovered as much.
Another perk of having a large body of work is that each new piece you create becomes a smaller and smaller part of your entire oeuvre. When you’re first starting out, it feels like each creation you put out defines you. After all, if you only have one post, it’s the only thing people can judge you on. If you have a hundred, a wayward post is a drop in the bucket.
That said, wouldn’t you still want to see the creations your friends or favorite creators aren’t proud of? Or see their art even if it doesn’t quite fit the niche they’ve carved out for themselves? Everybody half-asses things in their own unique way. There’s a beauty in doing things imperfectly, too.
All that is to say, keep up what you’re doing. Creative inertia is a very real thing. You’re doing the right thing by posting, even if you feel like you’re just posting to break the streak of inactivity. Writing in any form begets more writing.
Anyway, welcome back to Bear! It’s good to have you back.
Yours,
misu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Jews be Nazis?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322714</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/can-jews-be-nazis/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many people, the question is inflammatory. The crimes of the German Nazis were of such magnitude that comparison with any other historical violence is invidious. The genocide of the Jews was deliberate and methodical and intended to eliminate every last one. The goal was the same with the Romani and Sinti people. By comparison, the Israelis – currently accused of genocide -- are rank amateurs. They have so far killed some 35,000 Palestinians in Gaza out of a population of 2.3 million. More
The post Can Jews be Nazis? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the Missiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322850</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/follow-the-missiles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, the Biden administration has approved more than 100 Foreign Military Sales arms transfers to Israel. Two of the shipments used an emergency authority to circumvent Congressional review. The surge of weapons transfers to Israel began in early October and so much material was being shipped that the Pentagon had a difficult time finding enough cargo aircraft to deliver them. More
The post Follow the Missiles appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking Clearly About the Protesters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322963</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/thinking-clearly-about-the-protesters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Do you think ‘sit-ins’ at lunch counters, ‘Freedom Buses’ and other demonstrations by Negroes will hurt or help the Negro's chances of being integrated in the South?” This question was posed by Gallup, a leading polling organization, back in 1961, during the heyday of the Civil Rights Movement. A majority of Americans at the time, 57%, believed that the sit-ins would “hurt” the movement. They were wrong. Today, we credit the Civil Rights Movement with ending racial segregation in the United States, but we cannot disconnect its success from its tactics. Martin Luther King Jr. was no advocate of passive resistance, but a firm believer in “militant nonviolence”– a consistent torrent of protests in the form of boycotts, mass marches, sit-ins, and strikes. These are similar tactics to those that students across the world are using to spread awareness of the over 30,000 Palestinians killed in Gaza and to push their universities to dissociate from the Israeli State. More
The post Thinking Clearly About the Protesters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raihan Alam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Permafrost Showdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322855</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/permafrost-showdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the Arctic to Antarctica the planet is sagging, dripping, slouching, changing the face of 10,000 years of nature coexisting with humanity side-by-side until only recently as it transforms into an adversarial relationship. Permafrost ranks alongside the Arctic, Antarctica, Greenland, The Great Barrier Reef, and the world’s three largest rainforests as the most important determinates of this changing future. Within permafrost’s confines exist thousands of years of latent ingredients that have the potential to set the world on fire. Its impact could be transcendent. More
The post Permafrost Showdown appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friedman, Biden and US Weapons Sales to Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322596</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/friedman-biden-and-us-weapons-sales-to-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a long oped on Sunday titled “Biden’s Error in Pausing Military Aid,” Thomas Friedman buys into Israeli propaganda that describes Iran as an “existential threat,” and harshly denigrates President Joe Biden for announcing a pause in U.S. weapons sales to Israel. Friedman is critical of Biden for announcing the pause in the transfer of 3,500 bombs to Israel in an “off-the-cuff-exchange with CNN’s Erin Burnett during a campaign stop in Wisconsin. More
The post Friedman, Biden and US Weapons Sales to Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Humble Request]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322868</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-humble-request/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please, if you can, chip in this Spring Fund Drive, we have almost reached our goal.
The post A Humble Request appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No One’s Neutral Come Eurovision Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323045</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/no-ones-neutral-come-eurovision-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Eurovision Song Contest cannot be neutral. There is just one winner. That winner is chosen by combining the popular cellphone votes of millions of viewers with the tallies of the five-member juries in each country. There is just one contestant—whether a soloist or an entire band—from each nation that makes it into the finals.  More
The post No One’s Neutral Come Eurovision Time appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brutal Punishment: The Sentencing of David McBride]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322838</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/a-brutal-punishment-the-sentencing-of-david-mcbride/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, it’s best not to leave the issue of justice to the judges.  They do what they must: consult the statutes, test the rivers of power, and hope that their ruling will not be subject to appeal.  David McBride, the man who revealed that Australia’s special forces in Afghanistan had dimmed and muddied before exhaustion,  More
The post A Brutal Punishment: The Sentencing of David McBride appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel as a Jewish Nation-State and Antisemitism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322908</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/israel-as-a-jewish-nation-state-and-antisemitism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Judaism cannot be separated from Israel. Zionism is, simply put, the manifestation of that belief,” stated a recent message from Jewish students at Columbia University. Israel’s politics are closely intertwined with its religious beliefs. Since 2018, Israel legally considers itself a Jewish nation-state with no separation between religion and politics. That explains why Israelis consider  More
The post Israel as a Jewish Nation-State and Antisemitism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Rube! Why No Room for Others at the Biden/Trump Debate Circus?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322917</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/hey-rube-why-no-room-for-others-at-the-biden-trump-debate-circus/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Robert F. Kennedy, Jr. participate in either of the two presidential election debates thus far announced by the Joe Biden and Donald Trump campaigns? How about independents Cornel West and Afroman, Green party candidate Jill Stein, Constitution Party candidate Randall Terry, and whoever receives the Libertarian Party’s nomination over Memorial Day weekend? The answer,  More
The post Hey, Rube! Why No Room for Others at the Biden/Trump Debate Circus? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wilderness Act at 60: A Brief Overview]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322941</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/the-wilderness-act-at-60-a-brief-overview/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 3, 1964, humanity’s unrelenting quest to tame, civilize, industrialize, and obliterate wild nature crashed into the Wilderness Act, signed into law by President Johnson on that momentous day. This visionary legislation—written primarily by the late Howard Zahniser of the Wilderness Society—created a federal policy to secure for the American people “an enduring resource  More
The post The Wilderness Act at 60: A Brief Overview appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howie Wolke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Features of Ancient Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322902</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/seven-features-of-ancient-enterprise/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are multiple differences between antiquity’s economic practices and those of the modern world, and these should be borne in mind when considering the changing context for enterprise through the centuries. Whereas modern business largely operates on credit, in archaic and classical times handicraft workshops were located on basically self-sufficient landed estates, including those of  More
The post Seven Features of Ancient Enterprise appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1,3-Dichloropropene: The Dangerous, Sweet-Smelling Pesticide You’ve Never Heard Of]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322899</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/13-dichloropropene-the-dangerous-sweet-smelling-pesticide-youve-never-heard-of/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California regulators were stunned by their air monitor results in April 1990. Concentrations of a cancer-causing pesticide at schools in Merced County were so high that regulators immediately stopped any use of that pesticide in California. It’s a chemical with an unwieldy name, 1,3-dichloropropene, that you may have never heard about. But there are many reasons why you should be  More
The post 1,3-Dichloropropene: The Dangerous, Sweet-Smelling Pesticide You’ve Never Heard Of appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Caroline Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck on Stupid, Biden and the Democrats Face Disaster in November]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322914</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/stuck-on-stupid-biden-and-the-democrats-face-disaster-in-november/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Let them eat cake,” Marie Antoinette once famously said, disdaining the immiseration of peasants in pre-revolutionary France.  Joe Biden didn’t use those exact words last week during his interview with CNN’s Erin Burnett, but his tone-deafness about the suffering of millions of Americans grappling with high food and gas prices and unaffordable rents was palpable. Burnett  More
The post Stuck on Stupid, Biden and the Democrats Face Disaster in November appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 20after4 in "The Downfall of DeviantArt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385401</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385401"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:29:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked at deviantArt from 2009 to 2013. It was my dream job. At the time deviantArt made money a few ways.
In no particular order, because I don't know which were profitable or which represented a larger portion of revenue:
- Subscriptions (users could pay for a few extra features and to disable ads on the site)
- DeviantArt branded merch.
- Prints and products with users' art printed on them
- Sponsored Contests. These promoted movies or other media properties, or software of interest to artists. Often the prizes included Wacom tablets and Adobe Photoshop licenses.
During my time there a significant problem we were dealing with was due to deviantArt's stance on adult content. Anything was allowed as long as it wasn't outright pornography.  In practice that meant that nudes were allowed but sexual acts were not. This had consequences for deviantArt's revenue. It meant that we could not run ads from the "reputable" ad networks and were forced to deal with seedier outfits that often (e.g. constantly) included malware in the display ads, exposing users to all sorts of nasty stuff. One of my projects was to detect and/or prevent the malware ads which proved challenging and at least given the amount of resources devoted to it, it was not very fruitful.
It really is sad for me to see what deviantArt has devolved into. Once the original founders sold out a few years ago I really didn't hold out much hope for the site's future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>20after4</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by derefr in "A forged Apple employee badge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385318</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40385318"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T01:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> And that typed text is way, way cleaner than any typewriter I’ve seen.
Pedantic point: electric typewriters (which have existed since the 1960s) do type in a way that looks exactly like this.
(In fact, note that the text on the real employee ID card, shown later in the article, doesn't look any less clean! It's just set in a different, narrower font.)
The smudginess of mechanical typewriters comes from 1. them striking (and especially, releasing) at the same speed you're depressing the key, and 2. having many of the keys necessarily approach the ribbon from an angle.
The keys being swung weakly by your fingers, also has the additional implication that the ink ribbons used in mechanical typewriters have to be soft and squishy (so: made of cloth), and use thin inks. These properties ensure a transfer from even a low-velocity impact. But the trade-off is that cloth ink ribbons transfer only a rough outline of what's struck; and thin inks are high-bleed inks.
An electric typewriter, playing out a pre-buffered line with a crisp, predictable report, using linear actuators and a rotating-ball type-head to bang a tape ribbon loaded with high-viscosity ink onto the page, can create text indistinguishable from books/newspapers of the same period, or from modern laser-printer reproductions of the same font faces. They're essentially character-at-a-time letterpresses!
(Also, ignoring electric typewriters for a sec: inks bleed more on thin, cheap paper. But this is [a forgery of] an employee ID card — where, for durability, a nice heavyweight paper or cardstock would have been used. You're always going to get a better-looking result inking such paper.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>derefr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zmmmmm in "Slack AI Training with Customer Data"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40384975</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40384975"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T00:18:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> For any model that will be used broadly across all of our customers, we do not build or train these models in such a way that they could learn, memorise, or be able to reproduce some part of Customer Data
This feels so full of subtle qualifiers and weasel words that it generates far more distrust than trust.
It only refers to models used "broadly across all" customers - so if it's (a) not used "broadly" or (b) only used for some subset of customers, the whole statement doesn't apply. Which actually sounds really bad because the logical implication is that data CAN leak outside those circumstances.
They need to reword this. Whoever wrote it is a liability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zmmmmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lily Lynch: &ldquo;Crosshairs&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shooting of Robert Fico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Kubernetes workload isolation and security using Kata Containers]]></title>
        <id>f2c6d73c0a99a5e7cc62d68bc9a22528e5bead29</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/enhancing-kubernetes-workload-isolation-and-security-using-kata-containers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have become the dominant method for deploying and managing applications in recent years. Their widespread adoption is attributed to numerous advantages, such as isolation, efficient hardware use, scalability, and portability. In situations where resource isolation is critical for system security, many users are forced to rely on virtual machines (VMs) to mitigate the impact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mirash Gjolaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye: Revolutionizing HD map creation for autonomous vehicles with Spark on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>ef56de61f8631e9846e056ddafcc46ba422f73dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/mobileye-revolutionizing-hd-map-creation-for-autonomous-vehicles-with-spark-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye (Nasdaq: MBLY), a global leader in advanced driver-assistance systems (ADAS), is at the forefront of the autonomous driving revolution. Founded in 1999, they have pioneered groundbreaking technologies such as REM™ crowdsourced mapping, True-Redundancy™ sensing, and Responsibility-Sensitive Safety (RSS). These innovations are paving the way for a future filled with self-driving vehicles and advanced mobility […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentzi Lifshitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSS is really simple, why do so many find it complicated?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7606</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/rss-really-simple-why-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris, writing at uncountable thoughts: RSS is a pervasive, but little known, web technology that allows you aggregate all your content into one place for easy reading. There are very few websites without an RSS feed, although many don’t advertise the link (or, even realise they have it). When you put an RSS feed link […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "The Downfall of DeviantArt"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40382759</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40382759"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T20:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So much of the DeviantArt story reads like Tumblr. Two platforms appealing to amateur and small artists grow to great relevance among a patchwork of subcultures. Then, they start trying to turn a profit and end up alienating the entire userbase that carried them to that point. DeviantArt is much further down that road than Tumblr is, though. It's sad to see. Both platforms were key to the WWW of my childhood.
I wish the artists well in their AI copyright legal pursuits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost opportunities?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/16/lost-opportunities/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T19:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford A pile of bricks is not a house.  A group of individuals is not an economy. A lot has to happen between the one and the other.  Which is why writing theories about economies as if it were simply an accumulation of individuals and their associated capital base misses the mark.  Nor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[158. Compounding heartbreaks and unsent love letters]]></title>
        <id>https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/</id>
        <link href="https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:23:05.119Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think one of the biggest reasons why I was utterly pissed off at the dude for ditching me was all of that  built-up anticipation, only to be disappointed at the very end. I had this really big expectation, but I think I really shouldn't count on people too much. In my mind, I hadn't had a little trip in a while, and having that cool rendezvous experience with a cute guy? I was so keen.
I can't believe that I made plans with someone, looked forward to our weekend getaway, only to find out he's changed his plans without a word and flew off somewhere instead. It completely left me feeling confused and downright pissed off. I didn't think I deserved to be left hanging like that and to not have an in-person apology. I haven't even seen him ever since we went to the museum together 1 2.

I sai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Stable Diffusion ComfyUI on AWS elastically and efficiently]]></title>
        <id>dcd98043e309fb462fb16c1c99293fceecad41fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/deploy-stable-diffusion-comfyui-on-aws-elastically-and-efficiently/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction ComfyUI is an open-source node-based workflow solution for Stable Diffusion. It offers the following advantages: Significant performance optimization for SDXL model inference High customizability, allowing users granular control Portable workflows that can be shared easily Developer-friendly Due to these advantages, ComfyUI is increasingly being used by artistic creators. In this post, we will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Recent Inflationary Spike a Global Phenomenon?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29961</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/is-the-recent-inflationary-spike-a-global-phenomenon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, inflation rose almost simultaneously in most economies around the world. After peaking in mid-2022, inflation then went into decline—a fall that was just as universal as the initial rise. In this post, we explore the interrelation of inflation dynamics across OECD countries by constructing a measure of the persistence of global inflation. We then study the extent to which the persistence of global inflation reflects broad-based swings, as opposed to idiosyncratic country-level movements. Our main finding is that the spike and subsequent moderation in global inflation in the post-pandemic period were driven by persistent movements. When we look at measures of inflation that include food and energy prices, most of the persistence appears to be broad-based, suggesting that international oil and commodity prices played an important role in global inflation dynamics. Excluding food and energy prices in the analysis still shows a broad-based persistence, although with a substantial increase in the role of country-specific factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martín Almuzara, Babur Kocaoglu, and Argia Sbordone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;A Bronx Tale&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperativism in New York.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - Thomas Paine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-thomas-paine?v=1715846977</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-thomas-paine?v=1715846977"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: Thomas Paine
Date: February 6, 1890
Notes: Delivered on February 2, 1890 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century February 6, 1890. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Thomas Paine is one of the most maligned and least understood of men. One of the noblest minded of men in most respects, he has been represented for nearly a century as a groveling nature and a monster of iniquity. Supremely generous in all his public career, he is said to have been mean and self-seeking. Having refused to profit by the copyright of his religious and political works, he is called parsimonious. A rarely equaled friend of mankind, he is scorned as the enem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - The Sins of Government]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-the-sins-of-government?v=1715846855</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-the-sins-of-government?v=1715846855"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: The Sins of Government
Date: March 13, 1890
Notes: Delivered on March 9, 1890 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on March 13, 1890. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 I am aware that in delivering a number of addresses with the object of persuading you that government by physical force is the real cause of poverty and the slowness of human development mentally and morally, I am opposing preconceived opinions, prejudices and superstitions even stronger than are aroused by open declarations of Atheism. Political superstition is more deeply rooted than religious superstition. Multitudes of persons have ceased to believe in Jehovah …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - ​First Anniversary Address]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-first-anniversary-address?v=1715846738</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-first-anniversary-address?v=1715846738"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: ​First Anniversary Address
Date: January 10, 1889
Notes: Delivered on January 6, 1889 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on January 10, 1889.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Unity Congregation has completed its first year of existence and, I hope, of usefulness. As we look back on that year I think we shall agree that it has been a year of peace and prosperity for which we should be profoundly grateful. Our career thus far has exceeded my most sanguine expectations. The congregation shave been large and enthusiastic, probably averaging during the year nearly two thousand persons in the three cities where our meetings have been held each Sunday.[1] They have come tog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-anarchism?v=1715846565</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-anarchism?v=1715846565"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: Anarchism
Date: July 4, 1889
Notes: Delivered on June 30, 1889 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on July 4, 1889. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Good people who hold opinions not commonly understood generally have a bad name. The world is ready to believe almost anything of a man except that he is a genuinely good man. If his life is stainless but unconventional, the world suspects some hidden shame or base motive. So far are most people from understanding or desiring what is true and right that the highest truth is often believed to be the lowest lie, and the purest right is looked upon as the blackest wrong. 
 Thus Jesus,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Hugh Owen Pentecost (1848–1907)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-hugh-owen-pentecost-1848-1907?v=1715846400</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-hugh-owen-pentecost-1848-1907?v=1715846400"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Hugh Owen Pentecost (1848–1907)
Subtitle: A Biographical Sketch
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Because he changed into so many different suits during his long career, historians have not focused on the dashing radical orator Hugh O. Pentecost. 
 Born September 30, 1848 at New Harmony, Indiana, Pentecost was given his middle name for Robert Owen, whose followers had established the town as a Fourierist colony a generation earlier. His parents, Emma Flower and Hugh Lockett Pentecost, were of English descent, with many Protestant clergy in their family tree. Hugh moved at age two to Albion, Illinois, which was founded by his grandfather, Scarborough Pentecost, Jr. 
 Hugh went as a boy to Kentucky during the Civil War, where he …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[catching up]]></title>
        <id>https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/</id>
        <link href="https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:28:05.926Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[woah, hello bear! it sure has been a while since i've last written.
a little bit after my last post, i went on some back-to-back trips around asia. i spent a few days in seoul and about a week in bali. i did actually write about both of those trips with the intention of sharing them with all of you on here but for some reason i couldn't quite bring myself to publish it. i've never really written on any sort of platform before this, but i'm assuming that just like visual art, some writing is just meant to be kept to yourself.
with the only things i had written in that span of 4 weeks being private, i didn't really have much else to post. and the longer i went without posting, the harder it was to come back. this always happens to me. it was the exact same mindset i had with my art account o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Code to Quill: Embark on a Legendary Kubernetes Quest with SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've likely heard the adage, "Contributing isn't just about writing code",
whispered in forums or seen etched into the digital walls of open source communities.
But what depth of truth lies within this ancient wisdom, especially in the vast,
evolving world of Kubernetes?
Today, contributing to open source extends far beyond the realm of coding.
It's an inclusive journey that welcomes the diverse skills of all who wish
to be a part of it. Whether you're a seasoned developer or someone whose strengths
lie outside traditional programming, your contributions hold immense value.
Imagine yourself embarking on a journey that leverages your expertise and love
for free software to enhance your capabilities and strengthen the very foundation
of the Kubernetes ecosystem. This is a real opportunity …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) winners]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7591</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-australian-book-industry-awards-abias-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) were held last week, on Thursday 9 May. The ABIAs are considered the Australian book publishing industry’s night of nights. A book-ish version of the Oscars, if you will. Award winners include Pip Williams, with her novel The Bookbinder of Jericho, in the General Fiction Book of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - How to find Your Local Wobbly History]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: How to find Your Local Wobbly History
Date: 2000
Notes: Published in Anarcho-Syndicalist Review #28, Spring 2000.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 One can find the forgotten Wobbly names and faces, strike stories, union halls and martyrs’ graves in any city where the IWW earned its legendary reputation. It is easy to find thorough information on the luminaries, such as Tresca, Flynn and Giovanitti, but what about those local organizers who invited these major figures to town, and then kept working after they were gone, pouring the wine of rebellion into workers’ hearts? It may take some time, but in all probability you’ll find syndicalist monuments and hallowed ground that you walk past every day, but never knew existed. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists
Date: September 2006
Notes: An earlier, much shorter version of this article, “Anarchists in Medicine and Pharmacy: Philadelphia, 1889–1930,” appeared in Clamor Magazine #6 (Dec. 2000/Jan. 2001), and had previously been posted on both the Guinea Pig Zero and Dead Anarchists websites.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 In the City of Philadelphia in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, there was a large group of professionals who practiced medicine or pharmacy as a livelihood, while committing great energies to the anarchist movement. Looking past the surface, we find a closely knit community of intellectuals who treated their comrades as patients, educated the publ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes to hours, hours to days, this is how you spend your time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7593</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/minute-hours-hours-days-how-you-spend-your-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A breakdown of how people, Americans in this case, spend their time, by each decade of their life. Things like sleeping, eating, working, caring for others, and socialising. The crunch is definitely on in our thirties, forties, and fifties, when time for sleep and socialising, for instance, is reduced. Kurzgesagt also did a presentation a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltairine de Cleyre - On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Voltairine de Cleyre
Title: On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion
Subtitle: A Private Letter to Samuel H. Gordon
Date: 1897
Notes: Edited and introduced by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

​Introduction
 Voltairine de Cleyre, by far Philadelphia’s brightest anarchist light, was 30 years old when, during the late summer or fall of 1897, she wrote the following letter in London. The letter was never finished, nor was it signed, dated, or mailed. Yet the letter, clearly in her handwriting and style, came to rest in a large group of her letters in the papers of Joseph J. Cohen (1878–1953), de Cleyre’s longtime associate in anarchism, which are stored in the Bund Collection, YIVO Archives, in New York City. It is one of the most compellin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin longlist for Australian novel writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7596</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-longlist-australian-novel-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well this is exciting, the longlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for Australian novel writing, has been published. Not sure how I missed the official announcement, but I went searching for a date the longlist would be unveiled, and instead found the longlist itself: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson - All Eyes on Rafah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson
Title: All Eyes on Rafah
Date: May 15th, 2024
Notes: The following article is a transcript of a speech given by Geelong Anarchist Communists member Tommy Lawson at an Independent and Peaceful Australia Network (IPAN) ‘Rally for Rafah’ held on Saturday 11th of May. Its content is supported unanimously by Geelong Anarchist Communists. We have decided to publish it today, on the 76th anniversary of the Nakba (‘catastrophe’) to declare that we stand with those resisting genocide and colonisation.
Source: Retrieved on May 15th, 2024 from https://geelonganarchists.org/2024/05/15/all-eyes-on-rafah/.

During al Nakba over 750,000 Palestinian people, from a total population of 1.9 million, were made refugees beyond the borders of their homeland. 53…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The aborted experiment of the Bank of the South in Latin America and the alternative policies that could have been adopted at the continental level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2007–2008, I helped to prepare the creation of the “Bank of the South” after being requested to assist in framing Ecuador's position on the issue by Argentine and Ecuadorian economists, as well as Ricardo Patiño, Minister of Economy and Finance in the administration of President Rafael Correa of Ecuador. I did so with commitment and without remuneration. In April 2007, in Quito, we drafted a proposal outlining Ecuador's position on the statutes, operating model, and objectives of the future (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Bank of the South, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World of Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T16:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A central feature of neo-liberal capitalism, which has ruled the global economy since the 1990s, is to deepen and widen inequalities. It makes a tiny minority indecently richer while leaving the majority in the lurch. Women and minorities such as indigenous peoples, LGBTQIA+ or racialized people are badly hit by those inequalities. In a situation in which famine and extreme poverty keep increasing, the withdrawal of the State further feeds the vicious circle of poverty and inequality. (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Capitalism, 
North, 
Inegalites 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7083</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/fixed-power-designs-its-not-if-you-peek-its-what-you-peek-at/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Sometimes we cannot estimate the required sample size needed to power an experiment before starting it. To alleviate this [...]
The post Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:10:26.460Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the longest time, I wanted to work in big tech. I got placed in one such company from campus placements. It was mostly due to my c programming skills and research work.
I am grateful for the role. I get to work on something I like. The people I work with are smart and kind. But it is just a job. Both to me and to the people I work with. One of the major perks that the HR department keeps repeating is a great work-life balance. You get time for yourself. That is very true.
Isn't that great? You get paid well. Get enough time for a good social life and side projects. You can also fund these side projects with your salary.
Yes, but what about working in a startup? A place where a lot of super passionate people are going ham at what they do. To them, it is not a job but a mission. A sort of crazy cult. Filled with kind passionate nerds. Some place where you own part of the dream. Have equity.
It sounds nice. But such places are very rare. The startup scene in India is pretty horrible. I have heard some really bad stories. So many of the startups look cool on the outside. Have great pay even. But are horrible to work for. I have had friends experience this.
I also feel like I am not good enough for those truly cracked places yet. So I am happy where I am for now and just Skill maxxing. I want to feel like a really capable engineer. I see so many of them at my org. All are really kind and happy to guide me.
Sometimes these essays help me put my life in context and clear my thinking a lot. This was one of those.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Consent and Bot Management features for Cloudflare Zaraz]]></title>
        <id>664272e7abf9e2000aee82a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-consent-and-bot-management-features-for-cloudflare-zaraz"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zaraz Consent Management now supports Google Consent Mode v2 and is compliant with the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework. Zaraz also added Bot Management support for keeping your analytics data clean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yo'av Moshe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Unexpected Inflationary Shocks Raise Workers’ Wages?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29398</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-unexpected-inflationary-shocks-raise-workers-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past year’s steady decline in nominal wage growth now appears in danger of stalling. Given ongoing uncertainty in Ukraine and the Middle East, this seems an opportune moment to revisit the conventional wisdom about the relationship between inflation and wages: if an unexpected increase in energy costs drives up the cost of living, will workers demand higher wages, reversing the recent moderation in wage growth? In new work with Justin Bloesch and Seung Joo Lee examining those concerns, our analysis shows that the pass-through of such inflationary shocks to wages is weak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I found a paper that denies one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism, so stating the obvious turns out to be useful!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52696</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/15/i-found-a-paper-that-denies-one-of-my-two-obvious-thoughts-about-originalism-so-stating-the-obvious-turns-out-to-be-useful/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a couple days to think on it, I think this post is right on. I just stumbled on a paper that stumbles, badly, over one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism. So let me point that out. Quick review. My first obvious thought is it’s weird, if you think about it, that one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidents Barber Conable and Lewis Preston (1986-1995)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with electric vehicles]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45369</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/15/the-problem-with-electric-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker For the last quarter century, those of us hoping we could slow global warming were anxious to see a quick conversion to electric vehicles (EVs). If we could get most people using electric vehicles, and have the energy coming from clean sources, we could radically reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The problem was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc. - How To Justify Workplace Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc.
Title: How To Justify Workplace Theft
Date: 14th April 2020
Source: Retrieved on 9th September 2020 from archive.org/details/workplacetheft-web

 Whether aware of it or not, your boss is stealing from you every paycheck. Employers profit off of the “excess” wealth that you, as an employee, produce. There are two ways to get paid in America: make money off the work you do, or make money off the work that other people do. Employees generate wealth, employers collect it. 
 We live in a capitalist society. We all know that. Most people are okay with it, too. After all, the competition (state communism like the USSR) doesn’t have such a good reputation. 
 But what exactly does capitalism mean? Our good friend the dictionary says capitalism is “an economic and political syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anne Archet - Sirventès of the Beast]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anne Archet
Title: Sirventès of the Beast
Date: 2014/06/27
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 I am no citizen 
 I am no consumer 
 I am no tax-payer 
 I am no employee 
 I am no convict 
 I am no beneficiary 
 I am no person of color 
 I am no lesbian 
 I am no mother 
 I am no wife 
 I am no erotic writer 
 I am no poetess 
 I am no anarchist 
 I am no woman 
 I am surely no Human 
 That vile and ethereal being 
 Which has never been spotted elsewhere 
 But in universal declarations 
 I don't want to stay seated and raise my hand 
 I don't want to wait for the teacher to tell me to speak 
 I don't want to w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, Return Fire - The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, Return Fire
Title: The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else
Subtitle: towards destroying electric mobility & decarbonizing lies
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 To read the articles referenced throughout this text in [square brackets], PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 [ed. – Taken from the German-language website SwitchOff.noblogs.org, this translation continues our interventions in the new climate movements. There are two fronts on which we would like to extend the thrust of the author/s further, in terms of its response to the text reproduced above in this chapter of Return Fire, Targets That Do Not Exist Anywhere Else. Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil - An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil
Title: An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society
Date: 02.22.2024
Source: Original translation of “Uma análise histórica anarquista das inscrições corporais na sociedade ocidental moderna”, published in Revista História em Reflexão 18(35), 2024. Retrieved on 05/07/2024 from https://doi.org/10.30612/rehr.v18i35.16476

Abstract
 In this paper, we aim to analyze the processes of stigmatization and pathologization to which certain categories of body inscriptions have been subjected throughout the history of modern Western society. Body inscriptions are defined as any and all modifications made to the body's structure. While some inscriptions are exalted and praised, others are stigmatized and discriminated aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agnes Henry - Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Agnes Henry
Title: Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism
Date: June 1896
Notes: Original text split between two consecutive monthly publications, with a misprint in the latter citing the first entry as having been published in July rather than June; transcribed from Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (June 1896) and Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (July 1896) on the Internet Archive.
Source: Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism

 The question of how for Anarchist Communism agrees exactly with State Socialism, and the exact line that divides them, has long seemed to me one that it would be well to enter into. And just now, in view of the approaching International Congress, seems a time particularly appropriate for this consideration. For surely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Scott-Brown - Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Scott-Brown
Title: Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy
Date: 2022
Notes: Routledge Studies in Radical History and Politics
Source: <doi.org/10.4324/9781003100409>

Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy is the first full account of Ward’s life and work. Drawing on unseen archival sources, as well as oral interviews, it excavates the worlds and words of his anarchist thought, illuminating his methods and charting the legacies of his enduring influence. 
 Colin Ward (1924—2010) was the most prominent British writer on anarchism in the 20th century. As a radical journalist, later author, he applied his distinctive anarchist principles to all aspects of community life including the built environment, education, and public policy. His thought was subtle, universal in a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Igor & Phil Mailer - And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Boy Igor & Phil Mailer
Title: And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)
Subtitle: The Realization and Suppression of Science and Technology
Date: 1985
Notes: A situationist critique of science and technology published in New York in 1985. This version is a new edition that was published on the 'Endangered Phoenix' website and credited to Phil Meyler. The Endangered Phoenix website is dead now, and I can’t find the updated version on the website through the wayback machine, so there are some footnotes and chapter heading levels which are unclear to me. Plus, I think chapter 3 & 4 were merged in the updated edition, so chapter numbers went out of sync, but chapter 8 was still called chapter 8 which makes it seem like chapter 7 is missing on the libcom website. It is all very confusing, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnarchyNouveau - We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: AnarchyNouveau
Title: We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy
Subtitle: An anarchist-communist’s response to Freedom News
Date: March 20, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 5/10/2024 from https://freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/23/we-dont-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-communists-response-to-freedom-news/

 In Freedom Anarchist Journal’s Winter 2023-2024 issue, Matthew Azoulay submitted an article introducing readers to Murray Bookchin’s ideas of the communalist assembly[1] which disturbed and surprised me for how much it was outdated. The means it proposes to achieve an ecologically revolutionary ends are lacking, stagnant, and fall back on modes of thinking that seem directly inherited from the anti-globalization and Occupy era[2] w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - A Proposal for the Unification of China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: A Proposal for the Unification of China
Date: 1927
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

The Political Capability of the Chinese People
 There are some who doubt that the Chinese people are capable of creating a truly democratic state. We emphatically disagree. The political environment in any country is created by its leaders. The perceptions and habits of the people can be changed to follow those of the leadership. Furthermore, Chinese society has been traditionally rich in self-governing organizations, which can be effectively used to reconstruct [China as] a democratic state. 
The Real Causes of the Turmoil over the Past Sixteen Years
1. The Problem of the Provisional Constitution
 [First,] no provision…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustav Landauer - Are These the Words of a Heretic?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gustav Landauer
Title: Are These the Words of a Heretic?
Notes: Translated from the German Daniel Wortel-London, originally entitled "Sind das Kertzergendanken?" ("Are These Heretic Thoughts?"). Originally published in Von Judentum (On Judaism) in 1911 by the Bar Kokhba League of Jewish Students.
Source: Retrieved on May 14th, 2024 from:https://x.com/dlondonwortel/status/1787470614107763006

 A characteristic of our time is that much is accomplished in spirit but little is accomplished in reality. Perhaps even the lack of actual implementation corresponds to a special activity of the mind, which constantly strives to overcome its own formations without leaving the form of fantasy and doctrine. One could imagine a human society that is structured in such a way that the ideas in it h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like describing a photo to a friend, how to write alt-text]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7584</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-describing-photo-friend-write-alt-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web designers and bloggers have been able to use alternative text, often referred to as “alt-text”, to describe images and photos, for decades. Alt-text helps people with little or no vision comprehend a website image, so long as the description is reasonably accurate. In recent years social media has caught up, and most channels, Instagram, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple text editor named Tine, by Martin Dorazil]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7582</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/simple-text-editor-tine-martin-dorazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text editor without the bells and whistles, called Tine. A nice name for a text editor. The main goal of this editor is to keep the focus on the text editing and not be distracted too much by buttons, tabs, menus, and animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New compute-optimized (C7i-flex) Amazon EC2 Flex instances]]></title>
        <id>a2b797c1aff33d1760b7816ad576286f2d84123f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-compute-optimized-c7i-flex-amazon-ec2-flex-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of applications don’t run run the CPU flat-out at 100% utilization continuously. Take a web application, for instance. It typically fluctuates between periods of high and low demand, but hardly ever uses a server’s compute at full capacity. CPU utilization for many common workloads that customers run in the AWS Cloud today. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Genders Are There?]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:45:06.631Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's 2 genders, right? We all know that.
Of course there is. You're either a bloke, who has the dangly bits between their legs, or you're a woman without said dangly bits.
But maybe there's more. Maybe you have the dangly bits, but it doesn't feel right to call yourself a man? Maybe it's the opposite? Or something in between?
Honestly, I don't give a fuck. For all I care, you could identify as a potato and I'll still respect your wishes. But getting pissed off at me if I mis-identify you is not cool.
Look, it's a fucking minefield out there when it comes to people identifying as non-binary. We've been mincing about this planet for hundreds of thousands of years, and for most that time there's been 2 genders. Male and female.
But in the last few decades there's been a number of other genders that have sprung up. So if I think you look like a man, and I refer to you as "him" don't get up on your high horse and start screaming "YOU ASSUMED MY GENDER! NAZI!"
I assumed your gender because you look like a fucking man. If you identify as something else, that's fine. Tell me politely and I'll happily respect your wishes. Live and let live, and all that. Makes no difference to me.
Irony is, if you're not a dick about the whole thing, you're far more likely to get people on-side. You're always gonna get bigoted wankers, that's par for the course. But just because someone makes a mistake, it doesn't make them a bigot, or a transphobe, or a TERF, or a Nazi.
It just makes them human.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes of Threads for web]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21199</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/14/web/threads-for-web-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Threads first launched one of the top feature requests was for a web client. In this episode of the Meta Tech Podcast, Pascal Hartig (@passy) sits down with Ally C. and Kevin C., two engineers on the Threads Web Team that delivered the basic version of Threads for web in just under three months. [...]
Read More...
The post Behind the scenes of Threads for web appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sacred black and red - Bonk]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: sacred black and red
Title: Bonk
Subtitle: University of California Office of the President Attacked
Date: May 14, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 14 May 2024 from indybay.org/newsitems/2024/05/14/18866217.php


 “The beginning of every revolution is an exit, an exit from the social order that power has enshrined in the name of law, stability, public interest, and the greater good.” 
 - Basel al-Araj 
 With the Aurora Borealis above us and the martyrs in our hearts, we attacked the UC Office of the President in solidarity with the Palestinian Resistance. Using a fire extinguisher filled with red paint we covered the facade and smashed seven windows. Then, with access to the building, we released 500 cockroaches inside and emptied a second fire exintguisher onto the interior. We finalized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Aparna Sinha, Capital One’s Head of AI Product]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5ad22603cb4f</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/introducing-aparna-sinha-capital-ones-head-of-ai-product-5ad22603cb4f?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation with AI product leader, Aparna Sinha, about her expertise in building and enabling enterprise AI/ML capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The student movement for Palestine is now spreading everywhere, inspiring resistance to the barbarism of our times…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the student movement in solidarity with the Palestinians and denunciation of their genocide by Israel intensifies in the United States and now spreads across the planet, there are growing indications that it is succeeding in influencing the central balance of forces while it is being recognized as a major factor in international developments of decisive importance! Thus, Washington's “sudden” distancing of itself from the Netanyahu government, which followed (or perhaps...preceded) Hamas' (...)
English

/ 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delinquency Is Increasingly in the Cards for Maxed‑Out Borrowers]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29844</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/delinquency-is-increasingly-in-the-cards-for-maxed-out-borrowers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, the New York Fed’s Center for Microeconomic Data released the Quarterly Report on Household Debt and Credit for the first quarter of 2024. Household debt balances grew by $184 billion over the previous quarter, slightly less than the moderate growth seen in the fourth quarter of 2023. Housing debt balances grew by $206 billion. Auto loans saw a $9 billion increase, continuing their steady growth since the second quarter of 2020, while balances on other non-housing debts fell. Credit card balances fell by $14 billion, which is typical for the first quarter. However, an increasing number of borrowers are behind on credit card payments. In this post, we explore the relationship between credit card delinquency and changes in credit card “utilization rates.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew F. Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle Scally, Wilbert van der Klaauw, and Crystal Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM done right for LLM-augmented applications]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b5abbea70c45</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/iam-done-right-for-llm-augmented-applications-b5abbea70c45?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How IAM can help you to leverage the advanced capabilities of LLMs while securing sensitive data and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i can quit any time (i won't)]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:09:15.529Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently writing this post as a break from working on the comic I have due at the end of the month. It's an eighteen-page oneshot and my very first contribution to an anthology, which is honestly very exciting. Intimidating, too, which is why I ended up putting off most of the work until the last minute.
Working on it has, as I anticipated, brought to light a number of my artistic weaknesses: I don't like inking, I half-ass shapes I don't understand rather than look for a reference, my faces are inconsistent... the list goes on. Seeing all the ways I fall short of my expectations is what I was afraid of happening, why I put it off for so long – but I don't really have the time anymore to sit and nitpick at my work, which is kind of a blessing. Stuff is getting done!
It's frustrating t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hard pills to swallow]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:56:55.178Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My throat hurts a little. I don’t know if this is because of the air quality here or because I’m actually getting sick, but I’m desperately hoping it’s not the latter. I stopped taking my immunosuppressants today and started drinking lots of juices high in vitamin C, despite research proving chugging OJ a rather ineffective method for warding off illness. (Something about all the sugar in it makes it hard for your body to absorb the Vitamin C, if I remember correctly.)
Traveling and getting sick go hand in hand for me. It’s as if arriving somewhere new triggers my immune system to self-immolate. When I visited New York in 2021 I lost my voice after a few days. I spent my first week in Latin America making chicken noodle soup and nursing myself back to health. My immune system’s never been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Radio Waves&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Ernst Schoen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>