<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-12-31T18:32:49.410Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-12-31T18:32:49.410Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking Reader Help in Finding New Site Contributor(s) to Fill Lambert’s Yellow Waders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284819</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/seeking-reader-help-in-finding-new-site-contributors-to-fill-lamberts-yellow-waders.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T18:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yves is in damsel in distress mode! Can you help Naked Capitalism find a new contributor to help take over for Lambert?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fond Farewell to Lambert]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284807</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/a-fond-farewell-to-lambert.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T18:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lambert is retiring in the early months of 2025! We will very much miss him and hope you will bear with us as we fill his big yellow waders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Meaney: &ldquo;A Year in German Culture&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-year-in-german-culture</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-year-in-german-culture"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza and censorship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transform lease agreement workflows with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>dab37534fc31f5c3a2ba27f017579fdc4f34674c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/transform-lease-agreement-workflows-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T15:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explores how Amazon Bedrock can transform property management operations and optimize costs. We examine a practical approach to tackle challenges such as processing high volumes of lease agreements, maintaining compliance with varied regulatory requirements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed Masudullah Sadullah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The forecast is clear: clouds on e-paper, powered by the cloud]]></title>
        <id>2b03lxutI7PqAfcxswe5aE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-forecast-is-clear-clouds-on-e-paper-powered-by-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow along as I build a custom weather display using Cloudflare Workers and a popular e-paper display.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marek Majkowski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/31/2024 New Year’s Eve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284714</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-31-2024-new-years-eve.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T11:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our crackling daily links: new ancient finds, moar Covid brain effects, plastic breakthrough? China EV dominance, SKorea impechment drama, Musk continues AfD trolling, Carter v. Israel apartheid, Ukraine-Russia-Slovakia energy row, privatizing Fannie and Freddie? moar H-1B, insurers heart bad MDs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Venezuela About to Face Another Regime Change Operation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284449</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/is-venezuela-about-to-face-another-regime-change-operation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T11:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Trump take a more pragmatic approach to US relations with Caracas this time? Or will he double down on an (until-now) failed strategy of sanctions escalation and regime change?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hanukkah 2024: Festival of Darkness and Light]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348344</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/hanukkah-2024-festival-of-darkness-and-light/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T07:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In liberal, Jewish households, Hanukkah has always been something of an embarrassment. First, there’s the unavoidable truth that Hannukah is no match for Christmas. Liturgically speaking, it’s a minor holiday; it ranks somewhere between Simchat Torah and Tu Bishvat, neither of which most Gentiles (and many Jews) have even heard of. So, efforts by assimilated Jews since the 19th century, and especially the 1950s, to treat Hanukkah like Christmas are a stretch. The birthday of God (even if you are a non-believer) in 1 CE is objectively speaking a much bigger deal than the re-dedication by the victorious Maccabees (Judean rebels) of the second temple of Jerusalem (long since destroyed) in the 2nd century BCE. More
The post Hanukkah 2024: Festival of Darkness and Light appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenland Redux: Trump and America’s Continuing Obsession]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348449</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/greenland-redux-trump-and-americas-continuing-obsession/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[History shows that empires acquire territories in various ways.  Dynasties link arms through marriage, as the Habsburgs were famous for doing.  Territories are pinched by means of arms or stolen through sham contracts and undertakings.  They might also be purchased. The United States made much of the vast property sale in acquiring an empire.  The Louisiana purchase of 1803  More
The post Greenland Redux: Trump and America’s Continuing Obsession appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Auschwitz to Gaza: The War Against International Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348348</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/auschwitz-to-gaza-the-war-against-international-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Home and Abroad Police in America need a great deal of reform, a project that translates to freeing them from the racist nature of U.S. culture while tying them more firmly to the culture of civil and human rights. Not easy, but certainly a worthwhile task compared to maintaining the present situation. Here is  More
The post Auschwitz to Gaza: The War Against International Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dylan’s Creative Leap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348337</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/dylans-creative-leap/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bob Dylan biopic “A Complete Unknown,” starring Timothée Chalamet, focuses on Dylan’s early 1960s transition from idiosyncratic singer of folk songs to internationally renowned singer-songwriter. As a music historian, I’ve always respected one decision of Dylan’s in particular – one that kicked off the young artist’s most turbulent and significant period of creative activity.  More
The post Dylan’s Creative Leap appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ted Olson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farewell Jimmy Carter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348425</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/farewell-jimmy-carter/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 100 years among us, Jimmy Carter is gone. Like a lot of people, I’m playing Ramblin’ Man in his memory tonight. Saying good-bye to Jimmy Carter is complicated as Dickey Bett’s guitar. All complications considered, Jimmy was my favorite U.S. President during my lifetime. Nobody’s perfect, and a U.S. President’s imperfections are bound to  More
The post Farewell Jimmy Carter appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Cowards Do]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348381</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/what-cowards-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two kinds of cowards. Charles Joseph Coward was a British soldier who grew up in Edmonton, London, and enlisted in the British Army in 1937. During the war, he was wounded and captured by the Germans at the fall of Calais in 1940 while serving as a battery sergeant. He tried to escape  More
The post What Cowards Do appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year’s Resolution Number One: Join the Movement Against World War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348375</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/new-years-resolution-number-one-join-the-movement-against-world-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T06:10:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a precipice and we are standing on its edge. The world as it exists on the eve of 2025 is a world of war and genocide. It is a world where millions of humans exist in a state not just of uncertainty, but in a state where tomorrow is likely to be worse than  More
The post New Year’s Resolution Number One: Join the Movement Against World War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sen. Chris Coons and the Cult of Patent Monopolies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348401</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/sen-chris-coons-and-the-cult-of-patent-monopolies/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T05:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, Delaware Senator Chris Coons, the chair of the Senate Subcommittee on Intellectual Property, made an assertion about the nature of patents that is flat out wrong. Senator Coons said: “OUR FOUNDING FATHERS MADE IT CLEAR THAT INVENTORS SHOULD HAVE EXCLUSIVE RIGHTS TO THEIR INVENTIONS. IN OTHER WORDS, THE CONSTITUTION IN ITS SCRIPT GUARANTEES  More
The post Sen. Chris Coons and the Cult of Patent Monopolies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bombs Over Greenland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348487</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/31/bombs-over-greenland/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T05:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bombs are falling Trump’s taking Greenland By force of course It’s a crime — Or maybe it’s not Let’s ask Alito, see if he thinks so Maybe he’ll find It’s necessary for the pipeline Pipe that melting ice To the golf clubs of Nevada, Refill the Ogallala And don’t forget Oprah Who alone needs  More
The post Bombs Over Greenland appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Sperber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Are Eighteen Years Old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284748</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/we-are-eighteen-years-old.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T05:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by davidclark in "US credit card defaults jump to highest level since 2010"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42553307</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42553307"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T20:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Credit card delinquency rates, which are seen as a precursor to write-offs, peaked in July, according to data from Moody’s, but have only fallen slightly and remain nearly a percentage point higher than they were on average in the year before the pandemic.
This is a prime example of a style of reporting that really grinds my gears.
The citation is clearly to another internet source, so a link should be provided. If it truly cannot be linked because it is private, more context is still needed to understand what this data means.
I actually can’t find the source myself, but I can find “Delinquency Rate on Credit Card Loans, All Commercial Banks” from the Federal Reserve. [1]
The percents from that source somewhat match those referenced in the FT quote. “Peaked in July”
- 2024Q1 3.15%
- 2024Q2 3.24%
- 2024Q3 3.23%
Using 2019 as “the year before the pandemic”, the average was 2.5825. Is +0.6475 “nearly a percentage point”? I guess it technically would round up.
Seemingly important context that the quote doesn’t give is that 3.23% is lower than any time 1991Q3 to 2011Q4. But, maybe the trend matters more for this metric.
[1] https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/DRCCLACBS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davidclark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favourite monospaced font for coding, do people have such a thing?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9015</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/favourite-monospaced-font-coding/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T20:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code is code, what difference does the font you choose in whatever app you use for coding possibly make? As long as the code works as intended, what does appearance have to do with it? But the conversation I found on the topic — which in fact started months ago — actually relates to a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ten best novels of the twenty-first century to date]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9021</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ten-best-novels-twenty-first-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T19:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Literary writers at The Sydney Morning Herald canvassed critics, editors, and writers, including Jane Sullivan, David Free, Gyan Yankovich, and Beejay Silcox, to determine the best ten books of this century, or the last twenty-five years. Producing such a small list from a relatively long time frame, will doubtless generate discussion. Anyway, Praiseworthy by Alexis […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 12/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284785</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/200pm-water-cooler-12-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T19:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; H1B controversy rolls along;  Norovirus surge; Amazon attacks third-party sellers again ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tranquil Motion, a new album from All India Radio]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9027</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/music-tranquil-motion-new-album-all-india-radio/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m talking about the Australian downtempo electronica music act, not the public broadcaster of India. In the hubbub of the silly season, I forgot to mention a new album, Tranquil Motion, was released earlier this month. Track it down on Bandcamp, or your favourite music streamer. I could use some tranquil motion right now…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Fracking Billionaires and Climate Denial Groups Behind Trump’s Cabinet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284788</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/6-fracking-billionaires-and-climate-denial-groups-behind-trumps-cabinet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T17:47:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s nominees are backed by major players in the world of climate obstruction – from Project 2025 and Koch network fixtures to oil-soaked Christian nationalists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ababaian in "'Obelisks': New class of life has been found in human digestive system"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42550873</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42550873"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T16:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cool :) I'm a co-author on this. AMA.
This is now a peer-reviewed paper, published last month in Cell [https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(24)01091-2].
Obelisks are part of a larger research program we're developing at the University of Toronto + collaborators, see also: Virus-Viroid Hybrids paper [https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-023-38301-2] and the Zeta-Elements [https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-021-04332-2].
Computational biology is driving a revolutionary expansion of our understanding of Earth's biodiversity. I believe Zeta-elements, Ambiviruses, and Obelisks are just the beginning. If you're interested, our "Laboratory for RNA-Based Lifeforms" (University of Toronto) is hiring passionate developers/post-docs/graduate students [https://www.rnalab.ca].
Edit: OK going to call it for now. I'll check in later today if there's any outstanding questions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ababaian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by chrismorgan in "Fun facts about SQLite"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42550846</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42550846"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T16:38:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> SQLite is not open source in the legal sense, as “open source” has a specific definition and requires licenses approved by the Open Source Initiative (OSI).
This is wrong, and harmfully wrong. OSI are not the arbiters of open source. Their Open Source Definition, though generally useful and accepted, is not without legitimate criticism and controversy. As for their approval, that’s a dreadful thing to rely on for any purpose; https://writing.kemitchell.com/2019/05/05/Rely-on-OSI.html> is a good description of most of what’s wrong with it (it doesn’t really get into the broken politics enough; but some of his other articles contain more), and I like its summary: “The list of OSI-approved licenses reflects OSI’s practical and political history, not any useful, consistently functional category of license terms.”
As for whether SQLite is open source, well, the only reason a public domain dedication doesn’t meet the OSD is that it’s not a license. It’s more open. In a way that is legally mildly uncertain in some jurisdictions, sure, but to call it “not open source in the legal sense” is just wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chrismorgan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open sourcing h3i: a command line tool and library for low-level HTTP/3 testing and debugging]]></title>
        <id>2yX9ADcaKBprzyI9BaBoqN</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/h3i/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[h3i is a command line tool and Rust library designed for low-level testing and debugging of HTTP/3, which runs over QUIC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Pardue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284772</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T11:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EU Threatens to Cut Itself off From Another of Its Major Natural Gas Suppliers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284727</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/284727.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T11:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issues with supplies from Qatar — the world's third largest exporter of LNG — could be a major boon for US gas companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personal endebtment and debt forgivness in the Roman empire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Personal-endebtment-and-debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Personal-endebtment-and-debt"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt in History, 
Histoire Jubi EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jean Andreau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Palestinian Year in Review: Genocide, Resistance and Unanswered Questions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348356</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/a-palestinian-year-in-review-genocide-resistance-and-unanswered-questions/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T07:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of the Israeli war on Gaza can be epitomized in the story of the Israeli war on Beit Lahia, a small Palestinian town in the northern part of the Strip. When Israel launched its ground operations in Gaza, Beit Lahia was already largely destroyed due to many days of relentless Israeli bombardment which  More
The post A Palestinian Year in Review: Genocide, Resistance and Unanswered Questions   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Death of Ambassador Raymond Garthoff and Disarmament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348336</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/the-death-of-ambassador-raymond-garthoff-and-disarmament/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T07:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mainstream media ignored the passing of a beloved former colleague of mine, Ambassador Raymond Garthoff, whose career spanned the most important years of arms control and disarmament between the United States and the Soviet Union.  Over the years, the media have devoted much attention to the opponents of arms control such as George W. Bush, Paul Wolfowitz, John Bolton, and Casper Weinberger, but have done little to explore the importance of its advocates and practitioners.   More
The post The Death of Ambassador Raymond Garthoff and Disarmament appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter: the False Savoir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348392</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/jimmy-carter-the-false-savoir/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pious Sunday school teacher confessing to lust in his heart but swearing never to lie, he came to Washington to reestablish public faith in government just when popular disgust at monstrous U.S. crimes in Indochina had reached unprecedented heights. The big business agenda during his term in office (1977-1981) was to roll back the welfare state, break the power of unions, fan the flames of the Cold War to increase military spending, engineer tax breaks for wealthy corporate interests, and repeal government regulation of business. While portraying himself as a peanut-farming populist, Carter delivered the goods for Wall Street.
More
The post Jimmy Carter: the False Savoir appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael K. Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fascism and Radical Left Lunacy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348272</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/fascism-and-radical-left-lunacy/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald, the idiot, the madman, the consummate cowardly thug is preparing to unleash shock and awe to paint his agenda onto the American and the world stage such as we have never seen before. Day one, two, three…infinity. He will attempt to unleash the hounds of horror. Why? To impose his horrendous agenda—of course. But  More
The post Fascism and Radical Left Lunacy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Albert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sinking Mike Pompeo: Tucker Carlson, Assange and Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348409</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/sinking-mike-pompeo-tucker-carlson-assange-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Pompeo’s role in the first Trump administration as both director of the Central Intelligence Agency and US Secretary of State will be forever associated with the venom and desperation he had in targeting Julian Assange, a publisher who drove him to distraction and engendered mania.  As the chief founder of WikiLeaks, Assange had regularly published  More
The post Sinking Mike Pompeo: Tucker Carlson, Assange and Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 7: A History in Threads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348274</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/october-7-a-history-in-threads/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What follows is the final installment of ‘October 7: A History in Threads,’ which connects the present to the past 141 years of Zionism and Israel’s occupation of Palestine. Please go here to see all of the 11 threads in this series that includes embroidered portraits of the ongoing Palestinian struggle for liberation. According to  More
The post October 7: A History in Threads appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Priti Gulati Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uprising for Democracy in the Caucasus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348370</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/uprising-for-democracy-in-the-caucasus/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tempest’s Ashley Smith and Posle Media’s Ilya Budraitskis interview Georgian activists and scholars Ia Eradze, Luka Nakhutsrishvili and Lela Rekhviashvili about the roots of the uprising, its trajectory, and Georgia’s place in global capitalism and the imperialist order. The country of Georgia, a small nation of 3.8 million people in the Caucasus, has been thrown into a profound crisis. Its people have risen up against  More
The post Uprising for Democracy in the Caucasus appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tempest and Posle Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Year Past and the Year Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/the-year-past-and-the-year-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The global citizen agenda for 2025 is very much like that for 2024—and probably for some years afterward. It includes global warming and related environmental crises; US-China tensions; challenges to democracy and peace in Europe and Africa; interstate and intrastate violence in the Middle East; and nuclear weapons upgrading. A new addition to this list  More
The post The Year Past and the Year Ahead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cinema Beyond Cinemas: the Best Films of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347930</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/30/cinema-beyond-cinemas-the-best-films-of-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T06:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bibi Files Dir. Alexis Bloom Dahomey Dir. Mati Diop Ernest Cole: Lost and Found Dir. Raoul Peck Eno Dir. Gary Hustwi The Goldman Case Dir. Cédric Kahn Green Border Dir. Agnieszka Holland The Night Won’t End: Biden’s War on Gaza  Dir. Laila Al Arian and Fault Lines No Other Land Dir. Basel Adra, Yuval  More
The post Cinema Beyond Cinemas: the Best Films of 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashley Dawson: Environmentalism from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348403</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/ashley-dawson-environmentalism-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T00:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Joshua Frank and Erik Wallenberg talk to Ashley Dawson about his new book, Environmentalism from Below: How Global People's Movements Are Leading the Fight for Our Planet (Haymarket Books).
Ashley is a Professor of English at the Graduate Center / City University of New York and the College of Staten Island. He is the author of several books on key topics in the environmental humanities, including People’s Power: Reclaiming the Energy Commons, Extreme Cities: The Peril and Promise of Urban Life in the Age of Climate Change, and Extinction: A Radical History. A member of the Public Power NY campaign and the founder of the CUNY Climate Action Lab, he is a long-time climate justice activist.  More
The post Ashley Dawson: Environmentalism from Below appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmclnx in "Jimmy Carter has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42543338</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42543338"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T21:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back, to me he was a much better president then people believed in the 80s.
I believe if he got re-elected in 1980, the US would be in a much better place.  One thing, it could be argued real work on Climate Change would have begun in 1981 as opposed to where we are now, which is just watching the average probably blowing past 3C in around 70 years from now.
For his loss in 1980, I still blame Kennedy.
RIP, he did a lot to help regular people through his life, far more than our current crop of politicians.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmclnx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MAGA Can Stuff DOGE Back in Its Box and Win the Day on H1B]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=284746</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/how-maga-can-stuff-doge-back-in-his-box-and-win-the-day-on-h1b.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T20:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A simple plan....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the End of the World and I Don’t Feel Fine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347506</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/its-the-end-of-the-world-and-i-dont-feel-fine/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier Miranda. Image by Javier […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post It’s the End of the World and I Don’t Feel Fine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Dolack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poetry From Today’s Frontlines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348265</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/29/poetry-from-todays-frontlines/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T06:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis in December. (Screengrab from video posted to X.) Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis in December. (Screengrab from video posted to X.) Palestinians gather amid the ruins of a residential complex bombed by the Israelis […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Poetry From Today’s Frontlines appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jchw in "Apple Photos phones home on iOS 18 and macOS 15"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42537165</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42537165"/>
        <updated>2024-12-29T03:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What I want is very simple: I want software that doesn't send anything to the Internet without some explicit intent first. All of that work to try to make this feature plausibly private is cool engineering work, and there's absolutely nothing wrong with implementing a feature like this, but it should absolutely be opt-in.
Trust in software will continue to erode until software stops treating end users and their data and resources (e.g. network connections) as the vendor's own playground. Local on-device data shouldn't be leaking out of radio interfaces unexpectedly, period. There should be a user intent tied to any feature where local data is sent out to the network.
So why didn't Apple just simply ask for user permission to enable this feature? My cynical opinion is because Apple knows some portion of users would instantly disallow this if prompted, but they feel they know better than those users. I don't like this attitude, and I suspect it is the same reason why there is an increasing discontent growing towards opt-out telemetry, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jchw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scosman in "Apple Photos phones home on iOS 18 and macOS 15"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42534096</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42534096"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T20:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["I don't understand most of the technical details of Apple's blog post"
I do:
- Client side vectorization: the photo is processed locally, preparing a non-reversible vector representation before sending (think semantic hash).
- Differential privacy: a decent amount of noise is added the the vector before sending it. Enough to make it impossible to reverse lookup the vector. The noise level here is ε = 0.8, which is quite good privacy.
- OHTTP relay: it's sent through a 3rd party so Apple never knows your IP address. The contents are encrypted so the 3rd party never doesn't learn anything either (some risk of exposing "IP X is an apple photos user", but nothing about the content of the library).
- Homomorphic encryption: The lookup work is performed on server with encrypted data. Apple can't decrypt the vector contents, or response contents. Only the client can decrypt the result of the lookup.
This is what a good privacy story looks like. Multiple levels of privacy security, when any one of the latter 3 should be enough alone to protect privacy.
"It ought to be up to the individual user to decide their own tolerance for the risk of privacy violations." -> The author themselves looks to be an Apple security researcher, and are saying they can't make an informed choice here.
I'm not sure what the right call is here. But the conclusion "Thus, the only way to guarantee computing privacy is to not send data off the device." isn't true. There are other tools to provide privacy (DP, homomorphic encryption), while also using services. They are immensely complicated, and user's can't realistically evaluate risk. But if you want features that require larger-than-disk datasets, or frequently changing content, you need tools like this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by HarHarVeryFunny in "I automated my job application process"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42533327</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42533327"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T18:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe not your company, but it seems hiring companies brought this upon themselves with immediate AI rejects of qualified candidates, ghost jobs, ghosting candidates after interview, etc, etc.
If it takes a qualified candidate 100's of applications to land a single interview, then can you blame someone for automating it? I'd say that having the initiative and ability to automate it well would make this guy a great hire, if he hadn't already found a job!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HarHarVeryFunny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI tool will identify diabetes risk 13 years early + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/new-ai-tool-will-identify-diabetes-risk-13-years-early-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/new-ai-tool-will-identify-diabetes-risk-13-years-early-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T17:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NHS launches trial for AI diabetes prediction; Eni unveils €100 million supercomputer for energy; UN Security Council approves peacekeeping in Somalia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Left to Say?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348214</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/28/whats-left-to-say/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T15:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamal Adwan Hospital workers, doctors, and staff are being forcibly evicted from the grounds of the hospital by IDF soldiers. (Screengrab from a video posted to X.) Kamal Adwan Hospital workers, doctors, and staff are being forcibly evicted from the grounds of the hospital by IDF soldiers. (Screengrab from a video posted to X.) Kamal […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post What’s Left to Say? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by noodlesUK in "The paper passport's days are numbered"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527809</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527809"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T01:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are significant downsides to the digitalization of travel documents. The biggest one I can think of is ownership - the UK is moving to an entirely digital visa system and bringing in an ESTA style system called ETA for visa free countries. Unfortunately this means that residency cards for noncitizens are being phased out. This means that when the Home Office messes up and accidentally deletes your immigration status, or you are at an airport with no internet access, you have no evidence whatsoever of what status you hold. It also means you will no longer be in possession of any records that might be useful years in the future when the current database containing immigration records will likely have been replaced. It’s much easier to keep a piece of paper around for 30+ years than it is to make sure a digital record doesn’t rot in that time.
I feel strongly that any future digital travel credentials that are offered by governments should be able to operate entirely offline, and provide records that can be retained by the data subject. That means that revocation is harder, but IMO that’s a tradeoff that is worth making to avoid another Windrush scandal.
This has already become a pain when dealing with countries that don’t stamp passports, because when you need to apply for something that asks for your travel history over the past 10 years, you might not have any records anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>noodlesUK</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dlisboa in "Should more of us be moving to live near friends?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527549</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42527549"/>
        <updated>2024-12-28T00:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming from a Latin American the idea of re-starting your life across the country for college and then again for work (multiple times sometimes) while away from family and friends is very foreign.
A lot of the conversation around modern American youth feeling isolated, lacking socialization and not building strong relationships seems that stem from this drive.
Another thing that’s really weird and related is another recurring theme in the American ethos: the cultural shame that comes with living “at home” or staying in the same small town for your whole life. Somehow they made it so living close to your family and friends for your 20s-30s  and maybe forever means you’re a “loser”.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dlisboa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Why OpenAI's Structure Must Evolve to Advance Our Mission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42522209</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42522209"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't understand why they are spending so much time and effort trying to put a positive spin on this whole for-profit thing. No one is buying it. We all know what's going on. Just say "we want to make lots of money" and move on with your lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Cloudflare: MASQUE now powers 1.1.1.1 & WARP apps, DEX now generally available with Remote Captures]]></title>
        <id>1zc4C9M6VIkj5TrfugGxum</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/masque-now-powers-1-1-1-1-and-warp-apps-dex-available-with-remote-captures/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This roundup blog post shares the latest new features and capabilities at Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mari Galicer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Civil Discourse in a Time of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348069</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/civil-discourse-in-a-time-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T07:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Civil discourse is preferable to the alternatives of coerced silence and violence. Coerced silence means that one side has exercised power to end conversation—to say, in effect, there is no point in further discussion; be quiet and accept that our desires will prevail. Violence means that reason has failed and we are reduced to the condition of resolving disputes by means of fang and claw, rock and club, bullet and bomb. More
The post Civil Discourse in a Time of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Schwalbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sound of da Police: the Year Criminal Injustice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=347882</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-sound-of-da-police-the-year-criminal-injustice/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For nearly two days, the NYPD covered up the fact that one of their officers had fired a gun inside Hind Hall, while they were arresting students. Ultimately, the shooting was only revealed by the New York City DA's office. If you call in the NYPD, you can pretty much guarantee there will be bang-bang...Is there any doubt now that the NYPD raid did more damage to the buildings at Columbia than the students? The people who invited these cops on their campus should never be guardians of students again. More
The post The Sound of da Police: the Year Criminal Injustice appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Days? World War, Tech Takeover, and Global Warming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348067</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-end-days-world-war-tech-takeover-and-global-warming/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One can be excused for worrying over what tomorrow might bring as expanded battle lines are redrawn across the globe, the world’s wealthiest nation ever consumes itself in a cataclysm of partisan hate amid a growing digital reformation, and unchecked carbon emissions continue to cause more environmental disaster by the day. Will nuclear conflict, machine control, or climate breakdown ultimately destroy our pale blue dot of a planet or is it all just more apocalyptic blather that never comes to pass? More
The post The End Days? World War, Tech Takeover, and Global Warming appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John K. White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Favorites of 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348095</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/my-favorites-of-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a big fan of these “best of” lists, but of all the new(ish) arts entertainment (or edutainment, as KRS-One would say) I consumed these past twelve months, here’s what helped me most in surviving (and contemplating) the relentless horrors of 2024. FILMS No Other Land, co-directed by Basel Adra, Hamdan Ballal, Yuval Abraham, and  More
The post My Favorites of 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Leading Edge of Global Heat – Arabian Peninsula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348087</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/the-leading-edge-of-global-heat-arabian-peninsula/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major portions of the Arabian Peninsula are already exceeding 2°C above pre-industrial and likely headed for a staggering temperature rise over coming decades. This disturbing news comes via a major new study by Saudi Arabia’s most prestigious university. The epicenter of world oil & gas production is in direct line of fire of unnerving acceleration  More
The post The Leading Edge of Global Heat – Arabian Peninsula appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesting on the Environment: Australian Mining Gets a Present]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348153</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/jesting-on-the-environment-australian-mining-gets-a-present/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining magnates seem to have it all.  Far more significant than royalty, such figures are the unelected captains of industry who know that governments will do whatever they can to accommodate their wishes and whims.  True, the official rhetoric might sometimes be sharp and seemingly at odds, especially when it comes to that great irritation known as  More
The post Jesting on the Environment: Australian Mining Gets a Present appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Not About What Class You’re From: It’s About What Class System You Serve]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348117</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/its-not-about-what-class-your-from-its-about-what-class-system-you-serve/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York Times columnist Bret Stephens recently published a widely read opinion piece claiming that Brian Thompson, the United Health Group insurance CEO that Luigi Mangione assassinated, is the “real working-class hero” in the story of Thompson’s murder. By Stephen’s reckoning, Thompson and not Mangione deserves the label because the murder victim came from a  More
The post It’s Not About What Class You’re From: It’s About What Class System You Serve appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, the Marlboro Man and the New Frontier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=348021</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/27/trump-the-marlboro-man-and-the-new-frontier/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T06:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Marlboro Man are case studies of branding success. When Philip Morris introduced the cowboy on its ads in 1955, sales were at $5 billion. Two years later, sales were at $20 billion. Ellen Merlo, the vice president of marketing services at Philip Morris, described the cowboy image as “very rugged, individualistic, heroic.” Rugged and individualistic is exactly the image Trump tries to portray. Why else go to WWE Raw events or a college football game? How else to describe his raised fist cry “Fight, fight, fight,” when struck by a bullet during an assassination attempt. Trump’s mythological image has helped him to be re-elected president despite (because of) twice being impeached and convicted of 34 felony accounts. The Marlboro Man and Trump’s image portrayal are fundamental to the American mythology of the pioneer spirit exploring new frontiers which now includes the popular success of tech start-up heroes like Elon Musk. More
The post Trump, the Marlboro Man and the New Frontier appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debt cancellation in the land of Canaan in the first millennium BC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Debt-cancellation-in-the-land-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Debt-cancellation-in-the-land-of"/>
        <updated>2024-12-27T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt in History, 
Histoire Jubi EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabelle Ponet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mitchellh in "Ghostty 1.0"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42517852</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42517852"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T21:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://mitchellh.com/writing/ghostty-1-0-reflection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mitchellh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The web today is not necessarily worse than the early web]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8992</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-web-today-is-not-necessarily-worse-than-the-early-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xavier H.M., writing on his Mastodon page: Your neocities blog is cute but I can’t read the 5pt font and your cursor is the size of a bread crumb. The web page is loading so many gifs my computer sounds like a boeing 747. disassociated once, in a way, looked like a Neocities website. Or, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time, not dark energy, may be causing the universe to expand]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9004</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/time-not-dark-energy-causing-universe-expand/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dark energy does not exist, and the universe, while continuing to expand, is not doing so in a uniform fashion. In other words, the cosmos may look more like a potato, rather than a sphere. This according to recent research by astronomers and scientists at the University of Canterbury (UC), based in Christchurch, New Zealand. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pack plenty of books and take yourself into internal exile in 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9007</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/pack-books-internal-exile-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introverts among us live almost permanently in a sort of internal exile, or a rich inner life, as Waleed Aly referred to it during the COVID-19 lockdowns. But the idea of getting away from it all, without actually going anywhere, is gaining traction more widely, writes Jacqueline Maley, for The Sydney Morning Herald. This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Bottlerocket FIPS variants]]></title>
        <id>16e90ff8cb5363cf2d70b6dd873e01b284520e09</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-bottlerocket-fips-variants/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T16:51:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In 2020, AWS announced Bottlerocket, an open source, container-optimized Linux distribution designed for hosting containers. Each Bottlerocket image, known as a variant, is specialized for a specific combination of container orchestrator and cloud environment. Bottlerocket variants are provided to users as a set of Amazon Machine Images (AMI), currently optimized for either Amazon Elastic Container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I cache: implementing lock-free probabilistic caching]]></title>
        <id>4Xek2BRcXVKNsI4vCa3Zuj</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/sometimes-i-cache/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to know what cache revalidation is, how it works, and why it can involve rolling a die, read on. This blog post presents a lock-free probabilistic approach to cache revalidation, along]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thibault Meunier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by K0nserv in "Cognitive load is what matters"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42511276</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42511276"/>
        <updated>2024-12-25T21:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been thinking about the notion of "reasoning locally" recently. Enabling local reasoning is the only way to scale software development past some number of lines or complexity. When reasoning locally, one only needs to understand a small subset, hundreds of lines, to safely make changes in programs comprising millions.
I find types helps massively with this. A function with well-constrained inputs and outputs is easy to reason about. One does not have to look at other code to do it. However, programs that leverage types effectively are sometimes construed as having high cognitive load, when it in fact they have low load. For example a type like `Option>` carries a lot of information(has low load): we might not have a set of user ids, but if we do they are unique.
The discourse around small functions and the clean code guidelines is fascinating. The complaint is usually, as in this post, that having to go read all the small functions adds cognitive load and makes reading the code harder. Proponents of small functions argue that you don't have to read more than the signature and name of a function to understand what it does; it's obvious what a function called last that takes a list and returns an optional value does. If someone feels compelled to read every function either the functions are poor abstractions or the reader has trust issues, which may be warranted. Of course, all abstractions are leaky, but perhaps some initial trust in `last` is warranted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>K0nserv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>