<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-02T12:48:05.953Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-02T12:48:05.953Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/2/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277742</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T10:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stupid Price Gouging Discourse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277750</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/the-stupid-price-gouging-discourse.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T09:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is Kamala's price gouging proposal is a ruse, and why won't she voice support for Lina Khan at the Federal Trade Commission?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Bombs and Bullets: The Full Tally of Gaza’s Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332236</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/beyond-bombs-and-bullets-the-full-tally-of-gazas-dead/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T06:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The impact of losing access to healthcare is starkly illustrated by the example of pregnant women in Gaza, estimated at 50,000 when the war began. Many have miscarried and are having stillbirths, faced C-sections with unsensitized equipment and without anesthetic, while increasing numbers of newborns are “simply dying,” according to the World Health Organization, because starving mothers are giving birth to critically underweight babies. More
The post Beyond Bombs and Bullets: The Full Tally of Gaza’s Dead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spencer Osberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago Post Mortem 2024: How This Time Can be Different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332231</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/chicago-post-mortem-2024-how-this-time-can-be-different/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T06:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Currently, the President sending the limitless money and weapons happens to be a Democrat.  Lest anyone forget the Republican’s loyalty to the cause, however, the “sane” presidential aspirant, Nikki Haley thought it was a great idea to be photographed autographing the U.S. manufactured and supplied bombs before they were loaded on the U.S. made warplanes.  More
The post Chicago Post Mortem 2024: How This Time Can be Different appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Joyce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons of Kristallnacht, “Civil War,” and Mass Deportation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332367</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/lessons-of-kristallnacht-civil-war-and-mass-deportation/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent trip to Germany, I sought to better understand how the Nazi Party rose to power, and carried out the Holocaust, in which most of my Hungarian Jewish relatives perished. I gained some new insights, and learned several lessons that may be useful in the polarized United States today, with the election looming and far-right agitation growing.
More
The post Lessons of Kristallnacht, “Civil War,” and Mass Deportation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoltan Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sanitation in Namibia Is a Catastrophe for Its People and Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332413</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/sanitation-in-namibia-is-a-catastrophe-for-its-people-and-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the outskirts of cities to the most rural parts of the country, more than 1 million Namibians lack adequate access to toilets, and they are often faced with only one option: open defecation. According to the World Health Organization and UNICEF’s Joint Monitoring Program (JMP) 2020 data, Namibia ranked sixth for the highest rate of open  More
The post Sanitation in Namibia Is a Catastrophe for Its People and Environment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Freddie Clayton and Sonja Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting the Widow Maker: The US Marines Exonerate the Osprey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332415</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/protecting-the-widow-maker-the-us-marines-exonerate-the-osprey/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tiltrotor V-22 Osprey has a plagued, bloodied history.  But blighted as it is, the aircraft remains a cherished feature of the US Marines, regarded as vital in supporting combat assault, logistics and transport, not to mention playing a role in search-and-rescue missions and delivering equipment for the Navy carrier air wings. In March this year,  More
The post Protecting the Widow Maker: The US Marines Exonerate the Osprey appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost in Translation: Radical Politics of a Trans Trade Unionist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332405</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/lost-in-translation-radical-politics-of-a-trans-trade-unionist/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imane Khelif: Working Class Muslim Hero For the millionth time: Imane Khelif is not a trans woman. She is AFAB, has female body parts from birth, all the essentialist markers that transphobes use to justify their bigotry. This truly is an instance of horse-shoe theory at its best. Transphobes start off by laying down these  More
The post Lost in Translation: Radical Politics of a Trans Trade Unionist appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andie Stewart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collaborators on the Ropes as Wilderness Advocates Fight Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332363</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/collaborators-on-the-ropes-as-wilderness-advocates-fight-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Somewhere, the industry lobbyists who successfully introduced “collaboration” to the arena of conservation policies and politics are toasting their success at splitting the conservation community.  The proof is playing out right now over the collaborators’ Gallatin Conservation and Recreation Act — which is meeting significant opposition from long-time wilderness advocates. This is nothing Montanans haven’t  More
The post Collaborators on the Ropes as Wilderness Advocates Fight Back appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cease-fire Agreements in the Middle East Seem More Remote than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332403</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/cease-fire-agreements-in-the-middle-east-seem-more-remote-than-ever/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Blood on His Hands” “After close to a year of neglect, Netanyahu doesn’t miss a single opportunity to ensure that there won’t be a deal. Not a day goes by in which Netanyahu doesn’t take concrete action to jeopardize the return home of all the hostages.” Those are the outraged words of the Hostages and  More
The post Cease-fire Agreements in the Middle East Seem More Remote than Ever appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Low-Wage Corporations That Blew Half a Trillion Dollars to Inflate CEO Pay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332232</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/the-low-wage-corporations-that-blew-half-a-trillion-dollars-to-inflate-ceo-pay/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T05:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Lowe’s home improvement store spent $43 billion on stock buybacks over the past five years. With that sum, the big box chain could’ve given each of its 285,000 employees a $30,000 bonus every year between 2019 and 2023. The extra cash would’ve meant a lot to Lowe’s workers — half of whom make less  More
The post The Low-Wage Corporations That Blew Half a Trillion Dollars to Inflate CEO Pay appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dirty Deleting, a Lack of Accountability, and Next Steps]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332407</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/02/dirty-deleting-a-lack-of-accountability-and-next-steps/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T04:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perhaps you’ve heard the term “teachable moment” in recent years. It is a way of framing or reframing a mistake or misfortune into a learning opportunity or chance for growth. I have had “teachable moments” unfold when text message alerts have hit multiple mobile phones in a classroom at the same time: “Warning! Active shooter  More
The post Dirty Deleting, a Lack of Accountability, and Next Steps appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wim Laven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "Ask HN: How to store and share passwords in a company?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41420875</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41420875"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T22:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You generally want to minimize the number of passwords you manage; for instance, you should generally be paying the SSO tax and getting as many services as you can onto OIDC. After that, just do the cloud version of 1Password, which is easy to audit and manage access for, which you'll thank yourself for when it comes time to SOC2.
Remember, as you give people access to passwords, that those passwords will need to be rotated when those people change to incompatible roles or depart the company. If passwords aren't a total pain in the ass for you, you're probably doing something wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Academic nepo babies ?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53118</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/01/academic-nepo-babies/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T21:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This study showing that US academic faculty members are 25 times more likely than Americans in general to have a parent with a PhD or Masters degree has attracted a lot of attention, and comments suggesting that this is unusual and unsatisfactory. But is it? For various reasons, I’ve interacted quite a bit with farmers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland: home of some of the best literature in the world]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8381</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ireland-home-best-literature-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Publication of Irish author Sally Rooney’s fourth novel, Intermezzo, on 24 September 2024, nears. It promises to be quite the event. I don’t know about Australia, but in Ireland and the UK, some bookshops will open early on the day, so eager Rooney fans can get hold of her latest offering. But Sally Rooney is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilians flock to Bluesky after authorities block X]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8376</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/brazilians-flock-bluesky-authorities-block-x/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T20:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilians are turning to Bluesky — the microblogging platform founded by then Twitter co-founder Jack Dorsey — in droves, following a ban on X in the South American country. The surge in signups however has prompted warnings from Bluesky that the service may experience outages, as a result. But that seems like a good sort […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[get with the program]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/get-with-program/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/get-with-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote this 2 weeks ago while I was particularly sad about my situation and in a lot of pain; after keeping it in the drafts for a while to consider it, I felt like publishing it now because it's easy to just portray the hopeful, productive ill person to the outside world, but sometimes accepting that stuff is tough!
I’ve been complaining about being ill sometimes, about specific symptoms, about being unable to do stuff and being stuck in bed so much.. and the response I seem to get (whether outright or implied) is like “Duh, you are chronically ill, of course this is happening.” Like it’s the most normal thing in the world. As if everyone has already known it for ages and has readily accepted it, but I am lagging behind. “Get with the program already!”
I remember asking my girlfriend if …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by smugglerFlynn in "Founder Mode"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41418149</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41418149"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T16:26:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This whole article is written around one key sentence:
  > There are things founders can do that managers can't, and not doing them feels wrong to founders, because it is.

And to be honest this hn comment section scares me, as it feels like people are discussing Paul’s new clothes without actually voicing out what they are talking about.
What the hell is “Founder mode”, exactly?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>smugglerFlynn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thought about conservative psychology re: the abortion issue]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53107</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/01/a-thought-about-conservative-psychology-re-the-abortion-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So is Trump going to be able to pivot to pro-choice in the run-up to the election? I mean: he’s trying. But will it work? And will his pro-life base accept it, because he’s Trump? I hope no pro-choice voters are fooled. I hope they hold him responsible for overturning Roe. It’s beyond obvious they […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Osa the Dog and the Last Goodbye]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/osa-the-dog-and-the-last-goodbye/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/osa-the-dog-and-the-last-goodbye/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we got to my son's house yesterday, he explained to me that one of his dogs wasn't feeling well. Osa, a 13-year-old lab/pit mix had a swollen stomach and was moving around very gingerly. Her condition had not changed by this morning and he elected to take he to the emergency vet's office in his neighborhood. The two of them were not gone long when he returned, grim faced. "She's dying" he told me.
Osa survived the removal of stomach tumors three years ago. Now they have returned and in such profusion and size that removing them at her age isn't a practical option. my granddaughte,r who lives in Virginia had an October trip already planned to come home for a visit with Osa, the family dog since she was in kindergarten. She planned that visit because of Osa's age and health history. My …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/1/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277677</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-1-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T10:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Responsible Is the Rental Housing Cartel for the Explosion in Homelessness?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277656</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/how-responsible-is-the-rental-housing-cartel-for-the-explosion-in-homelessness.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T10:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since collusion in pricing and vacancy hit critical mass in 2016, homelessness has soared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by magnio in "Honey, I shrunk {fmt}: bringing binary size to 14k and ditching the C++ runtime"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41415406</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41415406"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T09:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> All the formatting in {fmt} is locale-independent by default (which breaks with the C++’s tradition of having wrong defaults)
Chuckles]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>magnio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Lessons From Ancient Civilizations for Keeping Homes Cool in Hot, Dry Climates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277690</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/5-lessons-from-ancient-civilizations-for-keeping-homes-cool-in-hot-dry-climates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T09:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To prepare for an even hotter future, designers today could learn from the past.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionary Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332027</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/01/revolutionary-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T06:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As students worldwide head back to school this fall, in Gaza, there are no schools left. The U.N. considers the systemic obliteration of the education system by the Israeli military to be a “scholasticide” — all universities, over 80% of schools, the Central Archives of Gaza, and at least 13 libraries have been destroyed, as of April 2024, in Israel’s relentless bombing campaign. Almost 10,000 students are dead and 16,000 wounded, many killed in attacks on schools being used as sites of refuge.
Academics and university administrators in Gaza released an open letter asking for solidarity and resistance from the rest of the world: “We call upon our colleagues in the homeland and internationally to support our steadfast attempts to defend and preserve our universities for the sake of the future of our people, and our ability to remain on our Palestinian land in Gaza. We built these universities from tents. And from tents, with the support of our friends, we will rebuild them once again.”
As a graduate student, an aspiring professor, and the child of a Jewish academic, I take this call for solidarity seriously. Where and how do we learn ideologies of resistance, radicalism, and revolution? Once we have inherited a radical idea, what do we do with it? And how do we choose what ideas not to inherit?
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Revolutionary Inheritance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Maria Goldschmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Looking towards Great Howard Street (Liverpool) at night]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53104</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/01/sunday-photoblogging-looking-towards-great-howard-street-liverpool-at-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T05:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clowns Can Be Killers, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331759</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/01/clowns-can-be-killers-too/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T05:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Pau Casals.
These days, I find myself in a strange place. Despite the Democrats’ miraculous replacement of Biden, Trump’s reelection remains distinctly possible. I studied authoritarianism for my master’s degree, and I strongly believe that a second Trump presidency would represent the end of American democracy. Yet even so, I find myself frequently tempted to dismiss commentators’ pleas as hyperbolic handwringing. I think I’m probably not alone in this confusing toggling between panic and blaséness. After some soul-searching, I think one of the reasons for the ever-present allure of complacency, other than the natural human tendency towards denial, is Trump’s humor.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Clowns Can Be Killers, Too appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Remer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pfraze in "Brazil's X ban is sending lots of people to Bluesky"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41412758</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41412758"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T23:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copying over my latest backend status update; figure folks would find it interesting
Servers are holding up so far! Fortunately we were overprovisioned. If we hit 4mm new signups then things should get interesting. We did have some degradations (user handles entering an invalid state, event-stream crashed a couple times, algo crashed a couple times, image servers hit bad latencies) but we managed to avoid a full outage.
We use an event-sourcing model which is: K/V database for primary storage (actually sqlite), into a golang event stream, then into scylladb for computed views. Various separate services for search, algorithms, and images. Hybrid on-prem & cloud. There are ~20 of the k/v servers, 1 event-stream, 2 scylla clusters (I believe).
The event-stream crash would cause the application to stop making progress on ingesting events, but we still got the writes, so you'd see eg likes failing to increment the counter but then magically taking effect 60 seconds later. Since the scylla cluster and the KV stores stayed online, we avoided a full outage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pfraze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs are weird and I do not understand them]]></title>
        <id>https://unwissen.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-weird-and-i-do-not-understand-them/</id>
        <link href="https://unwissen.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-weird-and-i-do-not-understand-them/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Off course I knew what a blog was before finding Bear.1 I read blogposts and used tumblr (…), and I think my mother had a blog for some time, too. But I did not know about the technicalities (wtf is RSS?) and the culture of blogging. And although it took some time to set this whole endeavor up2, it is the culture-thing that is the hardest for me.
I am used to Twitter and Bluesky, where posts have to be short and draw attention. This combination rewards posts that say divisive shit3 and punishes those that are nuanced and complex. It is easier to wish death onto some asshole politician than to explain what they did wrong. If you want to write something personal or sincere you have to meme and/or bury it under ironic detachment.
Like posts on microblogging platforms, blogposts follow their o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bhauer in "Buy, Borrow, Die – Explained"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41411273</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41411273"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T19:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The step-up in cost basis on death is the original sin that underpins the entire debate over unrealized gains.
It's disheartening to see so much thought and deliberation going into an obviously toxic idea (taxing unrealized gains) when the obvious solution (removing the cost basis step-up when assets change hands) is being ignored.
Inherited wealth is the least earned, so it should be politically palatable to change this. But presumably because such a change would acutely affect the people who make laws in the country specifically, it is never seriously considered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bhauer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rzimmerman in "My fake job in Y2K preparedness"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41410912</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41410912"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T18:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked for about a year with a consulting firm that handled "Y2K compliance". Unlike this Andersen exercise in legal face-saving, it was a real job. Big companies hired us to do a full inventory of their site equipment (this included manufacturing plants, Pharma stuff) and go line by line with their vendors and figure out which components had known Y2K issues, which had not been tested at all, and which ones were fine/had simple fixes. We helped them replace and fix what needed to be fixed.
Y2K was a real problem. The end-of-the-world blackouts + planes falling from the sky was sensationalism, but there were real issues and most of them got fixed. Not trying to take away from this very interesting story of corrupt cronyism, but there were serious people dealing with serious problems out there. "Remember Y2K? Nothing happened!" is a super toxic lesson to take away from a rare success where people came together and fixed something instead of firefighting disasters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rzimmerman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on the last day of Blaugust 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/notes-on-the-last-day-of-blaugust-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/notes-on-the-last-day-of-blaugust-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy World Blog Day!
In mid-July, I wanted to find a way to challenge myself in August for my birthday month. I initially wanted to do a photo challenge (a photo a day?) of sorts. As I was trying to figure out what to do, it was happenstance to have come across someone posting about Blaugust: A Festival of Blogging. I had no idea what it was but then I read this bit under What is Blaugust?:
The goal is to stoke the fires of creativity and allow bloggers and other content creators to mingle in a shared community while pushing each other to post more regularly. Above all the goal of Blaugust has always been to prove to folks that they can in fact sit down every day and create something fresh and then share it with the world.
I knew I just had to try it.
And here we are.
I joined telling mys…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Best to Do Bad Things That Hurt Your Spirit]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53098</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/31/how-best-to-do-bad-things-that-hurt-your-spirit/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T14:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read reddit. Yeah, I know. Plain People of Crooked Timber: “why would you go and do a thing like that when you could sit on the kitchen floor and watch your packet of English muffins slowly pass its sell-by date and develop that unpleasant sour flavour you usually don’t notice until it’s too late […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Whiter Shade of Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332199</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/31/a-whiter-shade-of-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T13:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It’s hard not to feel invisible as a Palestinian-American. Our trauma and pain feel unseen and ignored by both parties. One party uses our identity as a slur, and the other refuses to hear from us.” – Rep. Rashida Tlaib Israel drew all sorts of US military forces and intelligence assets into the Middle East […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post A Whiter Shade of Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Debt, Economic Collapse and the Ancient World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277672</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/michael-hudson-debt-economic-collapse-and-the-ancient-world.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T12:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robinson Erhardt conducts a wide-ranging discussion of Michael Hudson's work, including  the social cost of debt bondage and rentierism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/31/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277573</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-31-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T10:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our puckish daily links: fingerprint loss, Long Covid Alzheimerish brain effects, US government solar farms, China growth worries, Mpox economic fallout in Africa, UK suicide rises, painters' union divests from Israel, Ukraine F-16 "crash", Trump wobbles,Kamala interview splat, Durov arrest, Intel breakup? Federal ruling curbs Section 230]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277653</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-problem-with-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T07:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why AI is likely to have more limited use than boosters anticipate, particularly in replacing professionals like teachers and accountants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PSA: Remove your location when uploading pictures to bearblog]]></title>
        <id>https://bakavic.net/psa-remove-your-location-when-uploading-pictures-to-bearblog/</id>
        <link href="https://bakavic.net/psa-remove-your-location-when-uploading-pictures-to-bearblog/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T06:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR: Bearblog doesn't (currently) strip location data from your uploads, so you need to do it yourself
I noticed that bear blog posts with pictures were loading rather slowly - turns out images are being stored and served as-is, full-sized and all.
This is probably a Good Thing(tm) for people running photo blogs, but I also realised that photo metadata, including your location, are being retained - not something you would want, e.g. if your pictures were taken at home.
If you have posted images via the native bearblog insert image feature in the past, it is a good idea to check that your location hasn't been inadvertently leaked.
Also, if you would like this to be solved for everyone, please help to upvote the suggestion to preprocess images.
Android
I'm not too sure how to this natively in Android (do let me know if you have an elegant way to remove location data!) - I'm wary to recommend any of the numerous apps that seem to do this, as I'm not sure which of them can be trusted.
EDIT: Jd dropped me an email recommending Aves (F-Droid|Github) for Android :-
Just saw your post and I was thinking to write the same a few days ago.
To remove metadata on your android phone, Aves is a really good gallery app. You can edit all of your metadata and also sort images in different ways.
It is available on playstore as well as fdroid.
Thanks for the recommendation! I haven't been in touch with the Android ecosystem for a while, and it's great to see photo/file manager apps which are not riddled with ads.
iOS
In the meantime, if you're on iOS 17+, there is an option in the photo picker when inserting images, to remove location and resize the image:
Example images (of a sunrise on Alishan)
Original image, with GPS metadata:

Inspector in macOS Preview:
Resized image, without GPS metadata:

Inspector in macOS Preview:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tux1968 in "Crows are even smarter than we thought"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41405773</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41405773"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T00:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have posted this before, but it really left an impression about crows, and the bond between their mates:
Years ago I was putting out the garbage in the back alley behind our building where I lived on the 8th floor. A crow attacked me out of the blue. Distracted by the attack, the back door slammed shut behind me. Since my key was only good for the front door, I had to walk around the building. That damn crow followed me the entire time, dive bombing my head, and screaming bloody murder at me. It was a little spooky.
When I finally got back inside and upstairs, I went and looked out the living room window, which looked out the same direction as the back alley. The crow had flown back around and was at the 8th floor looking in the window, from the other side of the pigeon netting we had on our balcony. On the inside of the pigeon netting, was another crow, desperately trying to figure out how it could escape. Not really sure how it had got itself through the pigeon netting in the first place.
I went out and sliced a hole through the netting and the trapped crow quickly joined its mate outside, who finally stopped screaming bloody murder. To this day it still amazes me that the crow's mate, knew which apartment I lived in and spotted me downstairs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tux1968</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Engineering with Empathy: My Journey to Understanding the User Experience]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16945</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/engineering-with-empathy-my-journey-to-understanding-the-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T22:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“What are your goals for this quarter?” It’s the question every manager asks, and one that often prompts a flurry of technical objectives and project milestones. Jumping into this internship, I knew my answer. I wanted to practice making informed decisions on my project, since that was one of the challenges I faced last summer. […]
The post Engineering with Empathy: My Journey to Understanding the User Experience appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaili Liang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RE: Write like you talk]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/re-write-like-you-talk/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/re-write-like-you-talk/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T22:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today I was reading some new posts by Visa. There’s not much to say about that, except that he uses pretty normal words and writes very well.
This might seem like an odd comment, but it stems from my reading of another post, A Brief Case on Bearblog. The author of that post is clearly a talented and experienced writer who, it must be said, writes very (very) well. However, the words they use are so fancy, and the way they’re woven is so perfect that reading them feels ?strange?1.
This thought reminded me of an excellent essay by Paul Graham, Write Like You Talk. In it, he argues that if you want people to connect with you, you must write in a way that feels familiar to them. Essentially, the essay rests on the assumption that we all speak similarly but think differently.
I’m the fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rock_artist in "AnandTech Farewell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41403970</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41403970"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T20:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Finally, I’d like to end this piece with a comment on the Cable TV-ification of the web. A core belief that Anand and I have held dear for years, and is still on our About page to this day, is AnandTech’s rebuke of sensationalism, link baiting, and the path to shallow 10-o'clock-news reporting. It has been our mission over the past 27 years to inform and educate our readers by providing high-quality content
That’s the core of it. And too bad they’re off. Finding a news outlet that isn’t “tweeting” an article and isn’t a blog post on HN was great. And while they mention Tom’s hardware. It always felt (to me) less verbose where I needed it.
Fair well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rock_artist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277617</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; New RCP averages show 2024 race neck-and-neck, plus new Covid charts show positivity improvement; Kamala and joy; Trump needs a campaign reset; Unions and worker power ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oops! I Did It Again]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/oops-did-again/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/oops-did-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A month ago, I decided to shut down this blog. The next day I changed my mind, which I wrote about in the post "The blog that refuses to die."
Yesterday, I launched a membership called Birming Buddies. When I woke up this morning after a long and good night's sleep, I realized it didn't feel right. I have now removed the page.
It probably sounds crazy – and maybe it is.
But neither the decision to start Birming Buddies nor to shut down the blog were impulsive actions. It's always been a long period of consideration before I hit the OK button. Once I've done that, I quickly realize whether it was the right decision or not.
It's as if I can't reason my way through some decisions. I have to put them into action to really be able to determine what is right and what is not. Not very practical, I know, but that's apparently how I work.
Anyway, no harm done. The member fees are  refunded and the blog lives on. And I'll continue to develop the Bearming theme. Today I released an add-on to show excerpts of your blog posts (see example on my home page), and a new color palette named Green Screen.
I hope you have the patience to continue following my rather crooked blog journey. Hopefully, the transparency will bring some comfort to those who can relate.
By the way, I also launched a newsletter today. Subscribe now, who knows, maybe I'll delete it tomorrow ;)
I wish you a wonderful weekend!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby shebang behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://agj.bearblog.dev/ruby-shebang-behavior/</id>
        <link href="https://agj.bearblog.dev/ruby-shebang-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby has a surprising hack in its interpreter. If the file starts with a shebang line, ruby will skip all lines until it encounters a shebang line which contains the string "ruby" in it.
This lets you start out as a shell script and then after some setup switch over to ruby
#!/bin/bash

rvm use 3.3.4

exec ruby $0 "$@"

echo "I am a bash line too but I will never run"

#!/usr/bin/env ruby
puts "I run in ruby"

There is some ugliness to this hack though. The interpreter only looks for the word "ruby" so the shebang line could be whatever including.
#!/bin/bash

rvm use 3.3.4

exec ruby $0 "$@"

echo "I am a bash line too but I will never run"

#!/I/am/a/rubyist
puts "I run in ruby"

will work but
#!/bin/bash

rvm use 3.3.4

exec ruby $0 "$@"

echo "I am a bash line too but I will never run"

#!/bin/rb
puts "I run in ruby"

will result in a print of "no Ruby script found in input"
Source: ruby.c#L2681
I am not a fan of such hacks in a language. Python lets you do something similar too - but it takes advantage of the fact that triple-quoted strings are side-effect free in Python and """": is the same as just a : which is two empty strings followed by a true in bash.
#!/bin/bash
'''':
source /path/to/venv/bin/activate.sh

exec python $0 "$@"

echo "I am a bash line too but I will never run"
'''

print("I am in python")]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "AnandTech Farewell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400911</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400911"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T14:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anandtech is how I learned what Ubuntu is. I must have been about 10 years old, and the concept of any OS besides Windows or MacOS was completely foreign to me. Within a few weeks, I had dug an old laptop out of my dad's bin of "stuff work wasn't using anymore" and I managed to put Ubuntu on it. I think it was an HP. I don't remember the exact specs but I do remember that the GPU was failing, there were weird video glitches all the time, and the battery held a charge for about 15 minutes.
That was my first experience with Linux. That broken-ass computer was what I used when I learned Arduino. I'm now a firmware engineer, writing this comment on my work laptop, which is running Ubuntu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Sesse__ in "AnandTech Farewell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400265</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400265"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T13:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extremely sad. There basically is nothing like Anandtech; the depth, the ability to explain, the lack of sensationalism, and the integrity in benchmarking (I still vividly remember when they noticed an issue with HPET in Windows affecting their benchmarks, and promptly pulled all of them offline until they could reassess). Chips and Cheese is great but only covers a certain segment of it.
In the end, I would assume it just boiled down to lack of money. There were people among us who would gladly pay for this kind of coverage, but Anandtech said at some point they had considered it and couldn't find a good model. (As an aside, I pay for LWN, and I would pay for something that covered similar areas to Phoronix but actually was good.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sesse__</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Raging Atheist Like Me Became an Ordained Minister and Wedding Officiant]]></title>
        <id>https://linkage.lol/universal-life-church/</id>
        <link href="https://linkage.lol/universal-life-church/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About 15 years ago, two heathen friends of mine were planning to get married. They were severely unchurched, as we say in the South, meaning they didn't have a relationship with anyone in the clergy. I'm a lot of things, buy shy is not one of them, so I said that I'd be more than glad to marry them if I could figure out a way to get ordained by some online church. After some Google searching, I found the website for the Universal Life Church, filled out a form, clicked a button and became entitled to perform marriages. I went on to perform the ceremony for my friends and since then for about a dozen other couples, including my own daughter. I live in North Carolina and here the Universal Church checks the boxes to make such ceremonies legal (but voidable). Although the church claims to be able top make you legal in all 50 states, you are advised to do your research, since some states have regulations that make wedding officiants register and pay a fee. And, like anything on the Internet, there are conflicting opinions and homemade websites purporting to be experts in wedding law (I didn't know that was a thing ) People who charge money to perform weddings do not like the Universal Life Church and make a number of claims against it. Just saying.
Become Ordained - Universal Life Church (ulc.org)
Is Getting Ordained in the Universal Life Church legit? : r/wedding (reddit.com)
Enjoyed it? Please upvote 👇]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by codeslave13 in "AnandTech Farewell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400161</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41400161"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T12:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sad day. My buddy and I were the original developers of anandtech when it went live running on cold fusion and oracle as the backend. I started a hosting company and hosted anadtrch for a few years. Lots of memories there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>codeslave13</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277606</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T10:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our Friyay daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Casino capitalism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45579</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/30/casino-capitalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T10:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll According to Keynes, financial crises are a recurring feature of our economy and are linked to its fundamental financial instability: It is of the nature of organised investment markets, under the influence of purchasers largely ignorant of what they are buying and of speculators who are more concerned with forecasting the next […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alarming development: Rights activists, including a young woman, face blasphemy charges in Pakistani-administered Kashmir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Alarming-development-Rights-activists-including-a-young-woman-face-blasphemy</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Alarming-development-Rights-activists-including-a-young-woman-face-blasphemy"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T09:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joint statement and appeal by JKNSF and RSF 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Pakistan, 
South Asia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Looming Nuclear Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332068</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/a-looming-nuclear-catastrophe-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no greater strategic madness than the belief that nuclear superiority must be maintained at each rung of the nuclear ladder in order to maintain deterrence.  U.S. weapons technology was a major driver of escalation dominance throughout the 1950s and 1960s along with the belief that the Soviet Union would move to a level of nuclear conflict that the United States could not counter.  “Dr. Strangelove or How I Stopped Worrying and Learned to Love the Bomb” parodied these fears, and the arms control and disarmament developments of the 1970s and 1980s helped to defuse them.  Sadly, the Biden administration has taken a step that suggests a return to escalation dominance, which will spiral a Pentagon budget that will soon reach $1 trillion per year. More
The post A Looming Nuclear Catastrophe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death Camp]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332169</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/death-camp/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:01:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since 2007, when the State of Israel implemented its still-ongoing blockade of Gaza, several different monikers have emerged to describe the conditions for Palestinians living in the territory under the ongoing Israeli siege.  Now, after 11 months of the murderous Israeli assault on the people of Gaza, it is necessary once again to revise what the State of Israel has imposed on the territory.  What the state of Israel has created in the Gaza Strip is nothing less than a death camp akin to what the Nazis created for the massacre of Jews and other so-called enemies of the Reich. More
The post Death Camp appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Fields</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election Years Are Dangerous Times for People of Color]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332089</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/election-years-are-dangerous-times-for-people-of-color/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As he runs for reelection in 2024, former president Donald Trump has made the outlandish claim that “millions of people [have crossed the United States border] …from prisons, jails and mental institutions to come into our country and destroy our country.” His statement was a combination of two tropes that are often deployed by those seeking political  More
The post Election Years Are Dangerous Times for People of Color appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Genocide With a Smile]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332066</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/roaming-charges-genocide-with-a-smile/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[True to form, Trump has now taken to calling Kamala Harris “low IQ” and “stupid,” racist tropes he draws on whenever he’s confronted by minorities, women or both. But for all her faults, Harris isn’t stupid. In fact, she’s demonstrated her ability to swiftly master and deftly deploy the finer points of Clintonian triangulation, the strategy of political bait-and-switch that prioritizes running against the core issues held by her own party, even policies she once enthusiastically promoted as signature features of her own previous campaigns. Pulling this off required some pretty adroit political gymnastics, where Harris had to completely reverse herself without showing the strain over long-held positions on fracking, immigration, asylum, a human rights-based foreign policy, student loan forgiveness, torture, the death penalty, and a single-payer health care system. But she sold these policy retreats so smoothly that the Democratic base eagerly embraced her joyful politics of austerity, aggressive policing and genocide with a smile. More
The post Roaming Charges: Genocide With a Smile appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Reproductive Justice Without Palestinian Liberation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332094</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/no-reproductive-justice-without-palestinian-liberation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following speech was given at Union Park at the March on the DNC on Monday, August 19th. Chicago for Abortion Rights is out here today because we REFUSE to allow the Democrats to use abortion rights and trans rights as a bargaining chip to force us to vote for their imperialist agenda. We refuse the  More
The post No Reproductive Justice Without Palestinian Liberation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mandy Medley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break on Through: Finding The Doors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332156</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/break-on-through-finding-the-doors/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was at university when I first heard the Doors.  It was springtime, coming on summer.  I was living on campus, my first year, and I was eighteen.  I was in a housemate’s room, waiting for him to get back for some reason I don’t recall now.  The building we lived in was a little  More
The post Break on Through: Finding The Doors appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where Do the Candidates Stand on War? Someplace Very Vague]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332149</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/where-do-the-candidates-stand-on-war-someplace-very-vague/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since a prerequisite for the American presidency is being ready, willing and able to slaughter lots of foreigners, it would be nice to know where the candidates stand on war, especially for those of us against it. We know where Joe “Proxy War” Biden stands. He’s all in. We can only pray that Kamala “Military  More
The post Where Do the Candidates Stand on War? Someplace Very Vague appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dispatch on American Political Dystopia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332161</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/dispatch-on-american-political-dystopia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is seemingly no end to the lethal and dystopian absurdity of  US-American political life right now. Donald “Poisoning Our Blood” Trump not only walks free but has a decent shot of being re-elected to the most dangerous job on Earth. What the fascist fuck! Hey, so what if he’s a malignant narcissist, a fascist,  More
The post Dispatch on American Political Dystopia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 7 Has a Prehistory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/october-7-has-a-prehistory/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In belatedly disposing of teaching materials long after retiring, I came across a cutting from the Guardian Weekly (that convenient pre-internet medium for far-flung colonials, comprising articles from the UK Guardian, the Le Monde and the Washington Post). The cutting was a review of David Montgomery’s The Fall of the House of Labor; the issue, 22 May 1988. But wait, there’s something on  More
The post October 7 Has a Prehistory appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware the Derogators: The Geneva Conventions Turn 75]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332148</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/beware-the-derogators-the-geneva-conventions-turn-75/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 12, 1949, the four Geneva Conventions were adopted, laying the basis of a normative standard in international humanitarian law.  As Balthasar Staehelin, personal envoy of the International Committee of the Red Cross (ICRC) president to China, stated at an anniversary event at the Swiss Embassy in Beijing, “In the past 75 years, the four Geneva Conventions  More
The post Beware the Derogators: The Geneva Conventions Turn 75 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tasty Bacon or Fellow Being? The Paradox of How We Relate to the Intelligence and Emotions of Pigs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/tasty-bacon-or-fellow-being-the-paradox-of-how-we-relate-to-the-intelligence-and-emotions-of-pigs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pigs are fascinating animals. Science shows they can solve challenging problems, love to play, display wide-ranging emotions, and have unique personalities. In short, they are both intelligent and sentient—capable of feeling. It’s clear that it is illogical and immoral to treat pigs as mere objects. In 2015, I reviewed an essay notable for its summary and distillation  More
The post Tasty Bacon or Fellow Being? The Paradox of How We Relate to the Intelligence and Emotions of Pigs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Bekoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump IPOs His Presidency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332026</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/trump-ipos-his-presidency/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why does anyone think Donald Trump is actually running for president? Granted, he’s the Republican nominee and is on the ballot in all fifty states, but the only election day that interests Trump is the one around September 20. On that day (or perhaps a few days later) the lockout period on his Trump Media  More
The post Trump IPOs His Presidency appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Venezuela Elections of 28 July 2024:  What and Whom to Believe?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332163</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-venezuela-elections-of-28-july-2024-what-and-whom-to-believe/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our media rush to issue sensational headlines and frequently make premature judgements, which, when false, are seldom corrected. With regard to the Venezuelan elections of 28 July, we are expected to believe that Nicolas Maduro rigged them. But why do we tend to think that way?  Why do the journalists of the New York Times, WaPo,  More
The post The Venezuela Elections of 28 July 2024:  What and Whom to Believe? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DNC Protests: Freedom That Extends Beyond the Platitudes of the Democratic Party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332095</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-dnc-protests-freedom-that-extends-beyond-the-platitudes-of-the-democratic-party/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a pro-Palestine encampment at my local college in May, I booked a ticket to the DNC. The president of the college had just been forced to resign for “insubordination” for having the audacity to meet with demonstrators and listen to their demands. The student movement to oppose genocide and settler colonialism inspired me to  More
The post The DNC Protests: Freedom That Extends Beyond the Platitudes of the Democratic Party appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Prosecution of Trayon White]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332115</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/the-prosecution-of-trayon-white/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images of Trayon White in the passenger seat of a car, allegedly pocketing envelopes of cash on multiple occasions, have been splashed across the media. And now the 40-year-old DC councilmember, a protégé of the late Marion Barry, faces federal bribery charges and up to 15 years in prison. ly pocketing envelopes of cash on  More
The post The Prosecution of Trayon White appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Erdan’s War on the UN: The Brutal Wish of Failed Israel Diplomat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332084</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/erdans-war-on-the-un-the-brutal-wish-of-failed-israel-diplomat/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Departing Israeli Ambassador to the United Nations, Gilad Erdan clearly had an unpleasant experience at the world’s largest international institution. In an interview published in the Israeli newspaper Maariv on August 20, the disgruntled envoy said that “the UN building should be closed and wiped off from the face of the earth.” Whether Erdan has  More
The post Erdan’s War on the UN: The Brutal Wish of Failed Israel Diplomat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tribes and Greens Rally Against Uranium Mining Near Grand Canyon]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=332180</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/30/tribes-and-greens-rally-against-uranium-mining-near-grand-canyon/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T05:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I just want to remind people that this is about nuclear war, genocide and the ongoing colonialization of our land and the ongoing takeover of our resources and we are tired of being a resource colony. We are not a sacrifice zone.” – Leona Morgan, Diné, co-founder of Haul No!   On Saturday, Aug. 24, members  More
The post Tribes and Greens Rally Against Uranium Mining Near Grand Canyon  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hatch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Heath and the demise of western Marxism]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53089</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/30/53089/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T01:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am very pleased that our very own Chris Bertram has responded to Joseph Heath’s very entertaining and polemical “John Rawls and the death of Western Marxism,” a widely shared Substack post [HT: Dailynous]. Chris has made some important corrections to the public record, and the comments on his post are extending that. As it happens, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by adityapurwa in "The secret inside One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396943</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396943"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T01:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know. Reading this made me tear up a bit. I learned software engineering when I was in junior high school. I learned it because I sucked at math, and I want to write  programs that solve my homework. Then I continue writing LAN chat, HTTP server, Anti Virus, and a lot more things just because it was fun to do.
It was fun, it was challenging, it was rewarding, it was amazing.
Now that I’m working, with the endless stream of new technologies, the debates of X considered harmful, J is better than K, and a barrage of never ending new things. It started to numb my mind.
Somehow, those joyful feeling of engineering no longer feels like the blue sky. I think its still blue, but for an eye washed in silvers, everything looks gray.
Reading this story somehow light up that childhood feeling of me learning software engineering. It can still be fun. I can still write things for the sake of me and not for the sake of exit nor a new shiny SaaS.
Thank your for writing this. It gave me a ray of hope that it can still be fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>adityapurwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tgsovlerkhgsel in "Visit Bletchley Park"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396635</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396635"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T00:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're interested in historical buildings, go ahead, visit Bletchley Park. But expect most of the exhibits to be buildings, living quarters, offices etc. and mundane descriptions of day-to-day life there, not exhibits about the technical/cryptological aspects (although they do have some of those too).
If you're interested in computer history and Bombe/Colossus, visit the much lesser known National Museum of Computing at the same site. https://www.tnmoc.org/
I spent way too much time at the the boring parts of Bletchley Park and as a result didn't have enough time for the Museum of Computing.
I'd recommend starting at the Museum of Computing, then if you have time left, the 1-2 buildings inside the official Bletchley Park museum that have the crypto exhibits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tgsovlerkhgsel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eieio in "The secret inside One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396053</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41396053"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T22:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[author here :)
this is my favorite story from running the site, and possibly the best story I've ever been a part of. I'm not a big crier but I have cried so many times thinking and trying to write about it over the past 2 months. And of course, the process of discovery (and going from panic to excitement) was pretty crazy too.
One of my favorite things about this is that it validated one of the core beliefs I have when making these things - that you need constraints for the small group of people that are jerks, but that for the most part those constraints are fodder for the largely-good and very creative folks that play around on the internet.
Happy to answer any questions folks have!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eieio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asolove in "The secret inside One Million Checkboxes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41395709</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41395709"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This part is so important:
> The adults in my life were largely not mad at me. They asked me to knock it off, but also made me a t-shirt. I don’t think I’d be doing what I do now without the encouragement that I received then.
Teena need a place to be moderately mischievous, with semi-real social outcomes, but also some boundaries and help to not take it too far.
And adults who aren’t authorities over them except insofar that they have cool talents the kids want to learn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asolove</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Work Notifications Set to Off]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/work-notifications-set-to-off/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/work-notifications-set-to-off/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First day back to work.
One of my self-sabotaging behavior is my occasional inability to set boundaries, specifically when it comes to my personal time and work.
I rarely take days off from work. I know that it’s a problem because I have maxed out my vacation accrual days (like now) during several occasions. When I do take the time off from work, I still check my messages in case there’s something on fire and I need to fix it. I also have my notifications on in the evenings, because some of my co-workers also don’t have boundaries when it comes to work, and will ping me because they too are working late.
I know, it’s bad.
This time around, very in line with my Do Not Disturb mentality, I decided to turn my Slack messages and work email notifications off during my time off.
It worked out so well. I mostly didn’t think about work. I didn’t see any messages that needed my attention right away. I didn’t have to think about the things I need to solve for my team during my time off. I had a clear separation of me enjoying my time off, and work that stresses me out more than it should.
Because of this, I decided to make this separation a little bit more permanent. I’m going to actually turn my (work) notifications off when it’s time to log off, so that I’m not unintentionally working during the evenings. We’ll see if this pans out.
Just the little things to get my mental health sorted out.
29/31 - Blaugust
💬 Community Echoes
Always On - Freelancers and Notifications by Nathan Friend
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dusk, a novel by Robbie Arnott, being published in October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8373</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dusk-novel-robbie-arnott-published-october-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dusk, the new novel by Hobart based Australian author Robbie Arnott, is being published on Tuesday 8 October 2024. In the distant highlands, a puma named Dusk is killing shepherds. Down in the lowlands, twins Iris and Floyd are out of work, money and friends. When they hear that a bounty has been placed on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oasis regroup, this is not the second coming we were waiting for]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8371</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/oasis-regroup-unwanted-second-coming/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T20:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backbeat, the word is on the street, Oasis, the old nineties Britpop act — that was, in the words of co-founder Noel Gallagher — bigger than the Beatles, is set to play a series of reunion concerts. Honestly, I was more excited when in 2011, the Stone Roses, an even older act, announced they were* […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by caymanjim in "Can solar costs keep shrinking?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41394613</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41394613"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T19:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spend four months of the year traveling in an RV. Two years ago, I budgeted over $6000 for my desired solar setup (at least 1200Ah of battery, at least 2400W of solar, plus various controllers and other components). It was expensive enough for me to hold off, and more importantly, I didn't have the space on my current RV for the solar panels.
In just the two years since then, prices on batteries and panels have dropped 25% or more, and solar power per square foot at a good price point has gone up significantly (400W monocrystalline panels can be gotten for $200, in the same form factor as the 200W panels I had been budgeting for). I've now lowered my budget to $4000 for the same setup I was planning to spend $6000 on two years ago, and with 400W panels, I no longer need to upgrade to a l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>caymanjim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Quit My Job to Focus on My Studies]]></title>
        <id>https://matanabudy.com/i-quit-my-job-to-focus-on-my-studies/</id>
        <link href="https://matanabudy.com/i-quit-my-job-to-focus-on-my-studies/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T18:49:10.095Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week was my last day at work. By “work,” I mean my job as a software engineer at the data-security startup where I’ve been working for the last two and a half years.
As you can probably guess from the title, I quit my job to focus on my studies. I started a master’s degree in computational linguistics this year, and I've been juggling both work and university.
Working and studying simultaneously has its advantages—the first one is obvious: money. While academic life has its perks, financial gain isn’t usually one of them. Working while studying allowed me to make a living, plain and simple.
But there are other benefits, too—like advancing my career as a software engineer, working on interesting problems, interacting with customers, and having the routine of going to the office and spe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VyseofArcadia in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393216</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393216"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Hilarious that the entire TSA system is vulnerable to the most basic web programming error that you generally learn to avoid 10 minutes
The article mentions that FlyCASS seems to be run by one person. This isn't a matter of technical chops, this is a matter of someone who is good at navigating bureaucracy convincing the powers that be that they should have a special hook into the system.
What should really be investigated is who on the government side approved and vetted the initial FlyCASS proposal and subsequent development? And why, as something with a special hook into airline security infrastructure, was it never security audited?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VyseofArcadia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by macNchz in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393163</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393163"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What was surprising to me was that they didn't immediately do pre-dawn raids on the pentesters' homes and hold them without a lawyer under some provision of an anti-terror law.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>macNchz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by UniverseHacker in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393115</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41393115"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hilarious that the entire TSA system is vulnerable to the most basic web programming error that you generally learn to avoid 10 minutes into reading about web programming- and that every decent quality web framework automatically prevents.
It is really telling that they try to cover up and deny instead of fix it, but not surprising. That is a natural consequence of authoritarian thinking, which is the entire premise and culture of the TSA. Any institution that covers up and ignores existential risks instead of confronting them head on will eventually implode by consequences of its own negligence- which hopefully will happen to the TSA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>UniverseHacker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dylan604 in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392963</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392963"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since they actually went past the SQL injection and then created a fake record for an employee, I'm shocked that Homeland did not come after and arrest those involved. Homeland would have been top of the list to misinterpret a disclosure and prefer to refer to the disclosure as malicious hacking instead of responsible disclosure. I'm more impressed by this than the incompetence of the actual issue.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dylan604</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by woodruffw in "Bypassing airport security via SQL injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392938</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392938"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T17:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The TSA's response here is childish and embarrassing, although perhaps unsurprising given the TSA's institutional disinterest in actual security. It's interesting to see that DHS seemingly (initially) handled the report promptly and professionally, but then failed to maintain top-level authority over the fix and disclosure process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>woodruffw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nsagent in "Judges rule Big Tech's free ride on Section 230 is over"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392867</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41392867"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current comments seem to say this is rings the death knell of social media and that this just leads to government censorship. I'm not so sure.
I think the ultimate problem is that social media is not unbiased — it curates what people are shown. In that role they are no longer an impartial party merely hosting content. It seems this ruling is saying that the curation being algorithmic does not absolve the companies from liability.
In a very general sense, this ruling could be seen as a form of net neutrality. Currently social media platforms favor certain content, while down weighting others. Sure, it might be at a different level than peer agreements between ISPs and websites, but it amounts to a similar phenomenon when most people interact on social media through the feed.
Honestly, I think I'd love to see what changes this ruling brings about. HN is quite literally the only social media site (loosely interpreted) I even have an account on anymore, mainly because of how truly awful all the sites have become. Maybe this will make social media more palatable again? Maybe not, but I'm inclined to see what shakes out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nsagent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jehna1 in "OpenAI is good at unminifying code"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41390033</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41390033"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T12:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author of HumanifyJS here! I've created specifically a LLM based tool for this, which uses LLMs on AST level to guarantee that the code keeps working after the unminification step:
https://github.com/jehna/humanify]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jehna1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - Anti-Communist communists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-anti-communist-communists?v=1724924772</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-anti-communist-communists?v=1724924772"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T09:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: Anti-Communist communists
Subtitle: Or: on capitalization and capitalism
Date: August 28, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 29th August 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 It feels like two years ago but it was probably five. I drove from one side of North Carolina to another side of North Carolina because the “neo-confederates” were planning some kind of armed march through some small town and we needed all the numbers we could get to confront them. It worked, and we outnumbered them, and the people in town seemed grateful for our presence. 
 After a few hours, it devolved into a strange shouting match alongside a rural road. The confederates on one side of the road, the anti-fascists on the other. We probably called them Nazis. They called us communists. 
 “I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Joseph Heath’s account of the trajectory of analytical Marxism]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53079</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/29/on-joseph-heaths-account-of-the-trajectory-of-analytical-marxism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been much attention online to a piece by Joseph Heath arguing that analytical Marxism disappeared because the analytical Marxists all turned into Rawlsian liberals. At a certain level of resolution (blurred, zoomed out) the argument has something going for it. But at that level, all it amounts to is the claim that this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by broodbucket in "HDMI Forum rejects AMD's HDMI 2.1 open-source driver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387420</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387420"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T04:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>On the one hand, this move ensures the quality and consistency of HDMI experience.
Does it though? Does it really?
I don't understand this move from HDMI Forum. They're handing a win to DisplayPort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>broodbucket</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gstar in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387112</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387112"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incidentally, if you root your tablet you can just change the build.MODEL to "MyAir5" and everything will work on a third party tablet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gstar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gstar in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387108</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41387108"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OMFG; I am in Perth, I have the same system, the very same problem and solved it almost the same way and was in the process of writing it up.
The system uses RS422, with a base64 encoded AES key in the aaservice binary, and I was contemplating building an esp32 based open source implementation of the controller.
That's a crazy weird coincidence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gstar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ranebo in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386992</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386992"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T03:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You have no idea how true this is :).  I had to upgrade everything, the old site didn't even have SSL.  But this annoyed me so much I wanted others to know how to fix it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ranebo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by redact207 in "Air Con: $1697 for an on/off switch"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386671</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41386671"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T02:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that this man resurrected his blog after 10 years just to write this. Anger and spite are strong motivators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>redact207</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommending for Long-Term Member Satisfaction at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ac15cada49ef</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/recommending-for-long-term-member-satisfaction-at-netflix-ac15cada49ef?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T01:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jiangwei Pan, Gary Tang, Henry Wang, and Justin Basilico]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending August 25, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240828</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240828"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GitOps for Stateful Workload Management with vSphere CSI driver on on-premises Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>ed82f2e2617bb8ba0abe2dbd4214f8982ac7d851</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-gitops-for-stateful-workload-management-with-vsphere-csi-driver-on-on-premises-kubernetes-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T22:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the de-facto standard for container orchestration, providing powerful capabilities for deploying and managing stateless workloads. However, users running stateful applications on Kubernetes face unique challenges, especially in VMware environments. A key issue is that the virtual disks used by stateful apps can’t be attached to pods as easily as ephemeral storage. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elamaran Shanmugam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I Become a Vaishnavite?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53071</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/should-i-become-a-vaishnavite/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OK guys, here’s the deal. Last night I had a decently long dream in which Vishnu appeared to me personally, blue but golden with godly light and so on, to explain to me that he was real, and that I should worship him but not necessarily his avatars, more just him, (though I objected that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[404 Media are not going anywhere, but yes they are]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8368</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/404-media-not-going-anywhere-but-they-are/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T21:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What we learned in our first year of 404 Media, by 404 Media. Has it really been a year? Here we are a year later, and we are very proud and humbled to report that, because of your support, 404 Media is working. Our business is sustainable, we are happy, and we aren’t going anywhere. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The photorealistic AI-generation revolution is here]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8363</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/photorealistic-ai-generation-revolution-here/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris Welch, a writer for The Verge, on the new “reimagine” feature, that shipped with Google’s recently launched Pixel 9 smartphones. Long story short, “reimagine” allows someone to edit/enhance any photo, anyway they choose: With a simple prompt, you can add things to photos that were never there. And the company’s Gemini AI makes it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignacy Jóźwiak - Interview with Denys Pankratov, organizer of the Crane Operators Union of the Lviv Region — Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignacy-jozwiak-interview-with-denys-pankratov-organizer-of-the-crane-operators-union-of-the-lvi?v=1724876882</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignacy-jozwiak-interview-with-denys-pankratov-organizer-of-the-crane-operators-union-of-the-lvi?v=1724876882"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignacy Jóźwiak
Title: Interview with Denys Pankratov, organizer of the Crane Operators Union of the Lviv Region — Ukraine
Subtitle: Comrades from the Polish trade union OZZ IP, a member of the International Labour Network of Solidarity and Struggles give a voice to trade unionists from Ukraine
Date: March 5, 2022
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from laboursolidarity.org

 We met Denys and members of the Crane Operators Union in spring 2021, during online meetings and exchange of experience between unionised operators in Poland and Ukraine. At the time, protests were underway in both countries over pay rises and improved workplace safety in this sector. Ukrainian operators regularly informed about our actions and expressed solidarity in their social media. We wrote about the s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whitney Kimball - Revenge: Spectrum Workers on Strike Build Their Own ISP]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/whitney-kimball-revenge-spectrum-workers-on-strike-build-their-own-isp?v=1724876594</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/whitney-kimball-revenge-spectrum-workers-on-strike-build-their-own-isp?v=1724876594"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Whitney Kimball
Title: Revenge: Spectrum Workers on Strike Build Their Own ISP
Date: April 14, 2021
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from gizmodo.com

 If, for any number of reasons, you’d like to burn telecoms to the ground and build a new internet service provider on their smoldering remains, good news for you. New York City Spectrum workers, who’ve weathered an anguishing four-year strike, have built their own internet service provider. If the city throws its support behind it, People’s Choice Communications could liberate New Yorkers from cable gangsters once and for all. 
 The city itself is almost constantly fighting Spectrum. With its rise to dominance in New York, Gov. Andrew Cuomo has tried to evict it; attorneys general had to chase it around for allegedly defrauding…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Le Tréhondat - “I, Kostya, Ukrainian high school student, member of the Direct Action union”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/patrick-le-trehondat-i-kostya-ukrainian-high-school-student-member-of-the-direct-action-union?v=1724876246</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/patrick-le-trehondat-i-kostya-ukrainian-high-school-student-member-of-the-direct-action-union?v=1724876246"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Patrick Le Tréhondat
Title: “I, Kostya, Ukrainian high school student, member of the Direct Action union”
Subtitle: Interview by Patrick Le Tréhondat
Date: April 19, 2023
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from laboursolidarity.org

Please introduce yourself to our readers
 My name is Kostya, I am a student of the second grade. [Kostya lives in the Volyn region in northwestern Ukraine.] 
How did you experience the beginning of the war?
 In fact, I sensed that a full-scale invasion would soon occur, but I did not expect it to be so large and destructive. I remember the beginning very well. My mother asked me to buy food, which was practically non-existent, and told me to stay at home. The first week was very scary, nobody knew what was going to happen. We were just hoping for the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volodya Vagner - Builders in Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/volodya-vagner-builders-in-solidarity?v=1724876004</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/volodya-vagner-builders-in-solidarity?v=1724876004"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Volodya Vagner
Title: Builders in Solidarity
Subtitle: A rambunctious Russian-speaking union shakes up Sweden’s labor movement
Date: August 16, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 28th August 2024 from meduza.io

 Sweden is usually outside of The Beet’s purview, but the migrant workers at the heart of its growing shadow economy are not. In the construction sector in particular, many of these migrants hail from the countries that emerged from the Soviet Union’s collapse and they still use Russian as their lingua franca. To fight for their rights and combat exploitation, hundreds of these workers have formed Builders in Solidarity (Solidariska Byggare, in Swedish). Freelance journalist Volodya Vagner reports on this rapidly growing Russian-speaking union shaking up the Swedish labor movement. …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arthur C Clarke predicts some of the future in 1964]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8358</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/arthur-c-clarke-predicts-future-1964/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T20:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Speaking in 1964, the late British author and futurist made numerous predictions, mainly relating to advances in technology, many of which were prescient. Clarke called artificial intelligence (no surprise there, coming from the co-writer of the 1968 movie, 2001: A Space Odyssey). He also foresaw the internet, working from home, and a favourite of mine, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Minute Park, One Million Checkboxes, win Tiny Awards 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8355</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/one-minute-park-one-million-checkboxes-tiny-awards-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One Minute Park by Elliott Cost, has been named winner of the main prize of the Tiny Awards 2024, while One Million Checkboxes by Nolen Royalty, took out the multiplayer player gong. One is your lucky number this year. Held annually since last year, 2023, the Tiny Awards recognise excellence in non-commercial websites designed by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Insights with High-Quality Dashboards at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7186</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/08/unlocking-insights-with-high-quality-dashboards-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T19:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have a lot of dashboards at Spotify. Our Insight teams and analysts from across the company are constantly whipping [...]
The post Unlocking Insights with High-Quality Dashboards at Scale appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aj7 in "A dishwasher can make or break a restaurant (2017)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41382859</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41382859"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a PhD in Physics from Berkeley. Still, in the strictest real estate sense, my best and highest use is as a dishwasher.
I was managing a small optics factory in Livermore. We made laser mirrors to order there — any wavelength, any reflectivity, any angle, any polarization, you name it. I was working my ass off and was unmarried at the time. Thanksgiving came around and I had nowhere to go. But I hooked up with a church in San Jose that had a dinner for poor people and went as a volunteer. After serving the dinner, I wandered back into the dish room. I immediately went over to the sink and kicked out the lady who was pretending to work. I then washed all the dishes and left.
Comes one year later.  I’m in the exact same situation.  I call up that church.  The lady says, “Oh, that’s very nice of you.  But we don’t need any more volunteers, we have enough.”  Oh shit.  What to do.  I found my old replica army parka I had bought in a Cambridge surplus store 20 years earlier. I went as a poor person. I didn’t want to be alone.
The first thing I found out is that poor people are herded, controlled, treated like children. We had to wait outside the church in the mild cold until permitted to enter, in a kind of line. So I sit down.  I will never forget the beatific smiles of the volunteers that served us.  This was performance art, and they were the stars.  Everyone on the supplicant end noticed this, I’m sure. So the meal ends. I walk back into the dish room, survey the situation, once again kick out whoever was pretending to do the dishes, do the dishes, and leave.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aj7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Dad]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/dear-dad/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/dear-dad/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Dad,
Today marks the first anniversary of your passing. Not a day goes... eeh, what’s that you said?
"I know, you don't have to rub it in."
Haha! Your sense of humor is intact. That's still one of the first things people mention when your name comes up: your wonderful sense of humor, and how incredibly kind you were.
You truly treated everyone with the same care and respect.
I still remember the incident in the garden from when I was little. A drug addict had wandered in and fallen asleep there. Mom and all of us kids stood at a safe distance, nervously watching as you helped him. Before staggering off, he turned around with tears of gratitude and asked:
"Are you a priest?"
That’s the kind of person you were. A helping hand and a life saver. A true hero.
As you know, your other son turns 50 today. But this day is not about birth or death. It’s a day of celebration and love. A day of unity, no matter the realm of residence.
Thank you for the long and wonderful time you gave us. Thank you for all the lovely memories that keep your spirit alive. Thank you for all the beautiful things you passed on to us.
I'll end with your last words:
I love you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memories of the Last Few Days]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/memories-of-the-last-few-days/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/memories-of-the-last-few-days/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T18:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re finally back home.
I’ve had a really good few days (since Friday) break. We did a lot in a relatively short amount of time.
So many indicators of a memorable time.
Tan lines in random places to indicate getting that much needed Vitamin D.
Photographs that froze time to be remembered and printed.
(Enamel) Pins added to my collection of places visited.
Stickers. All of the stickers, even though pins have replaced that obsession.
A couple of library cards to show that even during vacation, I still think about all of the books to be read in the future.
Memories of full bellies because we ate a lot of really yummy food.
I’m still processing everything. I’ll be posting all of the photos in the future, whether it be on here, or on the photoblog.
Last day of my very short “vacation” today.
I woke up this morning after having dreamt of work, with tears in my eyes. Is it respectable for me to throw a tantrum to show that I really don’t want to go back to work tomorrow?
Probably not. For today, I’m going to try really hard to just not think about it.
Vacation is not over until it’s over.
28/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing AWS Parallel Computing Service to run HPC workloads at virtually any scale]]></title>
        <id>a5b458691b849a5cf02d12c1cf9dca72099fe15e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-aws-parallel-computing-service-to-run-hpc-workloads-at-virtually-any-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T17:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Parallel Computing Service, run HPC workloads at virtually any scale effortlessly; leverage Slurm and managed clusters to accelerate simulations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is getting ready for post-quantum cryptography]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21662</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/28/security/post-quantum-cryptography-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T16:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Quantum Apocalypse is coming. The advent of quantum computers has raised real questions about the future of data privacy over the internet.  Someday, advances in quantum computing will make it possible to decrypt sensitive data that was encrypted using today’s complex cryptography systems. In the latest episode of the Meta Tech Podcast you’ll meet Sheran [...]
Read More...
The post Meta is getting ready for post-quantum cryptography appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fritz Brupbacher - Bakunin and his Confession]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fritz-brupbacher-bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724856892</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fritz-brupbacher-bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724856892"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T14:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fritz Brupbacher
Title: Bakunin and his Confession
Date: 1929
Notes: Original title: *Bakunin e la sua Confessione
 Fritz Brupbacher 
 Témoins, III, n. 10–11, autunno-inverno 1955–56 
 via: finimondo.org/node/2118 
 Michael Bakunin: Der Satan der Revolte 
 by Fritz Brupbacher First published in 1929
Source: Retrieved on August 28, 2024 from https://www.elephanteditions.net/library/bakunin-and-his-confession?v=1724822630

I
 
 For most contemporaries, Michail Bakunin is unknown. If a certain number of people only know him by name, that is enough to hate and slander him. But there are some who love him with fervour. 
 Once Bakunin was truly a great name. While one would search in vain in the edition of the great encyclopedic dictionary published in 1866 for the name of Karl Marx, tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "Diffusion models are real-time game engines"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41378523</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41378523"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T11:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Apparently there’s more cause, effect, and sequencing in diffusion models than what I expected
To temper this a bit, you may want to pay close attention to the demo videos. The player rarely backtracks, and for good reason - the few times the character does turn around and look back at something a second time, it has changed significantly (the most noticeable I think is the room with the grey wall and triangle sign).
This falls in line with how we'd expect a diffusion model to behave - it's trained on many billions of frames of gameplay, so it's very good at generating a plausible -next- frame of gameplay based on some previous frames. But it doesn't deeply understand logical gameplay constraints, like remembering level geometry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[G.A. Cohen on the output bias]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53064</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/g-a-cohen-on-the-output-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Originally drafted for a conference at Frankfurt in 2018 to mark the 40th anniversary of Karl Marx’s Theory of History: A Defence. I’ve done a bit of editing of my conference script and added a few footnotes etc, but it isn’t necessarily produced to the scholarly standards one might require of a journal article.) In […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polar Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://wait.lol/polar-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://wait.lol/polar-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[:root {
  --image-border: rgba(0,0,0,0.1);
  --image-shadow: rgba(0,0,0,0.1);
}
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  :root {
    --image-border: rgba(255,255,255,0.2);
    --image-shadow: rgba(255,255,255,0.1);
  }
}
.app-image {
  box-shadow: 0 4px 8px var(--image-shadow);
  border: 1px solid var(--image-border);
}
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  .app-image {
    box-shadow: 0 4px 8px var(--image-shadow), 0 0 0 1px var(--image-border);
  }
}
sup { font-size: 0.6em; }
.footnotes { font-size: 0.8em; color: #666; }
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
  .footnotes { color: #aaa; }
}
.image-container {
  display: flex;
  justify-content: space-between;
  gap: 10px;
  margin: 60px 0;
}
.image-container img {
  width: calc(50% - 5px);
  height: auto;
  object-fit: cover;
  cursor: p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The (Electoral) Politics of Age Gaps]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53062</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/28/the-electoral-politics-of-age-gaps/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T09:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harris’ nomination locks in another Boomer presidency. This single generation — those born in the nineteen years between 1946 and 1964 — is guaranteed another presidency. 36 consecutive years, not counting the Biden Interregnum (he’s technically too old). Despite being a Boomer, you may have noticed that she’s the young, exciting candidate. Yes, the generational […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook operates a little differently in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8351</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/facebook-operates-differently-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Swan, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Rampant celebrity cryptocurrency scam ads are as Australian as Tim Tams, koalas or the Great Barrier Reef, according to American Facebook whistleblower Frances Haugen, who says the tech giant’s lack of focus on Australia has let scams run wild on its platform compared with other markets. It’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21618</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/27/security/privacy-aware-infrastructure-purpose-limitation-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we’ve been diligently working to incorporate privacy into different systems of our software stack over the past few years. Today, we’re excited to share some cutting-edge technologies that are part of our Privacy Aware Infrastructure (PAI) initiative. These innovations mark a major milestone in our ongoing commitment to honoring user privacy.  PAI offers [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta enforces purpose limitation via Privacy Aware Infrastructure at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Getting Multiple Library Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-getting-multiple-library-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I read a lot. Probably more than a lot of people, but still not as much as some.
When you read a lot, libraries can become your best friend. Although I would love to buy all of the books, it's just not sustainable. As much as I love having a physical collection, there are times when just borrowing a book over buying it, makes more sense.
I loved visiting libraries growing up. There was one next to my middle school that I would go to after school. I remember getting lost in the pages of a book, tucked in a corner between shelves.
I went to libraries less and less as an adult. Then e-books happened. I still read a lot, and found myself buying most of the e-books I read. At some point, I got a Kindle Unlimited subscription. Despite its name, the book selection really wasn't unlimited, especially if you read outside of the genre of their book offerings.
Enter Libby.
If you haven't heard of it, Libby is a game changer for anyone who loves reading. All you need is a library card, and suddenly you have access to the library's entire e-book collection.
I started a Libby account with just one local library card. Simple enough, right? But then I had an epiphany: as long as I'm a California resident, I can get different library cards across the state. Now that is the real game changer. More library cards = even more selection of books.
Now, every time I visit a new California town, I try to stop by their library to get a card. Yesterday, we visited a new town for my birthday. We passed a library while roaming around town. Guess what I did?
I got myself yet another library card.
Thinking about collecting all of the cards up and down California at this point. A librarian Thanos, if you will.
27/31 - Blaugust
💬 Community Echoes
Multiple Library Cards and Libby by Noisy Deadlines
Tab Cleaning by axxuy
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Irrationality and mass paranoia invade our societies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Irrationality-and-mass-paranoia-invade-our-societies"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T08:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“But why are they attacking us? What have we done to them to make them hate us and bomb us like this?”. These are surprising and thought-provoking questions from ordinary Russians living in the Kursk region, asked by reporters sent to cover the advance of Ukrainian troops into this Russian territory. And they are all the more surprising given that these Russians do not live in Vladivostok or Siberia, but practically straddle the Russian border with Ukraine, just a few dozen kilometers from (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Palestine, 
Antifascism, 
Ukraine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>