<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-06T12:42:47.177Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-06T12:42:47.177Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;Wartime Lithuania&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/wartime-lithuania</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/wartime-lithuania"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T12:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jingoism and unrest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272837</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bearish daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Virginia, Data Centers Collide with Zero-Carbon Goals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272844</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/in-virginia-data-centers-collide-with-zero-carbon-goals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With electric demand from data centers skyrocketing, the state considers how to meet its goal of decarbonizing the grid.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Georgia Appeals Court Halts Trump Election Interference Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272842</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/georgia-appeals-court-halts-trump-election-interference-case.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is much rending of hair over Trump winning delay in his election interference case that will push any trial past the election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting vulnerable communities for 10 years with Project Galileo]]></title>
        <id>66609308e955c4000a8b49da</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/galileo10anniversaryradardashboard"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In celebration of Project Galileo's 10th anniversary, we want to give you a snapshot of what organizations that work in the public interest experience on an everyday basis when it comes to keeping their websites online]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mount Sinai Eye & Ear Nurses Rally for Layoff Plan as Beth Israel Shutdown Looms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272828</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/mount-sinai-eye-ear-nurses-rally-for-layoff-plan-as-beth-israel-shutdown-looms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:31:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City's Mount Sinai is trying to shutter acquired Beth Israel and its own respected eye and ear facility despite state opposition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by openrisk in "Microsoft AI spying scandal: time to rethink privacy standards"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40593986</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40593986"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to understand consumer privacy behaviors outside the prevalent social contract that the vast majority of people operate under is bound to missinterpret what is happening and why.
We live in a regulated "supermarket" economy. What surfaces on a screen is entirely analogous to what surfaces on a shelf: People check the price and make their choices based on taste, budget etc. They are not idiots, they operate under a simplifying assumption that makes life in a complex world possible.
The implicit assumption central to this way of organising the economy is that anything legally on sale is "safe". That it has been checked and approved by experts that know what they are doing and have the consumer interest as top priority.
People will not rush back home to their chemistry labs to check what is in their purchased food, whether it corresponds to the label (assuming that such a label even exists) and what might be the short or long term health effects. They dont have the knowledge, resources and time to do that for all the stuff they get exposed to.
What has drifted in the digital economy is not consumer standards, it is regulatory standards. Surfacing digital products with questionable short and long term implications for individuals and society has become a lucrative business, has captured its regulatory environment and will keep exploiting opportunities and blind spots until there is pushback.
Ultimately regulators only derive legitimacy from serving their constituencies, but that feedback loop can be very slow and it gets tangled with myriad other unrelated political issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>openrisk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of an Era: Pro-Palestine Language Exposes Israel, Zionism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324769</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/end-of-an-era-pro-palestine-language-exposes-israel-zionism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If one were to argue that a top Spanish government official would someday declare that “from the river to the sea, Palestine would be free”, the suggestion itself would have seemed ludicrous. But this is precisely how Yolanda Diaz, Spain’s Deputy Prime Minister, concluded a statement on May 23, a few days before Spain officially  More
The post End of an Era: Pro-Palestine Language Exposes Israel, Zionism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Drums of War are Banging in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324701</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/the-drums-of-war-are-banging-in-europe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These weeks see the end of the term for an ineffectual European legislature which served during the worst pandemic of this century, during Vladimir Putin’s invasion of Ukraine, and with it, the outbreak of a war on European soil that evokes the worst memories of the world wars of the last century. And as we witness the televised genocide of the Palestinian people, it appears that the international system of liberal governance seems to be collapsing like a house of cards. More
The post The Drums of War are Banging in Europe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miguel Urban, Eric Toussaint and Paul Murphy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Uranium Ban Reopens Threat of Uranium Mining Escalation in US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324509</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/russian-uranium-ban-reopens-threat-of-uranium-mining-escalation-in-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inkai Uranium Mine, Kazakhstan. Kazakhstan uranium comprises 25% of all US uranium imports. (Photo: NAC Kazatomprom JSC/Wikimedia Commons) When Russia first invaded Ukraine on February 24, 2022, no one knew how long the fighting would continue and what the outcome might be. Kyiv was expected to fall immediately. It didn’t. More than two years on,  More
The post Russian Uranium Ban Reopens Threat of Uranium Mining Escalation in US appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Pentz Gunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hispanics in Pennsylvania?  Their Defections Could Doom Biden in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324753</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/hispanics-in-pennsylvania-their-defections-could-doom-biden-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where is the Hispanic vote most likely to affect the outcome of this year’s bitterly-contested race for the White House?   If you ask most analysts, one-time battleground state Florida and the swing states in the US Southwest, especially Arizona and Nevada, both of which went for Biden in 2020, would likely be cited. According to Real  More
The post Hispanics in Pennsylvania?  Their Defections Could Doom Biden in 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The GOP’s Stalinesque Plan 2025 to Shape the Future of U.S. Food and Agriculture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324755</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/the-gops-stalinesque-plan-2025-to-shape-the-future-of-u-s-food-and-agriculture/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since I started organic farming more than 40 years ago, I have heard the same claims about the wonders of farmers in the United States: They are unparalleled in their productivity, feed the world with safe food, and are innovative and efficient. From the glowing accounts from industry leaders, the American Farm Bureau Federation, the secretaries of  More
The post The GOP’s Stalinesque Plan 2025 to Shape the Future of U.S. Food and Agriculture appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Henderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destroying the Natural World in Order to Save it?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324717</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/destroying-the-natural-world-in-order-to-save-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue Headlines in the Los Angeles Times infuriated me. One was about the planned destruction of thousands of Joshua Trees in “private” land in the Mojave Desert in order to produce electricity for a relatively rich community that preferred ceramic roofs to rooftop solar panels. This obscene decision will wipe out more than the treasure  More
The post Destroying the Natural World in Order to Save it? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radicals on the Run]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/radicals-on-the-run/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joel Whitney’s Flights: Radicals on the Run (O/R Books) is a wonderfully written text about a truly remarkable if also painfully elusive subject: artists and others on the run from Cold War capitalism. The evidence of the pursuit, even the meaning of the pursuit, has of course been hidden as carefully as possible. The first  More
The post Radicals on the Run appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Buhle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need to Reclaim the Muddy Waters of the Louisiana Gulf Coast From the Climate Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324496</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/we-need-to-reclaim-the-muddy-waters-of-the-louisiana-gulf-coast-from-the-climate-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:45:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up in the shadow of the Mississippi River, whose mythology pressed upon my imagination. Its culture inspired iconic works and political movements, while its agency resisted efforts to corral it. When researching my book, Muddy Thinking in the Mississippi River Delta: A Call for Reclamation (University of California Press, 2024), I found myself wrestling with  More
The post We Need to Reclaim the Muddy Waters of the Louisiana Gulf Coast From the Climate Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ned Randolph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Activists Must do More]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324715</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/climate-activists-must-do-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An environmental activist was arrested Saturday after she stuck a protest sign or sticker to a Monet painting at the famed Orsay Museum in Paris. The activist, representing the group Riposte Alimentaire, targeted Claude Monet’s Coquelicots or “Poppy Field” painting, affixing a sticker to the artwork and which depicted an apocalyptic, futuristic vision of the  More
The post Climate Activists Must do More appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chloe Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shattered Theory: the War on Terror and Western Impunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/shattered-theory-the-war-on-terror-and-western-impunity/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ICC request for arrest warrants against Netanyahu and others is only the beginning. Around the world evidence is being gathered and cases are being prepared, including against British, American and EU politicians and officials for complicity in genocide and other crimes against humanity.  This week the ICC received a request from jurists and human  More
The post Shattered Theory: the War on Terror and Western Impunity appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, the Savings Rate Is Not Near a Record Low]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324711</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/06/no-the-savings-rate-is-not-near-a-record-low/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been popular for people commenting on the state of the economy to say that consumers have to pull back on consumption because they have exhausted their savings. A big part of this story is that the saving rate is supposedly near a record low. The reported saving rate, at 3.8 percent in the  More
The post No, the Savings Rate Is Not Near a Record Low appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by roenxi in "U.S. clears way for antitrust inquiries of Nvidia, Microsoft and OpenAI"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40593519</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40593519"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T04:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia solved a hard problem and their competitors all failed. I spent years with an AMD card growing progressively more annoyed at their self-inflicted apparent inability to multiply matrices on demand. Nvidia had nothing to do with their failure, unless they had some sort of high-level mole in AMD's driver teams.
Hitting the only successful company in a difficult field with legal assaults is not the obvious path to success. Nvidia has nothing close to a monopoly; there is no moat and they operate in a commodity space that will behave like a normal competitive market. It just happens that their competitors were wall-to-wall complacent about how quickly the hardware world can change and they stupidly thought graphics cards were for displaying graphics. It turns out graphics cards are for building AI and crypto markets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>roenxi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Years of Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/06/10-years-of-kubernetes/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/06/10-years-of-kubernetes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten (10) years ago, on June 6th, 2014, the
first commit
of Kubernetes was pushed to GitHub. That first commit with 250 files and 47,501 lines of go, bash
and markdown kicked off the project we have today. Who could have predicted that 10 years later,
Kubernetes would grow to become one of the largest Open Source projects to date with over
88,000 contributors from
more than 8,000 companies, across
44 countries.
This milestone isn't just for Kubernetes but for the Cloud Native ecosystem that blossomed from
it. There are close to 200 projects
within the CNCF itself, with contributions from
240,000+ individual contributors and
thousands more in the greater ecosystem. Kubernetes would not be where it is today without them, the
7M+ Developers,
and the even larger user community that have all hel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four-day workweeks are nigh, followed by zero-day workweeks]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7769</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/four-day-workweeks-nigh-zero-day-workweeks/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There has been talk of the four-day workweek for as long as I can remember. We were told about it when I started school. Yet it’s to fully, properly, officially, arrive. The work week is still, for the most part, in many places, five days: Monday to Friday. We don’t live in an age where […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cletus in "Boeing Starliner launches first crewed mission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40589501</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40589501"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:37:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SLS is a jobs program. It's not economically viable at over $1 billion per launch.
As for Blue Origin and New Glenn, this is an object lesson that simply throwing money at the problem doesn't necessarily solve it. Did you know Blue Origin was founded ~18 months before SpaceX?
For the longest time (up until ~9 months ago), Bezos had the former Honeywell CEO in charge of Blue Origin, which to me was such an odd choice. You see, this guy seems to embody everything wrong with corporate America: he was completely focused on not failing rather than succeeding. So there were constant delays with New Glenn and the BE-4 engine, which is years behind schedule. You can't fail if you don't launch.
And the new CEO (David Limp) used to be in charge of Kindles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cletus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ukoki in "Employees who stay in companies longer than two years get paid 50% less (2014)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40589260</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40589260"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employers don't reward long-term employees because they don't need to. Even though everyone knows you make more by job-hopping, companies are following a rational strategy because too few people "walk the walk" despite wanting more salary. Arguably unethical, but rational.
At the cost of losing a minority of job-hoppers they retain the cheap majority that:
    - finds job interviews exhausting, or is anxious about being rejected

    - dislikes conflict or negotiation

    - has good relationships with colleagues they don't want to lose

    - has a comfortable commute or WFH arrangement they don't want to change

    - is proud of becoming an expert / go-to-person in some part of the business and doesn't want to lose that source of social capital

    - is proud of product or service they have made a big contribution to and wants to "see it through to the end"

    - believes leaving would place an unfair burden on other team-members or would be disloyal to a manager they consider a friend

    - (US only) cannot risk losing healthcare

It's the same reason why your phone/insurance/whatever provider puts up the prices year-after-year: although some people leave, enough people simply put up with it that they make more money this way. "Do nothing" is an easy choice and companies are banking on enough people making that choice.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ukoki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[en] rabbit r1 it's a SCAM]]></title>
        <id>https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/en-rabbit-r1-its-a-scam/</id>
        <link href="https://paulogpd.bearblog.dev/en-rabbit-r1-its-a-scam/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:55:10.692Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not new that the promise of artificial intelligence capable of helping us and solving a series of problems we don't have has emerged. However, it is only from 2022 onwards that large models (LLM, LAM, and others) are gaining traction and attention worldwide. It started with OpenAI and ChatGPT, followed by Humana's AI Pin and Rabbit R1 from Rabbit Inc. Neither delivered on their promises, but the Rabbit R1 has an extra touch.
While Humane's brooch is just an overpriced product that doesn’t work properly, the Rabbit R1 is a mishmash of poorly executed features and a good dose of scams, especially coming from a company previously involved with NFTs and "pay-to-win" games (which use NFTs). Most of the instructions are hardcoded into the device, meaning that most actions are predefined acc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nothing nonnegotiable]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/nothing-nonnegotiable/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/nothing-nonnegotiable/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vegetating aside, the last few days before big moves usually also brings lots of appointments. This week I get my teeth cleaned and eyes checked before I leave, scheduling follow-ups in a year and making plans to be back for them.
Going to these appointments is one of the few activities I actually prefer my parents come along. Not because I enjoy their company (it's hit or miss), but because I'm no good at doing the things they usually do. (And by 'they' I mean my mom.)
Today before I leave for the optometrist Mom tells me I shouldn't agree to pay more than $110 for my visit, the same amount we paid last year. Upon arrival, the receptionist informs me that the fee for checkups is $250 now. $250? I thought it was supposed to be $110, I say. She shows me a packet with the price printed in bo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mbonnet in "Diamond industry 'in trouble' as lab-grown gemstones tank prices further"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40588626</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40588626"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good. The diamond industry has destroyed multiple countries, one of which I lived in (Sierra Leone). Screw em.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mbonnet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CobrastanJorji in "Win for copyright user rights in Canada: Digital locks do not trump fair dealing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40588400</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40588400"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've always been confused by how these decisions go. Everybody agrees that the user has the right to make a copy, so when the company puts a 
"digital lock" on it, the fight is whether the user has a right to break the lock. But if I have a right to go through my door, and somebody has put a padlock on the door to keep me out, the right question shouldn't be whether I'm allowed to pick the lock, it should be why the padlock is legal.
If customers may legally make a copy of the e-book you sell to them, it should be on you the merchant to ensure customers are able to do so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CobrastanJorji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272813</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T18:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler:  Politics, syndemics, Biden's cognitive decline, Alvin Bragg's helpers, "mild," more Boeing whistleblowers ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our brand-new cohort of AWS Heroes has arrived – June 2024]]></title>
        <id>064422b90ddb5c6a2f9e1679e220258b147e6e10</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/our-brand-new-cohort-of-aws-heroes-has-arrived-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vibrant AWS community is made up of millions of builders worldwide. Within this global audience, there are technical enthusiasts who are going above and beyond to solve problems and generously share their learnings and best practices to empower others—the AWS Heroes. These inspirational leaders make significant contributions, and the AWS Heroes program is our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_90</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_90"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code May 2024
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fiftyfifty in "Boeing Starliner launches first crewed mission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40587170</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40587170"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T16:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's crazy the US could soon have up to 5 different spacecraft/launch systems that can take humans to orbit with 2 more in development:
Falcon 9 + Dragon, SLS + Orion, Atlas V (Vulcan Centaur) + Starliner
Close to orbital payload launch, likely human rated in the future: Vulcan Centaur + Dream Chaser, Superheavy + Starship
Under development: New Glenn + Space Vehicle (?), Neutron]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fiftyfifty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by talldayo in "Vulkan1.3 on the M1 in one month"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40586859</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40586859"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There will be a small bit of irony if the gaming experience on Asahi ends up easier and more straightforward than MacOS.
Really just drives home how big of a mistake it was ignoring Vulkan for the past decade on Apple's behalf, but lord knows they won't admit that until it's too late.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>talldayo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genomics workflows, Part 7: analyze public RNA sequencing data using AWS HealthOmics]]></title>
        <id>68a73badc4128fca45f9a02fca4a40354c43ba89</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/genomics-workflows-part-7-analyze-public-rna-sequencing-data-using-aws-healthomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genomics workflows process petabyte-scale datasets on large pools of compute resources. In this blog post, we discuss how life science organizations can use Amazon Web Services (AWS) to run transcriptomic sequencing data analysis using public datasets. This allows users to quickly test research hypotheses against larger datasets in support of clinical diagnostics. We use AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rostislav Markov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Threatening to Take on Hezbollah After Cross-Border Attacks Produce Intense Wildfires]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272810</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/israel-threatening-to-take-on-hezbollah-after-cross-border-attacks-produce-intense-wildfires.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T14:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel desperately wants a hotter conflict with Hezbollah even though Israel is likely to lose bigly. What next?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thinkmassive in "Nintendo leak:employee accessing private YouTube videos"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40584480</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40584480"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title is difficult to decipher, here’s what it’s about:
> A new report on old privacy incidents [2017] suggests that at least one Nintendo leak came from a Google employee showing off private YouTube videos to a friend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thinkmassive</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[European Union elections 2024: securing democratic processes in light of new threats]]></title>
        <id>6658791a7d1754000b5c0e7a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/eu-elections-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between 6 and 9 June 2024, hundreds of millions of EU citizens will be voting to elect their members of the European Parliament (MEPs). All EU member states have different election processes, institutions and methods, and the security risks are significant]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Petra Arts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[another successful molt!]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/another-successful-molt/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/another-successful-molt/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excited to see this little guy emerge bigger with a new, colorful shell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272756</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T10:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our frolicking daily links: Amazon tribe becomes porn junkies, Modi setback, Philippines shreds China fishing nets, WSJ shreds Biden cognition, Israel-Lebanon war imminent? Turkiye to join BRICS? landmark free speech win for MDs, Meta chases Gen Z, moar AI hype]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chronic Crisis of American Democracy: A Review]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272794</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/the-chronic-crisis-of-american-democracy-a-review.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T10:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cogent discussion of the complex, accelerating legitimacy crisis masked by bleats about "defending our democracy"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Becomes Latest State To Try Capping Health Care Spending]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272798</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/california-becomes-latest-state-to-try-capping-health-care-spending.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T10:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[California joins the list of states trying to choke health industry profiteering via spending limits. Can it work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Battles Brew Over Radioactive Wastewater Discharge from Shuttered Nuclear Plants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=272789</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/battles-brew-over-radioactive-wastewater-discharge-from-shuttered-nuclear-plants.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T09:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York State is trying to bar radioactive wastewater releases from out-of-service nuclear plants, as proponents insist they are safe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank's accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-s-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-s-accounts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI FR]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Enemy is Us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324595</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/the-enemy-is-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a sense, war is human history. It’s been the rare moment when we’ve proven capable of not making war on ourselves somewhere on this planet. It seems to be in the bloodstream, so to speak (as in the endless streams, even rivers, of blood eternally being spilled). And in a sense, war, the urge to take someone else’s territory or simply kill endless numbers of… well, us… has certainly been in that very same bloodstream at least since the first great literary work of the Western world, The Iliad, was written. In some sense, you could say that, 3,000 years later, we’re all still in Troy. More
The post The Enemy is Us appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Engelhardt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Wealth Inequality Virus is Getting Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324601</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/the-u-s-wealth-inequality-virus-is-getting-worse/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared to the recent past, Covid-19 is not killing as many people. On the other hand, the U.S. wealth inequality virus continues to become more virulent as reflected in widespread poverty, food insecurity, homelessness, and other social ills. Over time, the wealth inequality virus, like Covid-19, has had its ups and downs in the damage it causes. Figures on the distribution of family wealth provided by the Federal Reserve Board show that when the wealth inequality virus recovers after a downturn, it generally produces new levels of inequality. More
The post The U.S. Wealth Inequality Virus is Getting Worse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Baum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Russians Still Support the War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324656</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/why-russians-still-support-the-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian President Vladimir Putin arrived in Beijing for a two-day trip on May 15, 2024, and was greeted with a red-carpet welcome by Chinese President Xi Jinping. The two leaders pledged a “new era” for the Russia-China relationship, building on their “no limits partnership” struck just before Russia’s 2022 invasion of Ukraine. As Putin’s first  More
The post Why Russians Still Support the War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Social Security Crisis Myth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324654</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/the-social-security-crisis-myth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last weekend, the Washington Post ran an editorial that bothered me more than most Washington Post editorials. The headline said it all, “Telling Americans the economy is good won’t work.” I knew I had heard this before but couldn’t remember where. Then it hit me, the Social Security debate of the 1990s. The 1990s were the heyday of the  More
The post The Social Security Crisis Myth  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Humble Carrot’s Colorful History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324658</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/the-humble-carrots-colorful-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have the Arabs to thank for introducing carrots (Daucos carota) to Western Europe. Two distinct subspecies led to the domesticated carrot. The subspecies D. carota sativus, native to Turkey, was grown by the Arabs and consumed by their invading armies, both animal and human. At the end of the 10th century, carrots were mentioned in a  More
The post The Humble Carrot’s Colorful History appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Alexander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Dobbs, Obergefell?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324454</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/after-dobbs-obergefell/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 18, 2003, the Massachusetts Supreme Judicial Court (SJC) ruled that gay and lesbian couples could no longer be excluded from obtaining a civil marriage. Six months later, on May 17, 2004, same-sex marriage was legally recognized in Massachusetts. Nearly a decade later, on June 26, 2015, the U.S. Supreme Court ruled, in Obergefell v. Hodges, that the  More
The post After Dobbs, Obergefell? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imprisoned Presidential Candidate(s)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324466</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/imprisoned-presidential-candidates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that a New York jury convicted Donald Trump of 34 counts of falsifying business records in order to conceal hush money paid to a porn star and to evade campaign financial regulations, speculation has begun about his sentencing. Even though his outrageous behavior towards and slander of the district attorney, the judge, the witnesses,  More
The post Imprisoned Presidential Candidate(s) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fran Shor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Air Today, Gone Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324477</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/letter-from-london-air-today-gone-tomorrow/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I picked up a paperback copy of Vladimir Nabokov’s Laughter in the Dark in a charity shop last week. I’ve been reading it ever since. I didn’t know that the Russian writer — when a penniless thirty-one-year-old living in Berlin — first called it Camera Obscura. Nor that he retranslated it himself retitling it in  More
The post Letter from London: Air Today, Gone Tomorrow appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yashap in "You'll regret using natural keys"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581759</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581759"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is bad advice.
Say I have a user table, and the email is unique and required, and we don’t let users update their email, and we don’t have user deletion. If I’m going natural PK, I make email the primary key.
But … then we add the ability for users to update their email. But it should still be the same user! This is trivial if we have a surrogate primary key, a nightmare if we made email the natural primary key.
Or building on that example, maybe at first we always require an email from our users. But later we also allow phone auth, and you just need an email OR a phone number. And later we add user name auth, SSO, etc. Again, all good with surrogate primary keys, a nightmare with natural primary keys.
There are countless examples like this. You brought up cars, same thing with licence plates, for example. Or even Social Security Numbers/Social Insurance Numbers - in Canada SINs are generally permanent, but temporary residents can have their SIN change if they later become permanent residents, but they’re still the same person.
You want your entities to have stable identity, even if things you at one time thought gave them identity change. Surrogate primary keys do that, natural primary keys do not. Don’t use natural primary keys, use surrogate primary keys with unique constraints/indexes.
I challenge you to come up with a single plausible example where you’re screwing yourself by choosing surrogate PK + unique constraints/indexes. Meanwhile there are endless examples where you’re screwing yourself by choosing natural PK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yashap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bibi Fought the Law, Will the Law Win?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324456</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/bibi-fought-the-law-will-the-law-win/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:45:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Benjamin Netanyahu’s face may soon be on Wanted posters around the world. In Israel, the prime minister has been charged with various counts of corruption. But now that the International Criminal Court has requested a warrant for Netanyahu’s arrest on war crimes, he may become a global outlaw as well. It’s not a done deal.  More
The post Bibi Fought the Law, Will the Law Win? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel, Russia, and International Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324611</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/05/israel-russia-and-international-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T05:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[International law―the recognized rules of behavior among nations based on customary practices and treaties, among them the United Nations Charter and the Universal Declaration of Human Rights―has been agreed upon by large and small nations alike. To implement this law, the nations of the world have established a UN Security Council (to maintain international peace  More
The post Israel, Russia, and International Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Wittner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "You'll regret using natural keys"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581206</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581206"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T03:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another massive annoyance with natural keys - privacy. If your table's primary key contains personal information, that PII now infects every other table that holds a foreign key to that table.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crabmusket in "You'll regret using natural keys"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581197</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40581197"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T03:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The surrogate key uniquely identifies a row in your database, which is an entity just as real and significant as the car or the employee or what-have-you. Don't confuse the two!
I agree with you that having a surrogate key isn't going to save you from the reasons why natural keys can be difficult. The complexity has to go somewhere. But not having a unique identifier for each row is going to make things extra difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crabmusket</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mullen in "Things the guys who stole my phone have texted me to try to get me to unlock it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40580076</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40580076"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T23:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If someone in China starts harassing you or threatening you, just start sending messages that the two of you are conspiring to overthrow the Chinese government and the messages will stop real quick.
These Chinese mafia types talk tough until you start sending anti-Chinese government copy-pasta to them and they shut up real quick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mullen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bnchrch in "Things the guys who stole my phone have texted me to try to get me to unlock it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40578911</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40578911"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T21:03:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honestly. This is a pretty good advertisement for Apple.
I appreciate the effort that they've put into making my device less valuable to thiefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bnchrch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Xylakant in "Things the guys who stole my phone have texted me to try to get me to unlock it"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40578886</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40578886"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The police state is interested in maintaining the power structure in the police state. As long as petty or even organized crime does not upset the balance of power, the authorities couldn’t care less - crime against Americans is no danger to them. Just as the  Russian government has no interest in cracking down on its blackhat population, as long as they target non-Russian orgs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Xylakant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An extremely simple way to detect potential late bloomers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7764</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/extremely-simple-way-detect-potential-late-bloomers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T21:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Colonel Sanders founded KFC at age sixty-two. Anna Mary Robertson Moses AKA Grandma Moses, started painting when she was seventy-six, and had an illustrious career spanning twenty-five years. American actor Kathryn Joosten began her Hollywood career aged fifty-six. These are just a few examples of people who are considered to be late bloomers. Those who […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hackmiester in "Hacking millions of modems and investigating who hacked my modem"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40576355</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40576355"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T16:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just the craziest, wrongest ones]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hackmiester</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[💻 A New Digital Home, Etc.]]></title>
        <id>https://krueger.ink/a-new-digital-home-etc/</id>
        <link href="https://krueger.ink/a-new-digital-home-etc/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T16:33:23.439Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My blog was housed on Scribbles since February, but I recently started playing around with Bear, another Indie Web blogging platform. it offers light customization and uses Markdown — two things I’d really been missing on Scribbles.
Well, here I am — permanently blogging on Bear now. I’ve also changed the name of my blog and have a new domain. It feels a bit like starting over, but not quite because I brought some old posts over with me. I’m certainly looking forward to this new adventure, though.
My old blog is still online and still available to visit, if anyone has an inkling to do so. I’m also not leaving the Scribbles platform entirely. My Camp Snap Chronicle photo blog will still remain there. And since that camera arrived yesterday, I’m hoping to maybe have some photos to post by the weekend. We’ll see. It’s been a busy few days for me.
Anyway, feel free to add this new blog to your RSS reader of choice. I apologize for changing things, but I did what I felt was best for me. Stay tuned for all of the weird rambles you’ve come to expect, haha.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Post-real economics — a severe case of mathiness]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45403</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/04/post-real-economics-a-severe-case-of-mathiness/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T16:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll In practice, what math does is let macro-economists locate the FWUTVs [facts with unknown truth values] farther away from the discussion of identification … Relying on a micro-foundation lets an author say, “Assume A, assume B, … blah blah blah … And so we have proven that P is true. Then the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I have nothing to write]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/nothing-to-write/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/nothing-to-write/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is one of those days when I feel I have nothing to write.
Then I started thinking...
What is it that says you have to have something to write to start writing? It's just an idea, an idea of how things work.
You have something to write.
You write it.
It doesn't have to be like that. It's perfectly possible to just start writing without having anything to write about. Or, as one writer put it, sit down at the typewriter and just bleed.
There are so many things in life that we have preconceptions about...
It should be sunny on Midsummer day (it's a Swedish thing), everyone should be happy on Christmas Eve and the slice of cheese should be on top of the hamburger (ok, bad example – it should always be on top).
When life doesn't go the way it's “supposed to” (read: the way we demand) - which of course is often the case - the whole world is turned upside down.
What if we slow down a bit when it comes to how things "should be”? What if we face the day with a little "let's see what this day (or blank sheet of paper) brings"?
It's worth trying.
all posts · rss feed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pain]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/pain/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/pain/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short story I wrote a while back :
It was warm and cozy in his room.The walls, adorned with peeling wallpaper, seemed to hug him in a comforting embrace. He was safe here, cocooned in this familiar space. As long as he didn’t open the door, he could pretend. Pretend that everything was okay, that the world outside was just as gentle and forgiving as his secluded corner.
Sometimes, he heard loud, jarring knocks on the door. Bang Bang. Each knock sounded like a thunderclap, threatening to shatter his illusion. The door, scarred from previous assaults, was almost giving way. He remembered being afraid, trembling as he went to the door and pressing his body weight against it to lend it support. After all, it was his sole protector from the outside world, a barrier between him and the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Creaghe - The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-the-argentine-republic-and-english-radical-reformers?v=1717513259</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-the-argentine-republic-and-english-radical-reformers?v=1717513259"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Creaghe
Title: The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers
Date: January 1890
Notes: Original Title: 'The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers' in Commonweal Bibliography Creaghe, John, 'The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers' in Commonweal, Vol. 6, No. 208, (London, 1890), pg. 2-3 Creaghe, John, 'The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers' in Commonweal, Vol. 6, No. 209, (London, 1890), pg. 10 Creaghe, John, 'The Argentine Republic and English Radical Reformers' in Commonweal, Vol. 6, No. 210, (London, 1890), pg. 20-21
Source: Retreived on 4 June 2024 from https://www.marxists.org/history/international/social-democracy/commonweal/1890/index.htm

The writer of the following pages, having lived for many years in the Argentine Republi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by velcrovan in "Encryption at Rest: Whose Threat Model Is It Anyway?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40574412</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40574412"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T13:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the article: "Disk Encryption is important for disk disposal and mitigating hardware theft, not preventing data leakage to online attackers."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>velcrovan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by HelloNurse in "Use context-free grammars instead of parser combinators and PEG"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40572510</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40572510"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T09:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing is an application domain where I'd expect more hard logic and less soft feelings than in this article.
"I feel that CFGs more naturally represent how we think" but
"All this doesn't apply to situations where you trying to parse some language, whose specification explicitly says that the language is based on PEG formalism"
A terrible context free grammar (with left and right recursion, not a small feat) is presented.
"I blindly converted grammar above to Haskell code"
"I accidentally discovered my grammar was ambiguous!"
"All this gave me psychological trauma (figuratively speaking). I will never use Parsec (and PEG parsers) anymore."
Denial that an ambiguous grammar is a defect, denial that the ambiguity has to be resolved, refusal to use parser combinators to resolve the ambiguity in the correct way.
It's also strange to see someone react to a modest, non-shameful failure (guess what, parsing is difficult is language design is even more difficult) that should be a nice learning opportunity (elegant context free grammars are usually insufficient in practical usage) with anger and radicalization far beyond an acceptable level of blaming the tools.
The other post in the blog, however, follows a similar general pattern: never use a popular technique (de Bruijn indices rather than parser combinators), because they advocate another technique (expressing lambda calculus terms with randomly generated globally unique identifiers for all bound variables rather than pure context free grammars) because that's what they like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>HelloNurse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by veddox in "The Moral Economy of the Shire"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40572276</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40572276"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T09:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Because this opinion has surfaced a number of times here: Yes, Tolkien did care deeply about the realism of his world. And because he spent his whole life studying pre-modern societies, the societies he creates in Middle Earth do function very realistically. I think there are two reason why many readers miss this:
(1) Much of Tolkien's world-building is implicit rather than explicit. He doesn't talk about Aragorn's tax policy because he doesn't need to; Aragorn is recognisably a feudal king and there is a standard way taxes are done a feudal system (i.e. the vassals take care of gathering them). Tolkien has a deep understanding of how such societies function, but much of this comes out indirectly in the story, through the way the characters behave and what they can and cannot do.
(2) Pre-modern societies are so deeply different from modern ones (economically, culturally, and socially) that I think many readers stumble across things they find unexpected and dismiss it as "unrealistic fantasy", without understanding that in such a context, this is exactly how one would expect the world to work. For example, the deep devotion and self-sacrificial service Sam shows to Frodo is often discussed in terms of friendship (and it is a great friendship), but one cannot fully understand it unless one also understands it as a (very positive) master-servant relationship.
If you want a better understanding of the deeper realism of LotR, I cannot recommend Bret Devereaux' blog highly enough. He is an ancient military historian and has written extensive (but entertaining!) analyses of both LotR and GoT. See here for two samples: https://acoup.blog/2020/05/22/collections-the-battle-of-helm..., https://acoup.blog/2019/05/28/new-acquisitions-not-how-it-wa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veddox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[invisible struggles]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/invisible-struggles/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/invisible-struggles/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:52:17.097Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cape Cod Morning by Edward Hopper, 1950, via the Smithsonian.
What triggers this feeling of being overwhelmed for no reason? From an outside perspective, there is no objective reason things should feel so heavy. My circumstances have not markedly changed. There are no notable stressors present. Yet, internally, everything seems foggy, fuzzy, and oppressive. On these overwhelming days, I want so badly to grasp why I feel this way or make sense of some cause, yet no cause or reason can be found. The only reasonable response is rebellion through persistent, passionate, and lucid living despite it all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SilverBirch in "I am sick of LeetCode-style interviews"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571575</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571575"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:20:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I understand the frustration, but at the end of the day I think they do serve a purpose. They're not great at that purpose, but they're good enough and they generally produce false negatives (smart people fail) rather than false positives (you hire an idiot). And this makes sense, because a false negative is low cost (maybe you spend 50% longer interviewing candidates) but a false positive is high cost (you hire an idiot and have to spend months establishing that, firing them and starting the hiring process again).
The side effect of this though, is that it's an extremely painful process for the applicant. Even if you're a great software engineer, you're going to freeze up, miss something, have a bad day, and fail a few interviews. Now for most software engineers failure is an unusual and harrowing experience, so they react really badly to it. Especially ina 
 scenario where it's difficult to blame anyone but yourself. But just don't! It's fine! just move on, there's plenty of jobs and the interview process is a blunt tool, not a final evaluation of your worth in life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SilverBirch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dinobones in "I am sick of LeetCode-style interviews"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571515</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571515"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:11:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leetcode style interviews probably serve two functions:
1) A way to suppress wages and job mobility for SWE. Who wants to switch jobs when it means studying for a month or two? Also, if you get unlucky and some try hard drops an atomic LC hard bomb on you now you have an entire company you can no longer apply to for a year.
2) A way to mask bias in the process while claiming that it’s a fair process because everyone has a clear/similar objective.
Meet someone who went to your Alma mater? Same gender? Same race? Give them the same question as everyone else, but hint them through it, ignore some syntax errors, and give them a strong hire for “communication” when they didn’t even implement the optimal approach…
Or is it someone you don’t like for X reason? Drop a leetcode hard on them and send them packing and just remain silent the entire interview.
To the company this is acceptable noise, but to the individual, this is costing us 100s of thousands of dollars, because there’s only a handful of companies that pay well and they all have the same interview process. Failing 3 interviews probably means you’re now out $200-300k of additional compensation from the top paying companies.
I’ve interviewed for and at FAANGs. I can’t believe the low bar of people that we’ve hired, while simultaneously seeing insane ridiculous quad tree/number theory type questions that have caused other great engineers to miss out on good opportunities.
Someone will reply to me “if you know how to problem solve you will always pass.” Ok, come interview with me and I will ask you verbatim one of those quad tree/number theory/inclusion exclusion principle questions and I’d love to see you squirm, meanwhile another candidate is asked a basic hash map question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dinobones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by phs318u in "Hacking millions of modems and investigating who hacked my modem"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571189</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40571189"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a great article. Very easy to follow. The best part was that instead of attacking the messenger and denying any problem, Cox seem to have acted like the very model of responsible security response in this kind of situation. I'd love to read a follow up on what the bug was that intermittently permitted unauthorised access to the APIs. It's the kind of error that could easily be missed by superficial testing or depending on the reason behind the bug, perhaps not even experienced in the test environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phs318u</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Tough-on-Crime’ Doesn’t Apply to People Like Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324371</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/tough-on-crime-doesnt-apply-to-people-like-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Americans are celebrating the news of Donald Trump’s conviction on 34 felony charges in a hush-money incident that took place ahead of the 2016 presidential election. Newspaper headlines screamed “TRUMP GUILTY ON ALL COUNTS” and media reports relied on superlatives such as “historic” and “unprecedented” to label the unanimous jury verdict. Given that Trump has been unusually adept at avoiding accountability for a staggering number of alleged crimes, the verdict felt like a long-overdue comeuppance. More
The post ‘Tough-on-Crime’ Doesn’t Apply to People Like Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making More Babies to Drive Economic Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324383</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/making-more-babies-to-drive-economic-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments worldwide are in a race to see which one can encourage the most women to have the most babies. Hungary is slashing income tax for women with four or more children. Russia is offering women with 10 or more children a “Mother-Heroine” award. Greece, Italy, and South Korea are bribing women with attractive baby bonuses. China has instituted a three-child policy. Iran has outlawed free contraceptives and vasectomies. Japan has joined forces with the fertility industry to infiltrate schools to promote early childbearing. A leading UK demographer has proposed taxing the childless. Religious myths are preventing African men from getting vasectomies. A eugenics-inspired Natal conference just took place in the U.S., a nation leading the way in taking away reproductive rights. More
The post Making More Babies to Drive Economic Growth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nandita Bajaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dangerous Class Consciousness of Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324446</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/the-dangerous-class-consciousness-of-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a desire to restore a supposed national glory, Trump’s quest to “make America great again” is the search for his own “authentic essence.” His narcissism is pathological. He displays pomposity, grandiosity, and superiority, constantly seeking attention. He expects perfect loyalty from others to affirm his own value. He chooses wives and lovers based solely on their looks to convince himself of his own, physical beauty. He belittles and bullies others to affirm himself. He plays the victim to make sure that any failure is the fault of others, since he is faultless. And he exhibits a profound sense of emptiness – his hours-long perorations at MAGA rallies are ways of filling the void in his spirit and soul. There, he mirrors the ideological stance of his most damaged and desperate working-class followers, and they do the same with him. More
The post The Dangerous Class Consciousness of Donald Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triumph and Vision: the Tachi Tribe Environmental Protection Agency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324365</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/triumph-and-vision-the-tachi-tribe-environmental-protection-agency/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the spring of 2024, I met top members of the Tachi Yokuts Tribal Environmental Protection Agency at their offices on the Santa Rosa Rancheria near Lemoore CA. During the extremely wet winter a year earlier, the great Tulare Lake had once again overflowed its dams, dikes, levees and ditches, as it does every once in a while despite all the efforts of government and agribusiness, and spread to its full size of 800 square miles just south of the Rancheria, The return of the lake brought new faith and determination to these extraordinary people, who have lived here since long before the coming of the Europeans whom they have barely managed to survive. More
The post Triumph and Vision: the Tachi Tribe Environmental Protection Agency appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Hatch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Democracy and Billionaires Coexist?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324449</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/can-democracy-and-billionaires-coexist/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One person, one vote. The classic essence of democracy. But what if that one person happens to be a fabulously rich? Does that one person actually have just “one” vote? Can we have anything approaching democracy when some among us are sitting on fortunes grander than the rest of us can even imagine? Americans have  More
The post Can Democracy and Billionaires Coexist? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Who’s Spreading Disinformation on Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324522</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/look-whos-spreading-disinformation-on-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘Black kettle’ Tony Blinken’ accused Russia of spreading propaganda to mislead the Americans and Europeans, while hiding US decision to escalate the confrontation in Ukraine Last week, US Secretary of State Antony Blinken, during a set of whirlwind meetings in several European NATO countries, warned against Russian propaganda programs he accused of spreading “misinformation and  More
The post Look Who’s Spreading Disinformation on Ukraine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Two State Solution – Why Recognizing State of Palestine is Important]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324524</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/beyond-two-state-solution-why-recognizing-state-of-palestine-is-important/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In politics, context is crucial. To truly appreciate the recent decision by Ireland, Spain and Norway to recognize the state of Palestine, the subject has to be placed in proper context. On November 15, 1988, Yasser Arafat, then Chairman of the Palestine Liberation Organization, declared Palestine as an independent state. The proclamation took place within  More
The post Beyond Two State Solution – Why Recognizing State of Palestine is Important appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Impasse Will Show as Multinational Occupation Force Heads for Haiti]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324554</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/us-impasse-will-show-as-multinational-occupation-force-heads-for-haiti/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under U.S. arrangements, a so-called Multinational Security Support (MSS) force will soon be descending on Haiti. Its mission is that of suppressing gang violence. With their experience of earlier U.S. interventions, beleaguered Haitians can expect aggravation of oppression, social disaster and dependency. Supplies arrive from the United States. A U.S. military base is taking shape near the Port-au-Prince  More
The post US Impasse Will Show as Multinational Occupation Force Heads for Haiti appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Slaughterhouse Bans Merely Symbolic?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=324552</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/04/are-slaughterhouse-bans-merely-symbolic/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T05:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve followed with interest the campaign by Pro-Animal Future to pass a slaughterhouse ban in Denver. I appreciate the ambition behind the effort and how it focuses on political change, as opposed to individual or corporate change. That said, while I’m open to changing my mind, I’m a little skeptical of the impact such a  More
The post Are Slaughterhouse Bans Merely Symbolic? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whimsicalism in "New telescope images of Jupiter's moon Io rival those from spacecraft"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40570371</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40570371"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The telescope photo: https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2024/glimpses-of-a-vol...
Stitched spacecraft photo: https://science.nasa.gov/resource/high-resolution-global-vie...
This seems awesome but I would say 'rival those' is a bit of a stretch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whimsicalism</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[in my lame duck era (& when does the frog jump out of the pot?)]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lame-duck/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lame-duck/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T01:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a few days remain before I move to New York, which means I am firmly in my lame duck era. "Lame duck" is what you call a politician in the final stretch of their term who already knows that they won't be re-elected. Lame ducks can mess around and get away with a lot of things they might not otherwise if they were facing re-election.
I like to use that term to describe the habit I have of completely abandoning my usual routine before big life changes like going to college or starting a new job. This week I've replaced my usual routine of exercise and healthy eating with junk food binges and late bedtimes. Instead of reading and writing before bed I play videogames. I don't so much consciously decide to do this as much as I fall into it without meaning to: I think my brain knows that th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[【废一级】who is danielle]]></title>
        <id>https://daniellesunflower.bearblog.dev/4842/</id>
        <link href="https://daniellesunflower.bearblog.dev/4842/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🔅ID CARD🔅

⭐⭐⭐ 
◽姓名: Danielle June Marsh
◽中文名: 牟智慧
◽韩文名: 모지혜
◽外号: 蛋妞 蛋堡 dani 
◽代表emoji: 🦌/🌻/🐶/🦋
◽生日: 2005.04.11
◽身高: 165cm(5’5”)
◽星座: 白羊座
◽血型: AB型
◽国籍: 澳大利亚 韩国
◽出生: 韩国京畿道坡州市文山区
◽澳大利亚住址: 新南威尔士纽卡斯尔
◽MBTI：ENFP
◽所属团体: NewJeans
◽所属社: ADOR/HYBE
◽出道日: 2022.07.22
大年事表



.grid-container {
  display: grid;
  grid-template-columns: auto auto auto;
  grid-gap: 10px;
  padding: 10px;
}

.IDcard {
  grid-column-start: 1;
  grid-column-end: 2;
}

.item1 {
  grid-column-start: 2;
  grid-column-end: 3;
}

table {
width: 400px;
font-size: 15px;
border-image-slice: 50 51 132 51;
border-image-width: 20px 20px 54px 20px;
border-image-outset: 21px 21px 54px 21px;
border-image-repeat: stretch stretch;
border-image-source: url("https://bear-images.sfo2.cdn.digitaloceanspaces.com/daniellesunflower-1716521680-0.png");
border-style: solid;
}
.b1 {
  border-style: outset;
}
.b2 {
  border-style: groove;
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vitiral in "I'm forking Ladybird and stepping down as SerenityOS BDFL"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40569078</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40569078"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fill your bowl to the brim and it will spill. Keep sharpening your knife and it will blunt. Chase after money and security and your heart will never unclench. Care about people’s approval and you will be their prisoner. Do your work, then step back. The only path to serenity.
Tao Te Ching]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vitiral</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gpvos in "If English was written like Chinese (1999)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40568594</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40568594"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As far as I know it's not English or any Western entity that has grouped the Chinese languages together as one, but the Chinese government, for political reasons. Western linguists recognize the variants of "Chinese" as different languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gpvos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People may not read longer novels, but they do win literary awards]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7761</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/people-not-read-longer-novels-but-win-literary-awards/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tangentially related to the last post. Longer novels might pose a challenge to certain readers, especially those who require apps to do the reading for them. But, longer titles are more likely to win literary awards: Judgment and decision-making research suggests several causes of the apparent bias. One is the representativeness heuristic: longer novels resemble […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conquer your TBR with apps that read books in fifteen minutes]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7758</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/conquer-tbr-apps-read-books-fifteen-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T20:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Such apps don’t exactly read novels in fifteen minutes, but they scan through them, and produce relatively short summaries. Seems like cheating to me, don’t we read books to be taken along on a journey? Still, I imagine these apps have their uses. Like, where were they when I was at high school? Especially when […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by scosman in "Show HN: I made a tiny camera with super long battery life"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40567191</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40567191"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T20:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay, you also made a drag and drop terminal app for rebasing?? Super cool products all round. True hacker news.
https://toaster.llc/debase/index.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>scosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ‘Billions to Trillions’ charade]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45399</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/03/the-billions-to-trillions-charade/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:57:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Jayati Ghosh The international-development sector has become fixated on calculating financing gaps. Hardly a day goes by without new estimates of the funds low- and middle-income countries (LMICs) need to meet their climate targets and achieve the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The Independent High-Level Expert Group on Climate Finance, for example, estimates that developing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by davekeck in "Show HN: I made a tiny camera with super long battery life"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40566840</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40566840"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T19:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Totally fair question! My reasons were:
1. To maximize Photon's battery life I tried to make the hardware do the absolute minimum to record imagery. To that end, Photon stores images on an unformatted SD card (ie one huge linear array of bytes) which is easy and fast to index into.
2. A 16-bit MSP430 handles writing the image data, and the MSP430's codespace is 99% exhausted without dealing with the complexities of a filesystem like FAT32, so adding support for a filesystem wouldn't currently fit. (This line of MSP430, MSP430FR2433, has a maximum of 16 KB of FRAM, but perhaps I could use a different line.)
3. Photon stores images as RAW image data that require post-processing to view the images. Since I wanted to provide a polished app to view the imagery anyway, I figured I'd just make it a requirement.
I'm not saying those are all particularly good reasons, but that was my reasoning anyhow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>davekeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by laweijfmvo in "Show HN: I made a tiny camera with super long battery life"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565681</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565681"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T18:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> exclusively for Mac
Why not just have it connect as a generic mass-storage device?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>laweijfmvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mrb in "Why YC went to DC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565410</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565410"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T18:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This year, we’ll fund more than 500 companies out of 50,000 applications, and almost all of them are related to AI in some way."
So, what this means: that in 2024, if you want to get VC capital, your startup must be related to AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mrb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by siliconc0w in "Why YC went to DC"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565375</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40565375"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T18:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you need more things to fix:
* Software R&D Amortization - taxes on make-believe profits
* Patent law - protect small businesses from patent trolls
* Automate government-driven compliance standards - enable small businesses to sell into large companies/government entities, automatic certification when using pre-approved cloud solutions.
* Healthcare insurance - employees of SMBs automatically get access to medicare]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>siliconc0w</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub reduced testing time for iOS apps with new runner features]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-03-how-github-reduced-testing-time-for-ios-apps-with-new-runner-features/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-03-how-github-reduced-testing-time-for-ios-apps-with-new-runner-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T16:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Learn how GitHub used macOS and Apple Silicon runners for GitHub Actions to build, test, and deploy our iOS app faster.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-03-how-github-reduced-testing-time-for-ios-apps-with-new-runner-features/">How GitHub reduced testing time for iOS apps with new runner features</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Freddie Mac used Amazon EKS to modernize their platform and migrate applications]]></title>
        <id>3c3360f277065058342fa8bc314bed62983bcb6b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-freddie-mac-used-amazon-eks-to-modernize-their-platform-and-migrate-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T16:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Freddie Mac has a mission to provide a stable US housing Market. Freddie Mac identified the need for faster application delivery, scalable performance, increased resiliency, and cost optimization of their existing application portfolio. To achieve their mission goals, Freddie Mac undertook a migration from on-premises Kubernetes to Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Saha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2 U7i Instances, Bedrock Converse API, AWS World IPv6 Day and more (June 3, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3f19c95f29bda37b6717aedaa8d5a6566eb2061e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-ec2-u7i-instances-bedrock-converse-api-aws-world-ipv6-day-and-more-june-3-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life is not always happy, there are difficult times. However, we can share our joys and sufferings with those we work with. The AWS Community is no exception. Jeff Barr introduced two members of the AWS community who are dealing with health issues. Farouq Mousa is an AWS Community Builder and fighting brain cancer. Allen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting OpenTelemetry for our logging pipeline]]></title>
        <id>6659ca91bdbaa8000a84c543</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/adopting-opentelemetry-for-our-logging-pipeline"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T13:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Cloudflare's Observability team undertook an effort to migrate our existing syslog-ng backed logging infrastructure to instead being backed by OpenTelemetry Collectors. In this post, we detail the process that we undertook, and the difficulties we faced along the way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Douch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 2nd, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240603</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240603"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Left and THE LEFT: Responding to the crisis of soft neoliberalism]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52738</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/03/the-left-and-the-left-responding-to-the-crisis-of-soft-neoliberalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T01:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brad DeLong (in a recent post summarising a joint podcast with Noah Smith) walks back his previous suggestion that it was time for neoliberals, among whom he had numbered himself, to pass the baton to “the Left”. The political basis for this is that 20 or so Senate Republicans have been willing to pass legislation […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five-thousand kilometre long cloud-band across Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7753</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/five-thousand-kilometre-cloud-band-across-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Daily Aus (TDA), Friday, 31 May 2024: Rain is forecast across 90% of the country over the coming days as a 5,000km ‘cloudband’ makes its way from WA‘s north to south-east Australia. According to the Bureau of Meteorology (BOM), a ‘northwest cloudband’ is an extensive layer of air and moisture from over the Indian […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guzman y Gomez goes to IPO, eyes burrito world domination]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7747</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/guzman-y-gomez-ipo-eyes-burrito-world-domination/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T20:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not exactly a fan of large-chain food and beverage outlets. But Sydney based Mexican cuisine fast food restaurant Guzman y Gomez, AKA GYG (to me, anyway) is not quite large-chain. Not at the moment, though there are near to two-hundred stores in Australia, sixteen in Singapore, and a handful in Japan, and the United […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I wasn't able to sing before having a son]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.bearblog.dev/i-wasnt-able-to-sing-before-having-a-son/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.bearblog.dev/i-wasnt-able-to-sing-before-having-a-son/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T16:40:05.477Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was never what you would considered a singer or even an outgoing person (not that the two are the same). When singing was involved I would usually remain silent, worrying that I would sound off key, or that I wouldn't know the words and people would notice, or any other myriad of possible scenarios which are common to those who worry endlessly about stuff. In some way, I perceived the act of singing as something very intimate and I never managed to break through that barrier I had imposed upon myself. That is, until I had a son, but it wasn't that easy.
After he was born, my wife used to sing to him all the time. She has beautiful voice, knows lots of songs, and is so confident in her ability that she doesn't really think about it. I, however, shied away from the act, as if a panel of ju…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Ward - The Child in the City]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/colin-ward-the-child-in-the-city?v=1717335517</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/colin-ward-the-child-in-the-city?v=1717335517"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T13:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Colin Ward
Title: The Child in the City
Date: 1978
Notes: Pictures and captions are not included in this version due to them being very faded in the source book scan, but the book has been republished by AK Press, so they may get added in the future. First published by The Architectural Press in 1978. This version is an OCR from a Penguin Books version from 1979.
Source: <archive.org/details/childincity00wardrich>

Synopsis
 How can the link between city and child be made more fruitful and enjoyable for both the child and the city? 
 At a time when a significant proportion of the city’s children are at war with their environment, the question raised by this book becomes ever more urgent for teachers and parents, citizens and policy makers. Through an enormously rich range of refere…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eva X Moberg - International Workers Aid To Bosnia]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eva-x-moberg-international-workers-aid-to-bosnia?v=1717325359</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/eva-x-moberg-international-workers-aid-to-bosnia?v=1717325359"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T10:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Eva X Moberg
Title: International Workers Aid To Bosnia
Subtitle: Syndicalists truck flour directly to Bosnia unions
Date: December 1994
Notes: This article, from a presentation on June 1993 at the European Syndicalist Conference, appeared in Nov.-Dec. 1994 Industrial Worker newspaper
Source: Retrieved on 2nd June 2024 from www.spunk.org

 I’d like to present to you a very concrete example of international solidarity and proof that it really works. I’m here as spokeswoman for International Workers Aid but I’m also a member of SAC which played an important role in developing this idea to reality. 
 International Workers Aid started last summer with a plea for help from mine workers in Tuzla, a mining town in central Bosnia, to comrades in Britain. The miners of Tuzla have a long his…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: lunchtime]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52736</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/02/sunday-photoblogging-lunchtime/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T07:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing is unfiltered speech]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/writing-unfiltered-speech/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/writing-unfiltered-speech/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T17:16:31.398Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw a documentary about the Swedish singer-songwriter and poet Cornelis Vreeswijk. In one of the scenes, someone tells Cornelis that writing seems to be necessary for him.
He replies:
Yes, it is. I can panic if I'm not allowed to write.
I think many of us can relate to that, at least to some extent. I know that I can. That’s why we write.
If I don't write in one form or another, it's like a blockage in the system. To get that shit out, I need to write in one form or another. Blog, journal, napkin - it doesn't matter. Just get it out of the system.
I think it was Stephen King who said something like:
"If you don't have time to read, how will you have time to write?”
For me, it's the other way around. If I don't write, there's no way I can be fully present and absorb what I'm reading.
Writing is a valve, a way to release the pressure of repetitive thoughts. Writing is a way to give words to the wordless. Writing is an unfiltered way of speaking.
Follow: email · rss]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico: from AMLO to Sheinbaum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Mexico-from-AMLO-to-Sheinbaum</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Mexico-from-AMLO-to-Sheinbaum"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T16:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico has its general election this Sunday. With a population of over 130 million, Mexico is among the 15 largest economies in the world and the second-largest economy in Latin America. 
English

/ 
Mexico, 
Private debt, 
Inequality, 
Precarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Squashing the Perfection Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://sreekarscribbles.com/squashing-the-perfection-bug/</id>
        <link href="https://sreekarscribbles.com/squashing-the-perfection-bug/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:19:18.684Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love my blog! I really do! I want to write every day. But I don't. Why? Because of the Perfection Bug!
"You need to share a unique thought"
"Your idea should be worth penning"
"You need to write in great detail"
Buzz, buzzz, buzzzz....the perfection bug keeps buzzing in my ear.
But today, I decided to squash that bug!
I don't need unique thoughts. I don't need amazing ideas. I don't need to explain things in detail.
All I need is a thought (which can be ordinary) and a bunch of words to share it. That's it! That's all I need to write on my blog.
So, see you again tomorrow with an ordinary thought and a bunch of words!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsflash: Inequality in Neoliberal America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Newsflash-Inequality-in-Neoliberal-America</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Newsflash-Inequality-in-Neoliberal-America"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If anyone is perplexed or surprised why Americans are so upset about the economy, they should look no further than the Income Distribution and Dynamics in America (IDDA) recent report by the Federal Reserve Board of Minneapolis and its data site that looks at the stagnation of American income and economic mobility in America. It unfortunately confirms what we already know—the neoliberal state benefits unevenly and in ways that confound an ability to challenge it.. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Inequality, 
Neo-liberalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schultz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify custom contact center insights with Amazon Connect analytics data lake]]></title>
        <id>b44f4d90bbfa2e0d08f57e4bdcf5b0d09dfc7e16</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-custom-contact-center-insights-with-amazon-connect-analytics-data-lake/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T16:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Connect's analytics data lake centralizes customer data for powerful performance analysis without complex pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luke Roberts: &ldquo;Raspberries&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/raspberries</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/raspberries"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[J.H. Prynne’s ‘Poems 2016-2024’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Single Sign On (SSO) to manage project teams for Amazon CodeCatalyst]]></title>
        <id>fbcf566b2175883fe6c6b7622cccf1911f785fd5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/using-single-sign-on-sso-to-manage-project-teams-for-amazon-codecatalyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T14:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst is a modern software development service that empowers teams to deliver software on AWS easily and quickly. Amazon CodeCatalyst provides one place where you can plan, code, and build, test, and deploy your container applications with continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) tools. CodeCatalyst recently announced the teams feature, which simplifies management of space and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Konaka Satyapal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back on Bear Blog - for life]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-blog-life/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-blog-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:15:23.670Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I decided to start blogging again after a long absence, Bear was the platform I fell in love with. I published the first post, It's alive!, on February 16, 2023, while on vacation in Chiang Mai, Thailand.
After about half a year, I went on a blogging tool spree. Why? I'm not sure why. Maybe because of my love and fascination for the web.
I tried many different platforms. Eventually, there were three left:
Bear
Pika
Scribbles
They are all fantastic! If you're on one of them today and find it to be the right blogging tool for you, congratulations. You made a great choice!
For me, Bear ended up being the winner. I will write a separate post on this later, but basically, it was the combination of simplicity and customization that won me over forever.
When I say "forever," I mean “for the rest of my life”. I decided to upgrade to the lifetime plan. Partly because it's a great deal, but also to keep me from looking elsewhere. This is my home, and I'm very happy to have found my way back.
I look forward to writing many more posts, but more importantly, I look forward to reading what other "Bears" publish in this beautiful community.
Happy blogging!
all posts · rss feed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending local traffic management load balancing to Layer 4 with Spectrum]]></title>
        <id>66599d35bdbaa8000a84c512</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/extending-local-traffic-management-load-balancing-to-layer-4-with-spectrum"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is adding support for all TCP and UDP traffic to our local traffic management (LTM) load balancing solution, extending the benefits of LTM to more than just HTTP(S) applications]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Ward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Discount Window Stigma Be Cured?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30230</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/can-discount-window-stigma-be-cured/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the core responsibilities of central banks is to act as “lender of last resort” to the financial system. In the U.S., the Federal Reserve has been operating as a lender of last resort through its “discount window” (DW) for more than a century. Historically, however, the DW has been plagued by stigma—banks’ reluctance to use the DW, even for benign reasons, out of concerns that it could be interpreted as a sign of financial weakness. In this post, we report on new research showing that once a DW facility is stigmatized, removing that stigma is difficult.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivier Armantier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thinking of Pursuing a PhD in Economics? Info on Graduate School and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30228</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/thinking-of-pursuing-a-phd-in-economics-info-on-graduate-school-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Becoming a PhD economist can provide a fulfilling and financially secure career path. However, getting started in the field can be daunting if you don’t know much about the preparation you’ll need and the available job opportunities. If you’re wondering what it means to be an economics researcher or how to become one, please read on. We’ll review how to prepare for a career in economics research, what an economics PhD program entails, and what types of opportunities it might bring. Economic education is a core component of the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s mission to serve the community. To empower would-be economists, this post provides information for students who seek a career in economics research. We hope this information will be helpful to students interested in economics, regardless of their background and economic situation.  This information is most applicable to students applying to programs in the United States.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kasey Chatterji-Len and Anna Kovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hassan Ould Moctar: &ldquo;Hors Camp&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hors-camp</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hors-camp"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[War and migration in the Sahel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[toast button!!! 🥐🥐🥐]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/toast-button/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/toast-button/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:50:39.130Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've finally gotten around to messing with the blog's CSS! I found this fantastic toast button by A Functioning Blog, which is everything I've ever wanted: the opportunity to make the toast button actual toast. Well, a croissant, in this case. Please have fun with it. Thank you so much, A Functioning Blog.
I've also been thinking about messing with the font on this site. I love serif fonts as much as the next guy, but I might go and change it to a sans serif for better readability. And the colors. I love the color of the blog as it is right now (off-white backgrounds hurt less than pure white!), but accent colors...
While I'm deciding, please enjoy the croissant button. It's given me more serotonin than it should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[who's afraid of a big bad word?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/big-bad-word/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/big-bad-word/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T03:03:42.726Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I got coffee with a college friend who I last saw in July of 2023. In the months since then, she has not only quit her job, but also somehow gotten engaged AND married (in a courthouse wedding) without telling any of us. What is going on? Life is going 80 in a school zone and I don’t have my seat belt on. I haven't even met her boyfriend (now husband) yet.
This is the third friend I grew up with to get married, and with all of them I struggle to use the right terms to refer to their partners. It's not that I don't know the words. First fiancée, then husband and wife. I'll start sentences fully intending to use the most up-to-date term but midway through 'husband' will catch in my mouth and 'boyfriend' will slip out instead.
Most of this can be chalked up to unfamiliarity. I've been u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>