<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-28T12:54:30.977Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-28T12:54:30.977Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/28/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294637</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-28-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T10:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our florid daily links: Doomsday preppers, mass casualty at graduations, EU warmongering, Iran exits IAEA oversight, Israel puts Oxy in Gaza flour, Russia troops massing? NATO bootlicking, Trump wins at Supremes, new fundamental AI problems, Tesla robotaxi fail, leverage loan worries, police state]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: The U.S. Empire’s Plan for Global Domination]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294664</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/michael-hudson-the-u-s-empires-plan-for-global-domination.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T09:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: War on Iran is part of the US empire’s effort to re-impose its dominance on the global political and financial system]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dark Side of Ecotourism: When Green Travel Exploits People and the Planet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294661</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-dark-side-of-ecotourism-when-green-travel-exploits-people-and-the-planet.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-28T07:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As luxury eco-retreats and voluntourism surge, experts warn that without systemic reform, ecotourism may be doing more harm than good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 27, 2025 (#577)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23395</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/27/daily-reading-list-june-27-2025-577/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T23:29:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how much AI impacts development speed, the best way to prompt text-to-video model Veo, and what context engineering is all about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Funding Medical Education, A Human Ancestor, Tardigrades to the Rescue, Trashing the Earth, Plus MAHA and Measles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294651</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-funding-medical-education-a-human-ancestor-tardigrades-to-the-rescue-trashing-the-earth-plus-maha-and-measles.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T18:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part the First: Financing Professional Education in the United States.  College costs too much in the United States.  Professional School costs way to much.  Up until the present – who knows what will happen next as the broad attacks on American universities continue – graduate education at the PhD level in traditional disciplines in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Suffering]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArEFXEPRXhTvhg6exDPqRd</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItArEFXEPRXhTvhg6exDPqRd"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:47:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Canadian, the issue of people removing snow from the sidewalk is a big deal. Some years ago I lived near a house where they never removed the snow. It piled up till it was almost four feet high, and some partial thaws meant that underneath all that snow was ice. Every time I had to walk in that direction I cursed the owners (there was an SUV that came and went, so I knew it wasn’t uninhabited.) And one time I did slip and I was furious, even though the pain of the fall was minor.
Thing is, I don’t enjoy being furious or upset. Oh, a little anger is sometimes nice enough, but overall it’s an unpleasant feeling unless you’ve been having even worse emotions like fear, despair, powerlessness or self-pity.
This is what Buddha called the second arrow. If you’ve been shot by an arrow, you’re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIT and Mass General Brigham launch joint seed program to accelerate innovations in health]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-mass-general-brigham-launch-seed-program-innovations-health-0627</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/mit-mass-general-brigham-launch-seed-program-innovations-health-0627"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT-MGB Seed Program, launched with support from Analog Devices Inc., will fund joint research projects that advance technology and clinical research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Beth Gallagher | Office of Innovation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using generative AI to help robots jump higher and land safely]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/using-generative-ai-help-robots-jump-higher-land-safely-0627</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/using-generative-ai-help-robots-jump-higher-land-safely-0627"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIT CSAIL researchers combined GenAI and a physics simulation engine to refine robot designs. The result: a machine that out-jumped a robot designed by humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shipps | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ursula von der Leyen faces no-confidence vote]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ursula-von-der-leyen-faces-no-confidence</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ursula-von-der-leyen-faces-no-confidence"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T16:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if driven by right-wing factions within the European Parliament, the motion reveals growing cross-party unease with the EU’s escalating techno-authoritarian regime]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Term Toxic Masculinity is Nothing But A Gratuitous Insult to Men.]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBjcaEIu3BaRz2NcPWUnK_W</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBjcaEIu3BaRz2NcPWUnK_W"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only a woman with solid feminist bona fides can make this argument in modern America. The high tech economy has leveled the playing field between men and women. This is a great development. But it ignores, like the Democratic party in general, a larger reality: blue collar men. White collar men are indoctrinated in high school and college now how to behave around women. But blue collar men are not. And there are more of them than white collar Ivy Leaguers. Give the video a watch. It refreshing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrate Micro-Small, and Medium-sized Enterprises Day with Cloudflare]]></title>
        <id>RZxPGrzjOiPmMdVhXUdSi</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrate-micro-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-day-with-cloudflare/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate United Nations Micro, Small, and Medium Sized Enterprises Day, Cloudflare is sharing success stories of small businesses building and growing on our platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jocelyn Woolbright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frédéric Lordon: &ldquo;Endgame&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/endgame</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/endgame"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism and its destiny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Flattering Donald Trump Could Be Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294648</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/why-flattering-donald-trump-could-be-dangerous.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why power players should not apply their tongues to Trump's posterior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff Dyer <em>&amp;</em> Leo Robson: &ldquo;Theory in the Air&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/theory-in-the-air</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/theory-in-the-air"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T13:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Geoff Dyer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/27/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294616</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-27-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T10:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our dawning daily links, including "big, beautiful bill" speedbumps, the feckless fighting Democrats, and a deal with China?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Washington Declares Mexico An “Adversary”, Russia Offers to Help Mexico Reduce Its Energy Dependence on US]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294596</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/as-washington-declares-mexico-an-adversary-russia-offers-to-help-mexico-reduce-its-energy-dependence-on-us.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump administration's global charm offensive continues apace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Financial Times on Coming Climate-Change-Driven Meltdown in Real Estate: Gradually, Then Suddenly?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294626</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/financial-times-on-coming-climate-change-driven-meltdown-in-real-estate-gradually-then-suddenly.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T09:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed, yet still softball, take on how climate change damage will wreck property values and much of what passes for an economy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carl von Clausewitz and the Clausewitzian Viewpoint of Warfare: A Theoretical Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294608</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/carl-von-clausewitz-and-the-clausewitzian-viewpoint-of-warfare-a-theoretical-approach.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-27T05:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of Clausewitz's thinking winds up showing how the US has ignored it, with the bad results  Clausewitz predicted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 26, 2025 (#576)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23374</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/26/daily-reading-list-june-26-2025-576/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T23:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at choosing the right host for your AI agents, how to prepare APIs for AI agents, and whether it matters if your manager writes code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The War in the Ukraine Enters A New Phase]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMBgbFOo9fbF8i5kwdxT2n</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMBgbFOo9fbF8i5kwdxT2n"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T22:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russo-Ukrainian War of 2021-present has entered a new phase. In the wake of the Ukraine’s hybrid/asymmetric attack on Russia’s strategic bomber fleet–aka Operation Spiderweb–Russia is getting its revenge in the smartest way possible. Russia has begun a massive month long air/missile/drone campaign that is systematically attacking command and control centers all over the country. The latest was a Russian X-22 missile attack on a former drilling rig disguuised as a seaborne command and control center. A Tu-22M3 Backfire bomber launched the X-22 cruise missile where it reached Mach 4 and then dove into the command center and obliterated it. There are dozens of videos out now on reputable sites indicating this campaign is ongoing and will continue.
This is very, very bad news for the Ukraine. This might not be the beginning of the end, but it is the end of the middle.
The site for reasonably unbiased updates is Military TV. But, viewer beware, this is uncensored warfare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Internet users are unable to access the open Internet]]></title>
        <id>vyxFL3zp5DqpF5RpHznRv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/russian-internet-users-are-unable-to-access-the-open-internet/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T22:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since June 9, 2025, Internet users located in Russia and connecting to the open Internet have been throttled by Russian Internet Service Providers (ISPs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tremante</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Zohran Mamdani Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAljUbemCh_wgFivPETZmjk</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAljUbemCh_wgFivPETZmjk"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T19:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Democratic Socialist (ie. has politics a 70s liberal would have agreed with, but is less racist) Zohran Mamdani has won the nomination for Democratic candidate for New York city Mayor.
The best analysis I’ve read of this is definitely from Matt Stoller. He defines this win as a “system defining election”, that is an attempt to not just to change who runs a system, but how that system is run. Read the article.
I’ll point out here that there have been a few such attempts. Matt talks about Lamont’s challenge to Lieberman, where Lamont won the primary, then Lieberman won the election. That is what will be tried here: the oligarchical part of the party will align behind another candidate, possibly even the Republican one. Those who don’t will try to co-opt Mamdani and turn him into a centri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel–Iran Conflict Tests “America First” and Redefines ‘Auctoritas’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294612</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-israel-iran-conflict-tests-america-first-and-redefines-auctoritas.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s attack on Iran tests the limits of “America First” and reveals a deeper MAGA divide over who holds legitimate authority—auctoritas]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Curro Jimenez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying sustainability reporting using AWS and generative AI in banking]]></title>
        <id>232ff3b2fb66dde737470efdab18cf1de7afed37</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/simplifying-sustainability-reporting-using-aws-and-generative-ai-in-banking/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T17:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, you learn how you can use generative AI services on Amazon Web Services (AWS) to automate your sustainability reporting requirements, reduce manual effort, and improve accuracy. You do this by implementing an automated solution for extracting, processing, and validating data from corporate reports.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sachin Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemini CLI might change how I work. Here are four prompts that prove it.]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23311</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/26/the-gemini-cli-might-change-how-i-work-here-are-four-prompts-that-prove-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T16:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday morning, we took the wraps off one of the most interesting Google releases of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Tiratelli <em>&amp;</em> Ali Helwith: &ldquo;Stagnation State&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stagnation-state</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/stagnation-state"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T15:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the UK economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to save Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/how-to-save-europe</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/how-to-save-europe"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T15:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is necessary to articulate a confederal Europe capable of overcoming the technocratic, militaristic, post-national and Atlanticist design of the European Union]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orange Me2eets: We made an end-to-end encrypted video calling app and it was easy]]></title>
        <id>6X6FQzpKaqVyTLVk7rw6xm</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/orange-me2eets-we-made-an-end-to-end-encrypted-video-calling-app-and-it-was/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-26T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Orange Meets, our open-source video calling web application, now supports end-to-end encryption using the MLS protocol with continuous group key agreement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Rosenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 25, 2025 (#575)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23333</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/25/daily-reading-list-june-25-2025-575/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T23:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the exciting new Gemini CLI, how Salesforce rolled out AI to their engineering teams, and where AI features should sit in your product's UI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for OpenZFS now supports Amazon S3 access without any data movement]]></title>
        <id>becd74c154f4b3a13344b15c9ef71b24566da206</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-openzfs-now-supports-amazon-s3-access-without-any-data-movement/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T20:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now attach Amazon S3 Access Points to your Amazon FSx for OpenZFS file systems so that you can access your file data as if it were in S3. With this new capability, you can work with your file data using a broad range of applications that work with S3—all without any refactoring or data movement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing Our Asian Allies – And Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA_5DHONSDQ2FmVwyvLb9Gr</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA_5DHONSDQ2FmVwyvLb9Gr"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T20:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ian in his last post mentioned that our Asian allies are slipping away from us. While we pretend to strategically re-orient the Japanese are engaging in massive rearmament begun by Abe and being continued by the current government. Japan has lost confidence in the American security umbrella because of the deceit we’ve displayed in foreign relations. The Koreans? I lived in Korea. They’re simply apoplectic. Some are even at the point where they are willing to consider a loose confederation with the north, an entente of sorts so the South has the protection of the North’s nuclear umbrella and the North gains goods and services from the South.
This is simply unheard of. When I talked to one of my former students who now works in the foreign ministry and he told me this I was gobsmacked.
Ian’s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Middle East Is Hastening Ukraine’s Fall &amp; The End of the European Era]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCldAklcjs27uMa83tGKrNn</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCldAklcjs27uMa83tGKrNn"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T14:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rarely spoken of is the effects of the Middle Eastern wars on Ukraine. For a long time, Ukraine got everything it wanted, but since Oct 7th, it has been #2, or worse, on America’s priority list. Mossad has a great deal of influence in America, just short of control, almost certainly due to a sickening collection of videos and pictures, and Israel has received the first cut off everything it needed: most especially of interceptor missiles.
Even so, the reason that Israel and the US called for a ceasefire and Iran did not (though it accepted one) is that Israel was less than a week from running out of air defense missiles, and as best I can tell, the US could only have supplied about another 7-10 days worth.
What this means for Ukraine is simple enough, they’re being absolutely hammered by R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building agents with OpenAI and Cloudflare’s Agents SDK]]></title>
        <id>3RJX3pjuKNyVyxPYsPBbGg</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-agents-with-openai-and-cloudflares-agents-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re building AI agents where logic and reasoning are handled by OpenAI’s Agents SDK, and execution happens across Cloudflare's global network via Cloudflare’s Agents SDK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kate Reznykova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merging AI and underwater photography to reveal hidden ocean worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/lobstger-merging-ai-underwater-photography-to-reveal-hidden-ocean-worlds-0625</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/lobstger-merging-ai-underwater-photography-to-reveal-hidden-ocean-worlds-0625"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LOBSTgER research initiative at MIT Sea Grant explores how generative AI can expand scientific storytelling by building on field-based photographic data.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MIT Sea Grant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlanticism — not nationalism — is driving German rearmament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/atlanticism-not-nationalism-is-driving</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/atlanticism-not-nationalism-is-driving"/>
        <updated>2025-06-25T11:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The policies now being implemented — from massive rearmament to the escalation of conflict with Russia — are not rooted in a cold pursuit of German national interests, but in their negation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 24, 2025 (#574)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23292</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/24/daily-reading-list-june-24-2025-574/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T23:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at what AI to use right now, how to prioritize better, and why the AI revolution won't happen overnight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New: Improve Apache Iceberg query performance in Amazon S3 with sort and z-order compaction]]></title>
        <id>338ab1a5449dedd3d0a422376be4e668fc6d6075</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-improve-apache-iceberg-query-performance-in-amazon-s3-with-sort-and-z-order-compaction/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T20:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon S3 now enables improved Apache Iceberg query performance through two new compaction strategies—sort and z-order—available for both S3 Tables and general purpose S3 buckets, helping organize data more efficiently by clustering similar values together and reducing file scanning during queries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran Screws Up &amp; Gaza Death Toll]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T17:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Iran has accepted the ceasefire offer. Iran was, as best I can tell, winning. The Iron Dome could not stop their more advanced missiles and was days from running out of interceptor missiles. Two weeks if the US sent its entire stockpile. The US attack on Iran’s nuclear facility was a dud, the enriched uranium has been moved, etc…
I said that Iran had finally gotten over its caution, but feared it would revert, and so it has. It’s clear that the sooner Khameini dies and is replaced the safer Iran will be, also because that will be the end of the non-nuclear fatwa. (It should be noted that 60% enriched is enough to create a dirty bomb which would render Israel uninhabitable, and Iran should inform Israel that it has created a number, read for missile deployment.)
Iran could have kept goi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are available in public beta for simple, global, and programmable compute]]></title>
        <id>5StUs8TMNjY9aDG2TzFJ06</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/containers-are-available-in-public-beta-for-simple-global-and-programmable/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T16:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Containers are now available in public beta. Deploy simple, global, and programmable containers alongside your Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabi Villalonga Simón</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s craziest ceasefire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The smug idea that Israel can get away with anything without ever paying a price seems to have vanished]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deluge of Metanarrative Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T07:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime anyone anywhere begins an argument or uses the word “narrative” my bullshit detector goes off. Because it’s a nonsense construct.
My suggestion is to follow French philosopher Jean-François Lyotards definition of “narrative.” He said: “Simplifying to the extreme , I define postmodern as incredulity toward metanarratives.”
So, if you hear someone use the term in a conversation, one of three things can happen: you can choose to remain willfully ignorant (I doubt many in this crowd would pursue this course), two, your bullshit detector can go off, like mine and you can begin an argument or three you can simply sit with a Cheshire cat grin and be skeptical.
But chose one, please.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 23, 2025 (#573)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23026</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/23/daily-reading-list-june-23-2025-573/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T23:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at why not all micromanagement is bad, agent-to-agent protocol truly becoming an industry standard, and why software development won't ever be the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture in an AWS landing zone]]></title>
        <id>d99d4df75c23e56992bed599dc075700701c55d6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/amazon-bedrock-baseline-architecture-in-an-aws-landing-zone/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T18:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore the Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture and how you can secure and control network access to your various Amazon Bedrock capabilities within AWS network services and tools. We discuss key design considerations, such as using Amazon VPC Lattice auth policies, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) endpoints, and AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to restrict and monitor access to your Amazon Bedrock capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdel-Rahman Awad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: re:Inforce re:Cap, Valkey GLIDE 2.0, Avro and Protobuf or MCP Servers on Lambda, and more (June 23, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>939e6ae6e5cce485ea26e1e9c5165b803613c28b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-reinforce-recap-valkey-glide-2-0-avro-and-protobuf-or-mcp-servers-on-lambda-and-more-june-23-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s hallmark event was the security-focused AWS re:Inforce conference. Now a tradition, the blog team wrote a re:Cap post to summarize the announcements and link to some of the top blog posts. To further summarize, several new security innovations were announced, including enhanced IAM Access Analyzer capabilities, MFA enforcement for root users, and threat […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangster empire: what the bombing of Iran reveals about the West]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T13:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have now entered a new phase of Western-led global savagery — prefigured by the genocide in Gaza — in which all pretences have been dropped and only the logic of raw, unrestrained violence remains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TACO Trump Bombs Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re getting a bit tired of Iran all the time, so am I, and we’ll see if we can slip in an article on something else.
In the meantime, Trump hit Iran’s nuclear enrichment site. As best I can tell, the attack was ineffective and did essentially no damage. Even if it had, Iran’s highly enriched, 60% stockpile, had already been moved. I’ve seen Israeli claims they know where, but there’s a good chance they’re lying and if the Iranians are smart, they’ve split it up and made sure that only a few people know where each package is, and no one knows where all the packages are, which doubles as “if you hit it, you lose your spy.”
Iran’s parliament has passed a motion asking for the Straits of Hormuz to be closed, it’s waiting for Khameini’s approval. Some ships appear to be already turning aw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs factor in unrelated information when recommending medical treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find nonclinical information in patient messages — like typos, extra white space, and colorful language — reduces the accuracy of an AI model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
War
[TW: This is what the “globalist” elites centered on the City of London and Wall Street have been scheming for ever since Franklin Roosevelt told Winston Churchill at the 1943 Casablanca Conference that there would be no restoration of the British empire.
[Now that Trump has fully thrown in with the pro-war faction, we will learn if those who supported Trump because they believed Trump would be a foil against the “globalist” elites, accept the chastening of a hard lesson learned. More importantly, now that Trump has allowed the globalists to steer us into a war against Iran, will those who supported Trump be vigilant against Trump using the war to exercise his “war powers” and impose authoritarian measures on the USA p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wars Metastize]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title says it own. So did Clausewitz.
We committed an act of war against a sovereign state that had every right to peaceful nuclear power.
Tulsi Gabbard told Donald Trump in March that Iran had NO nuclear weapons program.
There is a huge difference between radio medcine and nuclear power, and a nuclear weapons program. Iran has the former by legal right under the NNPT and does not, nor has plans for the latter.
This war will spiral out of control just like the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand in July 1914.
Prepare yourselves. We will all suffer before this is over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>