<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-03-07T12:46:39.018Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-03-07T12:46:39.018Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Here's how merge queue transformed the way GitHub deploys changes to production at scale, so you can do the same for your organization.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-06-how-github-uses-merge-queue-to-ship-hundreds-of-changes-every-day/">How GitHub uses merge queue to ship hundreds of changes every day</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficiently fine-tune the ESM-2 protein language model with Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>ddf89841a585bf7be6504b5aaede222934cad578</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/efficiently-fine-tune-the-esm-2-protein-language-model-with-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we demonstrate how to efficiently fine-tune a state-of-the-art protein language model (pLM) to predict protein subcellular localization using Amazon SageMaker. Proteins are the molecular machines of the body, responsible for everything from moving your muscles to responding to infections. Despite this variety, all proteins are made of repeating chains of molecules called […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Loyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping repository maintainer information accurate]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T21:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discover how keeping repository maintainer information accurate through CODEOWNERS files and automating maintenance with tools like cleanowners fosters efficient collaboration and sustainable software projects.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-03-04-keeping-repository-maintainer-information-accurate/">Keeping repository maintainer information accurate</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alida gains deeper understanding of customer feedback with Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>48b0384e21c7afe91f04358f166844b9537ca198</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/alida-gains-deeper-understanding-of-customer-feedback-with-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T20:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-written with Sherwin Chu from Alida. Alida helps the world’s biggest brands create highly engaged research communities to gather feedback that fuels better customer experiences and product innovation. Alida’s customers receive tens of thousands of engaged responses for a single survey, therefore the Alida team opted to leverage machine learning (ML) to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kinman Lam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a User Activity Dashboard for Amazon CodeWhisperer]]></title>
        <id>e17c98e50fee17e1252a66a41421483ba16a6307</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/creating-a-user-activity-dashboard-for-amazon-codewhisperer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T15:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing the value from Enterprise Software tools requires an understanding of who and how users interact with those tools. As we have worked with builders rolling out Amazon CodeWhisperer to their enterprises, identifying usage patterns has been critical. This blog post is a result of that work, builds on Introducing Amazon CodeWhisperer Dashboard blog and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Ernst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Innovation: AWS and Anthropic push the boundaries of generative AI together]]></title>
        <id>f2d1d14b9e37aaea010d34162491b1a3a5186a52</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/unlocking-innovation-aws-and-anthropic-push-the-boundaries-of-generative-ai-together/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T14:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock is the best place to build and scale generative AI applications with large language models (LLM) and other foundation models (FMs). It enables customers to leverage a variety of high-performing FMs, such as the Claude family of models by Anthropic, to build custom generative AI applications. Looking back to 2021, when Anthropic first started […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Swami Sivasubramanian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports hybrid search]]></title>
        <id>7ffffabc9cec704fd1243efbec0de4851f15dfff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-hybrid-search/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T22:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Invent 2023, we announced the general availability of Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock. With a knowledge base, you can securely connect foundation models (FMs) in Amazon Bedrock to your company data for fully managed Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). In a previous post, we described how Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock manages the end-to-end […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mani Khanuja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expedite your Genesys Cloud Amazon Lex bot design with the Amazon Lex automated chatbot designer]]></title>
        <id>311ddc9b0ef5e40d77db62247066030996179303</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/expedite-your-genesys-cloud-amazon-lex-bot-design-with-the-amazon-lex-automated-chatbot-designer/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T16:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise of artificial intelligence (AI) has created opportunities to improve the customer experience in the contact center space. Machine learning (ML) technologies continually improve and power the contact center customer experience by providing solutions for capabilities like self-service bots, live call analytics, and post-call analytics. Self-service bots integrated with your call center can help […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Morotti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use RAG for drug discovery with Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>02d55ce0ed6d682c097cf72ca88d094192d2e2e4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/use-rag-for-drug-discovery-with-knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T16:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock provides a broad range of models from Amazon and third-party providers, including Anthropic, AI21, Meta, Cohere, and Stability AI, and covers a wide range of use cases, including text and image generation, embedding, chat, high-level agents with reasoning and orchestration, and more. Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock allows you to build performant and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock personalized experiences powered by AI using Amazon Personalize and Amazon OpenSearch Service]]></title>
        <id>6e979e176f77d9e0b4817ac54dfb1d95e539bb03</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/unlock-personalized-experiences-powered-by-ai-using-amazon-personalize-and-amazon-opensearch-service/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T16:18:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSearch is a scalable, flexible, and extensible open source software suite for search, analytics, security monitoring, and observability applications, licensed under the Apache 2.0 license. Amazon OpenSearch Service is a fully managed service that makes it straightforward to deploy, scale, and operate OpenSearch in the AWS Cloud. OpenSearch uses a probabilistic ranking framework called BM-25 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reagan Rosario</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Amazon SageMaker Pipelines DAG creation]]></title>
        <id>792bd978c3d6421a2aba7932560dd5191458cf42</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/automate-amazon-sagemaker-pipelines-dag-creation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T16:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating scalable and efficient machine learning (ML) pipelines is crucial for streamlining the development, deployment, and management of ML models. In this post, we present a framework for automating the creation of a directed acyclic graph (DAG) for Amazon SageMaker Pipelines based on simple configuration files. The framework code and examples presented here only cover […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Felipe Yepez Barrios</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating large-scale neural network training on CPUs with ThirdAI and AWS Graviton]]></title>
        <id>cb2f8437368ef5aa3f9ac0f21c2600b99cdb9c69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/accelerating-large-scale-neural-network-training-on-cpus-with-thirdai-and-aws-graviton/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T16:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guest post is written by Vihan Lakshman, Tharun Medini, and Anshumali Shrivastava from ThirdAI. Large-scale deep learning has recently produced revolutionary advances in a vast array of fields. Although this stunning progress in artificial intelligence remains remarkable, the financial costs and energy consumption required to train these models has emerged as a critical bottleneck […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vihan Lakshman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge your AI team with Amazon SageMaker Studio: A comprehensive view of Deutsche Bahn’s AI platform transformation]]></title>
        <id>6f1c2ee493f6fea60b44edb50e7dc6278344aeb2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/supercharge-your-ai-team-with-amazon-sagemaker-studio-a-comprehensive-view-of-deutsche-bahns-ai-platform-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T15:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI’s growing influence in large organizations brings crucial challenges in managing AI platforms. These include developing a scalable and operationally efficient platform that adheres to organizational compliance and security standards. Amazon SageMaker Studio offers a comprehensive set of capabilities for machine learning (ML) practitioners and data scientists. These include a fully managed AI development environment […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasanna Tuladhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Architecture Blog Posts of 2023]]></title>
        <id>fc3e2465c18d9acd40d28e1e91cc60659e703e06</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/top-architecture-blog-posts-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T23:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was a rollercoaster year in tech, and we at the AWS Architecture Blog feel so fortunate to have shared in the excitement. As we move into 2024 and all of the new technologies we could see, we want to take a moment to highlight the brightest stars from 2023. As always, thanks to our […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Courtright</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a robust text-to-SQL solution generating complex queries, self-correcting, and querying diverse data sources]]></title>
        <id>9951b5307364aea9a4ac83fd049c25a4ca0ca4b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-robust-text-to-sql-solution-generating-complex-queries-self-correcting-and-querying-diverse-data-sources/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T19:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Structured Query Language (SQL) is a complex language that requires an understanding of databases and metadata. Today, generative AI can enable people without SQL knowledge. This generative AI task is called text-to-SQL, which generates SQL queries from natural language processing (NLP) and converts text into semantically correct SQL. The solution in this post aims to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanjeeb Panda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Axfood enables accelerated machine learning throughout the organization using Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>f8e591eb94398841268b77d312abb6be471c14da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/how-axfood-enables-accelerated-machine-learning-throughout-the-organization-using-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-27T17:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a guest post written by Axfood AB.  In this post, we share how Axfood, a large Swedish food retailer, improved operations and scalability of their existing artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) operations by prototyping in close collaboration with AWS experts and using Amazon SageMaker. Axfood is Sweden’s second largest food retailer, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Björn Blomqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Techniques and approaches for monitoring large language models on AWS]]></title>
        <id>68afc501f9a165633e1169de6be3c618a4bf0854</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/techniques-and-approaches-for-monitoring-large-language-models-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T17:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized the field of natural language processing (NLP), improving tasks such as language translation, text summarization, and sentiment analysis. However, as these models continue to grow in size and complexity, monitoring their performance and behavior has become increasingly challenging. Monitoring the performance and behavior of LLMs is a critical task […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Klein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI code generation works]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T18:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Explore the capabilities and benefits of AI code generation, and how it can improve the developer experience for your enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-22-how-ai-code-generation-works/">How AI code generation works</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline diarization using AI as an assistive technology: ZOO Digital’s story]]></title>
        <id>48523ce5f59200ebb761c7c115a5e7950a20820c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/streamline-diarization-using-ai-as-an-assistive-technology-zoo-digitals-story/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T18:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZOO Digital provides end-to-end localization and media services to adapt original TV and movie content to different languages, regions, and cultures. It makes globalization easier for the world’s best content creators. Trusted by the biggest names in entertainment, ZOO Digital delivers high-quality localization and media services at scale, including dubbing, subtitling, scripting, and compliance. Typical […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ying Hou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for managing Terraform State files in AWS CI/CD Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>ff0f4251002e39256c4600a1ae7afd903c1179d2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/best-practices-for-managing-terraform-state-files-in-aws-ci-cd-pipeline/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T19:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today customers want to reduce manual operations for deploying and maintaining their infrastructure. The recommended method to deploy and manage infrastructure on AWS is to follow Infrastructure-As-Code (IaC) model using tools like AWS CloudFormation, AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) or Terraform. One of the critical components in terraform is managing the state file which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Kumar Selvaraj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run ML inference on unplanned and spiky traffic using Amazon SageMaker multi-model endpoints]]></title>
        <id>51b6988ba0381ba23db50b7059a915cedea6e960</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/run-ml-inference-on-unplanned-and-spiky-traffic-using-amazon-sagemaker-multi-model-endpoints/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T18:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker multi-model endpoints (MMEs) are a fully managed capability of SageMaker inference that allows you to deploy thousands of models on a single endpoint. Previously, MMEs pre-determinedly allocated CPU computing power to models statically regardless the model traffic load, using Multi Model Server (MMS) as its model server. In this post, we discuss a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ram Vegiraju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Amazon Titan models for image generation, editing, and searching]]></title>
        <id>2d741c1e34a52e376dd8edaa0c6895805d83cd7a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/use-amazon-titan-models-for-image-generation-editing-and-searching/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T17:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock provides a broad range of high-performing foundation models from Amazon and other leading AI companies, including Anthropic, AI21, Meta, Cohere, and Stability AI, and covers a wide range of use cases, including text and image generation, searching, chat, reasoning and acting agents, and more. The new Amazon Titan Image Generator model allows content […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohit Mittal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a contextual chatbot application using Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>c8563805502583ca5ce22935a30683ba99a07ec5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/build-a-contextual-chatbot-application-using-knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T16:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern chatbots can serve as digital agents, providing a new avenue for delivering 24/7 customer service and support across many industries. Their popularity stems from the ability to respond to customer inquiries in real time and handle multiple queries simultaneously in different languages. Chatbots also offer valuable data-driven insights into customer behavior while scaling effortlessly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Chugh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Llama 70B is now available in Amazon SageMaker JumpStart]]></title>
        <id>67fe8c9d806efc9b80ab174653c1dae1f40959ed</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/code-llama-70b-is-now-available-in-amazon-sagemaker-jumpstart/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T16:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we are excited to announce that Code Llama foundation models, developed by Meta, are available for customers through Amazon SageMaker JumpStart to deploy with one click for running inference. Code Llama is a state-of-the-art large language model (LLM) capable of generating code and natural language about code from both code and natural language prompts. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kyle Ulrich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detect anomalies in manufacturing data using Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>d0b950b002bda39ea45c96562ac2f6b28d98ce42</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/detect-anomalies-in-manufacturing-data-using-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T15:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the use of cloud computing, big data and machine learning (ML) tools like Amazon Athena or Amazon SageMaker have become available and useable by anyone without much effort in creation and maintenance. Industrial companies increasingly look at data analytics and data-driven decision-making to increase resource efficiency across their entire portfolio, from operations to performing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helge Aufderheide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: January 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T20:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In January, we experienced three incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-github-availability-report-january-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: January 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance Amazon Connect and Lex with generative AI capabilities]]></title>
        <id>540f0e07712c73cd6271ca50eae9c725e862cdeb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/machine-learning/enhance-amazon-connect-and-lex-with-generative-ai-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:43:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective self-service options are becoming increasingly critical for contact centers, but implementing them well presents unique challenges. Amazon Lex provides your Amazon Connect contact center with chatbot functionalities such as automatic speech recognition (ASR) and natural language understanding (NLU) capabilities through voice and text channels. The bot takes natural language speech or text input, recognizes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamza Nadeem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T17:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A peek under the hood of GitHub Advanced Security code scanning autofix.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-14-fixing-security-vulnerabilities-with-ai/">Fixing security vulnerabilities with AI</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T18:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The npm engineering team recently transitioned to using GitHub Codespaces for local development for npm registry services. This shift to Codespaces has substantially reduced the friction of our inner development loop and boosted developer productivity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-13-bringing-npm-registry-services-to-github-codespaces/">Bringing npm registry services to GitHub Codespaces</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodePipeline adds support for Branch-based development and Monorepos]]></title>
        <id>f0f744d1d7cee205fd5ecbcf044e5620aa081fe8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/aws-codepipeline-adds-support-for-branch-based-development-and-monorepos/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T22:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodePipeline is a managed continuous delivery service that automates your release pipelines for application and infrastructure updates. Today, CodePipeline adds triggers and new execution modes to support teams with various delivery strategies. These features give customers more choice in the pipelines they build. In this post, I am going to show you how to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Ohde</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub&#8217;s Engineering Fundamentals program: How we deliver on availability, security, and accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-02-08-githubs-engineering-fundamentals-program-how-we-deliver-on-availability-security-and-accessibility/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-02-08-githubs-engineering-fundamentals-program-how-we-deliver-on-availability-security-and-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T17:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Fundamentals program has helped us address tech debt, improve reliability, and enhance observability of our engineering systems.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-02-08-githubs-engineering-fundamentals-program-how-we-deliver-on-availability-security-and-accessibility/">GitHub&#8217;s Engineering Fundamentals program: How we deliver on availability, security, and accessibility</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>