<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-21T06:30:21.627Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-21T06:30:21.627Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dead End of Liberal American Zionism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323343</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-dead-end-of-liberal-american-zionism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant number of American Jews are now willing to challenge the Zionist project while pointing out that it is inherently fated to suppress the human rights of non-Jews in Palestine. Speaking at a protest near Sen. Chuck Schumer’s home in Brooklyn last month, Naomi Klein said: “We don’t need or want the false idol of Zionism. We want freedom from the project that commits genocide in our name.” More
The post The Dead End of Liberal American Zionism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abba Solomon - Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empire Stumbling Toward Irrelevance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323274</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/empire-stumbling-toward-irrelevance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To a working family “camping” on the street or a homeless single mother, this is what political collapse feels like.  The UK is #1 in homelessness, the USA “leads” the developed world in percentage of its population living on the street.  Meanwhile, endless billions are borrowed and sent abroad to senselessly genocide millions.  These sure signs of Imperialist decline can’t be ignored forever.    More
The post Empire Stumbling Toward Irrelevance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High Noon at LA’s City Council]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323374</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/high-noon-at-las-city-council/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the classic 1952 Western High Noon, Katy Jurado portrays Helen Ramirez, former lover of Will Kane (Gary Cooper), the outnumbered, embattled Marshal at Hadleyville, who is being menaced by a looming shootout with a gang of gunslingers. Ramirez confronts Will’s newlywed, Amy Fowler (Grace Kelly), telling the bride that she should pick up a  More
The post High Noon at LA’s City Council appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Race to End Fossil Fuel Production]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323175</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-race-to-end-fossil-fuel-production/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given all this Green rhetoric and crude (oil) action, it’s hard to find examples around the world where people are actually doing something to end fossil fuel production. One of those places is Ecuador, which held a referendum last August about keeping oil under the ground of a certain plot of land in the Yasuní national park. “Yasuní is the most important park in Ecuador,” observes Esperanza Martínez, of Acción Ecológica in Ecuador. “It has been recognized as the most biodiverse region in the world, and it’s also home to many indigenous peoples.” More
The post The Race to End Fossil Fuel Production appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black MAGA Is Still MAGA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323381</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/black-maga-is-still-maga/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:57:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Consider Donald Trump to be in a racial bind when it comes to election 2024. After all, he needs Black voters to at least defect from Joe Biden in swing states, if not actually vote for him. Yet, more than ever, he also needs his white nationalist base to believe that a second Trump term  More
The post Black MAGA Is Still MAGA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power, or the Purpose of the Police]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323408</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/power-or-the-purpose-of-the-police/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What can we gain from a better understanding of the police as an American institution? A new documentary digs deep into the history, philosophy, and legality of US policing, tying historical injustices to the contemporary use and abuse of state violence. Following much praise for Power at Sundance and CPH:DOX earlier this year, Oscar-nominated director Yance Ford (Strong Island) brings his  More
The post Power, or the Purpose of the Police appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francis Brodsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Solidarity Triumphs Over Corporate Greed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323409</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/how-solidarity-triumphs-over-corporate-greed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Management at Amfuel tried to bully Jo Tucker and her 200 co-workers—most of them Black women, a number of them single moms—into accepting dozens of unnecessary concessions in a new contract. For four years, however, the manufacturing workers in Magnolia, Arkansas remained strong and resolute as the company tried to break the union and wear them  More
The post How Solidarity Triumphs Over Corporate Greed appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave McCall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Big Business of Obesity and Shame]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323412</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-big-business-of-obesity-and-shame/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturers of new weight loss drugs are salivating at the prospect of profit. What Americans eat, how they diet and exercise, the sugar content of their sodas, and the high fructose corn syrup in their processed foods have long been objects of endless gambling on Wall Street. Now, with drugs like Mounjaro, Wegovy, and Ozempic,  More
The post The Big Business of Obesity and Shame appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Affordable Rental Housing Policy Either Doesn’t Make Any Sense or Is Working as Intended]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323146</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/us-affordable-rental-housing-policy-either-doesnt-make-any-sense-or-is-working-as-intended/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:36:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Affordable rental housing policy fails to provide sufficient affordable rental housing decade after decade, yet policymakers continue to do largely the same things. A researcher at the Joint Center for Housing Studies recently observed that in 1960, about 45 percent of renters in the bottom income quintile spent more than 50 percent of their income  More
The post US Affordable Rental Housing Policy Either Doesn’t Make Any Sense or Is Working as Intended appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Assault on the Wages of American Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323379</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/donald-trumps-assault-on-the-wages-of-american-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although Donald Trump, as president, proclaimed in his 2020 State of the Union address that he had produced a “blue-collar boom” in workers’ wages, the reality was quite different. Using his control of the executive branch of the U.S. government, Trump repeatedly undermined the wages of American workers by blocking raises and imposing wage reductions.  More
The post Donald Trump’s Assault on the Wages of American Workers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Wittner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Liar Puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323418</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/the-liar-puzzle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T05:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember those language puzzles that used to stump us in our school days. that grow out of the human ability to say things that are not true? They come in many forms, some complex, some simple. Among the more complex, there was The Evil Emperor. Evil Emperor: Make a statement about anything.  If it’s true  More
The post The Liar Puzzle appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Douglas Lummis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From South Africa to Israel, the Greek State Has Always Had a Soft Spot for Apartheid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323174</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/21/from-south-africa-to-israel-the-greek-state-has-always-had-a-soft-spot-for-apartheid/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T04:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If some people think they can repeat what they’ve seen in other countries and occupy universities, pitch tents and make a mess, they’re deeply mistaken”. This – so eminently delicate – statement by the Greek Prime Minister, which followed the brutal “evacuation” of the law faculty on Tuesday May 14 (28 arrests), can only surprise  More
The post From South Africa to Israel, the Greek State Has Always Had a Soft Spot for Apartheid appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coal Still Powers More U.S. Electricity Than Any Renewable Energy Source]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271961</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/coal-still-powers-more-u-s-electricity-than-any-renewable-energy-source.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T04:44:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why coal's share of US energy output has not fallen as far as the ecologically-minded had hoped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The health benefits of giving up drinking coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/health-benefits-giving-up-drinking-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with many things we consume, the science on coffee can be conflicted. One decade caffeine consumption is a no-no, the next it seems coffee is quite beneficial. Regular readers will know I’m a coffee drinker, but in — what I consider to be — moderation: two (large serve) cups per day. But some people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271932</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics, wastewater data debacle as Bionbot ends its wasterwater visualization, Michael Cohen stole $30,000 from Trump, interviews with Kennedy voters, small beer ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;A Reprieve for Assange&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-reprieve-for-assange"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T17:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Journalism as ‘espionage’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup – Application Load Balancer IPv6, Amazon S3 pricing update, Amazon EC2 Flex instances, and more (May 20, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3ec4a6e752f974d277f95d9da7228e9f5bba4ba4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-application-load-balancer-ipv6-amazon-s3-pricing-update-amazon-ec2-flex-instances-and-more-may-20-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit season is in full swing around the world, with last week’s events in Bengaluru, Berlin, and  Seoul, where my blog colleague Channy delivered one of the keynotes. Last week’s launches Here are some launches that got my attention: Amazon S3 will no longer charge for several HTTP error codes – A customer reported […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the ICC’s Announcement of Arrest Warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant and Hamas’ Leadership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323355</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/on-the-iccs-announcement-of-arrest-warrants-for-netanyahu-gallant-and-hamas-leadership/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decision to announce these applications for arrest warrants prior to their formal approval may have been motivated by a sense that the conditions under which the people of Gaza are striving to survive are deteriorating so rapidly and horrifically that there is no time to waste and by a hope that announcing the applications now might have a positive impact on the decisions of relevant decision-makers for whom arrest warrants are not yet being sought but could be sought later. More
The post On the ICC’s Announcement of Arrest Warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant and Hamas’ Leadership appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Whitbeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Disruptions Have Eased, But Remain a Concern]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30028</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/supply-chain-disruptions-have-eased-but-remain-a-concern/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supply chain disruptions became a major headache for businesses in the aftermath of the pandemic. Indeed, in October 2021, nearly all firms in our regional business surveys reported at least some difficulty obtaining the supplies they needed. These supply chain disruptions were a key contributor to the surge in inflation that occurred as the economy recovered from the pandemic recession. In this post, we present new measures of supply availability from our Business Leaders Survey and Empire State Manufacturing Survey that closely track the New York Fed’s Global Supply Chain Pressure Index (GSCPI). We will begin publishing these data on a monthly basis starting in June. These indexes indicate that supply availability had generally been improving since early 2023, but over the past couple of months, improvement has stalled. This trend is concerning since our May Supplemental Survey indicates that between a third and a half of businesses in the region are experiencing difficulties obtaining supplies, and many are reducing operations and raising prices to compensate, though to a lesser extent than a few years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel and Richard Deitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel Godfrey Wood: &ldquo;Battle Machine&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/battle-machine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T11:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retrospectives on Podemos.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271903</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our buzzy daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review: The Untapped Knowledge of Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271919</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/book-review-the-untapped-knowledge-of-animals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:50:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In “The Internet of Animals,” Martin Wikelski highlights what insights humans can learn from creatures great and small.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Trade Desperation: Trump Insider Robert Lightheizer Recommends Third-World Capital Controls to Achieve Balanced Trade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271901</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/us-trade-desperation-trump-insider-robert-lightheizer-recommends-third-world-capital-controls-to-achieve-balanced-trade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New desperate ideas to fix chronic US trade imbalances, like capital controls, are getting a hearing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assassination Attempt on Slovak PM Highlights Dangers of Constant EU Demonization of Project Ukraine Opponents and Hypocrisy of ‘Misinformation’ Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271777</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/wheres-the-uproar-over-corporate-medias-history-of-spreading-hate-and-misinformation-about-slovak-pm-who-just-survived-assassination-attempt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T07:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will there be any self reflection among mainstream media and Atlanticist politicians for relentlessly going after Slovakian PM for the crime of opposing Project Ukraine while also silencing counter arguments? Don't hold your breath.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UMass Arrests: What Would Daniel Ellsberg Do?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323145</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/umass-arrests-what-would-daniel-ellsberg-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been a history professor at the University of Massachusetts, Amherst for twenty years. On May 7, I was one of a handful of faculty members arrested for standing in support of hundreds of students who were engaged in nonviolent protest of university complicity in the ongoing slaughter and suffering of Palestinians in Gaza. They want the school to divest from companies profiting from the carnage. More
The post UMass Arrests: What Would Daniel Ellsberg Do? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian G. Appy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323147</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/why-corporations-choose-lawlessness-to-fight-unions/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers in Towson, Maryland, have earned the distinction of becoming the first Apple retail workers in the nation to vote to strike over failed union negotiations with their employer. The approximately 100 Apple workers were also the first in the nation to successfully form a union. They did so in 2022, as the Coalition of Organized Retail Employees (CORE), joining the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM). Two-thirds of the store’s workers voted to join the union, a resounding success at a company that has long staved off union activity. More
The post Why Corporations Choose Lawlessness to Fight Unions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Toughest Job Today’s Richest Ever Face?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/the-toughest-job-todays-richest-ever-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York currently hosts, researchers at the London-based Henley & Partners have just reported, more centi-millionaires than any other city on Earth. And if hosting centi-millionaires ever became an Olympic sport, the Henley stats show, the USA would be bringing home gold, silver, and bronze. The San Francisco Bay Area — now teeming with 675 centi-millionaires — rates as the world’s second-most-popular home to fortunes worth over $100 million. Los Angeles sits third with 496. More
The post The Toughest Job Today’s Richest Ever Face? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Procter & Gamble, Mondelēz, and Nestlé Are Among 10 of the Leading Consumer Brands Driving Global Deforestation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323295</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/procter-gamble-mondelez-and-nestle-are-among-10-of-the-leading-consumer-brands-driving-global-deforestation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the turn of the century, there has been a consistent average annual loss of 3 to 4 million hectares (7.4 to 9.9 million acres) of tropical forest globally. This puts us far from reaching the goal of zero deforestation by 2030, a target embraced in 2021 by 145 countries during the COP26 climate summit in Glasgow. Besides  More
The post Procter & Gamble, Mondelēz, and Nestlé Are Among 10 of the Leading Consumer Brands Driving Global Deforestation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Laurel Sutherlin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bluelining Leaves Climate Vulnerable Communities Without Home Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323312</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/how-bluelining-leaves-climate-vulnerable-communities-without-home-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era of climate disasters, Americans in vulnerable regions will need to rely more than ever on their home insurance. But as floods, wildfires, and severe storms become more common, a troubling practice known as “bluelining” threatens to leave many communities unable to afford insurance — or obtain it at any price. Bluelining is  More
The post How Bluelining Leaves Climate Vulnerable Communities Without Home Insurance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Garcia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promising the Impossible: Blinken’s Out of Tune Performance in Kyiv]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323293</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/promising-the-impossible-blinkens-out-of-tune-performance-in-kyiv/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Things are looking dire for the Ukrainian war effort.  Promises of victory are becoming even hollower than they were last summer, when US President Joe Biden could state with breathtaking obliviousness that Russia had “already lost the war”.   The worst offender in this regard remains the United States, which has been the most vocal proponent of fanciful victory over  More
The post Promising the Impossible: Blinken’s Out of Tune Performance in Kyiv appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statement of ICC Prosecutor Karim A.A. Khan KC: Applications for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323359</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/statement-of-icc-prosecutor-karim-a-a-khan-kc-applications-for-arrest-warrants-in-the-situation-in-the-state-of-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ICC Prosecutor Khan on application for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine Today I am filing applications for warrants of arrest before Pre-Trial Chamber I of the International Criminal Court in the Situation in the State of Palestine. Yahya Sinwar, Mohammed Diab Ibrahim Al-Masri (Deif), Ismail Haniyeh On the basis of  More
The post Statement of ICC Prosecutor Karim A.A. Khan KC: Applications for arrest warrants in the situation in the State of Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yuval Noah Harari’s Odyssey into a Parallel Zionist Universe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323162</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/yuval-noah-hararis-odyssey-into-a-parallel-zionist-universe/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the vast expanse of the intellectual cosmos, there exists a luminary whose brilliance outshines even the brightest stars. Professor Yuval Noah Harari, a name whispered with reverence among the learned denizens of the galaxy, is a beacon of knowledge, whose canon traverses the celestial planes of history, philosophy, human psychology and beyond. Informed by  More
The post Yuval Noah Harari’s Odyssey into a Parallel Zionist Universe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tapping Into the Vast Safety Potential of “Loss Prevention” by the Insurance Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323160</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/tapping-into-the-vast-safety-potential-of-loss-prevention-by-the-insurance-industry/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent newspaper article reports that GEICO, one of the largest auto insurers in the U.S., has amassed a staggering $189 billion in cash, apart from the reserves required by law to insure the volume of potential claims by its policyholders. Angry consumers have cried out about auto insurance premiums going up as the prices  More
The post Tapping Into the Vast Safety Potential of “Loss Prevention” by the Insurance Industry appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Eat the Fish: The Astounding Failure of Our Regulatory Agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323258</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/dont-eat-the-fish-the-astounding-failure-of-our-regulatory-agencies/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when state and federal agencies refuse to adequately regulate industries and activities that produce pollution and release it into the environment?  Well, as reported by the Daily Montanan, a recent study by the Department of Fish, Wildlife and Parks has found the Clark Fork, Bitterroot and Blackfoot Rivers to be much more polluted with highly  More
The post Don’t Eat the Fish: The Astounding Failure of Our Regulatory Agencies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preying on White Fears Worked for Georgia’s Lester Maddox in the ’60s and is Working There for Trump Today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323144</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/preying-on-white-fears-worked-for-georgias-lester-maddox-in-the-60s-and-is-working-there-for-trump-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 1967, after a gubernatorial election that saw neither candidate gain enough votes to win, the Georgia Legislature was faced with a vital decision: the selection of the state’s 75th governor during the height of the Civil Rights Movement. Legislators chose the candidate who earned the least number of votes and was an ardent  More
The post Preying on White Fears Worked for Georgia’s Lester Maddox in the ’60s and is Working There for Trump Today appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Cason</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renting Your Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271870</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/renting-your-life.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T04:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More on the further erosion of ownership and property rights via required renting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Package Deal Full of Holes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323276</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/20/a-package-deal-full-of-holes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T04:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Biden administration has been working on a package deal with Saudi Arabia that would guarantee a path to a Palestinian state in return for a permanent cease-fire and establishment of Saudi-Israel relations. But the Saudis want more for themselves: a U.S.-Saudi mutual defense pact and cooperation on a civilian nuclear program in the kingdom.  More
The post A Package Deal Full of Holes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSGE models — a total waste of time]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45375</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/20/dsge-models-a-total-waste-of-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll While one can understand that some of the elements in DSGE models seem to appeal to Keynesians at first sight, after closer examination, these models are in fundamental contradiction to Post-Keynesian and even traditional Keynesian thinking. The DSGE model is a model in which output is determined in the labour market as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Completing the largest migration in Kubernetes history]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/20/completing-cloud-provider-migration/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since as early as Kubernetes v1.7, the Kubernetes project has pursued the ambitious goal of removing built-in cloud provider integrations (KEP-2395).
While these integrations were instrumental in Kubernetes' early development and growth, their removal was driven by two key factors:
the growing complexity of maintaining native support for every cloud provider across millions of lines of Go code, and the desire to establish
Kubernetes as a truly vendor-neutral platform.
After many releases, we're thrilled to announce that all cloud provider integrations have been successfully migrated from the core Kubernetes repository to external plugins.
In addition to achieving our initial objectives, we've also significantly streamlined Kubernetes by removing roughly 1.5 million lines of code and reduci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What has happened to cover versions of popular songs?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7624</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-happened-cover-versions-popular-songs/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, Australian radio station Triple J, invites a band or musician to record a cover of a song, for their Like A Version show. Anything goes here. About two years ago, Sydney based Australian DJ Dave Winnel performed a cover of Africa, by Toto, not the sort of music you’d usually hear on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Word of the Day: Don’t Say “Covid Pandemic.” Say “Covid Syndemic”!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271878</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/word-of-the-day-dont-say-covid-pandemic-say-covid-syndemic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T20:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["'Tis a mystery," except not!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World, I guess?]]></title>
        <id>https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/</id>
        <link href="https://meineeds.rest/hello-world-i-guess/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T16:28:15.910Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okay... exhales
Here we go.
Hi, I'm Meï ! And welcome to this blog. Or this attempt at a blog.
It's been a few weeks since I felt a lot of nostalgia for the Internet of old, the one I discovered as a lil' kid, on my tenth birthday, circa 2007.
A friend, Seeker, began working on his own blog a few months back. I really liked his articles about DIY and Game Dev, and on a whim asked him his tech stack with the intent of setting something up for myself.
I used to write quite a bit a few years ago. Especially when I got to the big city after high school. Welcome to Fucktopia1 was a small series detailing my new life far from the countryside.
As of late, I've been trying to get back into writing. Essays to recommend some games, some small fictions, and lore for TTRPGs, I've been slowly but surely getting back into it. But I didn't really manage to find a public, even for the essays in places (well, Discord servers in this case) dedicated to the exact IP I was trying to promote.
This built up as a bit of frustration, and is another of the reasons I felt like doing a blog. I wanted to be more open to the world, able to write in a place anyone could read if they stumble on the place.
So once again, here we go!
1. As a note, the "Fucktopia" is a reference to Souillon's comic book "Hello Fucktopia". Couldn't find a listing in English, sorry! It's available in French & Spanish, at least..
My small rules of writing
Try to write regularly. Not necessarily everyday, but I should strive for a post per week at least.
Focus! I'm super prone to tangents and often stray off-topic. A post should be on a single subject, unless this is a post consciously made for tangents and chaos.
No stressing over this. I already stress over too much, let's keep this place as my comfy Internet place.
Let's hope it goes well. And I hope you'll enjoy this blog and its topics.
Fan-art of Cyberpunk Bartender Action: VA-11 HALL-A, by rnna_7]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271855</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T10:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our stellar daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why One New York Health System Stopped Suing Its Patients]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271867</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/why-one-new-york-health-system-stopped-suing-its-patients.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T10:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American hospital officials often insist that lawsuits and other aggressive collections, though unsavory, are necessary to protect health systems’ finances and deter freeloading. But at Rochester Regional, ditching these collection tactics hasn’t hurt the bottom line.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Pézenas]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52709</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/19/sunday-photoblogging-pezenas-5/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T07:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fallen Angel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322548</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/19/fallen-angel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[llustration from the frontispiece of the 1831 edition of Mary Shelley’s Frankenstein by Theodor Von Holst. Public Domain.
When I was a young child, I would sometimes stay a weekend in the summer holidays with my cousins – who were of a similar age – on their farm.   I grew up in north London: all concrete and cars, and fumes and arcades, and long black railings and grey school playgrounds, and rising tower blocks and rushing roads.   Looking back, the farm of my uncle and aunt couldn’t have been more than a thirty- or forty-minute drive from where I lived in the city; the farm itself was situated only a few fields away from the motorway you would need to traverse to get there. Hardly the back and beyond.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Fallen Angel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Great Resignation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321754</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/19/the-great-resignation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T05:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Jon Tyson.
I am beyond tired of writing and reading about Trump, his minions Stephen Miller and Steve Bannon, and the evils they plan to inflict upon the world. Reading or watching the news is a daily exercise in dread, self-torment, and exhaustion. The return of spring notwithstanding, things are grim these days. The Trumpist menace seems of a piece with a far-right axis on the march in India, Russia, Israel, China, and Hungary. Of course, it’s futile to wring one’s hands and lament Trumpian aspirations to authoritarianism without taking concrete action to prevent them. Yet despite nearly eight years of experience confronting the Trumpian specter, the answer to the traditional, eminently practical leftist question “What is to be done?” remains elusive, and the sense of burnout and political defeat—with the concomitant, complicated welter of emotions —is a specter difficult to vanquish.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Great Resignation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Remer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart Generalist]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/smart-generalist/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bear in a circus is interesting. So is a juggler and a man on the unicycle. A bear on a unicycle juggling swords on the other hand is something extremely unique. Something you would pay good money to see. A smart generalist is kinda like that.
A smart generalist is a person who is 80/20 across multiple fields. This means they have reached 80 Percent understanding/capability across multiple fields leveraging around 20 percent of the effort that would typically be needed to fully master it. It makes them unique.
The primary skill of a smart generalist is the ability to get from 0 to 80 in a new field quickly. They can quickly identify high ROI leverage points of a subject. It is a learned skill. They also have strong convictions that anything can be learned and learned fast. Even things considered 'tough' by society.
On the other hand, we have the cracked specialists. People really good at one thing. Getting to the frontiers and advancing human knowledge. Creating absolutely beautiful works in that 'one thing'.
It is a sliding scale. We all lie somewhere between a specialist and a generalist. But we could all do some good to realise we are not limited. We can do multiple things if we want to. It is easy to be hemmed in. To define your identity as 'Software Engineer' or 'Writer' or 'XYZ'. That is what school teaches -'Specialisation'. But humans are versatile. We are the OG general intelligence. Capable of adapting and doing multiple things.
Don't forget the 'General' in General Intelligence.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The War on Humanitarians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=323013</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/18/the-war-on-humanitarians/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T14:38:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ilan Pappé is 70 years old. He’s Jewish. His parents fled persecution in Hitler’s Germany. He’s an Israeli and served in the IDF. He hasn’t been radicalized by TikTok. He is, in fact, one of Israel’s most celebrated historians. None of that stopped Pappé from being detained by Biden’s TSA in Detroit, interrogated by the agents from the Department of Homeland Security about whether he’s a supporter of Hamas, and having his phone data copied. This crackdown isn’t about protecting Jews or  Israelis or preserving the exceptional nature of the Holocaust.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The War on Humanitarians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To my Sunflower]]></title>
        <id>https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/</id>
        <link href="https://lvrz.org/to-my-sunflower-i/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:26:07.405Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little bird came to see me,
What’s you name? - I asked.
And he chirped the following words:
Leave a comment or Stay in touch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what makes for a good video essay?]]></title>
        <id>https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/what-makes-for-a-good-video-essay/</id>
        <link href="https://itskristin.bearblog.dev/what-makes-for-a-good-video-essay/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T19:46:01.832Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i've been a long-time fan of video essays for a while now, my first watches of the medium date back to my freshman year of high school with videos like Born Sexy Yesterday by Pop Culture Detective and Whiplash vs. Black Swan -- The Anatomy of the Obsessed Artist. I recall posting the links to these on my twitter and tumblr raving about how good and eye-opening they are, recommending them to my friends and mutuals, and soon thereafter reading their thoughts about the essays too. video essays became a sort of internet cultural phenomenon around this time, spurred on by those very videos, the former now holding 11 million views and the former with just a bit under 6 million. but what is so captivating about these videos? what about a video can make millions not only tune in for the first time…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[don't skip the openings]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/dont-skip-the-openings/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:35:12.065Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[the absolute worst thing someone can tell me about their anime viewing preferences has nothing to do with the kind of show they watch but how they watch it.
image from director nakayama ryū's chainsaw man (2022).
skipping openings just because you're on a binge can so easily rob you of what i'd argue are the best narrative and collective highs a series can offer.1
from a purely functional standpoint, they give us time to breathe and process what exactly we're watching. take, for example, the three versions of shippuden's penultimate opening— blood circulator. each variant denotes which point of the story you're at, and primes you for what's to come. (if you pay attention, you'll notice they lead into each other seamlessly! so neat.)
sometimes it's instinctual and more about building antici…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[traversing across a rainbow bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/rainbow-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T15:27:15.392Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[we lost our second dog today.
sherlock, my aunt’s darling boy, passed at 4:20 in the morning. at 3am, she knocked on my door saying the fateful words—i think sherlock’s dying. it was like my whole world came to a stop.
he died in her arms.
10 and a half beautiful years of his company. our kind, kind sherlock who sometimes snapped at us when we kissed him too much. our darling, darling boy who was great at finding toys we’d hide from him; who liked to eat the cheese crackers my grandma fed him when no one was looking.
he had chronic heart failure. we were counting down the months, really, but nothing could’ve ever prepared me for that 3am knock, his fading heartbeat, and his little eyes that wouldn’t close.
ten years ago today, my aunt’s dog quli—a botched attempt of naming him 去来, a dog wh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[even the dustiest of streets has a place in memory]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-china-last-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:09:35.956Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today is our last day at the grandparents’ house. Tomorrow we take a taxi to the city we flew into and we’ll spend the day and night there before departing in the morning.
Mom is in her parents’ bedroom with Grandma and Grandpa. She’s sharing photos of us to Grandma and showing her how to download them to her tablet. I laugh as Mom gets frustrated with Grandma’s technological ineptitude. It’s her turn to teach technology to a Boomer.
Earlier I mustered up the courage to wander a little further from home than normal. I walked all the way to the train station and park in the center of town. I’m glad I did, because I saw a lot of things I hadn’t before.
As the sun dips below the horizon vendors set up tables in front of the supermarket. They sell a wide assortment of wares. Cages with corgis,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Zerzan - He Means it — Do you?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-zerzan-he-means-it-do-you?v=1715942581"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Zerzan
Title: He Means it — Do you?
Date: 2002
Source: Retrieved on May 2024 from archive.org

 Today opposition is anarchist or it is non-existent. This is the barest minimum coherence in the struggle against an engulfing totality. 
 And while ten years ago the milieu generally called anti-authoritarian was largely syndicalist, those leftist residues are fading out altogether. Very few now find a vista of work and production at all liberatory. 
 As the smell of this false and rotting order rises to the heavens, registering an unprecedented toll on all living beings, faith in the whole modern world evaporates. Industrialism and its ensemble looks like it has been a very bad idea, sort of a wrong turn begun still earlier. Civilization itself, with its logic of domestication and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[re: the fear of audience expectations, by gabby]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/fear-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:07:27.208Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This open letter is inspired by a post I read yesterday by Gabby of woolgathering fame.)
Dear Gabby,
It’s not just you: getting over the fear of expectations is hard. I still struggle with it, after 300 something posts. I have a feeling I’ll never get completely over it, but here’s what’s helped me so far.
Posting a lot helps. I’ve posted so much nonsense on this blog that these days there’s not much I can do that will be worse than something I’ve written before. Somehow, I still have regular readers. Realizing that there are people out there still interested in what I have to say after all the good and not so good is a great comfort. From what you write, you seem to have discovered as much.
Another perk of having a large body of work is that each new piece you create becomes a smaller and smaller part of your entire oeuvre. When you’re first starting out, it feels like each creation you put out defines you. After all, if you only have one post, it’s the only thing people can judge you on. If you have a hundred, a wayward post is a drop in the bucket.
That said, wouldn’t you still want to see the creations your friends or favorite creators aren’t proud of? Or see their art even if it doesn’t quite fit the niche they’ve carved out for themselves? Everybody half-asses things in their own unique way. There’s a beauty in doing things imperfectly, too.
All that is to say, keep up what you’re doing. Creative inertia is a very real thing. You’re doing the right thing by posting, even if you feel like you’re just posting to break the streak of inactivity. Writing in any form begets more writing.
Anyway, welcome back to Bear! It’s good to have you back.
Yours,
misu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Jews be Nazis?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322714</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/can-jews-be-nazis/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many people, the question is inflammatory. The crimes of the German Nazis were of such magnitude that comparison with any other historical violence is invidious. The genocide of the Jews was deliberate and methodical and intended to eliminate every last one. The goal was the same with the Romani and Sinti people. By comparison, the Israelis – currently accused of genocide -- are rank amateurs. They have so far killed some 35,000 Palestinians in Gaza out of a population of 2.3 million. More
The post Can Jews be Nazis? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follow the Missiles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322850</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/17/follow-the-missiles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, the Biden administration has approved more than 100 Foreign Military Sales arms transfers to Israel. Two of the shipments used an emergency authority to circumvent Congressional review. The surge of weapons transfers to Israel began in early October and so much material was being shipped that the Pentagon had a difficult time finding enough cargo aircraft to deliver them. More
The post Follow the Missiles appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lily Lynch: &ldquo;Crosshairs&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/crosshairs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The shooting of Robert Fico.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Kubernetes workload isolation and security using Kata Containers]]></title>
        <id>f2c6d73c0a99a5e7cc62d68bc9a22528e5bead29</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/enhancing-kubernetes-workload-isolation-and-security-using-kata-containers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have become the dominant method for deploying and managing applications in recent years. Their widespread adoption is attributed to numerous advantages, such as isolation, efficient hardware use, scalability, and portability. In situations where resource isolation is critical for system security, many users are forced to rely on virtual machines (VMs) to mitigate the impact […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mirash Gjolaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye: Revolutionizing HD map creation for autonomous vehicles with Spark on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>ef56de61f8631e9846e056ddafcc46ba422f73dd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/mobileye-revolutionizing-hd-map-creation-for-autonomous-vehicles-with-spark-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobileye (Nasdaq: MBLY), a global leader in advanced driver-assistance systems (ADAS), is at the forefront of the autonomous driving revolution. Founded in 1999, they have pioneered groundbreaking technologies such as REM™ crowdsourced mapping, True-Redundancy™ sensing, and Responsibility-Sensitive Safety (RSS). These innovations are paving the way for a future filled with self-driving vehicles and advanced mobility […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bentzi Lifshitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RSS is really simple, why do so many find it complicated?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7606</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/rss-really-simple-why-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris, writing at uncountable thoughts: RSS is a pervasive, but little known, web technology that allows you aggregate all your content into one place for easy reading. There are very few websites without an RSS feed, although many don’t advertise the link (or, even realise they have it). When you put an RSS feed link […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost opportunities?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45372</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/16/lost-opportunities/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T19:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford A pile of bricks is not a house.  A group of individuals is not an economy. A lot has to happen between the one and the other.  Which is why writing theories about economies as if it were simply an accumulation of individuals and their associated capital base misses the mark.  Nor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[158. Compounding heartbreaks and unsent love letters]]></title>
        <id>https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/</id>
        <link href="https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/compounding-heartbreaks-and-unsent-love-letters-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:23:05.119Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think one of the biggest reasons why I was utterly pissed off at the dude for ditching me was all of that  built-up anticipation, only to be disappointed at the very end. I had this really big expectation, but I think I really shouldn't count on people too much. In my mind, I hadn't had a little trip in a while, and having that cool rendezvous experience with a cute guy? I was so keen.
I can't believe that I made plans with someone, looked forward to our weekend getaway, only to find out he's changed his plans without a word and flew off somewhere instead. It completely left me feeling confused and downright pissed off. I didn't think I deserved to be left hanging like that and to not have an in-person apology. I haven't even seen him ever since we went to the museum together 1 2.

I sai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Stable Diffusion ComfyUI on AWS elastically and efficiently]]></title>
        <id>dcd98043e309fb462fb16c1c99293fceecad41fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/deploy-stable-diffusion-comfyui-on-aws-elastically-and-efficiently/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction ComfyUI is an open-source node-based workflow solution for Stable Diffusion. It offers the following advantages: Significant performance optimization for SDXL model inference High customizability, allowing users granular control Portable workflows that can be shared easily Developer-friendly Due to these advantages, ComfyUI is increasingly being used by artistic creators. In this post, we will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Recent Inflationary Spike a Global Phenomenon?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29961</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/is-the-recent-inflationary-spike-a-global-phenomenon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, inflation rose almost simultaneously in most economies around the world. After peaking in mid-2022, inflation then went into decline—a fall that was just as universal as the initial rise. In this post, we explore the interrelation of inflation dynamics across OECD countries by constructing a measure of the persistence of global inflation. We then study the extent to which the persistence of global inflation reflects broad-based swings, as opposed to idiosyncratic country-level movements. Our main finding is that the spike and subsequent moderation in global inflation in the post-pandemic period were driven by persistent movements. When we look at measures of inflation that include food and energy prices, most of the persistence appears to be broad-based, suggesting that international oil and commodity prices played an important role in global inflation dynamics. Excluding food and energy prices in the analysis still shows a broad-based persistence, although with a substantial increase in the role of country-specific factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martín Almuzara, Babur Kocaoglu, and Argia Sbordone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;A Bronx Tale&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperativism in New York.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - Thomas Paine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-thomas-paine?v=1715846977</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-thomas-paine?v=1715846977"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:09:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: Thomas Paine
Date: February 6, 1890
Notes: Delivered on February 2, 1890 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century February 6, 1890. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Thomas Paine is one of the most maligned and least understood of men. One of the noblest minded of men in most respects, he has been represented for nearly a century as a groveling nature and a monster of iniquity. Supremely generous in all his public career, he is said to have been mean and self-seeking. Having refused to profit by the copyright of his religious and political works, he is called parsimonious. A rarely equaled friend of mankind, he is scorned as the enem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - The Sins of Government]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-the-sins-of-government?v=1715846855</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-the-sins-of-government?v=1715846855"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: The Sins of Government
Date: March 13, 1890
Notes: Delivered on March 9, 1890 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on March 13, 1890. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 I am aware that in delivering a number of addresses with the object of persuading you that government by physical force is the real cause of poverty and the slowness of human development mentally and morally, I am opposing preconceived opinions, prejudices and superstitions even stronger than are aroused by open declarations of Atheism. Political superstition is more deeply rooted than religious superstition. Multitudes of persons have ceased to believe in Jehovah …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - ​First Anniversary Address]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-first-anniversary-address?v=1715846738</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-first-anniversary-address?v=1715846738"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: ​First Anniversary Address
Date: January 10, 1889
Notes: Delivered on January 6, 1889 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on January 10, 1889.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Unity Congregation has completed its first year of existence and, I hope, of usefulness. As we look back on that year I think we shall agree that it has been a year of peace and prosperity for which we should be profoundly grateful. Our career thus far has exceeded my most sanguine expectations. The congregation shave been large and enthusiastic, probably averaging during the year nearly two thousand persons in the three cities where our meetings have been held each Sunday.[1] They have come tog…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Owen Pentecost - Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-anarchism?v=1715846565</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/hugh-owen-pentecost-anarchism?v=1715846565"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Hugh Owen Pentecost
Title: Anarchism
Date: July 4, 1889
Notes: Delivered on June 30, 1889 to the Unity Congregation at Newark, Brooklyn, and Manhattan. Published in Twentieth Century on July 4, 1889. Edited and annotated by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Good people who hold opinions not commonly understood generally have a bad name. The world is ready to believe almost anything of a man except that he is a genuinely good man. If his life is stainless but unconventional, the world suspects some hidden shame or base motive. So far are most people from understanding or desiring what is true and right that the highest truth is often believed to be the lowest lie, and the purest right is looked upon as the blackest wrong. 
 Thus Jesus,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Hugh Owen Pentecost (1848–1907)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-hugh-owen-pentecost-1848-1907?v=1715846400</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-hugh-owen-pentecost-1848-1907?v=1715846400"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Hugh Owen Pentecost (1848–1907)
Subtitle: A Biographical Sketch
Source: Retrieved on 16th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 Because he changed into so many different suits during his long career, historians have not focused on the dashing radical orator Hugh O. Pentecost. 
 Born September 30, 1848 at New Harmony, Indiana, Pentecost was given his middle name for Robert Owen, whose followers had established the town as a Fourierist colony a generation earlier. His parents, Emma Flower and Hugh Lockett Pentecost, were of English descent, with many Protestant clergy in their family tree. Hugh moved at age two to Albion, Illinois, which was founded by his grandfather, Scarborough Pentecost, Jr. 
 Hugh went as a boy to Kentucky during the Civil War, where he …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[catching up]]></title>
        <id>https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/</id>
        <link href="https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:28:05.926Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[woah, hello bear! it sure has been a while since i've last written.
a little bit after my last post, i went on some back-to-back trips around asia. i spent a few days in seoul and about a week in bali. i did actually write about both of those trips with the intention of sharing them with all of you on here but for some reason i couldn't quite bring myself to publish it. i've never really written on any sort of platform before this, but i'm assuming that just like visual art, some writing is just meant to be kept to yourself.
with the only things i had written in that span of 4 weeks being private, i didn't really have much else to post. and the longer i went without posting, the harder it was to come back. this always happens to me. it was the exact same mindset i had with my art account o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Code to Quill: Embark on a Legendary Kubernetes Quest with SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've likely heard the adage, "Contributing isn't just about writing code",
whispered in forums or seen etched into the digital walls of open source communities.
But what depth of truth lies within this ancient wisdom, especially in the vast,
evolving world of Kubernetes?
Today, contributing to open source extends far beyond the realm of coding.
It's an inclusive journey that welcomes the diverse skills of all who wish
to be a part of it. Whether you're a seasoned developer or someone whose strengths
lie outside traditional programming, your contributions hold immense value.
Imagine yourself embarking on a journey that leverages your expertise and love
for free software to enhance your capabilities and strengthen the very foundation
of the Kubernetes ecosystem. This is a real opportunity …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) winners]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7591</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-australian-book-industry-awards-abias-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) were held last week, on Thursday 9 May. The ABIAs are considered the Australian book publishing industry’s night of nights. A book-ish version of the Oscars, if you will. Award winners include Pip Williams, with her novel The Bookbinder of Jericho, in the General Fiction Book of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - How to find Your Local Wobbly History]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: How to find Your Local Wobbly History
Date: 2000
Notes: Published in Anarcho-Syndicalist Review #28, Spring 2000.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 One can find the forgotten Wobbly names and faces, strike stories, union halls and martyrs’ graves in any city where the IWW earned its legendary reputation. It is easy to find thorough information on the luminaries, such as Tresca, Flynn and Giovanitti, but what about those local organizers who invited these major figures to town, and then kept working after they were gone, pouring the wine of rebellion into workers’ hearts? It may take some time, but in all probability you’ll find syndicalist monuments and hallowed ground that you walk past every day, but never knew existed. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists
Date: September 2006
Notes: An earlier, much shorter version of this article, “Anarchists in Medicine and Pharmacy: Philadelphia, 1889–1930,” appeared in Clamor Magazine #6 (Dec. 2000/Jan. 2001), and had previously been posted on both the Guinea Pig Zero and Dead Anarchists websites.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 In the City of Philadelphia in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, there was a large group of professionals who practiced medicine or pharmacy as a livelihood, while committing great energies to the anarchist movement. Looking past the surface, we find a closely knit community of intellectuals who treated their comrades as patients, educated the publ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes to hours, hours to days, this is how you spend your time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7593</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/minute-hours-hours-days-how-you-spend-your-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A breakdown of how people, Americans in this case, spend their time, by each decade of their life. Things like sleeping, eating, working, caring for others, and socialising. The crunch is definitely on in our thirties, forties, and fifties, when time for sleep and socialising, for instance, is reduced. Kurzgesagt also did a presentation a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltairine de Cleyre - On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Voltairine de Cleyre
Title: On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion
Subtitle: A Private Letter to Samuel H. Gordon
Date: 1897
Notes: Edited and introduced by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

​Introduction
 Voltairine de Cleyre, by far Philadelphia’s brightest anarchist light, was 30 years old when, during the late summer or fall of 1897, she wrote the following letter in London. The letter was never finished, nor was it signed, dated, or mailed. Yet the letter, clearly in her handwriting and style, came to rest in a large group of her letters in the papers of Joseph J. Cohen (1878–1953), de Cleyre’s longtime associate in anarchism, which are stored in the Bund Collection, YIVO Archives, in New York City. It is one of the most compellin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin longlist for Australian novel writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7596</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-longlist-australian-novel-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well this is exciting, the longlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for Australian novel writing, has been published. Not sure how I missed the official announcement, but I went searching for a date the longlist would be unveiled, and instead found the longlist itself: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson - All Eyes on Rafah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson
Title: All Eyes on Rafah
Date: May 15th, 2024
Notes: The following article is a transcript of a speech given by Geelong Anarchist Communists member Tommy Lawson at an Independent and Peaceful Australia Network (IPAN) ‘Rally for Rafah’ held on Saturday 11th of May. Its content is supported unanimously by Geelong Anarchist Communists. We have decided to publish it today, on the 76th anniversary of the Nakba (‘catastrophe’) to declare that we stand with those resisting genocide and colonisation.
Source: Retrieved on May 15th, 2024 from https://geelonganarchists.org/2024/05/15/all-eyes-on-rafah/.

During al Nakba over 750,000 Palestinian people, from a total population of 1.9 million, were made refugees beyond the borders of their homeland. 53…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The aborted experiment of the Bank of the South in Latin America and the alternative policies that could have been adopted at the continental level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2007–2008, I helped to prepare the creation of the “Bank of the South” after being requested to assist in framing Ecuador's position on the issue by Argentine and Ecuadorian economists, as well as Ricardo Patiño, Minister of Economy and Finance in the administration of President Rafael Correa of Ecuador. I did so with commitment and without remuneration. In April 2007, in Quito, we drafted a proposal outlining Ecuador's position on the statutes, operating model, and objectives of the future (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Bank of the South, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World of Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T16:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A central feature of neo-liberal capitalism, which has ruled the global economy since the 1990s, is to deepen and widen inequalities. It makes a tiny minority indecently richer while leaving the majority in the lurch. Women and minorities such as indigenous peoples, LGBTQIA+ or racialized people are badly hit by those inequalities. In a situation in which famine and extreme poverty keep increasing, the withdrawal of the State further feeds the vicious circle of poverty and inequality. (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Capitalism, 
North, 
Inegalites 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7083</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/fixed-power-designs-its-not-if-you-peek-its-what-you-peek-at/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Sometimes we cannot estimate the required sample size needed to power an experiment before starting it. To alleviate this [...]
The post Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:10:26.460Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the longest time, I wanted to work in big tech. I got placed in one such company from campus placements. It was mostly due to my c programming skills and research work.
I am grateful for the role. I get to work on something I like. The people I work with are smart and kind. But it is just a job. Both to me and to the people I work with. One of the major perks that the HR department keeps repeating is a great work-life balance. You get time for yourself. That is very true.
Isn't that great? You get paid well. Get enough time for a good social life and side projects. You can also fund these side projects with your salary.
Yes, but what about working in a startup? A place where a lot of super passionate people are going ham at what they do. To them, it is not a job but a mission. A sort of crazy cult. Filled with kind passionate nerds. Some place where you own part of the dream. Have equity.
It sounds nice. But such places are very rare. The startup scene in India is pretty horrible. I have heard some really bad stories. So many of the startups look cool on the outside. Have great pay even. But are horrible to work for. I have had friends experience this.
I also feel like I am not good enough for those truly cracked places yet. So I am happy where I am for now and just Skill maxxing. I want to feel like a really capable engineer. I see so many of them at my org. All are really kind and happy to guide me.
Sometimes these essays help me put my life in context and clear my thinking a lot. This was one of those.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Consent and Bot Management features for Cloudflare Zaraz]]></title>
        <id>664272e7abf9e2000aee82a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-consent-and-bot-management-features-for-cloudflare-zaraz"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zaraz Consent Management now supports Google Consent Mode v2 and is compliant with the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework. Zaraz also added Bot Management support for keeping your analytics data clean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yo'av Moshe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Unexpected Inflationary Shocks Raise Workers’ Wages?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29398</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-unexpected-inflationary-shocks-raise-workers-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past year’s steady decline in nominal wage growth now appears in danger of stalling. Given ongoing uncertainty in Ukraine and the Middle East, this seems an opportune moment to revisit the conventional wisdom about the relationship between inflation and wages: if an unexpected increase in energy costs drives up the cost of living, will workers demand higher wages, reversing the recent moderation in wage growth? In new work with Justin Bloesch and Seung Joo Lee examining those concerns, our analysis shows that the pass-through of such inflationary shocks to wages is weak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I found a paper that denies one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism, so stating the obvious turns out to be useful!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52696</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/15/i-found-a-paper-that-denies-one-of-my-two-obvious-thoughts-about-originalism-so-stating-the-obvious-turns-out-to-be-useful/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a couple days to think on it, I think this post is right on. I just stumbled on a paper that stumbles, badly, over one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism. So let me point that out. Quick review. My first obvious thought is it’s weird, if you think about it, that one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidents Barber Conable and Lewis Preston (1986-1995)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with electric vehicles]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45369</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/15/the-problem-with-electric-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker For the last quarter century, those of us hoping we could slow global warming were anxious to see a quick conversion to electric vehicles (EVs). If we could get most people using electric vehicles, and have the energy coming from clean sources, we could radically reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The problem was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc. - How To Justify Workplace Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc.
Title: How To Justify Workplace Theft
Date: 14th April 2020
Source: Retrieved on 9th September 2020 from archive.org/details/workplacetheft-web

 Whether aware of it or not, your boss is stealing from you every paycheck. Employers profit off of the “excess” wealth that you, as an employee, produce. There are two ways to get paid in America: make money off the work you do, or make money off the work that other people do. Employees generate wealth, employers collect it. 
 We live in a capitalist society. We all know that. Most people are okay with it, too. After all, the competition (state communism like the USSR) doesn’t have such a good reputation. 
 But what exactly does capitalism mean? Our good friend the dictionary says capitalism is “an economic and political syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anne Archet - Sirventès of the Beast]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anne Archet
Title: Sirventès of the Beast
Date: 2014/06/27
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 I am no citizen 
 I am no consumer 
 I am no tax-payer 
 I am no employee 
 I am no convict 
 I am no beneficiary 
 I am no person of color 
 I am no lesbian 
 I am no mother 
 I am no wife 
 I am no erotic writer 
 I am no poetess 
 I am no anarchist 
 I am no woman 
 I am surely no Human 
 That vile and ethereal being 
 Which has never been spotted elsewhere 
 But in universal declarations 
 I don't want to stay seated and raise my hand 
 I don't want to wait for the teacher to tell me to speak 
 I don't want to w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, Return Fire - The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, Return Fire
Title: The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else
Subtitle: towards destroying electric mobility & decarbonizing lies
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 To read the articles referenced throughout this text in [square brackets], PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 [ed. – Taken from the German-language website SwitchOff.noblogs.org, this translation continues our interventions in the new climate movements. There are two fronts on which we would like to extend the thrust of the author/s further, in terms of its response to the text reproduced above in this chapter of Return Fire, Targets That Do Not Exist Anywhere Else. Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil - An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil
Title: An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society
Date: 02.22.2024
Source: Original translation of “Uma análise histórica anarquista das inscrições corporais na sociedade ocidental moderna”, published in Revista História em Reflexão 18(35), 2024. Retrieved on 05/07/2024 from https://doi.org/10.30612/rehr.v18i35.16476

Abstract
 In this paper, we aim to analyze the processes of stigmatization and pathologization to which certain categories of body inscriptions have been subjected throughout the history of modern Western society. Body inscriptions are defined as any and all modifications made to the body's structure. While some inscriptions are exalted and praised, others are stigmatized and discriminated aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agnes Henry - Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Agnes Henry
Title: Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism
Date: June 1896
Notes: Original text split between two consecutive monthly publications, with a misprint in the latter citing the first entry as having been published in July rather than June; transcribed from Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (June 1896) and Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (July 1896) on the Internet Archive.
Source: Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism

 The question of how for Anarchist Communism agrees exactly with State Socialism, and the exact line that divides them, has long seemed to me one that it would be well to enter into. And just now, in view of the approaching International Congress, seems a time particularly appropriate for this consideration. For surely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Scott-Brown - Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Scott-Brown
Title: Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy
Date: 2022
Notes: Routledge Studies in Radical History and Politics
Source: <doi.org/10.4324/9781003100409>

Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy is the first full account of Ward’s life and work. Drawing on unseen archival sources, as well as oral interviews, it excavates the worlds and words of his anarchist thought, illuminating his methods and charting the legacies of his enduring influence. 
 Colin Ward (1924—2010) was the most prominent British writer on anarchism in the 20th century. As a radical journalist, later author, he applied his distinctive anarchist principles to all aspects of community life including the built environment, education, and public policy. His thought was subtle, universal in a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Igor & Phil Mailer - And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Boy Igor & Phil Mailer
Title: And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)
Subtitle: The Realization and Suppression of Science and Technology
Date: 1985
Notes: A situationist critique of science and technology published in New York in 1985. This version is a new edition that was published on the 'Endangered Phoenix' website and credited to Phil Meyler. The Endangered Phoenix website is dead now, and I can’t find the updated version on the website through the wayback machine, so there are some footnotes and chapter heading levels which are unclear to me. Plus, I think chapter 3 & 4 were merged in the updated edition, so chapter numbers went out of sync, but chapter 8 was still called chapter 8 which makes it seem like chapter 7 is missing on the libcom website. It is all very confusing, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnarchyNouveau - We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: AnarchyNouveau
Title: We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy
Subtitle: An anarchist-communist’s response to Freedom News
Date: March 20, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 5/10/2024 from https://freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/23/we-dont-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-communists-response-to-freedom-news/

 In Freedom Anarchist Journal’s Winter 2023-2024 issue, Matthew Azoulay submitted an article introducing readers to Murray Bookchin’s ideas of the communalist assembly[1] which disturbed and surprised me for how much it was outdated. The means it proposes to achieve an ecologically revolutionary ends are lacking, stagnant, and fall back on modes of thinking that seem directly inherited from the anti-globalization and Occupy era[2] w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - A Proposal for the Unification of China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: A Proposal for the Unification of China
Date: 1927
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

The Political Capability of the Chinese People
 There are some who doubt that the Chinese people are capable of creating a truly democratic state. We emphatically disagree. The political environment in any country is created by its leaders. The perceptions and habits of the people can be changed to follow those of the leadership. Furthermore, Chinese society has been traditionally rich in self-governing organizations, which can be effectively used to reconstruct [China as] a democratic state. 
The Real Causes of the Turmoil over the Past Sixteen Years
1. The Problem of the Provisional Constitution
 [First,] no provision…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustav Landauer - Are These the Words of a Heretic?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gustav Landauer
Title: Are These the Words of a Heretic?
Notes: Translated from the German Daniel Wortel-London, originally entitled "Sind das Kertzergendanken?" ("Are These Heretic Thoughts?"). Originally published in Von Judentum (On Judaism) in 1911 by the Bar Kokhba League of Jewish Students.
Source: Retrieved on May 14th, 2024 from:https://x.com/dlondonwortel/status/1787470614107763006

 A characteristic of our time is that much is accomplished in spirit but little is accomplished in reality. Perhaps even the lack of actual implementation corresponds to a special activity of the mind, which constantly strives to overcome its own formations without leaving the form of fantasy and doctrine. One could imagine a human society that is structured in such a way that the ideas in it h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like describing a photo to a friend, how to write alt-text]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7584</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-describing-photo-friend-write-alt-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web designers and bloggers have been able to use alternative text, often referred to as “alt-text”, to describe images and photos, for decades. Alt-text helps people with little or no vision comprehend a website image, so long as the description is reasonably accurate. In recent years social media has caught up, and most channels, Instagram, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple text editor named Tine, by Martin Dorazil]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7582</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/simple-text-editor-tine-martin-dorazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text editor without the bells and whistles, called Tine. A nice name for a text editor. The main goal of this editor is to keep the focus on the text editing and not be distracted too much by buttons, tabs, menus, and animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>