<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-09T06:37:10.666Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-09T06:37:10.666Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critiquing Biden’s Worldview, Democratic Party Tactics and America’s Destiny]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327578</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/critiquing-bidens-worldview-democratic-party-tactics-and-americas-destiny/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T06:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears that even Biden is reluctant to claim credit in national settings for US support of Israel and Ukraine, and prefers to speak in generalities about the greatness of America as a country whose future is bright except to the extent dimmed by the threat advent of Trump and Trumpism. This tendency to ignore the world should be more troubling to American voters than even Biden’s refusal to leave the presidential stage in light of his thinly deniable disabilities of age and mental health that have put his 2024 candidacy in peril. More
The post Critiquing Biden’s Worldview, Democratic Party Tactics and America’s Destiny appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Falk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racism in the Life of Farage: From Enoch Powell to Reform UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327465</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/racism-in-the-life-of-farage-from-enoch-powell-to-reform-uk/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigel Farage has always been a bigoted posh boy with the gift of the gab. Raised in the rolling hills of Downe on the outskirts of London -- a village most famous for its association with Charles Darwin -- Farage attended Eden Park Preparatory School in the 1970s. His wealthy parents then paid for his attendance at one of South London’s most prestigious old boys’ clubs, Dulwich College. Farage’s germinal racism was public even at this early age, and in 1981, his fascist mannerisms were played down as ordinary “naughtiness” by his college’s “Master” when he chose to make him a prefect More
The post Racism in the Life of Farage: From Enoch Powell to Reform UK appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Barker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Twentieth-Century Family Planning Strategy Fueled the Climate Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327647</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/how-a-twentieth-century-family-planning-strategy-fueled-the-climate-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1948, the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (UDHR) was signed, marking a milestone in human rights history. It established the fundamental rights to be universally protected, with Article 1 proclaiming: “All human beings are born free and equal in dignity and rights.” In the following decades, however, specific events and policies revealed a critical oversight  More
The post How a Twentieth-Century Family Planning Strategy Fueled the Climate Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Scher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreaming of a Great World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/dreaming-of-a-great-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a warm, humid summer night, just the kind of night I remember my parents taking us kids to see the Lincoln Memorial.  I wanted Erika to have as her first memory of this place that same stunning vista of Lincoln looking at the brightly lit obelisk of the Washington Monument and illuminated dome  More
The post Dreaming of a Great World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dictatorial Trump Court Has Put Our Democracy’s Rule of Law on Quicksand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327676</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/the-dictatorial-trump-court-has-put-our-democracys-rule-of-law-on-quicksand/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The six “corporate state” U.S. Supreme Court Justices, occupying unaccountable lifetime unelected positions, handed over dictatorial power for presidents and corporations that disassembled our Founders’ Constitution and the centerpiece of the American Revolution. In one week! Led by the notorious Trump v. United States case these interwoven and dictatorial commands will live in infamy unless  More
The post The Dictatorial Trump Court Has Put Our Democracy’s Rule of Law on Quicksand appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who “Runs The Country?” We Do!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327646</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/who-runs-the-country-we-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Who runs the country?” I’ve been hearing variants of that question a lot over the last  few weeks, mainly in forms like “given Joe Biden’s age and apparent mental decline, can we trust him to run the country for another four years?” For the last eight or nine years, I’ve also heard it a lot,  More
The post Who “Runs The Country?” We Do! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Australia’s Luck Running Out?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327441</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/is-australias-luck-running-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Describing Australia as “the lucky country” has long been a metaphor for how “well” Australia has been doing economically. Unfortunately, for many Australians, things haven’t been going “well” for quite some time. Australia’s past prosperity had precious little to do with luck. Years ago, many analysts saw Australia’s luck as a product of its abundant  More
The post Is Australia’s Luck Running Out? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rory Ellison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Economic Boycotts of the Civil Rights Era Still Offer Lessons on How to Achieve a Just Society]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327500</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/black-economic-boycotts-of-the-civil-rights-era-still-offer-lessons-on-how-to-achieve-a-just-society/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signed into law 60 years ago, the Civil Rights Act of 1964 outlawed discrimination in the U.S. based on “race, color, sex, religion, or national origin.” Yet, as a historian who studies social movements and political change, I think the law’s most important lesson for today’s movements is not its content but rather how it  More
The post Black Economic Boycotts of the Civil Rights Era Still Offer Lessons on How to Achieve a Just Society appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin A. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NYT and the Low-Wage Worker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327498</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/the-nyt-and-the-low-wage-worker/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-wage workers have seen large real wage gains since the pandemic, so naturally as we come to the July 4th holiday the New York Times gives us a piece telling us how they are hurting. The piece is headlined, “America’s divided summer economy is coming to an airport or hotel near you.” If there is  More
The post The NYT and the Low-Wage Worker appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breathing New Life into the UN Charter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327674</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/breathing-new-life-into-the-un-charter/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:17:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental problem we face today in world affairs is our failure to adjust our international institutions to the imperative needs of a rapidly evolving age. The UN Secretary-General said as much last September when in a speech before the General Assembly he noted: “We cannot effectively address problems as they are if institutions don’t  More
The post Breathing New Life into the UN Charter appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Perell - Heba Aly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump to Visit Western Pa.: a Contrast with VP Bush’s Visit in 1982]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327577</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/trump-to-visit-western-pa-a-contrast-with-vp-bushs-visit-in-1982/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T04:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump is scheduled to visit Butler County (Pa) for another campaign rally in a few days. By the time this article is published, it may have already happened. He will probably be greeted with a large crowd as nature abhors a vacuum. Donald’s message in 2024 is not much different than that of former  More
The post Trump to Visit Western Pa.: a Contrast with VP Bush’s Visit in 1982 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Grystar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching a Lesson to the Palestinians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327678</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/teaching-a-lesson-to-the-palestinians/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T04:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will teach you, human animals who don’t value human life as we do, never to do this again to us, to our families, to our women and children, as you did on October 7. We will destroy your houses, your sewage systems, your hospitals, your schools, your crops and herds. We will ravage your  More
The post Teaching a Lesson to the Palestinians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is climate change increasing the strength of Australian red wine?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7973</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/climate-change-increasing-strength-australian-red-wine/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T21:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently red wines made in Australia — and quite possibly elsewhere, I imagine — have been increasing in alcoholic strength over recent decades. This seems like a mystery of the times, because the go-to culprit, global warming, may not be responsible. Rather, the way grapes are grown, and changes in fermenting methods — which apparently […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/8/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274587</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-8-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T18:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Janeway’s Mesoeconomics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45465</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/08/on-janeways-mesoeconomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T17:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford “Economics has become irrelevant.” PART ONE Oh my.  Apparently Brad DeLong and I have the same problem.  He, of course, is part of the elite club.  I am decidedly not.  So it is quite a shock to share something. What? He set out to write an 800 word review of Dan Davies’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End Austerity: A Global Report on Budget Cuts and Harmful Social Reforms in 2022-25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/End-Austerity-A-Global-Report-on-Budget-Cuts-and-Harmful-Social-Reforms-in-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/End-Austerity-A-Global-Report-on-Budget-Cuts-and-Harmful-Social-Reforms-in-2022"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T17:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This report exposes the dangers of a post-pandemic austerity shock, far more premature and severe than the one that followed the global financial crisis. It finds that 85 percent of the world's population is living in the grip of austerity, more than 6.3 billion people. Governments must urgently identify alternative financing options to support their populations that are coping with multiple and compounding crises - from health, energy, finance and climate shocks to unaffordable living (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabel Ortiz, Matthew Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon S3 Access Grants, AWS Lambda, European Sovereign Cloud Region, and more (July 8, 2024).]]></title>
        <id>33de3473228bf0a8001c1a2fab34dcc5d6379d50</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-s3-access-grants-aws-lambda-european-sovereign-cloud-region-and-more-july-8-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T16:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I counted only 21 AWS news since last Monday, most of them being Regional expansions of existing services and capabilities. I hope you enjoyed a relatively quiet week, because this one will be busier. This week, we’re welcoming our customers and partners at the Jacob Javits Convention Center for the AWS Summit New York on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French elections: political cyber attacks and Internet traffic shifts]]></title>
        <id>668c06d24f58a9000ada4845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/2024-french-elections-political-cyber-attacks-and-internet-traffic-shifts"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check the dynamics of the 2024 French legislative elections, the surprising election results’ impact on Internet traffic changes, and the cyber attacks targeting political parties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Edit My Photos]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/how-i-edit-my-photos/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/how-i-edit-my-photos/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:47:04.262Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During National Camera Day , I wrote about my non-exhaustive list of cameras I’ve owned. A lot of great discussions came out of this, both via Mastodon and email. One of those things is in regard to my post-processing workflow.

As you can see in my respose to Lou, I currently do very little when it comes to post-processing photos. It wasn’t always like this, but I think that’s a story for another post. This one will focus specifically on what I do now (which isn’t much).
Both of my primary cameras (Fujifilm X100V and Ricoh GRIIIx) have some sort of film simulation that I can set up in-camera and I rely on that to do a majority of my edits.
In my Fujifilm X100V, I primarily use the Reggie’s Portra film sim
Classic Chrome
Dynamic Range: DR-Auto
Highlight: -1
Shadow: -1
Color: +2
Noise Reduc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Would a Russian Victory in Ukraine Look Like?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274585</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/what-would-a-russian-victory-in-ukraine-look-like.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia has some thorny and apparently not resolved questions about its end game in Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/8/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274612</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-8-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T10:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nature Communications: Permaculture as a Better Alternative to Conventional Agriculture?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274599</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/nature-communications-permaculture-as-a-better-alternative-to-conventional-agriculture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T10:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Permaculture is a sustainable alternative to conventional agriculture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Newspaper Confirms IDF Employed ‘Hannibal Directive’ on October 7]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274621</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/israeli-newspaper-confirms-idf-employed-hannibal-directive-on-october-7.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T10:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IDF soldiers were reportedly ordered to "turn the area around the border fence into a killing zone."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Fed-Induced World Stagnation Deepens Debt Distress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274627</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/us-fed-induced-world-stagnation-deepens-debt-distress.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T08:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US and Fed bad cooking has led to weak growth the world, and by urging poor countries to borrow at once-low rates, debt distress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gaza Genocide: Who’s Complicit?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/the-gaza-genocide-whos-complicit/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T06:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the recent pro-Palestinian protests around the world and on many university campuses, it seems strange if not surprising that neither genocide nor the continuing flow of U.S. weapons to Israel were mentioned during the first (and maybe only) 2024 presidential debate. Nor did the New York Times Editorial Board see fit to cite complicity in genocide while calling for Biden to step down after his poor debate performance. Instead, it declared that Biden has been "an admirable president." More
The post The Gaza Genocide: Who’s Complicit? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massacre at the Ballot: The Punishing of the Tories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327479</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/massacre-at-the-ballot-the-punishing-of-the-tories/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most staggering feature of these elections, leaving aside the ritualistic savaging of the Tories, was the wholly lopsided nature of the share of votes relative to the winning of seats.  “This election,” the Electoral Reform Society solemnly declared, “saw Labour and the Conservatives receive their joint lowest vote share on record, with a combined 57.4%.” That did not prevent the two major parties from snaring the lion’s share.  Labour received 33.7% of the vote yet obtained 63.2% (411 seats) of the 650 on offer, making it the most disproportionate on record.  The Tories, despite the bloodbath, could still count on 121 MPs with 23.7% of votes winning 18.6% of seats in the House of Commons. More
The post Massacre at the Ballot: The Punishing of the Tories appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War and Famine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327556</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/war-and-famine/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many war stories end with hunger wreaking havoc on significant portions of a population. In Christian theology, the Biblical “four horses of the apocalypse,” believed by many in early modern Europe to presage the end of the world, symbolized invasion, armed conflict, and famine followed by death. They suggest the degree to which people have long recognized  More
The post War and Famine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Mazzarino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Paths Forward in Immigration Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327509</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/three-paths-forward-in-immigration-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This November, voters will choose between two radically different paths of immigration policy. Should Donald Trump be re-elected president, the nation will embark on a path of deportation, or the attempted deportation, of millions of people living in the U.S. Should Joe Biden or another Democrat occupy the White House next year, the country will  More
The post Three Paths Forward in Immigration Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 British Election: Big Change Ain’t Gonna Come]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327548</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/the-2024-british-election-big-change-aint-gonna-come/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, yeah, I know the Tories are out, Labour won big time and Keir Starmer is the new PM and at home at 10 Downing Street. Starmer called for “Change.” That’s what voters clearly wanted after years and years of disastrous Conservative Party rule that saw a widening gap between haves and have nots and  More
The post The 2024 British Election: Big Change Ain’t Gonna Come appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the NY Times Calling for Biden’s Ouster?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327543</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/why-is-the-ny-times-calling-for-bidens-ouster/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times, long considered the “newspaper of record” in the United States, has in recent weeks made no secret about its chief concern: President Joe Biden’s ability to defeat Donald Trump in November 2024. And, it has done everything it can to promote the idea that the Democratic Party ticket needs a new  More
The post Why is the NY Times Calling for Biden’s Ouster? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Barriers: The Political Empowerment of Bolivia’s Indigenous Women]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327544</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/breaking-barriers-the-political-empowerment-of-bolivias-indigenous-women/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remigia Ferrel Vallejos, a Bolivian union executive from Chimoré, in the coca-grower Chapare region, isn’t nostalgic for the old days. “Before there was a lot of fatalism. Many times, in meetings I was told, ‘women don’t count, the man has to come,” she explains. “That’s how it was; we didn’t even have the right to  More
The post Breaking Barriers: The Political Empowerment of Bolivia’s Indigenous Women appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Farthing - Thomas Grisaffi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Need a New Political Vocabulary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327537</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/we-need-a-new-political-vocabulary/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The July 4 landslide defeat of the neoliberal pro-war British Conservatives by the neoliberal pro-war Labour Party poses the question of just what the media mean when they describe the elections and political alignments throughout Europe in terms of center-right and center-left traditional parties challenged by nationalist neo-fascists. Political differences between Europe’s centrist parties are  More
The post We Need a New Political Vocabulary appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Spirit of the Law Should Prevail: A Cautionary Tale of Extremism From an Ex-Scrupulous Chaplain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327433</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/why-the-spirit-of-the-law-should-prevail-a-cautionary-tale-of-extremism-from-an-ex-scrupulous-chaplain/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between stimulus and response there is a space. In that space is our power to choose our response. In our response lies our growth and our freedom. – Viktor E. Frankl Content warning: This essay briefly describes a suicide attempt. If you or someone you know are/is struggling with thoughts of suicide or self-harm, please  More
The post Why the Spirit of the Law Should Prevail: A Cautionary Tale of Extremism From an Ex-Scrupulous Chaplain appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Zoosman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More Than Ever, Trump’s Most Effective Campaign Ally is Joe Biden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327437</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/more-than-ever-trumps-most-effective-campaign-ally-is-joe-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Joe Biden’s ABC News interview aired on Friday night, it made clear that he should not be running for re-election. Rather than reduce the concerns sparked by his abysmal debate performance eight days earlier, the interview underscored that the president is in denial about his current political standing and unable to offer reassurance that  More
The post More Than Ever, Trump’s Most Effective Campaign Ally is Joe Biden appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Cohen - Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environmental Groups Save Ashley National Forest Roadless Areas from Bulldozers and Chainsaws]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327439</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/08/environmental-groups-save-ashley-national-forest-roadless-areas-from-bulldozers-and-chainsaws/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T05:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The great news is the Ashley National Forest has been saved from a “landscape scale” deforestation plan in which the Forest Service planned to bulldoze in skid trails to log and burn up to 147,000 acres (230 square miles!) of Inventoried Roadless Areas. But when faced with the lawsuit brought by the Alliance for the  More
The post Environmental Groups Save Ashley National Forest Roadless Areas from Bulldozers and Chainsaws appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Garrity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The physics of running and keeping fit on the Moon]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7967</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/physics-running-keeping-fit-moon/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rhett Allain, writing for Wired, looks at the physics of this important question. If humanity is ever to establish bases on the Moon, ways of keeping occupants fit in the low lunar gravity need to be worked out. A wall of death sort of gizmo, that’s a little like a stationary hamster-wheel, but turned on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The emotional disconnect with AI made works]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/the-emotional-disconnect-with-ai-made-works/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/the-emotional-disconnect-with-ai-made-works/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T18:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm definitely not against the usage of AI. It's a very helpful and powerful tool for many things. It's being used for web designs, graphical elements, illustrations, articles, videos, stories, etc.
However, I think we might be missing one thing. For me, one of the reasons I love certain content, designs, and articles is because they are human-made. Human made things are not perfect. Imperfection makes the whole story/concept/design better. The beauty and charm lie in the imperfections and the fact that I know it's done by another living being like me. Thanks to this fact, I form connections to the things I consume.
Personally, I can not feel emotional connection to AI-made products. It does not matter if it is perfect or not. As soon as I know that it is AI-made, I start to dislike it suddenly. It's definitely not a rational way of thinking and is completely emotional, I know. But that's where AI might have difficulties understanding human behavior. Humans are unpredictable and imperfect. Stories — the whole process of creating something from beginning to end — are really important for humans, and knowing that there is a human in the process makes it more valuable.
So I think that, in the future, AI-made things might start to be something that people might try to avoid on purpose, and value non-AI-made/human-made things much more just because they are human-made, imperfect and have a story in it. People might start to demand non-AI works. \ AI might lose it's popularity just because of being AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[slapping watermelons]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/slapping-watermelons/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/slapping-watermelons/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite childhood memories is eating watermelons in the summer. Not just the carnal joy of eating them — crunching the sweetness between my teeth and feeling the wetness run down my chin — but the rest of the process too. Watching my dad slap and thump the melons in the supermarket to pick a good one while my brother and I clowned around and mimicked him. Crowding around the cutting board to seeing if we split open a good one. And of course, the best part: spooning the first bite of dark red flesh from the center and watching the juice pour into the crater left behind.
A crate of watermelons greeted me at the supermarket last week and I decided I wanted to buy one for the first time, just to try it. After slapping a few cluelessly (are they supposed to talk back to you or something?) I pushed my cart to a corner and looked up how to pick a good watermelon. I ended up coming across this helpful graphic:

I don't know what my dad was listening for when he tapped and slapped all those watermelons. Like with most things, I'm sure I asked him about it and promptly forgot his answer. In hindsight, I don't think he was that good at choosing them, despite growing up on a farm, because he took home a number of watermelons that were pale and watery inside. And I've been thinking about that as I sprinkle tajín on my watermelon slices and drip pink juice on the counter, how he was probably winging it too, along with the rest of adult- and parenthood, the same way I was slapping watermelons at the market last week and feeling like a fool waiting to be found out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274533</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T10:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spook Scholarship: A Prominent Former CIA Analyst and Project Ukraine Backer Moonlights as a Collegiate Textbook Coauthor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274555</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/spook-scholarship-a-prominent-former-cia-analyst-and-project-ukraine-backer-moonlights-as-a-collegiate-textbook-coauthor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T10:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students lucky enough to be assigned the books will learn that foreign countries resisting US imperialism aren’t the only danger to “democracy,” but the American people are as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: Reading Indie Blogs Right]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/re-reading-indie-blogs-right/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/re-reading-indie-blogs-right/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi Loren,
The story of how I found your blog is an interesting one. It fits perfectly with why I'm writing this to you (and any other reader who stumbles upon it). I came across a post by Chris on Uncountable about the magic of reading blog posts on the original website. He linked to your post with the same title. This is how the IndieWeb is supposed to work: you visit someone's website via a link and then embark on an adventure through the indie jungle, arriving somewhere you didn't expect.
These moments are magical. Adventures like these lead you from one scenic website to another. It's like walking through an ancient forest that seems straight out of The Lord of the Rings, only to find a light at the end where you enter a place as stunning as Rivendell.
This post could have been a Fw: (forward) instead of a Re: (reply). I couldn't agree more with your statement:
"These bloggers put time and effort into making their websites – the design, the 'About Me' page, the Archives. In an app, all that disappears, replaced by a sterile, uniform layout."
The real magic is in this effort, the years of tears and sweat that people put into creating their websites. It's something you completely miss out on when reading everything in the blandness of an RSS reader. It's like watching Mad Max on the tiny screen of your phone instead of the magnificent and overwhelming IMAX cinema experience.
There is so much enchantment in taking that little extra effort to open a post on someone's website.
This is where the real IndieWeb comes to life.
With love,
Yordi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your trash might be someone else’s treasure]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/trash-treasure/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/trash-treasure/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had dinner with a close friend yesterday.
Afterward, I sent a photo I took of her. She wrote back that she thought it looked awful. I replied that I thought it was beautiful, which I honestly did. I wrote that maybe it's like hearing your voice; it always feels a little strange and "ugly."
The thought lingered while I sat on the subway home…
Perhaps it's the same phenomenon that happens when we're dissatisfied with our writing. The observer and the observed are too close to each other to make a fair judgment. It's like looking at a painting up close and thinking it looks terrible. It's like a trial where the judge and the defendant are the same person.
We are in a constant state of bias when it comes to judging our work.
Anyone who's been blogging for a while has experienced this: You post something you almost threw away because you thought it was garbage, and it turns out to be one of your most popular posts.
Bias.
Next time you find yourself with your index finger resting on the delete button, move it to publish. Your trash might be someone else’s treasure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As New Campaign Implores Him to ‘Pass the Torch,’ Biden Rejects Calls to Drop Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274539</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/as-new-campaign-implores-him-to-pass-the-torch-biden-rejects-calls-to-drop-out.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T09:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A shadowy group of Democrat insiders leads the effort to pick the party’s nominee in smoke-filled room.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Swift]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52856</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/07/sunday-photoblogging-swift-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T07:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent many hours trying to take pictures of these over the past three years and have a large collection of indistinct blurs as a result. But I went back to basics, studied the camera setting, watched a bunch of “how to” videos on YouTube and actually managed this one:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Long Awaited Bear Media Center]]></title>
        <id>https://jbrr.dev/long-awaited-bear-media-center/</id>
        <link href="https://jbrr.dev/long-awaited-bear-media-center/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope I'm not telling any tales out of school. If I am, bring the lifetime ban hammer down on me hard, Herman.
A recent update has exposed an experimental media library in your Bear dashboard. It was committed two weeks ago, so this might be old news, but this is a considerable improvement for general ease of use.
The URL is https://bearblog.dev/<subdomain>/dashboard/media/ and should look like this.

Pro Tip: Use the Customize Dashboard functionality to add a link in your footer for easy access.
Excellent work, Herman, as always!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genocide Then and Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327237</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/07/genocide-then-and-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T05:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times has been justifiably criticized, as you probably know, for its anti-Palestine bias in covering Israel’s war on Gaza. But you may not know that the Times building is located near Manhattan’s theater district. This is why a lot of show people tend to walk past the Times, and why my friend, […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Genocide Then and Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susie Day</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migration is Not a Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327186</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/07/migration-is-not-a-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T05:50:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jocelyn Nungaray, a 12-year-old from Texas, was recently found dead in a creek near her home. Video footage from a convenience store and interviews with neighborhood residents led police to two men whom they later arrested. Both suspects are undocumented migrants from Venezuela. Her murder immediately became a narrative about the savagery of illegal aliens […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Migration is Not a Crime appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Slager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You've Got Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T17:44:04.350Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading Veronique's post this afternoon, Just A Small Town Girl, and smiled at her lovely doodles. But there was one that caught my eye and then, brought a lump to my throat. It featured a stamp and the words, Post Air Mail. And it hit me. I hadn't had any real mail from anyone (not including birthday or Christmas cards) not since my mum passed back in 1999.
It sent a shiver down my spine not just because that was over 20 years ago, but because, the last handwritten letter I ever got, was from a dead woman: my mother.
Where ever I was in the world, travelling and or working, my mother almost religiously took time out of her day to write an aerogramme to me. Do you remember those? You buy them at any post office, singularly or in packs. I think my mother had a draw full of them—after …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Human Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327368</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/06/moving-human-targets/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T14:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ This week’s Israeli seizure of nearly five square miles of land in the Jordan Valley of the occupied West Bank is the largest land grab in the more than three decades since the signing of the Oslo Accords. First, the lands were declared “closed military zones,” then the Netanyahu government reassigned them as “state […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Moving Human Targets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274415</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T10:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tetchy daily links: 2000 year old calculator, more Covid damage evidence, coal forever? EU v. China, Starmer's weak landslide, Nigeria starvation, Houthis punching harder, Putin Q&A, Interpol hates digital roaming, NATO wobbles? Biden agonistes, vending machine bullets, shareholder driven crapification, American dream dead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Barnay: &ldquo;Gaucho-Lepénisme?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On France’s far-right vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Seymour: &ldquo;Majority Without a Mandate&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why so serious?]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/why-so-serious/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/why-so-serious/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently did work in the Swedish archipelago. So beautiful! On days like that, it's hard to believe you're at work.
This time, the sky opened up, and the rain poured down for a short while. The sky looked amazingly powerful as I stood on the shore and looked out over the ocean.
It's stunning how small you feel at times like this. Not only that, but your worries and problems also feel small. Things that you otherwise attach great importance to suddenly don’t feel all that important there and then. You just stand there with your smallness somewhere in the vastness of the universe and marvel — everything stops.
A few hours later, I stepped ashore, jumped on my bike, and felt how everyday life was slowly but surely making its way back…
"I have to stop at the grocery store on the way home. Oh, I almost forgot; I have to do laundry today. I wonder if I can make it to the gym. On the last day of the month, I have to remember to report my working hours. Oh yeah, I have to log and send in my expenses for the month.”
Things that need to be done. They don’t get done by standing and staring straight up at the sky in an attempt to make them small enough to disappear.
But now and then, we can try to remind ourselves of the emptiness that surrounds all these little musts and problems. Our inner, limitless space can teach us not to take everything so seriously.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK election day 2024: traffic trends and attacks on political parties]]></title>
        <id>6687ef98a4598c000bd710d0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/uk-election-day-2024-traffic-trends-and-attacks-on-political-parties"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we explore the dynamics of Internet traffic and cybersecurity during the UK’s 2024 general election, highlighting late-day traffic changes and a post-vote attack on a political party]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Familiar Faces&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The photography of Johny Pitts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bye bye, Tories, hello what?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52851</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/05/bye-bye-tories-hello-what/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T09:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the UK, we’re all waking up to the prospect of a new government. The election was an oddity: Labour has converted a modest 35% vote share into a whopping Parliamentary majority; the Tories did somewhat better than suggested, on around 24%, but have lost more than two-thirds of their MPs. (The final figures were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Presidential Debate Harmed US Foreign Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327205</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/how-the-presidential-debate-harmed-us-foreign-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T06:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s Biden-Trump debate harmed U.S. foreign policy, and the international community was left to debate what was said and what was left unsaid.  In view of the harmful potential for wider wars in East Europe and the Middle East in addition to the potential for China’s increased military pressure on Taiwan, it is shocking that only ten minutes of the 90-minute debate was devoted to national security policy.  The inept CNN moderators—Jake Tapper and Dana Bash—were partly responsible because of the dearth of questions on foreign policy.  Nevertheless, the answers provided by President Joe Biden and former president Donald Trump were shocking for their misinformation and their polemics.   More
The post How the Presidential Debate Harmed US Foreign Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Animal Factories: On the Killing Floor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327256</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/animal-factories-on-the-killing-floor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T06:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up south of Indianapolis on the glacier-smoothed plains of central Indiana. My grandparents owned a small farm, whittled down over the years to about 40 acres of bottomland, in some of the most productive agricultural land in America. Like many of their neighbors they mostly grew field corn (and later soybeans), raised a few cows and bred a few horses.
More
The post Animal Factories: On the Killing Floor appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say It Ain’t So, Joe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327179</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/say-it-aint-so-joe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On screen, Biden looked and sounded like a somnambulist whose only connection to politics was a haphazard, recited laundry list of federal programs that have saved everyone from unwed mothers to homeless veterans, but at least the president came to the debate with malice toward none (Gazans might have been the exception), while from the other lectern Trump was little more than a fountain of bile. More
The post Say It Ain’t So, Joe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharon Revisited: Netanyahu’s Ultimate Aim in Gaza and Why It Will Fail]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327322</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/05/sharon-revisited-netanyahus-ultimate-aim-in-gaza-and-why-it-will-fail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T05:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel never learns from its mistakes. What Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is trying to implement in Gaza is but a poor copy of previous strategies that were used in the past by other Israeli leaders. If these strategies had succeeded, Israel would not be in this position in the first place. The main reason  More
The post Sharon Revisited: Netanyahu’s Ultimate Aim in Gaza and Why It Will Fail  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threads first birthday gift to users: advertising?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7958</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/threads-first-birthday-gift-users-advertising/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Break out the coffee and the cake: a celebration is on the cards. Tomorrow, Threads, Meta’s answer — and much needed foil — to X/Twitter, notches up its first birthday. I was there as the platform began rolling out, and managed to score (just) a relatively low (five-figure) badge number. 98,522 for the record. These […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[William Gillis - What’s In A Slogan? “KYLR” and Militant Anarcha-feminism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/william-gillis-what-s-in-a-slogan-kylr-and-militant-anarcha-feminism?v=1720111778</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/william-gillis-what-s-in-a-slogan-kylr-and-militant-anarcha-feminism?v=1720111778"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T16:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: William Gillis
Title: What’s In A Slogan? “KYLR” and Militant Anarcha-feminism
Date: June 25, 2024
Notes: William Gillis: https://twitter.com/rechelon
Source: Retrieved on July 4, 2024 from https://c4ss.org/content/59691

 An anarchist walks out of a punk show to smoke. On her vest are anarchist patches with various standard slogans, “No Gods No Masters,” “Death To Transphobes,” “Kill Your Local Rapist,” “All Cops Are Bastards,” “Punch Nazis,” “From The River To The Sea Palestine Will Be Free,” “Make Total Destroy,” “The Only Good Cop Is A Dead Cop,” “Eat The Rich,” “Death Before Detransition” and… “Fire To The Prisons.” 
 A suddenly red-faced bystander trots up to her to argue. 
“Oh so you’re saying you support a blanket social policy of allowing anyone to burn anything they accus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 30, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240704</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240704"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare 1.1.1.1 incident on June 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>668519cda4598c000bd709a9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-1111-incident-on-june-27-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 27, 2024, a small number of users globally may have noticed that 1.1.1.1 was unreachable or degraded. The root cause was a mix of BGP (Border Gateway Protocol) hijacking and a route leak]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryton Herdes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read: Theory and reality in economics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45462</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/04/weekend-read-theory-and-reality-in-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll So, certainly, both non-theorists and some theorists have little patience for research that displays mathematical ingenuity but has no value as social science. But defining this work exactly is impossible. This sort of work is like pornography quite simple to recognize when one sees it. Jeffrey Ely As researchers, we (mostly) want […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broken Britain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Broken-Britain</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Broken-Britain"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T11:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UK citizens vote in a general election on 4 July. The opinion polls currently forecast that the incumbent Conservative party will be heavily defeated after 14 years in government. The opposition Labour party is expected to gain a majority of over 250 seats, a record landslide, with the Conservatives getting less than 100 seats. 
English

/ 
United Kingdom, 
Capitalism, 
Inequality, 
Inflation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MB Sundjata - How and Why the US Left Betrayed Tigray]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mb-sundjata-how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray?v=1720081541</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mb-sundjata-how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray?v=1720081541"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T08:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: MB Sundjata
Title: How and Why the US Left Betrayed Tigray
Subtitle: US organizations like PSL and Black Alliance for Peace cannot be trusted to advocate for Palestine’s liberation after they condemned nearly a million Tigrayans to genocide.
Date: June 18, 2024
Source: Retrieved from <redvoice.news/how-and-why-the-us-left-betrayed-tigray> on July 3, 2024

 I thought further and said: “Why do men lie over problems of such great importance, even to the point of destroying themselves?” and they seemed to do so because although they pretend to know all, they know nothing. Convinced they know all, they do not attempt to investigate the truth. — Zara Yacob of Aksum (Tigray), 17th-century philosopher, in The Hatata Inquiries
 (Content Warning: this article describes acts of genocide and w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Di fraye arbeter shtime Editorial Board, An Anonymous Group of Polish Anarchists, Eyshe Beirich - Yiddish Anarchists’ Break Over Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-di-fraye-arbeter-shtime-editorial-board-an-anonymous-group-of-polish-anarchists-yiddish-ana?v=1720078025</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/the-di-fraye-arbeter-shtime-editorial-board-an-anonymous-group-of-polish-anarchists-yiddish-ana?v=1720078025"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T07:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: The Di fraye arbeter shtime Editorial Board, An Anonymous Group of Polish Anarchists, Eyshe Beirich
Title: Yiddish Anarchists’ Break Over Palestine
Date: 1929
Notes: An exchange in the anarchist newspaper Di fraye arbeter shtime after the 1929 Hebron massacre offers a case study in Jewish discourse and political reaction after immense violence. 
 Introduced and translated from the Yiddish by Eyshe Beirich
Source: Retrieved on 04/07/2024 from https://jewishcurrents.org/yiddish-anarchists-break-over-palestine-1929

On Friday, August 23rd, 1929, exaggerated rumors about the extent of Jewish violence against Palestinians and the desecration of holy sites in Jerusalem reached the Palestinian community of Hebron (Al-Khalil, in Arabic). What started as incensed Palestinians throwing stone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The indie web is saving my sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/the-indie-web-is-saving-my-sanity/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/the-indie-web-is-saving-my-sanity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T04:13:14.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of my posts have covered stuff I don't ever have the time of day to talk about. I work too much and almost all of my coworkers are conservative boomers. I don't talk to most of them  much but every once in a while I'll have to share a store with some of them. Sometimes they give me random phone calls. Luckily I have the option of just not picking up the phone.
I just don't relate with the people I have to interact with on the regular. I mean we aren't having heavy political conversations 24/7 but it just doesn't feel comfortable being around people who you know are the polar opposite of who you are.
I feel like being able to write about the stuff I never get to talk about is a healthy counterweight to that. I'm not a great writer, I know a lot of the stuff I write won't be read for weeks, or possibly ever. Some of it might be boring or come across cheesy. Sometimes I cover really broad, uninteresting things.
But it has had the unexpected effect of making me feel more valid as a person. It feels odd saying that, but it's true.
Maybe it's because I haven't had a hobby I can get lost in for too long. Making the rounds in different indie web neighborhoods, learning little bits of CSS and bringing my vision to life one piece at a time does a pretty good job at keeping me from getting bored and letting my mind wander to stress. Then when I'm done with that for a while I can write some more. Sometimes I'm proud of it, sometimes I delete it after a couple hours.
It feels... healthier than doomscrolling. I prefer this over traditional social media because of the ownership and freedom, and the fact that I sort of get to whisper what I'm saying rather than blasting it over a megaphone and putting myself on stage in front of an audience riding algorithmic dopamine waves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anarhija.info - Horror Vacui]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-horror-vacui?v=1720049426</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-horror-vacui?v=1720049426"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anarhija.info
Title: Horror Vacui
Date: February 10, 2018
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=29728>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 There are anarchists who run after uprisings on other continents wherever the spotlights of the media fall. There are anarchists who talk about “fortress Europe” and they don’t even know which States are part of the EU. There are anarchists who struggle against the borders and they don’t even know where the Schengen frontier runs. There are anarchists who, like “good white men”, see in the “dark-skinned” non-EU people potential comrades, and they don’t even notice that there are European non-EU people. 
 There are anarchists who talk about internationalism and they don’t even know (or don’t give a fuck) what happens on their own conti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anarhija.info - Aut Aut]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut?v=1720049269</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut?v=1720049269"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anarhija.info
Title: Aut Aut
Date: 2016
Source: <anarhija.info/library/anarhija-info-aut-aut-en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 When I translated and published the pamphlet "Individuality and the anarchist group", signed by one of the CCF cells, Guerilla Urbana Cell, I added in a note that I didn’t do it because I agree with the content, but to make public how much this project, in my opinion, has turned away from its original form of tension to propose (or re-propose) an anarchist individualism which, in some ways, can be found in the pages of a different insurrectionist theory, but in this case approaching or even in some points leading to formal ideas, that is the formal organization. 
 Similar proposals (informal platform, structured and specific organization…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adriano - Communiqué from prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adriano-communique-from-prison?v=1720049064</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/adriano-communique-from-prison?v=1720049064"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T23:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Adriano
Title: Communiqué from prison
Date: April 9, 2014
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=16535>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Violence generates violence. Regardless of what is right or wrong, no matter how abstruse is the boundary between opposites and how easily they can converge. The word violence and the concept it expresses present deep mystifications to those who have the monopoly on it. All expressions of dissent are being disproportionately repressed… no surprise… ‘go and tell them that it’s springtime’ [rough translation of ‘vagli a spiegare che è primavera’, a verse by the late anarchist singer and song-writer Fabrizio De Andrè]. 
 The modus operandi of cops and politicians is infamous enough, with their artistic architecture made of inexistent cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Potentially habitable Earth size planet forty light years away]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7951</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/potentially-habitable-earth-size-planet-forty-light-years-away/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s the good news. Tory Shepherd, writing for The Guardian, says the recently discovered exoplanet, dubbed Gliese 12b, might be able to host liquid water. We all know what that means. If there’s water, there may be life. Gliese 12b is so named because it orbits a star called Gliese. Now for the bad news. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refactoring to Serverless: From Application to Automation]]></title>
        <id>0b8bd15cb28746b280e7ed11144ffd013485b5aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/refactoring-to-serverless-from-application-to-automation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T20:41:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Refactor serverless apps by swapping application code with cloud automation: reduce costs, decouple logic from architecture, and leverage managed services' native capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sindhu Pillai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does Social Media Cause Anything?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52847</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/03/does-social-media-cause-anything/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 18 months since I quit Twitter, I can feel the atrophy of my vibe detector. I’m reading more than ever, on Substack and the FT, Discord and group chats — much of the same “content” I would’ve encountered on Twitter, in fact, but without the ever-present spiderweb of the social graph, the network […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Myself Beyond the Trading Floor]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/market-to-me/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/market-to-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[*** Add your email below if you’d like to get access to our overnight momentum trading chat! Free for a month, then $6/month.
In it, you’ll find both retail and proprietary traders. Guys who work(ed) for SMB, KTG, Avatar, Chimera & Seven Points that you can network and trade alongside with.
Subscribe to my blog
Over the last 7 years, I have exclusively focused on trading. Well, to be fair, it's more so the last 5 years. The first 2 years as a retail trader, I had one of those so called "well-rounded lives". I traded, went out often, hung out after the close with friends & fam, enjoyed snowboarding, camping, and mountain biking more than most.
But, over the last 5 years as a professional trader living in NY and ATX and working out of both offices, I gave up everything, one by one to focus e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Blog Tips & Tricks Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-blog-tips/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-blog-tips/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been here before, you may have visited the Blog Inspiration page. It contains a lot of good and useful resources when it comes to blogging: writing, design, blog challenges, webrings, shortcuts...
Now there's one more: Bear Blog.
It's the blogging platform I use and love. It's also used by many of my favorite bloggers and some of my readers. In other words, it deserves its own Bear section.
These are currently on the list (those marked with * requires an upgraded account):
Convert bear blog CSV exports to markdown files
Random link (external)
Random link (internal) *
Add external link markers
Add a search feature *
Estimated reading time *
Customizing the upvote button
Count your posts
Adding a "reply via email" button
Adding a private feedback box *
Do you have suggestions for things to include? Or maybe you have an idea for a "hack" you would like someone to put together?
Contact me and I will add it to this post.
Happy Bear blogging! 🐻
PS. For official changes and feature suggestions, see the changelog and roadmap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_91"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code June 2024 Release (1.91)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First round of French election: party attacks and a modest traffic dip]]></title>
        <id>66853348a4598c000bd709b9</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/first-round-of-french-election-2024-party-attacks-and-a-modest-traffic-dip"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare mitigated DDoS attacks targeting French political parties during the 2024 legislative elections, as detailed in our ongoing election coverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Declare your AIndependence: block AI bots, scrapers and crawlers with a single click]]></title>
        <id>668274eea4598c000bd707cf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/declaring-your-aindependence-block-ai-bots-scrapers-and-crawlers-with-a-single-click"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help preserve a safe Internet for content creators, we’ve just launched a brand new “easy button” to block all AI bots. It’s available for all customers, including those on our free tier]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Distributional Consequences of Responding Aggressively to Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30686</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/on-the-distributional-consequences-of-responding-aggressively-to-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post discusses the distributional consequences of an aggressive policy response to inflation using a Heterogeneous Agent New Keynesian (HANK) model. We find that, when facing demand shocks, stabilizing inflation and real activity go hand in hand, with very large benefits for households at the bottom of the wealth distribution. The converse is true however when facing supply shocks: stabilizing inflation makes real outcomes more volatile, especially for poorer households. We conclude that distributional considerations make it much more important for policy to take into account the tradeoffs between stabilizing inflation and economic activity. This is because the optimal policy response depends very strongly on whether these tradeoffs are present (that is, when the economy is facing supply shocks) or absent (when the economy is facing demand shocks).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Keshav Dogra, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structural Adjustment and the Washington Consensus Are Not Abandoned in 2000]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Structural-Adjustment-and-the-Washington-Consensus-Are-Not-Abandoned-in-2000"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T09:36:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian bookseller Booktopia in voluntary administration]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7947</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-bookseller-booktopia-voluntary-administration/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T03:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is sad and concerning news. The Melbourne based bookseller had become well ensconced in the Australian literary realm, since being founded about twenty-years ago. The company, which is also listed on the ASX (though trading of shares has been suspended), had been struggling financially in recent years though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Han Ryner - Ethical Individualism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/han-ryner-ethical-individualism?v=1719971059"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T01:44:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Han Ryner
Title: Ethical Individualism
Subtitle: Selected Texts
Date: 2019
Notes: Translated from French to English by Kirk Watson.

Translator’s Introduction
 At the dawn of the 20th century, Europe hosted a brief blossoming of individualistic thought. Inspired by the great thinkers of the preceding century such as Stirner, Ibsen, Nietzsche, and Spencer, they offered a free-thinking, non-dogmatic alternative to the increasingly powerful Marxists and syndicalists of the left, and the economists and theologians of the right. Importantly, this generation of thinkers developed the critique of the State into a critique of society as a whole, which immunized them from recruitment by the anarchist movement. As Ryner says in the Handbook, the anarchists are naive: victory by the anarchist…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize your Java application with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>405bbc736a74a4576b2623243a568f24e835610b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/modernize-your-java-application-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many organizations have critical legacy Java applications that are increasingly difficult to maintain. Modernizing these applications is a necessary, daunting, and risky task that takes the focus off of creating new value or features. This includes undocumented code, outdated frameworks and libraries, security vulnerabilities, a lack of logging and error handling, and a lack of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chetan Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Shevek - Leave, Or Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/lee-shevek-leave-or-else-giving-ultimatums-to-abuse-victims?v=1719968190"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T00:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Lee Shevek
Title: Leave, Or Else
Subtitle: Giving Ultimatums to Abuse Victims
Date: April 10, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2 July 2024 from butchanarchy.medium.com/leave-or-else-a60b0dbac2a6

 Abuse is ubiquitous in our society, and as a result there are very few among us, if any, who have not been abused themselves or in proximity to someone else being abused. Myths about why and how abuse occurs run rampant and the ones that dominate are ones that ultimately serve in the maintenance of the status quo that keeps victims disempowered and silent. As a result, even those few who do actually believe victims of abuse and see the danger such abuse poses to them still often respond to the conditions the victim is entrapped within in ways that ultimately affirm the abuser’s narrative and fur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I like your old music better than your new music]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7938</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-old-music-better-than-new-music/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I might say that of U2, whose music I once really liked, especially the stuff they did in the nineties. Achtung Baby. Zooropa. Pop. Even 2000’s All That You Can’t Leave Behind. These albums mostly represented their electronic music phase. I’d have them on loop for days at a time. I drew the ire of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Blogroll, or to not?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/to-blogroll-or-to-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-02T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I really love the idea of having a Blogroll. When checking out a new blog, after reading and perusing said blog, I typically check to see if it has one. I think it’s one of the best ways to find new people to subscribe to, new content to read, and/or new perspectives to be exposed to. However, I don’t have one on my blog. Hypocritical? Maybe. Or maybe it’s just really personal preference.
I grew up in the days of MySpace, and this irrational want to be included in everyone’s Top 8. Then when you’re in their Top 8, you watch that list like a hawk in case you drop from Top 2 to Top 5, or even worse, drop off altogether. Granted, blogrolls are a bit different since there’s no hard limit on how many can be included (or specified order), but the idea is similar.
You see, I’m fine and OK with no…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>