<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-15T06:28:50.390Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-15T06:28:50.390Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Must be High or Low]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325502</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/15/it-must-be-high-or-low/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T05:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jonathan Cott has written about the meaning of those stories and rhymes we consider to be for children. He has also written about the childlike nature of certain rock and pop songs, especially certain songs by The Beatles and Donovan. He has interviewed artists, musicians, writers and others from Chinua Achebe to John Lennon and many more. His works refer to everyone from Carl Jung to Tony Bennett; Rollo May to the Old Testament; Greg Bateson to Gaston Bachelard. At times, his ability to connect seemingly disparate phenomena is mind-blowing. Other time, one nods their head knowingly at a reference that they might have often considered just to see it verified via Cott’s quotation and argument tying the two things together. Some might consider his considerations too fanciful while others might see them as so simply obvious they wonder why he bothered to even write them down.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post It Must be High or Low appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[mk zariel - ambassador of homosexuality]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mk-zariel-ambassador-of-homosexuality?v=1718394609</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mk-zariel-ambassador-of-homosexuality?v=1718394609"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:50:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: mk zariel
Title: ambassador of homosexuality
Date: Summer 2024
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 queers like us ache to carve ourselves starring roles in the pageant 
 called gay rights. become picture-perfect 
 assimilated gays who’ve never once had an emotional breakdown 
 queers like us can’t have problems can we? if we do, you will realize 
 your hierarchies spell death for our chosen family 
 so queers like us create the illusion of the normal 
 erase the the way a slur not yet reclaimed 
 burns holes in luminous queer skin, our relatives claiming they don’t think of us as gay 
 and worst of all, we’re free: to be complicit in murder, to marry our oppressors 
 but in three fifths of the country, not all that free fro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neltnerb in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683864</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683864"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I do not think it is cynical to assume that Microsoft would sell this to companies as a way to do constant surveillance of their employees with OCR and LLMs used to make it easier for a manager to sift through massive amounts of data.
That's just an actual use case that their true customers would pay for, I think it's awful and should be illegal under any reasonable worker protections but why would they not advertise it this way privately to business customers?
I also don't think it's cynical to think that a manager looking for a reason to get rid of someone will have a much easier time justifying a PIP or just straight up firing someone if they can retroactively have an AI do it for them.
Why wouldn't they be able to ask the system "how much of 's time do they spend doing things on the computer that are not directly related to ?"
Is it technically happening already? Sure, there's nasty nasty spyware being forced on people and it is awful and I hate that those employers are getting away with it. But integrated into the OS, on by default, with a long memory? Just imagine how easy it will be to fire anyone that tries to unionize in an effort to fight against such surveillance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neltnerb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Audrid - What makes you think you can govern me?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-what-makes-you-think-you-can-govern-me?v=1718391451</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-what-makes-you-think-you-can-govern-me?v=1718391451"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Audrid
Title: What makes you think you can govern me?
Date: Summer 2024.
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 What makes you think you can govern me? 
 When my mind is about to explode and fling 
 Shrapnel in every direction and into the void 
 For this soul of mine is weeping, while yours gently 
 Blow sleeping in the gaze of protective eyes. 
 Barrage the barricades of your world ‘til they tumble 
 Crumble onto the doorstep of our anarchist utopia? 
 A ticking fission or fusion bomb around the nuclear family - 
 I cannot wait until it disintegrates into ash 
 It never did anything to me - Blood 
 Lines only weave together pain - Choose 
 Your own kind over the abstract confines 
 Of a triple helix with the extra back 
 Bone of suffering. 
 The bigotry ebbs and flows through our collective 
 Memories that we perhaps should forget but cannot 
 Unsee through flashbacks of those who harmed - 
 Us, through bricks at glass and break the institution 
 That hates us - that seeks to eradicate us 
 Yas I may be extreme but was that ever a bad thing - 
 I’ll just shine with the light of a trillion photons 
 Exploding and releasing the energy 
 Of my ungovernable queer self.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noam Audrid - Dear Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-dear-society?v=1718391083</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/noam-audrid-dear-society?v=1718391083"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Noam Audrid
Title: Dear Society
Date: Summer 2024.
Source: Retrieved on Jun 14 2024 from https://unfuturingzine.com/unfuturing-01-summer24.pdf.

 Dear Society, 
 Telling me the way to go - never fit myself into your gender 
 Confines and even in my disruption their compulsion to fit 
 Me into a box flickers behind… shadows. The flames 
 Burning my mind, or am I burning. Fuck. Their stereotypes. 
 You cannot speak up about anything. Be passionate. 
 Rant about ableism and transphobia and they give strange looks 
 And yeah girls can do that, but I’m not one of them… 
 And my identity of being loud… is this just internalized misogyny…? 
 Head and a broken body, too wrong, but I feel no connection to the physical 
 Right…? 
 I guess that’s a lie. Cannot be stoic. Only a fragment. 
 If …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by segasaturn in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683526</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683526"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My takeaway is that Microsoft has been trying to boil the frog, but slipped and turned the temperature up too quickly. They're retreating for now, but make no mistake that Recall will slowly trickle back into Windows under another name. Every major power broker wants something like Recall to become the norm - bosses to spy on their employees, governments to spy on their citizens/enemies, and tech CEO's to collect training data for AI and target more ads at end users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>segasaturn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by digging in "Microsoft to delay release of Recall AI feature on security concerns"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683432</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40683432"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is confusing and vague to me, which I believe is exactly the intent. It focuses on security, reiterates that security is their top priority (and we know that this is untrue). What were the security problems? They don't even allude to the existence or detection of any specific security problems.
It sounds to me like they're figuring out a new marketing approach, or they're softening the blow by "listening to users" and then rolling out more slowly, when outrage has died down and people will just accept it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>digging</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free trade frenzy: the hidden costs of South Asia's economic gamble]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Free-trade-frenzy-the-hidden-costs-of-South-Asia-s-economic-gamble</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Free-trade-frenzy-the-hidden-costs-of-South-Asia-s-economic-gamble"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As debt pressures rise, South Asia's economic strategies are increasingly revolving around FTAs. The frenzy, however, is not only reshaping the region's trade dynamics, but also a wide array of national legal frameworks, from labour rights to agriculture policies. 
English

/ 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
South Asia, 
Free Trade/Trade Liberalisation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GRAIN</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273335</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T18:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics; new Covid charts: stay safe out there; Kamala!; sleep and memory ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lina Moe: &ldquo;Hard Work&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hard-work</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hard-work"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T16:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The art of Käthe Kollwitz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by benjedwards in "I found a 55 year old bug in the first Lunar Lander game"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40680958</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40680958"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If anyone is curious, in 2009, I discovered that Jim Storer was the author of the first Lunar Lander game and interviewed him about it (and also chronicled the history of the game beyond that). He later provided the source code, which was awesome.
https://technologizer.com/2009/07/19/lunar-lander/index.html
My favorite part is this:
“After leaving high school I never thought about the game again,” says Storer. “Until about a couple of months ago when someone e-mailed me about this, I was completely unaware of any Lunar Lander game other than the one I wrote in high school.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benjedwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Debilitating a Generation”: Expert Warns That Long COVID May Eventually Affect Most Americans]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273327</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/debilitating-a-generation-expert-warns-that-long-covid-may-eventually-affect-most-americans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some updates on long Covid make for an indictment of US public health. Not that that should come as a surprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Fed DSGE Model Forecast—June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30360</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/the-new-york-fed-dsge-model-forecast-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post presents an update of the economic forecasts generated by the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s dynamic stochastic general equilibrium (DSGE) model. We describe very briefly our forecast and its change since March 2024. As usual, we wish to remind our readers that the DSGE model forecast is not an official New York Fed forecast, but only an input to the Research staff’s overall forecasting process. For more information about the model and variables discussed here, see our DSGE model Q & A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Del Negro, Pranay Gundam, Donggyu Lee, Ramya Nallamotu, and Brian Pacula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jacques Rancière: &ldquo;Grand Éditeur&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/grand-editeur</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/grand-editeur"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Hazan (1936-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273309</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our mercurial daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milei’s Latest Plan to Embroil Argentina in Ukraine Conflict Involves Sending Five French Fighter Jets That Cannot Fly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273262</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/mileis-latest-cunning-plan-to-embroil-argentina-in-the-ukraine-conflict-is-to-send-five-fighter-jets-that-cannot-fly.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milei's government appears to be determined to turn Argentina into the first Latin American country to send weapons to Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Officials and Press Starting to Acknowledge Impact of Russian Electric War on Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273308</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/western-officials-and-press-starting-to-acknowledge-impact-of-russian-electric-war-on-ukraine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T10:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Anglospehere press is slowly waking up to the relentlessness and effectiveness of Russia's electric war in Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our meaningless modern lives: Part 1]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45418</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/14/our-meaningless-modern-lives-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog The Most Valuable Kind of Knowledge These lectures aim to provide the reader with knowledge. But what is knowledge? Our lives consist of a small number of infinitely precious moments. What makes it worthwhile to invest these moments in the acquisition of knowledge? Is it the kind of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asad Zaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plain text journaling]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/plain-text-journaling/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/plain-text-journaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T07:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been journalling for a long time now. It's something I don't even think about anymore; just a thing I do. Some people meditate, others pray. I write.
I've published a few essays about how journaling has impacted my life by providing the space for me to reflect on my day. One thing I have never done until this year, however, is read any of my old journals.
This may seem strange, since what is the point of writing if not to be read. But that isn't why I do it. I write as a practice. As a thing that I do. If all my journals were lost in a house fire, I'd be sad, yes. But the documentation of my life isn't what's valuable. That value has already been gleaned through the act itself.
That being said, I tried reading one of my old journals at the beginning of this year and it turns out I can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The edge of extinction]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52771</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/14/the-edge-of-extinction/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T07:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Referring back to this 2002 post defining “neoliberalism”, I find the claim that the “The (UK) Conservative party is hovering on the edge of extinction”. That wasn’t one of my more accurate assessments, and I’m bearing it in mind when I look at suggestions that the party is now “facing a defeat so dramatic it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Way Out in Nuseirat: the Great Hostage Rescue Massacre]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325396</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/no-way-out-in-nuseirat-the-great-hostage-rescue-massacre/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T06:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Americans knew. The Americans helped. The Americans provided the bombs, the helicopters, the fighter jets, the bullets and the tank shells. The Americans watched the attack unfold. They watched from Biden's pier. They watched from drones. They watched as the streets filled with blood, bodies and limbs. Afterward, the Americans praised the rescue operation and said nothing about the dead Palestinian children and women. Nothing about the amputees and the eviscerated. Nothing about the three hostages who were also apparently killed in the Israeli attack, including an American citizen.  More
The post No Way Out in Nuseirat: the Great Hostage Rescue Massacre  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Can’t Fix the Immigration System by Banning Asylum]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325345</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/biden-cant-fix-the-immigration-system-by-banning-asylum/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden once pledged to adopt more humane immigration policies than his predecessor.  But in practice, as immigrant rights advocates have documented, his administration has escalated the attack on the legal right of people facing life-threatening conditions to seek safety. Even though this right is guaranteed regardless of how asylum seekers enter the country, he has sought to restrict access to ports of entry. More
The post Biden Can’t Fix the Immigration System by Banning Asylum appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanted: a Mass Uprising Against the Neoliberal Matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325303</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/wanted-a-mass-uprising-against-the-neoliberal-matrix/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neoliberalism seems impermeable to the facts. The theory is that markets are efficient, and privatization, deregulation, and liberalization will bring about the best of all possible worlds, so if the facts don’t fit the theory, so much the worse for the facts. The image that has haunted me is one from the movie The Matrix, where human beings are plugged into a system that has them dreaming of a pleasant alternate reality while their bodies are being sucked dry of the nutrients and energy to feed alien beings. More
The post Wanted: a Mass Uprising Against the Neoliberal Matrix appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dead Man’s Hand: Betting on Biden and Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325376</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/dead-mans-hand-betting-on-biden-and-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the current presidential election, the betting odds have Donald Trump as the favorite (-109), which estimates his chances at 52%, while Joe Biden is close but behind at +122, which puts his odds at 45%. (By way of definition, these odds mean anyone who bets $109 on Trump to win will receive, if he does win, $100. By contrast, $100 bet on Biden to win will earn you $122 if he prevails.) More
The post Dead Man’s Hand: Betting on Biden and Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Isolated: Why Some Western Capitals Are Shifting Positions on Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325398</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/america-isolated-why-some-western-capitals-are-shifting-positions-on-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 6, Spain joined South Africa’s case at the United Nations top Court, accusing Israel of genocide. This move followed a decision by Madrid and two other western European capitals – Dublin and Oslo – to recognize the state of Palestine, thus breaking ranks with a long-established US-led western policy. As per American thinking,  More
The post America Isolated: Why Some Western Capitals Are Shifting Positions on Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diamonds and Cold Dust: Slaughter at Nuseirat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325291</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/diamonds-and-cold-dust-slaughter-at-nuseirat/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ashes had barely settled on a Rafah tent camp incinerated by an Israeli airstrike before the next, gorged massacre presented itself for posterity’s gloomy archive.  It was intended as a golden operation and had been months in the making.  The rescue of four Israeli hostages, the killing of three others (bound to happen for the expertly inclined), and the massacre of over 274 Palestinians at the Nuseirat refugee camp were the end result.  More
The post Diamonds and Cold Dust: Slaughter at Nuseirat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chomsky & UN Forewarnings Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325382</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/chomsky-un-forewarnings-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently attended a family affair in Upstate NY and was informed that climate change articles, like this one, are too negative, causing close relatives to shutdown and going so far as to ignore articles, too gloomy, too negative, do something more positive. My response: Analyzing the planet’s climate system by studying peer-reviewed scientific publications  More
The post Chomsky & UN Forewarnings Revisited appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A WWII Canadian Soldier Honored for Killing Allied Troops]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325292</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/a-wwii-canadian-soldier-honored-for-killing-allied-troops/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Normandy celebrations of the 80th anniversary of D Day commemorated the victory of the Allies against the Axis powers. But a very different recent celebration in Italy paid tribute to a WWII Allied soldier who shot and killed fellow Allied soldiers. The heroics of the young Italian Canadian officer Captain Tony Scotti shooting French  More
The post A WWII Canadian Soldier Honored for Killing Allied Troops appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End the Israeli War on Gaza and Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325463</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/end-the-israeli-war-on-gaza-and-palestine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight months ago, Israel began a genocidal war against Gaza and the further increase of repression in the West Bank including thousands imprisoned, and expansion of the settlements there. Torture is commonplace of Palestinian prisoners in the West Bank and especially of prisoners in Gaza. 90 per cent of the population of Gaza is hungry,  More
The post End the Israeli War on Gaza and Palestine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bohmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[False Flag Over Ramapo: a Novella in Legal Pleadings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325427</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/false-flag-over-ramapo-a-novella-in-legal-pleadings/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ramapo, New York is per capita one of the most ultra-Orthodox Jewish communities in the United States.  Split between an ardent pro-Israeli/Zionist community and the Satmar’s -one of the largest and most vocal Hasidic dynasties that recognizes neither the state of Israel nor Zionism as representative of Jewish faith or history- until recently Ramapo tried  More
The post False Flag Over Ramapo: a Novella in Legal Pleadings appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stanley L. Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two European Thorns in the Empire’s Side: Rightist Orban and Leftist Fico (and Look What Happened to Him)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325288</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/two-european-thorns-in-the-empires-side-rightist-orban-and-leftist-fico-and-look-what-happened-to-him/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hungary’s prime minister, Viktor Orban may be a far-right politician, but he also opposes the west’s proxy war in Ukraine and that, much more than his extreme conservatism, is what infuriates imperial henchmen. The European Union is in a constant snit over Orban, because every time that organization turns around, he blocks funds or weapons  More
The post Two European Thorns in the Empire’s Side: Rightist Orban and Leftist Fico (and Look What Happened to Him) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Teamsters Bearing Gifts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325467</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/beware-of-teamsters-bearing-gifts-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Except for a handful of insiders in the Teamsters and the Amazon Labor Union (ALU), few of us were aware that negotiations were being held to affiliate the ALU with Teamsters, until the recent announcement. If anything, most of us stopped paying attention to the ALU, which two years ago had an important breakthrough in winning  More
The post Beware of Teamsters Bearing Gifts appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Crypto Industry Dodges Regulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325455</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/how-the-crypto-industry-dodges-regulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent bill passed by the House of Representatives claims to regulate the cryptocurrency industry and protect consumers. But the bill is a Trojan horse designed by an industry flush with cash — the real kind. The Financial Innovation and Technology for the 21st Century Act is the cryptocurrency industry’s big attempt to win favors from Washington.  More
The post How the Crypto Industry Dodges Regulation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Carss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They’re Arresting the Wrong People Inside of Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325423</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/theyre-arresting-the-wrong-people-inside-of-congress/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was arrested again inside of Congress for speaking out against US-backed genocide. Myself and others were brutally tackled and carried out of the room by Capitol Police. I was charged with “crowding, obstructing, or incommoding” for speaking out and holding a sign as the Secretary of State and the Secretary of Defense testified in Congress for  More
The post They’re Arresting the Wrong People Inside of Congress appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia DiNucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caste and the Colonization of Liberal Souls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325461</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/caste-and-the-colonization-of-liberal-souls/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The imagination!  [John] Brown’s faith in its transformative power was boundless…it gave him license to envision his death as an event that might spur the antislavery world to action…right down to “poor, little, dirty, ragged bare-headed and barefooted Slave Boys and Girls, led by some old grey-headed Slave Mother”  bearing witness to his hanging.    – Amy Godine,  More
The post Caste and the Colonization of Liberal Souls appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Losing Our Cool in the Twenty-First Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325386</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/losing-our-cool-in-the-twenty-first-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The odds are that the entire continental United States will swelter through a hotter-than-normal summer this year. And no surprise there. It seems as if that’s been the forecast every spring for years now. But this summer promises to eclipse even the summer of 2023, which, in the Northern Hemisphere, was the hottest since at least the year  More
The post Losing Our Cool in the Twenty-First Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sex, Death and Manuscripts: Ana Magdalena Bach Rises from the Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325537</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/sex-death-and-manuscripts-ana-magdalena-bach-rises-from-the-dead/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:50:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time the name Anna Magdalena appeared in fiction it was attached not to a human character but to an assassin’s rifle. The perpetrators of this crime were themselves a pair of highly paid hitmen: the world’s most-sold author (i.e., its biggest sell-out), James Patterson, and his frontman, ex-President Bill Clinton. Slogging through the  More
The post Sex, Death and Manuscripts: Ana Magdalena Bach Rises from the Dead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325439</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/the-secret-fire/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At midday on May 19th, Santa Fe National Forest (SFNF) fire managers were notified of a new wildfire start within the Chama River Canyon Wilderness on the Coyote Ranger District, northwest of the traditional rural village of Coyote. The cause of the fire ignition was a lightning strike. By the next day, the fire had  More
The post The Secret Fire appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Hyden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Columbia Law Review Article Critical of Israel Sparks Battle Between Student Editors and Their Board, Highlighting Fragility of Academic Freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325350</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/columbia-law-review-article-critical-of-israel-sparks-battle-between-student-editors-and-their-board-highlighting-fragility-of-academic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editors of Columbia Law Review, a prominent journal run by students from the prestigious university’s law school, say the publication’s board of directors urged them on June 2, 2024, to refrain from publishing an article critical of Israel. After the students published the article online the following day, the board, which includes Columbia Law School  More
The post Columbia Law Review Article Critical of Israel Sparks Battle Between Student Editors and Their Board, Highlighting Fragility of Academic Freedom appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neal H. Hutchens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biofuels Manufacturing Found To Be a Significant Source of Hazardous Air Pollution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273267</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/biofuels-manufacturing-found-to-be-a-significant-source-of-hazardous-air-pollution.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:47:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biofuels plants emit serious nasties like formaldehyde.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Governors Need to Do More to Protect Their Low-Income Residents from Climate Change, Especially in the South]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325300</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/governors-need-to-do-more-to-protect-their-low-income-residents-from-climate-change-especially-in-the-south/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tornadoes. Hurricanes. Wildfires. Extreme heat. Welcome to summer. In May, there were more than 500 tornadoes reported, a five-year record. Forecasters predict an above average Atlantic hurricane season, above normal summer temperatures, and an above average wildfire season this summer. Extreme weather and natural disasters must be taken seriously. While all the states in US  More
The post Governors Need to Do More to Protect Their Low-Income Residents from Climate Change, Especially in the South appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A National Chainsaw Epidemic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325336</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/a-national-chainsaw-epidemic/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A national chainsaw epidemic exists in America’s woodlands. A recent article in the New York Times titled “Plans for an Ailing Forest Include Logging” exemplifies this trend. In the article, officials in Oregon say that we must cut down the forests—including green trees to arrest the forest health crisis. Conveniently, precisely what constitutes a forest  More
The post A National Chainsaw Epidemic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resisting Authoritarianism in the Caucasus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325390</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/resisting-authoritarianism-in-the-caucasus/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The country of Georgia, a small nation of 3.7 million people in the Caucasus, has been thrown into a political crisis. In early April, the governing party, Georgian Dream, introduced “a foreign influence law” very similar to the one imposed on Russia in 2012. Vladimir Putin’s law helped transform Russia from a so-called managed democracy  More
The post Resisting Authoritarianism in the Caucasus appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tempest and Posle Media</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is It Time for This War to End? Evidently Not]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325406</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/is-it-time-for-this-war-to-end-evidently-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a major speech May 31, Pres. Biden offered a three-phase plan for ending the Israel-Hamas war, saying “it is time for this war to end.” (I have appended the White House outline of the plan to the end of this blog.) The proposal contains provisions for moving from a temporary to a permanent cease-fire,  More
The post Is It Time for This War to End? Evidently Not appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warren’s New Bill Makes Private Equity’s Death Grip on Hospitals a Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325296</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/warrens-new-bill-makes-private-equitys-death-grip-on-hospitals-a-crime/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private equity’s entrance into health care since 2000 has been dramatic. Both the number of private equity (PE) deals and annual PE investments in health care increased tenfold between 2001 and 2020, and peaked in 2021. Until now, lax corporate transparency and accountability regulations meant that there was nothing anyone could do when corporate owners  More
The post Warren’s New Bill Makes Private Equity’s Death Grip on Hospitals a Crime appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Appelbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ann Stokes Angus: A Memoir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325388</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/ann-stokes-angus-a-memoir/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:43:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1972 I completed a PhD in philosophy at Columbia University. My dissertation subjects were the art historian Ernst Gombrich, the philosopher Nelson Goodman and, also, Adrian Stokes, who wrote about Italian art. I learned about Stokes from my teacher, the English philosopher Richard Wollheim. Little known in the United States, Stokes was a legend  More
The post Ann Stokes Angus: A Memoir appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Carrier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addiction Recovery is Hard. Funding It Shouldn’t Be.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325447</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/addiction-recovery-is-hard-funding-it-shouldnt-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Treating addiction is hard. But as someone who’s in recovery and now helps mothers on their own recovery journey, one thing is very simple: We need more investment in the solutions that work. Every person in recovery has their own story. My grandmother was an American missionary who rescued and adopted my mother — an  More
The post Addiction Recovery is Hard. Funding It Shouldn’t Be. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heidi  Gerard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local and EU Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325421</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/local-and-eu-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:41:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The results of the local and European elections show that Ireland has, for the moment, tilted to the right. However, we live in a volatile world where the prospects of sudden, dramatic change exist. The drift rightwards can be seen in the modest rise in support for FF and FG; in the rise of predominantly  More
The post Local and EU Elections appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kieran Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Valdes Steps Out of a Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325348</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/richard-valdes-steps-out-of-a-dream/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stepping Out of a Dream: A Retrospective 1965 to 2024, is Richard B. Valdes’s first solo retrospective exhibit. It is a retrospective worldview through the lens of a Chicano artist. His artistic voyage in display spans six decades. With more than 45 pieces of artworks in exhibition at the Jean Deleage Art Gallery located in  More
The post Richard Valdes Steps Out of a Dream appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmy Centeno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native Wisdom and Advanced Archaeology in a Time of Surging Wildfires]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325335</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/14/native-wisdom-and-advanced-archaeology-in-a-time-of-surging-wildfires/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a sharp increase in uncontrollable wildfires across the northern U.S. and Canada in recent decades, the Bureau of Indian Affairs and the U.S. Forest Service have been open to new approaches and ways to address the inherent weaknesses of their bureaucracies. Due to their lack of historical understanding of past fire management methods, they  More
The post Native Wisdom and Advanced Archaeology in a Time of Surging Wildfires appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Irina Matuzava</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just keep doing the bit (Karma Yoga Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/just-keep-doing-the-bit-karma-yoga-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been preparing for job interviews (looking to get into genai+backend roles you know). I like building projects and learning new stuff but job search is something that scares me. Partly because of the various uncertainties involved like places to apply, strenous interview processes, where I would work next, what kind of work I will get. It’s not the first time I am going through this process but it sucks (a lot in the beginning atleast). The other aspect is the grind.
Translation: I am not afraid of slap sir, I am afraid of job search
I could be solving some leetcode problems right now, I could be applying right now… I have many things to do even outside job search - oh no - fuck fuck fuck. That’s sort of the state of my mind - atleast in the background. Till I don’t build some momen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What you post determines your tribe]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/tribe/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/tribe/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T05:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What you post determines who you attract. Tweets are like prompts to attract fascinating people towards you based on shared context, ideas, interests, taste, knowledge, and expertise - your "context overlap" determines your tribe.
If you do shitposting, people who are here for fun will join (I think most people love shitposting, because even founders sometimes follow me and my mutuals for memes lol). In my experience, shitposting is often authentic. There's a lot of space for improv replying and leads to fun interactions -> good connections. People like to have fun together. Everyone should do it. It's the backbone of Twitter.
Posting about Rust or AI (I love to see there are several students who post ML stuff and then they follow and hype each other) will attract a different cluster, whil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics anon?]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/are-you-milking-the-basics-anon/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T04:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you milking the basics enough before indulging in optimization
hacks? Don't tell me you are already watching videos on how to do xyz thing fast instead of focusing on basics.
First step of optimization should be to profile if you are milking the basics enough or not.
Leveling up in anything boils down to a few simple processes. I repeat simple but hard to execute - doing minimum viable research to get started, understanding the basics, doing the thing and focusing.
Minimum viable research - finding the correct resources, enough to get started with, finding a mentor or a teacher. The emphasis is to get enough to get started. This is pretty easy especially for knowledge work given we have internet and chatgpt. The basics are more or less similar across most resources plus as you progress…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Gelderloos - Worshipping Power]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-worshipping-power?v=1718332230</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/peter-gelderloos-worshipping-power?v=1718332230"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T02:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Peter Gelderloos
Title: Worshipping Power
Subtitle: An Anarchist View of Early State Formation
Date: January 10, 2017

 “And perhaps solving the mystery of the birth of the State might also permit us to clarify the conditions of the possibility […] of its death.” 
 —Pierre Clastres 
 “Acudid los anarquistas 
 empuñando la pistola hasta el morir 
 con petróleo y dinamita 
 toda clase de gobierno 
 a combatir 
 ¡y destruir!” 
 —“Arroja la Bomba” 
 Spanish anarchist song composed in prison in 1932, popularized in the revolution of 1936 
 Dedicated to Harold H. Thompson and Kuwasi Balagoon, who died in the dungeons of the State after decades of confinement, to Matías Catrileo, shot down in the struggle to regain his people’s land, and to all those who continue fighting, inside and out.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jean-Pierre Voyer - An inquiry into the causes and nature of the misery of people]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-an-inquiry-into-the-causes-and-nature-of-the-misery-of-people?v=1718317284</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-an-inquiry-into-the-causes-and-nature-of-the-misery-of-people?v=1718317284"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:21:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jean-Pierre Voyer
Title: An inquiry into the causes and nature of the misery of people
Date: 2017
Notes: Translated by Isaac Cronin, Roger Gregoire, and Linda Lanphear. Originally published by Champ Libre, 1976, Paris
Source: Text provided to library by the publisher.

Introduction
The Wicked Ways of This 
Devious World Explained 
An Inquiry into the Nature and Causes 
of the Misery of People
 In the mid 70s in Europe and the United States, the wave of radical revolt had ebbed. In the Bay Area, the Situationist milieu was quietly falling into inglorious disarray with vicious infighting over internal hierarchies based in part on male domination of the network. The New York-based former members of the American Situationist International had largely gone silent, had disappeared from t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jean-Pierre Voyer - It’s Crazy How Many Things Don’t Exist]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-it-s-crazy-how-many-things-don-t-exist?v=1718316915</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jean-pierre-voyer-it-s-crazy-how-many-things-don-t-exist?v=1718316915"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Jean-Pierre Voyer
Title: It’s Crazy How Many Things Don’t Exist
Subtitle: Selected Writings of Jean-Pierre Voyer
Date: 2015
Notes: Cruel Hospice 2015. “Reich, Mode d’emploi” was translated by Ken Knabb under the title “Reich, How to Use;” the other texts were translated collaboratively by Isaac Cronin, Roger Gregoire, and Linda Lanphear. Little Black Cart.
Source: PDF source provided to library by publisher

Introduction
Who is Jean-Pierre Voyer?
 French social thinkers don’t have the best reputation in America. Typically they are seen as humorless, self-important, elitist intellectuals whose purpose is to tell the world not only what to believe, but what to do with those beliefs. We know Jean-Pierre Voyer, and he is none of those things. He has worked as a cab driver, a plumber an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What about anti-virus apps? On going #IndieOS with Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7810</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/what-about-anti-virus-apps-on-going-indieos-with-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I wrote a few days ago, I’m in the process of trying out Linux operating systems, specifically Linux Mint. With the release of Windows 11, I think Microsoft has (finally) jumped the shark. Others will probably argue that happened long before Win 11 came along. They’re likely right. I’ve been doing a lot of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you use Vison Pro in a group or social setting?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7807</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/use-vison-pro-group-social-setting/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T20:30:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or when snuggled up on the sofa, say watching a movie, with your better half? I feel isolated when watching media, and it’s also much harder to snack and get cozy. This is a point — raised by Hacker News/Y Combinator member archagon — and is not something I’d thought of, in regards to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writers not using AI being accused of using AI… by AI apps]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7800</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/writers-not-using-ai-accused-using-ai-by-ai-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T20:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not anti-AI (well, not too much), but when there’s a one-hundred percent reliance on their abilities, and more crucially, the judgements some AI apps make, then there’s a problem. News that (human) writers and journalists, who have never used AI-powered tools in their work, but are being fired for apparently doing so, because an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On prioritising what you want to learn]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/on-prioritising-what-you-want-to-learn/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/on-prioritising-what-you-want-to-learn/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it's easy to get distracted by the current discourse on what people are learning (or posing to learn).
you need to be careful on prioritising what you want to learn.
somehow these days the meme has been let's do hardware, c is cracked, we will go cuda. it's downstream of what influential figures like karpathy are pursuing.
problem is, mere exposure can make you feel more interested in new things like gpu programming, writing llm in c and unconsciously prioritise the same when let's say you were already trying to learn about the transformer architecture. (shiny object syndrome sort of situation lol)
frequently hopping bandwagons will lead to scattered attention and you don't want that. now i get it, you gotta pursue your intellectual curiosity but you also need to think from your usecase point of view.
what do i require to learn more urgently? what will allow me to build the thing i want to build faster? what is more relevant for me based on my previous understanding? is it worth going this deep in the stack for now?
depending on the time you have, you can pursue more than 2 things in parallel but you gotta stick to what you have decided atleast for a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by the_snooze in "Group chats rule the world"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40673318</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40673318"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T19:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>Salons and groups have always existed but why the recent shift to private discourse?
Because the public internet makes it too easy for people to sell you stuff, extract value from you, or harass you. Private chats are human-scale environments where understandable social norms---not commerce, algorithms, or formal rules---drive the interactions. It's an authentic experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>the_snooze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273272</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Electoral college moves toward Trump (slightly); Hillary Clinton services AIPAC; CDC publishes tweet with upside down mask; mushrooms and citizen science ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by michaelt in "Please maintain eye contact for the duration of the ad"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40672233</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40672233"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T17:22:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do note that this twitter account is posting fake screenshots of product ideas.
Other posts include "Google Meet option to punish interrupters by sending them to meeting jail" "iOS camera lock if you record too much concert footage" and "Spotify feature to lock Christmas music until after Thanksgiving"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>michaelt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of unstructured data with RAG]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unstructured data holds valuable information about codebases, organizational best practices, and customer feedback. Here are some ways you can leverage it with RAG, or retrieval-augmented generation.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-13-unlocking-the-power-of-unstructured-data-with-rag/">Unlocking the power of unstructured data with RAG</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by minisooftwin in "Microsoft Chose Profit over Security, Whistleblower Says"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670551</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40670551"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> “If you’re faced with the tradeoff between security and another priority, your answer is clear: Do security,” the company’s CEO, Satya Nadella, told employees.
Satya's model of making security a priority at Microsoft:
- Cram ads in every nook and corner of Windows. Left, right, centre, back, front, everywhere. What else is an operating system for?
- Install a recorder which records everything you do. For the benefit of users of course - you know, what if a user missed an ad and wants to go back and see what they missed.
- Send a mail to your employees and tell them "Do security". Mission accomplished - Microsoft is now the most secure platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>minisooftwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intrigue About Exit of Mustafa Nayyem, Ukraine Restoration Funding Chief and Maidan Revolt Instigator, Diverts Attention from Boneheadness of the Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273256</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/intrigue-about-exit-of-mustafa-nayyem-ukraine-restoration-funding-chief-and-maidan-revolt-instigator-diverts-attention-from-boneheadness-of-the-scheme.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overdue discussion of the Ukraine restoration con, with tooth-gnashing over the exit of Mustafa Nayyem as a tell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MLow: Meta’s low bitrate audio codec]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21258</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/13/web/mlow-metas-low-bitrate-audio-codec/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we support real-time communication (RTC) for billions of people through our apps, including WhatsApp, Instagram, and Messenger.  We are working to make RTC accessible by providing a high-quality experience for everyone – even those who might not have the fastest connections or the latest phones. As more and more people have relied on [...]
Read More...
The post MLow: Meta’s low bitrate audio codec appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Etheryte in "Indian startup 3D prints rocket engine in 72 hours"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40669488</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40669488"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T13:37:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The machine also automatically outputs a report that details any deviations during printing, removing the need for postfabrication qualification.
Anyone who's previously worked with 3D printing knows that this simply does not pass any kind of a sniff test. Both preventing and detecting internal defects is one of the, if not the hardest problem in 3D printing. There are many large companies trying to find ways to reliably solve just this problem alone. Saying that this method doesn't require any checks after production is simply false.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Etheryte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[words and their rhythms]]></title>
        <id>https://wordplay.bearblog.dev/words-and-their-rhythms/</id>
        <link href="https://wordplay.bearblog.dev/words-and-their-rhythms/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T12:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Music — the art of weaving ethereal emotion and unseen sound together to form a tapestry of tangible sensation to those who listen.
More than mere entertainment, music is a vessel for intimate meaning, a medium through which the most profound truths and innermost feelings can be expressed.
Michael Spitzer, a renowned musicologist, speaks about the origins of our innate musical inclinations, tracing them back to the Australopithecus, our southern ape ancestors who roamed the Earth over 4,000,000 years ago.
He unveils the profound connection between our walking patterns and the very essence of rhythm: when we stride forth, our steps fall into a natural, cadenced beat.
Spitzer's insights shed light on the intricate interplay between our physical and auditory realms. They reveal that the same …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273244</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T10:58:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our relaxing daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christopher Bickerton: &ldquo;After Euroscepticism&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/after-euroscepticism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/after-euroscepticism"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T10:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The assimilation of the far right.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Dollar Doomsters Have Got It All Wrong”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273239</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/dollar-doomsters-have-got-it-all-wrong.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T09:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why reports of the [imminent] death of the dollar are greatly exaggerated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Money Is Stored Time]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/money-is-stored-time/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/money-is-stored-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most helpful perspective of looking at money is stored time. You can exchange money for time or time for money. It's like a balance. To make money you need to invest time. And you get back time by spending money. That can be time saved by hiring someone to do something for you. Even when buying a nice painting you are buying the stored time of a painter(not to mention the talent).
This perspective is helpful as it gives a clear motivation. You would want to leverage your time to make a lot of money. This can be working efficiently at things where you exchange your time for money like a job or freelance work. But such things only scale linearly. True leverage is owning a piece of something. Something valuable. Something exponential. This can be taking the time to build products that people want, invest or have equity.
On the other side of the equation, you want to make sure you are not doing anything stupid with your time. Let's say you spend 1 hour cooking to save money. Is the value of the saved money less or more than the value of 1 hour of your time? Have you ever thought about it? Cooking for fun or just as a hangout with friends or lack of healthier alternatives is a different value proposition. One that you might be more than happy to make.
Thinking of your time and money as an interchangeable value store gives a framework that you can leverage in your favour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The productivity/pay gap and phony debates]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45414</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/13/the-productivity-pay-gap-and-phony-debates/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker New York Times columnist Peter Coy did a piece yesterday questioning the existence of a gap between productivity growth and the typical worker’s pay. This gap was established decades ago by my friends and former colleagues at the Economic Policy Institute (EPI). The fact that it is now being questioned says a lot […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by immortan in "Serious Sam handled massive amounts of enemies on 56k modem connections"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40666661</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40666661"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T06:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was one the developers responsible for implementing the netcode on Serious Sam.  We often slept under the desks in the offices at croteam after lurking usenet.  One post in particular described the QuakeWorld prediction system which inspired us.  That night we coded a simplistic mvp as a colleague (hi dan) tested it over an old 486 nix machine acting as a router that we could simulate lag with.  This was well before the actual game was built around it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>immortan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta trains large language models at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21330</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/12/data-infrastructure/training-large-language-models-at-scale-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T22:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we continue to focus our AI research and development on solving increasingly complex problems, one of the most significant and challenging shifts we’ve experienced is the sheer scale of computation required to train large language models (LLMs). Traditionally, our AI model training has involved a training massive number of models that required a comparatively [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta trains large language models at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iron Triangle - Richmond, CA]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/iron-triangle-richmond-ca/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/iron-triangle-richmond-ca/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T21:41:01.432Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ricoh GRIIIx I reserved at the beginning of May finally came in earlier this month. The camera has a bit of a learning curve that I'm still getting used to, but am really enjoying the portability of it. Although I'm used to shooting with a 35mm, I'm still finding myself having to work around a 40mm. I think at the end of the day, this is still better for me than a 28mm (that the GRIII has) since I prefer tighter frames.


Marty's Grill has pretty decent Cheesesteak, although obviously not comparable to an authentic Philly Cheesesteak. LSC also seems to like their burgers.

First post on this platform. It's already a breath of fresh air compared to WP 😮‍💨]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software vendors… supercharge their apps with AI. But why?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7796</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/software-vendors-supercharge-apps-ai-but-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a disturbing trend, vendors of software and apps, in particular those that have been around for years, suddenly introducing AI functionality. Indeed, whose idea was this? What Apple announced looks like more of the same that’s been offered lately. Help writing emails that don’t need to be written, bad generative images that look […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "The GJK Algorithm: A weird and beautiful way to do a simple thing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40663042</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40663042"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T20:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent about a year struggling with GJK back in the 1990s.
It's useful for collision detection in 3D, and it can also be used as a closest-points algorithm. As a closest-points algorithm, it's easy to understand the basics. You have two convex solids. Start with a random point on each, and get the distance between those points. On each solid, try to improve the distance by advancing along each edge from the current point. Pick the new closest point. Repeat.
This stops working when the closest point is no longer a vertex. That's when the "simplex" concept is needed. The closest points can be vertex-vertex, vertex-edge, vertex-face, edge-edge, edge-face (no unique solution) and face-face (no unique solution). The simplex thing is really doing a case analysis of those cases.
Lots of things go wrong in practice. If you are doing a physics engine, objects will often settle into face-face contact. A single-point collision model will then result in vibration or incorrect movement. Also, as positions settle into face-face contact, the GJK algorithm runs into a small difference of large values problem that can result in a complete loss of floating point significance. 
The termination condition can also cause infinite looping.
In theory, this is an elegant solution, but it's a difficult numerical analysis problem.
Despite that, it's probably the fastest approach to the problem. It's O(log N) in normal cases, and O(1) for situations where the positions are closest to the previous positions and you use the last solution as the starting point.
The late Prof. Steven Cameron at Oxford did a lot of work on getting GJK right.
I used GJK in "Falling Bodies", the first commercial 3D ragdoll system, in the late 1990s.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Automation for SAP on AWS Operations using Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>eb364b2e48c0d12e84d148bc9bf27c3a87452c88</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-your-automation-for-sap-on-aws-operations-using-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on discussions with several SAP on AWS customers, we have discovered that the number of SAP administration or operational task requirements often exceed the capacity of the available team. Due to lack of time, resources, and heavy focus on operations, strategic initiatives like digital transformations often remain unaddressed. Although 1P and 3P automation solutions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bidwan Baruah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In May, we experienced one incident that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-12-github-availability-report-may-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: May 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryandrake in "Star botanist likely made up data about nutritional supplements, new probe finds"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40661641</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40661641"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My pet theory: Nobody wants to go up against a very charismatic phony in what will almost certainly turn into a battle of wits instead of a battle of facts.
Our entire society deifies charismatic phonies. They are the ones that get elevated to the highest positions in politics and the C-level business suite. They're always the heroic Main Character. They build up cult followings. They often look so good, speak so smoothly and have those irresistible Ivy League mannerisms. You're supposed to like them and help elevate them even higher.
Do you want to expose this person? The Main Character? You better be right, and you better be ready to have the full force of his charm, persuasion, and cult following at your throat forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryandrake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining large-scale AI capacity at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21309</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/12/production-engineering/maintaining-large-scale-ai-capacity-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T18:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta is currently operating many data centers with GPU training clusters across the world. Our data centers are the backbone of our operations, meticulously designed to support the scaling demands of compute and storage. A year ago, however, as the industry reached a critical inflection point due to the rise of artificial intelligence (AI), we [...]
Read More...
The post Maintaining large-scale AI capacity at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilv in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40659620</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40659620"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> If a founder cashes out 10% of their position for $500k @ $25M Series A valuation, that de-risks a lot of their personal life. But when the startup ends up selling for $250M, that $500k of 'early' selling would have been worth $5M (less any dilution between rounds) - hard not to regret the choice in that case even if hedging is going to be the correct choice 99% of the time.
IMHO, it's very easy not to regret, with those particular numbers.
I'd take $500K now plus possibly $45M later -- over $0 now and possibly $50M later.
I'd take that deal even if "possibly" were "guaranteed".
(Who might regret that is a founder who was otherwise already wealthy.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mental Yoga]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/mental-yoga/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/mental-yoga/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["All of humanity's problems stem from man's inability to sit quietly in a room." — Blaise Pascal
I'm constantly surprised, and, by this point in my life, I shouldn't be, but I am. What of? People who feel the need to constantly be busy or doing this, and that, and, well, the other. Is it something that happened slowly, over night, I wonder? Is it since the advent of smart phones, or maybe TV even? Or was it always there and I just didn't notice it?
Because, I'm of a mind that I really don't feel the need to be constantly doing something, anything, or going somewhere to do something (like sports), whether to participate or watch. I'm not always in front of a screen, or TV. I have a life outside of smart gadgets that involves me walking around a garden, or sitting in a park staring at, well,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macron’s gamble and the myth of the Republican Barrier]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52764</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/12/macrons-gamble-and-the-myth-of-the-republican-barrier/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emmanuel Macron’s decision to call legislative elections in France, following a strong showing for the extreme-right-wing Rassemblement National of Marine Le Pen constitutes an extreme risk. No doubt he thinks that either the RN will fail to get as many seats as they hope under France’s two-stage election system or he calculates that since he […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deaths of infants and young children in Gaza. A fact-based estimate.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45429</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/12/deaths-of-infants-and-young-children-in-gaza-a-fact-based-estimate/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To the death toll of the violence in Gaza, around 15.000 additional deaths of infants and children between 1 and 5 have to be added. This is a rough and, in my opinion, a lower-bound estimate. However, the calculations are based on robust information, and sizeable additional mortality in infants and young children in Gaza […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 years of Project Galileo]]></title>
        <id>6668ec88e955c4000a8b4dd4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrating-10-years-of-project-galileo"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years ago today, Cloudflare launched Project Galileo, a program which today provides security services, at no cost, to more than 2,600 independent journalists and nonprofit organizations around the world supporting human rights, democracy, and local communities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lrvick in "Raspberry Pi is now a public company"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656761</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656761"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I only ever bought Pis because it was a mission focused company.
Now that they are in stock-price-go-up mode, I am inclined to buy and promote cheap clones, and I expect most will feel the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lrvick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by doodda in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656617</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40656617"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post has managed to piss off everyone: employees who didn't realize founders were getting liquidity events while they're still sitting on their more-often-than-not valueless equity, and founders who feel they've earned it and don't like the implication they haven't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>doodda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Paul Wolfowitz (2005-2007) to Ajay Banga (2023-...): the US President's men control the World Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/From-Paul-Wolfowitz-2005-2007-to-David-Malpass-2019-the-US-President-s-men</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/From-Paul-Wolfowitz-2005-2007-to-David-Malpass-2019-the-US-President-s-men"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Finbarr in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654678</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654678"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secondary at Series A is very rare. Part of the reason more early employees don't get included in secondary sales is because of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 14e-2. If you have more than 10 sellers involved, the transaction can be considered a tender offer, which triggers additional regulatory requirements and disclosures.
> As of 4 months ago I left a very successful stealth startup (which grew to 40M in ARR in two years) to become a founder and that is when it clicked - I expected to feel stressed, pressured, and the weight of all of the risk I was taking.
Please let us all know how that's working out for you in 5-10 years. 4 months in and no stress? Must be easy riding from here!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Finbarr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by josh2600 in "Silicon Valley's best kept secret: Founder liquidity"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654349</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40654349"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best startups have a concept which is summed up thusly:
“We all go to the pay window at the same time.”
It’s ok for founders to take a little bit of money off of the table if they extend that to their employees as well. Asymmetry is where things get weird.
I’ve seen many founders who got deep into the fundraising cycles without ever realizing they could take a cent out. VCs will constantly tell you to let it all ride, and sometimes that works out, but for most people, having a little bit of financial security while you’re trying to change the world is necessary.
The best startups figure out how to manage liquidity through financing in a way that aligns incentives, keeps the goalposts at the mission, while allowing their teams to thrive.
It’s about alignment. If everyone is pulling in the same direction you’re going to execute the vision. Whether you win in the startup lottery is up to the threads of fate, but alignment is the straightest path towards a result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>josh2600</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Works – AWS Region in Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>8da48ee2807e1e4e56d1d5e36b5355877d24b331</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/in-the-works-aws-region-in-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T03:12:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we’re announcing that a new AWS Region will be coming to Taiwan by early 2025. The new AWS Asia Pacific (Taipei) Region will consist of three Availability Zones at launch, and will give AWS customers in Taiwan the ability to run workloads and store data that must remain in Taiwan. Each of the Availability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini - International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-international-network-of-action-and-solidari?v=1718153607"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini
Title: International Network of Action and Solidarity – Informal Anarchist Federation
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/01/05/ccf_int_net>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 “Solidarity is a constant attack against the system and society, an act where the words fabrication, innocent, guilty, do not fit. Because as revolutionaries it is our duty to always be guilty for this system, always dangerous and always proud of our choices. We are not persecuted for our ideas, but because it seemed poor to us to not transubstantiate them into actions.” 
 (Gerasimos Tsakalos member of the prisoners cell of C.C.F.). 
 Real solidarity between revolutionary consciences and groups of comrades is what the dominators fear most…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - 2008’s communiques]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-2008-s-communiques?v=1718153185"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: 2008’s communiques
Date: December 1, 2010
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3269>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Communique on the arson against the French press agency (Athens, 3/12/2008)
 While the peaceful citizens where enjoying the coffee break of their inexistance in the paved street of Kolonaki, we set ourselves for once again under the “services” of destruction and prepared a new gift out of idyllic ashes. With these, we send our revolutionary greetings to the French comrades that selected to attack the network of the high speed trains, sabotaging the routes of everyday hurry and anxiety, of a determined pre-set life imposed by the bio-authority to its subjects. 
 Striking at the ordinary flaw of the system, using aggres…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Post-anarchism Today]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-post-anarchism-today?v=1718149008</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-post-anarchism-today?v=1718149008"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T23:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Post-anarchism Today
Date: 2014-01-12
Source: <journals.uvic.ca/index.php/adcs/issue/view/1258>

Editorial — Post-anarchism Today
 Lewis Call{1}
 Welcome to Post-anarchism Today. This is certainly not USA Today, et ce n’est certainement pas Aujourd’hui en France. Indeed, it is a refreshing antidote to all such discourses of modern state capitalism. During its short but colourful existence, post-anarchism has always been libertarian and socialist in its basic philosophical outlook: that’s the anarchism part. But post-@ has also maintained its independence from modern rationalism and modern concepts of subjectivity: that’s the post- part. As I survey post-anarchism today, I find to my surprise and delight that both parts are stronger than ever. It’s now clear t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 9, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240611"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 9dev in "Home-Cooked Software and Barefoot Developers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40651618</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40651618"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:18:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I have learnt one thing working in software engineering, specifically on AI-enabled products empowering junior engineers, and using Copilot professionally, it’s that you need even more experience to detect the subtleties in the lack of the models understanding of your domain, your specific intent. If you don’t know exactly what you’re after, and use the LLM as a sparring partner to bounce your ideas off, you’re in for a lot of pain.
Depending on the way you phrase questions, ChatGPT will gleefully suggest you a wrong approach, just because it’s so intent on satisfying your whim instead of saying No when it would be appropriate.
And in addition to that, you don’t learn by figuring out a new concept. If you already have a feeling of the code you would write anyway, and only treat the model as a smart autocomplete, that doesn’t matter. But for an apprentice, or a layperson, that will keep code as scary and unpredictable as before. I don’t think that should be the answer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>9dev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Well-built furniture should last centuries, not a couple of years]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7793</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/well-built-furniture-should-last-centuries-not-couple-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Bray: When Lauren was pregnant with a child who’s now turning 25, we purchased a comfy dark-brown leather sofa which fits our living room nicely. What with kids and relatives and employees and cats and Standards Comittees and friends and book clubs and socials, the butt-support cushions had, a quarter century later, worn out. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by spencerchubb in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649334</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incredible
"The fact that I started a new career all over again, at the bottom of the ladder, after being fired by IBM and rejected by family and friends . . . may also give hope to others trapped in similar situations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>spencerchubb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mlsu in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649244"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recommend reading Lynn's story, written in her own words:
https://ai.eecs.umich.edu/people/conway/RetrospectiveT.html
It is amazing, tragic, and triumphant in so many ways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mlsu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DonHopkins in "Lynn Conway has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649014</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40649014"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lynn Conway co-wrote "the book" on VLSI design, "Introduction to VLSI Systems", created and taught this historic VLSI Design Course in 1978, which was the first time students designed and fabricated their own integrated circuits, including James Clark (SGI) who made the Geometry Engine, and Guy L Steel (MIT) who made the Scheme Microprocessor.
She invented superscalar architecture at IBM, just to be fired in 1968 after she revealed her intention to transition, then 52 years later IBM formally apologized to her in 2020. She successfully rebooted her life, invented and taught VLSI design to industry pioneers who founded many successful companies based on the design methodology she invented, wrote the book on, and personally taught to them, and then she became a trans activist who helped many people transition, find each other, and avoid suicide, fight abuse and bigotry, and find acceptance, by telling her story and building an online community.
Lynn Conway receives 2009 IEEE Computer Society Computer Pioneer Award:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i4Txvjia3p0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DonHopkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we improved push processing on GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Pushing code to GitHub is one of the most fundamental interactions that developers have with GitHub every day. Read how we have significantly improved the ability of our monolith to correctly and fully process pushes from our users.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-06-11-how-we-improved-push-processing-on-github/">How we improved push processing on GitHub</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticker Anxiety and the Idea of Permanence]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/sticker-anxiety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to LOVE collecting stickers, and in some ways, I still do. Every time I traveled or visited some place, if they had stickers, I would get at least one. They were my souvenirs from all the places I visited, each sticker told some kind of story or memory.
Over the years, I started facing a dilemma that I never truly faced when I was collecting other things like magnets or keychains: where do I put them? The idea of permanence gave me some unneeded anxiety. On one hand, I loved the idea of decorating my laptop with the stickers, but the thought of losing those stickers when my laptop died (because they all inevitable do), made me super sad. This hesitation led to a growing collection of stickers sitting unused, each waiting for that perfect place that never seemed to come.
The crazy th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21299</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/11/core-infra/mobileconfig-meta-mixed-reality-mr/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MobileConfig enables developers to centrally manage a mobile app’s configuration parameters in our data centers. Once a parameter value is changed on our central server, billions of app devices automatically fetch and apply the new value without app updates. These remotely managed configuration parameters serve various purposes such as A/B testing, feature rollout, and app [...]
Read More...
The post Unlocking the power of mixed reality devices with MobileConfig appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jedberg in "All three game console makers have now abandoned X integration"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40647128</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40647128"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T15:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amusingly this was posted on reddit, and the top comments were all "What's X?" "Oh they mean Twitter why doesn't the headline say that?" "I thought this was some Xbox integration, didn't realize it was Twitter".
Talk about the worst rebrand ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jedberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sofixa in "Norway discovers Europe's largest deposit of rare earth metals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646825</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40646825"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On one hand, it's unfair that a country already very rich with natural resources discovers more of them.
On the other hand, if there is a country which can be trusted to exploit natural resources in a way that benefits the whole country and its population, and not fall down the resource curse[1], it's Norway.
1 - https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Resource_curse]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sofixa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Audit Manager extends generative AI best practices framework to Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>f0f3c70728357d6ed187ea0df993809736f41c25</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-audit-manager-extends-generative-ai-best-practices-framework-to-amazon-sagemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain comprehensive visibility with the AWS Audit Manager generative AI best practices framework v2, which now includes Amazon SageMaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify AWS CloudTrail log analysis with natural language query generation in CloudTrail Lake (preview)]]></title>
        <id>24bdb2fd2e9ad8e57868d4acc1da126f35a18e52</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-aws-cloudtrail-log-analysis-with-natural-language-query-generation-in-cloudtrail-lake-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline compliance and security analysis using natural language query generation. Ask questions like "What errors occurred last month?" and get ready-to-run SQL queries tailored to your needs – no technical expertise required.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon GuardDuty Malware Protection for Amazon S3]]></title>
        <id>dd44be812e425caecd4fb1915afa474d215f2431</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-guardduty-malware-protection-for-amazon-s3/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty expands malware scanning to secure S3 uploads, enabling continuous monitoring and isolation of malicious files without infrastructure overhead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM Access Analyzer Update: Extending custom policy checks & guided revocation]]></title>
        <id>940b08797e1a3df84f46252ee98dfbdd72457eea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/iam-access-analyzer-update-extending-custom-policy-checks-guided-revocation/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New custom policy checks for critical resources, public access detection, and guided revocation to remove unused permissions - proactively securing AWS environments with tailored analysis and actionable insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS adds passkey multi-factor authentication (MFA) for root and IAM users]]></title>
        <id>21e15c1e7596eeb37b7d4390f7e9925a4b0eb8aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-adds-passkey-multi-factor-authentication-mfa-for-root-and-iam-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortify your AWS account security with new passkey MFA and mandatory root user MFA. Experience seamless authentication while bolstering protection against unauthorized access.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hate reading]]></title>
        <id>https://ree.bearblog.dev/hate-reading/</id>
        <link href="https://ree.bearblog.dev/hate-reading/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:58:59.423Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever watched a show because of how annoying it is, or maybe it makes you feel angry but you just can’t stop consuming it, perhaps akin to watching a train wreck?
That’s how it feels reading my RSS feed these days.
Perhaps the biggest mistake I made was adding some aggregator feeds, one that features posts from various uncurated blogs. Which is weird because it didn’t feel that way before, but now.. I’m not quite sure what happened.
When I get lucky, I get to read and discover some nice things happening to a stranger, or perhaps read about their current struggles and dilemma. When I’m not so lucky (which is half the time), I get to read how AI is the next big inevitable shining future, and make a million dollars in a few months with a written ad every three paragraphs.
I guess it’s time to clean up my morning newspaper and manually curate it if I want to read quality human posts from now on. I feel sad for all the new, worthy blogs I won’t get to randomly discover because of this change, but I know I will eventually find my way to it if I’m meant to encounter it.
Life has always been that way, and I know it always will.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Student protests and academic freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52754</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/11/on-student-protests-and-academic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T09:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier post (here), prompted by some writings by Jacob T. Levy, I defended the idea that student protests can fall under academic freedom. My argument for this starts from the fact that while many universities can have mission specific interpretations of the latitude and constraints on how they interpret academic freedom (non-trivially constrained […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perinomics: a yet to exist discipline]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45410</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/11/perinomics-a-yet-to-exist-discipline/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Edward Fullbrook Humankind urgently needs a new discipline.  Our very survival may depend on it.  Natural science tells us that the economy now threatens humanity with calamity and potentially with extinction; and the daily news tells us that the economy’s forty-year upward redistribution of wealth, income and power threatens democracy and social order.  But […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Fullbrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lz400 in "Noam Chomsky 'no longer able to talk' after 'medical event'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40643491</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40643491"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T07:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chomsky was doing so many podcasts up to the moment he disappeared from the radar presumably due to medical issues. I've seen him going for 2 hours with some nobody with 5K followers, being asked juvenile and stupid questions and answering with the patient of a Saint. He looked quite diminished physically, elderly and frail but mentally he's always sharp and his recall and memory is scary.
I feel that in his later years he made a conscious effort to talk to young people and made them aware of the history and depth of the problems the world is facing, and he used very modern avenues to do so, like podcast interviews. I will always have the highest degree of respect for this man and an admiration for his integrity, sensitivity and scholarship.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lz400</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[so it begins (pick one)]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/first-days-work/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/first-days-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first two days at work have been alright. People have been pretty nice, which is always a good start. Orientation is a little messy though. I started on Monday with maybe twelve or so other new hires, mostly summer interns. The trainings are geared more heavily towards them and less towards us full-timers, which I totally understand, but it has meant that there are empty blocks in my calendar when I have no idea where to go or what to do.
My team's pretty small — there are only four or five of us total spread out across the globe — and I'm the only new hire, so I'm on my own when the other new hires group up by team and eat lunch together in the cafeteria. I ate lunch alone today, which was somehow more awful than I anticipated. Social anxiety hits me hard at work.
On Monday I had lunc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by userbinator in "Ship Something Every Day"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641762"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T02:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMHO "every day" is far too frequent, and this ADHD-ish attitude is one of the reasons why the quality of average software has gone down the drain. Developers need to step back, think more deeply, and not worry about being pressured into "shipping code" that barely works.
The dopamine rush of your code being shipped
This frequent overstimulation leads to less ability for long-term attention. When I taught programming, I saw plenty of beginners do this, especially with an IDE, and the addictive nature of being able to edit and run to see the changes immediately lead to many of them falling into an unproductive rapid iteration loop where they were barely even thinking about what they were doing, just making random changes until something seemed to work.
Your team (and manager) sees you're working
Tough problems need time to solve, and you won't see much meanwhile. If needing to put on a show for others is more important than actually working, something is very wrong.
Your git commit streak looks good
Yes, people say this doesn't matter. But I'm sure people like recruiters look at GitHub profiles, and an empty page isn't a great look.
Optimising for metrics never works for those who can see through the illusion, and that's an increasing number of people over time. If I was a recruiter and saw that sort of activity, I wouldn't think of it as more than someone just putting on a show --- especially if the majority of those commits are effectively "thrashing" or "churning".
The satisfaction (and mental benefits) of getting something done
I can personally say that the satisfaction is far bigger the longer you've persevered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>userbinator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rishabhjain1198 in "Apple's On-Device and Server Foundation Models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641415</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40641415"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T01:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For people interested in AI research, there's nothing new here.
IMO they should do a better job of referencing existing papers and techniques. The way they wrote about "adaptors" can make it seem like it's something novel, but it's actually just re-iterating vanilla LoRA. It was enough to convince one of the top-voted HackerNews comments that this was a "huge development".
Benchmarks are nice though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rishabhjain1198</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call to support Australia’s most at-risk entities]]></title>
        <id>6650a29807441c000a06ea10</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/heeding-the-call-to-support-australias-most-at-risk-entities"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T00:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heeding the call for industry to step up support of Australia's most at-risk entities, Cloudflare and CI-ISAC are teaming up to help protect Australia’s General Practitioner clinics]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carly Ramsey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bedobi in "Deterioration of local community a major driver of loss of play-based childhood"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640212</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40640212"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The design of the physical environment is in no small part responsible for this. Don't believe me go to Europe and Japan where kids are still allowed to walk and bike to school, to friends places and just in general play and exist outside unattended to a much higher degree than in the US. Because in the US they would be roadkill, and even if they somehow survived outside of a car, car centric design means there's nowhere for them to go on foot or by bike anyway. Everything is too far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bedobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just enough social media]]></title>
        <id>https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/</id>
        <link href="https://pcalv.es/just-enough-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:50:21.615Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve had this paragraph on the home page of my personal website for a while now:
Disconnected from social media, but will always answer an email.
My retreat from social media was gradual and uneventful. I left Facebook so long ago that I barely remember what I used it for. I left Instagram well before it became the weird jumble of videos, shorts and occasionally photos it is today. People trying to be brands, brands posing as people. Twitter broke my heart - it connected me to many cool people, helped me find an audience as a musician, and led to lifelong friendships. And then it all went to shit - though honestly, it had been going to shit for a while.
It was a clean break. For the most part, I haven’t missed social media. I’ve kept in touch with friends in other ways, from the ubiquitous…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Linux, farewell to toxic Windows operating systems]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7787</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/hello-linux-farewell-toxic-windows-operating-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve read a stack of articles recently about Windows 11 (11), the successor operating system (OS) to Windows 10 (10), and am not liking a single thing I’ve seen. Microsoft (MS) will soon begin forcing users to install Windows 11, whether they like it or not. If that’s not toxic behaviour on Microsoft’s part, what […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by basisword in "Apple unveils 'Passwords' manager app at WWDC 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638702</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638702"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:37:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>> People don't want everything tied to one identity, one service, one login.
I think this is exactly what _most_ people want.
With password management specifically, Apple has had a Chrome extension available for a while now which has allowed me to use it on other browsers/platforms. Not ideal, but good enough for most.
On top of that, they don't lock you in with passwords. You can easily import and export your passwords, just like you can with 1Password.
Apple Music has had a web client for a long time. iTunes has been on Windows for 20+ years and Apple Music was supported via that until recently when they built an Apple Music specific app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>basisword</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cletus in "Apple unveils 'Passwords' manager app at WWDC 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638134</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40638134"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T20:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's Apple's big problem: it's not a replacement for so many alternatives because it isn't supported on all platforms.
Safari? Not on Windows.
Apple Music? This actually has a Windows client. I'm not sure how good it is. But Spotify supports Windows and even Linux.
Apple Password Manager? Will this be tied to iCloud? Will I be able to use it on Android? If I no longer have an iPhone will it be a pain to maintain and use?
A dog cannot serve two masters. A company like Apple doesn't see any of these things as a product. They're a means to an end: to push the iPhone platform (and hardware sales). That priority will always trump the interests of a product like this.
It's also why I refuse to buy more into Google products: it's too much of a risk to lose access to everything if Google wakes up one day and decides to suspend your account with no recourse other than making enough of a stink on social media such that an employee will actually look into it.
People don't want everything tied to one identity, one service, one login.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cletus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "Apple Intelligence for iPhone, iPad, and Mac"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637674</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637674"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I always saw this level of personal intelligence to come about at some point, but I didn’t expect Apple to hit it out of the park so strongly. Benefit of drawing people into their ecosystem.
It's the benefit of how Apple does product ownership. In contrast to Google and Microsoft.
I hadn't considered it, but AI convergence is going to lay bare organizational deficiencies in a way previous revolutions didn't.
Nobody wants a GenAI feature that works in Gmail, a different one that works in Messages, etc. -- they want a platform capability that works anywhere they use text.
I'm not sure either Google or Microsoft are organizationally-capable of delivering that, at this point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by blueelephanttea in "OpenAI and Apple Announce Partnership"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637620</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40637620"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T19:27:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IMO this really feels like the Facebook / Twitter integration from early iOS. That only lasted a few years.
Apple clearly thinks it needs a dedicated LLM service atm. But still thinks it is only supplemental as they handle a bunch of the core stuff without it. And require explicit user consent to use OpenAI. And Apple clearly views it as a partial commodity since they even said they plan to add others.
Tough to bet against OpenAI right now...but this deal does not feel like a 10 year deal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>blueelephanttea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In praise of pluralism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45407</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/10/in-praise-of-pluralism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:19:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Recognition of the speculative value of counterfactualizing provides the grounding for a defense of theoretical pluralism in economics. The existence of multiple contending theories in economics is inconvenient, of course. It casts doubt on the truth content of the counterfactual scenarios generated by the predominant approach and challenges the predominant causal claims […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless Jupyter Notebooks at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21209</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/10/data-infrastructure/serverless-jupyter-notebooks-bento-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, Bento, our internal Jupyter notebooks platform, is a popular tool that allows our engineers to mix code, text, and multimedia in a single document. Use cases run the entire spectrum from what we call “lite” workloads that involve simple prototyping to heavier and more complex machine learning workflows. However, even though the lite [...]
Read More...
The post Serverless Jupyter Notebooks at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New AWS Heroes, Amazon API Gateway, Amazon Q and more (June 10, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>9cfd65284251edc6dd58c8e354d0d331f26c8185</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-aws-heroes-amazon-api-gateway-amazon-q-and-more-june-10-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T16:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last AWS Weekly Roundup, Channy reminded us on how life has ups and downs. It’s just how life is. But, that doesn’t mean that we should do it alone. Farouq Mousa, AWS Community Builder, is fighting brain cancer and Allen Helton, AWS Serverless Hero, his daughter is fighting leukemia. If you have a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the 2024 EU Election: Internet traffic trends and cybersecurity insights]]></title>
        <id>666716c4e955c4000a8b4cf1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exploring-the-2024-eu-election-internet-traffic-trends-and-cybersecurity-insights"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 EU Parliament election caused declines in Internet traffic during voting and spikes during results announcements, with persistent cyber threats targeting government sites]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The importance of record keeping and choosing your platform]]></title>
        <id>https://isejael.com/record-keeping/</id>
        <link href="https://isejael.com/record-keeping/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you certainly will not know, I have been writing blogs for almost ten years. Do I have any proof of this? I do not. For I have deleted them all. Why?, I hear you not ask, well I never felt comfortable with the name, the platform, you name it. All I wanted to do was write but I found myself instead worrying about being judged, rejected, subscriber numbers, aesthetics, and the time it took to load a page on Wordpress.
shudders
I began, like most of us, on Wordpress. After growing disillusioned with it and the years it took to rectify margins, I transitioned to Medium. Medium promised me the world, money and followers. It encouraged me to write often and with hooks. It spat out posts by writers claiming they made their first million on Medium.
It was the worst writing of my life.
To this d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Pombo Da Silva - On detention]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-on-detention?v=1717970489</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-on-detention?v=1717970489"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gabriel Pombo Da Silva
Title: On detention
Date: December 17, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15779>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 JANUARY – OCTOBER – THE STRUGGLE CONTINUES 
 To my friends, brothers and sisters, comrades
I remember that last day as if it were yesterday, when !finally! I left (was expelled from) the cold,narrow aseptic cell of the maximum security prison of Aachen, Germany… On January 16 (2013) I was escorted to the airport of Barajas, Madrid, by Interpol, and from there I was taken to the tribunal of Plaza Castilla, not before being photographed (they were particularly interested in my chest as they looked in vain to find a tattoo of the acronym FAI/FRI), ‘playing the piano’ (had my fingerprints taken) in order to ascertain that it was …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Tucker - Jurnal Anarki Interview with Anarchist Author Kevin Tucker]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker?v=1717970217</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker?v=1717970217"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T21:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kevin Tucker
Title: Jurnal Anarki Interview with Anarchist Author Kevin Tucker
Date: Feb 18, 2020
Source: <web.archive.org/.../anarchistsworldwide.noblogs.org/post/2020/02/18/indonesia-usa-jurnal-anarki-interview-with-anarchist-author-kevin-tucker>

The following interview with self-described primal anarchist advocate, writer, editor, independent researcher, publisher, musician and rewilding human, Kevin Tucker, originally appeared in the first issue of the new Indonesian anarchist journal, Jurnal Anarki. Jurnal Anarki is written entirely in Bahasa Indonesian, and this is the first time content from it has been republished in English. We’d like to thank comrade Eat for making this possible!
1. Looking at the Anarcho-Primitivist Primer by John Moore, he explains that Anarcho-Primiti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Tolstoy - A Calendar of Wisdom]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-a-calendar-of-wisdom?v=1717970042</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/leo-tolstoy-a-calendar-of-wisdom?v=1717970042"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T21:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Leo Tolstoy
Title: A Calendar of Wisdom
Subtitle: Daily Thoughts to Nourish the Soul, Written and Selected From the World’s Sacred Texts
Date: 1906
Notes: Translated From the Russian by Peter Sekirin.
Source: <archive.org/details/calendarofwisdom0000tols>

This translation is dedicated to MELISSA TEMERTY
Translator’s Acknowledgments
 I would like to express my deepest and most sincere acknowledgments to the following people: 
 professors who introduced me to Russian literature: K. Lantz, R. Bogert, Ch. Barnes, H. Marshall, R. Lindheim, O. Bakitsh, C. Bedford, M. Valdez, L. Hutcheon; and other professors and students of the Slavic Department and the Department of Comparitive Literature of the University of Toronto; my literary agent, Ivy Fischer Stone, of the Fifi Oscard Agency; my …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Pombo Da Silva - A Letter]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-a-letter?v=1717966612</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-pombo-da-silva-a-letter?v=1717966612"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gabriel Pombo Da Silva
Title: A Letter
Date: December 30, 2015
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=22046>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 ‘..while there is a lower class, I am in it, and while there is a criminal element I am of it, and while there is a soul in prison, I am not free.’ — Eugene Debs 
 Comrades!
Today I’m in high spirits (you know our life is not a straight line, nor constant, or static…), and those who know me personally know that I have a pretty black a sense of humour (what ‘scandalizes’ others makes me smile, etc.) almost cynically (especially when it comes to talking about/describing facts to do with the ‘Law’, ‘Rights’, the ‘Authorities’, etc.); because these are ‘things’ that I can’t take seriously (even though my life is wrapped up in all tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Francisco Solar - Nothing is over]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/francisco-solar-nothing-is-over?v=1717966072</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/francisco-solar-nothing-is-over?v=1717966072"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Francisco Solar
Title: Nothing is over
Subtitle: On the need to accept the fullness of our choices
Date: June 5, 2016
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=23856>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 ‘Anarchist prisoners are not alone’ and ‘if they touch one, they touch all’ are slogans that lived once again in the everyday anarchist action before, during and after the trial against us. The screams of disgust for authority that pierced the police control and the walls around those on trial clearly enraged the judge and magistrates, as was evident on their faces and which put smiles on ours. The presence in court of dear ones known and unknown filled us with pride and joy, preventing the prosecutors’ accusations and demands from having any possibility of intimidating us. T…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Theofilos Mavropoulos - Chaos just around the corner]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-chaos-just-around-the-corner?v=1717964569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-chaos-just-around-the-corner?v=1717964569"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Chaos just around the corner
Date: July 9, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=10293>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

(Italy, Mexico, Greece)
 On Wednesday, June 13th, the international anti-anarchist campaign under the name ‘operation boldness’ was set up. The Italian antiterrorism forces of ROS and carabiniers were put under the command of the Inquisitor-prosecutor of Perugia Manuela Comodi, and proceeded to arrest eight anarchist comrades. In parallel, investigations are conducted against other comrades as well (among them are the comrades of Edizioni Cerbero). 
 We neither know the details of the case, nor are we lawyers to speak the language of documentary evidence or not. All we know is that the wo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos - Bullets of words for the bullets of FAI/FRI]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-bullets-of-words-for-the-bullets-of-fai-fri?v=1717964491</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-bullets-of-words-for-the-bullets-of-fai-fri?v=1717964491"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:21:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Bullets of words for the bullets of FAI/FRI
Date: May 14, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=9380>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It is a wonderful moment, the moment that the enemy kneels and falls from the determination of your brothers and sisters. A few days ago Roberto Adinolfi, CEO-magister of the nuclear energy company Ansaldo Nucleare, was shot by our brothers and sisters of the Olga Cell of the Informal Anarchist Federation (FAI)–International Revolutionary Front (FRI). 
 Roberto Adinolfi is a high priest of the new totalitarianism of science and technology imperatives. Science has become the modern religion of our time, promising an apathetic society the lethargy of a stuffed belly and arti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos - Breaking down the myths of prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-breaking-down-the-myths-of-prison?v=1717964334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-theofilos-mavropoulos-breaking-down-the-myths-of-prison?v=1717964334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire & Theofilos Mavropoulos
Title: Breaking down the myths of prison
Date: May 13, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=9359>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 SOLIDARITY TO OLGA ECONOMIDOU 
 “Turn off the main switch in this dump. Here the beautiful becomes ugly, the choice becomes a habit and the meaningless important. Prison dirties creases and swallows pieces of dreams, desires, thoughts and feelings. Its most permanent residents, the majority of the prisoners are now a part of the appliances of the prison. Bars, yard, cameras, locks, prisoners mix all together and re-enact the world of captivity. Nothing is worthy in here. Come let’s go and don’t look back… Only fire will cleanse this place… ” 
 Prison and its numbered residents. Pris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Unless We Die for Each Other, We Are Already Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-unless-we-die-for-each-other-we-are-already-dead?v=1717964258</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-unless-we-die-for-each-other-we-are-already-dead?v=1717964258"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Unless We Die for Each Other, We Are Already Dead
Subtitle: Communique by the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire About the Hunger Strike
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/11/ellada-keimeno-spf-gia-apergia-peinas>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 On March 3rd, “justice” decided on the pre-trial detention of the mother of the comrades Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos and the second one’s girlfriend, with the charge of accession and participation in a terrorist organization.
 Behind the obvious ridiculousness of the charge, it is the morbid vindictiveness of the counter-terrorism and the judicial authority hiding, which wishes to blackmail emotionally both the two comrades and all of us. It is not ju…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Two Statements of Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-two-statements-of-solidarity?v=1717964154</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-two-statements-of-solidarity?v=1717964154"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Two Statements of Solidarity
Source: <actforfreedomnow.wordpress.com/2011/11/16/a-flame-of-solidarity-from-the-ccf-for-the-brothers-and-sisters-in-chile> & <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=8188>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

A flame of solidarity from the CCF for the brothers and sisters in Chile (2011)
When the prison bars stop our hands from throwing the fire of anarchy into the world of power, our words become the sharp rasp of escape.
 Armed with thoughts, desires, secret plans, new conspiracies, we give a warmest embrace in our imaginary meeting with the comrades of action across the world. 
 Now we want our voice to reach our brothers and sister in distant Chile to Luciano (Tortuga) prosecuted on November 22 and to Monica, to Fe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-statement?v=1717963961</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-statement?v=1717963961"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T20:12:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Statement
Date: 31 March 2010
Source: <sysiphus-angrynewsfromaroundtheworld.blogspot.com/2010/03/athens-statement-from-conspiracy-of.html>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 The past 24 hours find us in an extreme emotional antithesis… 
 On the one hand, great sorrow for the death of the 15-year old Afghani and the injury of his sister and on the other hand, maximum rage for the reportages of the media which totally arbitrarily and purposefully try to involve our organisation in this event. We are not usually “bothered” by the panic-ridden scenaria of the media, yet the importance of the event forces us to take a public position directly, without a connection to any attack of ours. 
 For this reason we CLEARLY STATE THAT THE CONSPIR…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Political Statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-political-statement?v=1717960334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-political-statement?v=1717960334"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T19:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Political Statement
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/12/02/politiki_dilwsi>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This statement is made to clarify and publicly state our position in relation to our recent attempted escape from prison. 
 The fact that we are captives in the prison cells of democracy does not mean that we accept for a moment our position either as prisoners or as defendants before the civil court-martial that you have set up against us. There will never be either a prison guard to lock up our soul or a judge to rule on our values. We are eternal enemies of law and order and eternal prison breakers. 
 Obviously these few following words cannot describe the miserable conditions inside penitentiaries that are experi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Memory is our Weapon]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-memory-is-our-weapon?v=1717958906</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-memory-is-our-weapon?v=1717958906"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Memory is our Weapon
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/05/19/ellada-i-mnimi-einai-to-oplo-mas-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It was the dawn of May 22, 2009, when an explosion in Santiago, Chile caused fragments which crossed endless kilometers and borders until they brought us the news that were nailed in our hearts. 
 It was the dawn of May 22, 2009 when our brother and comrade Mauricio Morales, consistent fighter of the anarchist insurrection, put his conspiratorial plan in place, heading to the school of prison guards in Santiago in order to blow it up. But fate played an ugly game that day. The bomb our brother was carrying exploded prematurely resulting in him falling dead, just …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Letter regarding the new investigations by prosecutors]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-letter-regarding-the-new-investigations-by-prosecutors?v=1717958712</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-letter-regarding-the-new-investigations-by-prosecutors?v=1717958712"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Letter regarding the new investigations by prosecutors
Date: March 29, 2012
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=8558>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I The choice of claiming responsibility and not capitulation
 We as Conspiracy of Cells of Fire-imprisoned members, chose and claimed responsibility from inside the prison for our participation in our project. The responsibility claim is the least way to defend and honour the most beautiful acts that we share. Not as a memory that fades away after our arrests but as a living reality and prospect of carrying on our actions in the continuous present, the here and now. 
 We believe that the responsibility claim and the words we express through this contribute decisively to the intensific…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - In Cold Blood]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-in-cold-blood?v=1717958555</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-in-cold-blood?v=1717958555"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:42:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: In Cold Blood
Subtitle: Concerning Gatherings, the Referendum and Complicit Democracy
Date: August 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma
Source: <interarma.info/2015/08/02/ellada-en-psixro-peri-sygkentoseon-dimopsifismatos-kai-sinenoxis-dimokratias-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

It is sometimes useful to keep a distance from events before you talk about them. Anticipation and the frozen time of captivity in prison accelerate, nevertheless, the cool-headed distance from events. A self-possessed distance gives you the opportunity to observe details which are usually ignored and bulldozed by the warm blood conditions’ momentum of intensity. So, as they often say, “the devil is hidden in the details”…
I. The rise before the fall …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Fire and Gunpowder]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-fire-and-gunpowder?v=1717958445</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-fire-and-gunpowder?v=1717958445"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:40:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Fire and Gunpowder
Subtitle: From Indonesia to Chile… A proposition for FAI/IRF
Date: December 4, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 We hear the song of fire that comes from far away. The words smell of gunpowder. From the other side of the world rebellious comrades burn the nights and liberate places and moments. we can hear them… They conspire, plan, attack… We do not have to say anything else, we leave our brothers and sisters to speak for us. 
“We are all Conspiracy Cells of Fire. C.C.F. is not an organization or just a group. On the contrary it is a antagonistic expression of rage and contempt towards authority and its structures. To spread the C.C.F. all you need is gasoline, matches and t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Either with Anarchy or with Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-either-with-anarchy-or-with-authority?v=1717958374</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-either-with-anarchy-or-with-authority?v=1717958374"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Either with Anarchy or with Authority
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/27/ellada-i-me-tin-anarxia-i-me-tin-eksousia-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 It’s been already 25 days that the mother of Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos and the girlfriend of the second one are locked up in the cells of democracy. 
 We have already been for 25 days on hunger strike until death, demanding their immediate release. 
 It’s been 25 days and already eight of us are in hospitals with their health condition on the limits. 
 25 days are not just a number on a calendar, it is the experiment of evolution of repression, with new methods of emotional blackmail against imprisoned anarchist urban guerrillas.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Communization]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communization?v=1717958232</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communization?v=1717958232"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Communization
Subtitle: The Senile Decay of Anarchy (or Re-Inventing Anarchy)
Date: 2015
Notes: Fragment of the unpublished pamphlet “FAI Reloaded” by the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire. Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2015/06/01/ellada-kommounistikopoiisi-i-gerontiki-ania-tis-anarxias-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. Frozen Marxism
 Today’s era smells like engine oil, cheap labor sweat and naphthalene of the morality of voluntary obedience… We do not want to be defined by the culture of techno-industrial fascism, the white uniforms of scientists, the neckties of technocrats, the eager silences of ordinary people, the stupid smiles of consumers… We do not match with the aesthetics of the glass world of flat t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Communique for the Arrested Comrades]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communique-for-the-arrested-comrades?v=1717958118</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-communique-for-the-arrested-comrades?v=1717958118"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Communique for the Arrested Comrades
Date: 25/11/2010
Source: <guerrillanews.wordpress.com/2010/12/25/communique-for-the-arrested-comrades-by-conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Declaration for the 1st November letter-bombing against European State targets by Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
 Currently our three brothers, three members of our group are incarcerated in the prisons of Greek democracy. Their absence from our side is not rectified through the text of a proclamation. The words seem hopelessly small and insignificant against the intensity of situations and emotions that we share with them. But even during these moments, when the walls and bars of the prison rise among us, nothing has changed… Gerasim…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Better to Be a Demon of Vengeance, Than an Angel of Forgiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-better-to-be-a-demon-of-vengeance-than-an-angel-of-forgiveness?v=1717957988</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-better-to-be-a-demon-of-vengeance-than-an-angel-of-forgiveness?v=1717957988"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Better to Be a Demon of Vengeance, Than an Angel of Forgiveness
Date: 2015
Notes: A signal of complicity from the Greek prisons, for the international call of solidarity made from Publicacion Refractario, Colectivo Lucha Revolucionaria (Revolutionary Struggle Collective) and Sin Banderas Ni Fronteras, to our brothers and sister Nataly Casanova, Juan Flores, Guillermo Durán and Enrique Guzmán, who are imprisoned in Chile, accused for attacks made by the International Conspiracy of Revenge and the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire, Chile. 
 Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: interarma.info/2015/05/05/ellada-kalytera-daimonas-ths-ekdikhshs-para-aggelos-ths-sygxwreshs-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 Nothing is uglier than ugliness repe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - And death will no longer have any power]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-and-death-will-no-longer-have-any-power?v=1717957804</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-and-death-will-no-longer-have-any-power?v=1717957804"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: And death will no longer have any power
Subtitle: Concerning the fire in the Marfin Bank
Date: July 10, 2010
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=2188>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 In the incidents of the 5th May concerning the fire in the Marfin Bank there were three dead bank employees and thousands of “charred” truths. The suffocating atmosphere of the heartbreaking hypocrisy of propaganda and the worn moralistic humanism of the radical movement’s Cassandras, force us to take a public stand concerning these events. This does not mean that we are talking as “specialists” of violence, or that we are “self-appointed” prosecutors or defenders of the people who attacked the bank building. But we find it necessary that some things …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - Amongst Two Worlds]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-amongst-two-worlds?v=1717957605</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-amongst-two-worlds?v=1717957605"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: Amongst Two Worlds
Subtitle: International Call of Action for the Hunger Strike of the Conspiracy of Cells of Fire Until Death
Date: 2015
Notes: Translated by Inter Arma
Source: <interarma.info/2015/03/29/ellada-anamesa-se-2-kosmous-diethnes-kalesma-drasis-apo-spf>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 The moment the following words were written, we’re on the 25th day of hunger strike, for the liberation of Christos and Gerasimos Tsakalos’ mother, as well as the second one’s girlfriend. 
 The pre-trial detention of our two comrades’ relatives was an act of revenge by the judicial power against us, in retaliation for the escape we had prepared, with the bombing of the prison. 
 Now, reaching a tipping point between life and death, we wa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - About the attacks against State and Capital]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-about-the-attacks-against-state-and-capital?v=1717957404</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-about-the-attacks-against-state-and-capital?v=1717957404"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: About the attacks against State and Capital
Date: 9 November 2009
Source: <sysiphus-angrynewsfromaroundtheworld.blogspot.com/2009/11/about-attacks-against-state-and-capital.html>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 A huge storm of revolt raged through the streets of Greece in December 2008. After the young Andreas Grigoropoulos was murdered by a cop, riots spread throughout the whole country for several weeks. Hundreds of banks, shops, car dealers, offices,… were attacked, plundered and put on fire. Although it were anarchists and anti-authoritarians who took the lead in this storm during the first week after the murder, it spread itself fast and many people got involved in this revolt against miserable living conditions, against the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy of Cells of Fire - A small contribution about Solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-a-small-contribution-about-solidarity?v=1717957177</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-of-cells-of-fire-a-small-contribution-about-solidarity?v=1717957177"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy of Cells of Fire
Title: A small contribution about Solidarity
Date: May 4, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=4500>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Until the day comes we will remain with the head held high....
1. Solidarity is our weapon
 Many things have been written and said about solidarity. Usually when there have been so many discussions and so many texts have circulated on a matter, it ends up trite, predictable and without any particular interest. It seems as if its content has run out and it’s constantly being repeated. 
 We believe there are no trite practices, but trite ways of thinking. Particularly today, in the suspicious days we are living in, with the dozens of imprisoned urban guerrillas and anarchists, we should sharpen the blade o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini - Claim of responsibility for the bomb attack against the Administrative Court]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-claim-of-responsibility-for-the-bomb-attack?v=1717956838</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/conspiracy-cells-of-fire-commando-horst-fantazzini-claim-of-responsibility-for-the-bomb-attack?v=1717956838"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T18:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Conspiracy Cells Of Fire — Commando Horst Fantazzini
Title: Claim of responsibility for the bomb attack against the Administrative Court
Date: January 6, 2011
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=3457>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. “The days are coming when they try…”
 “Whoever passed by the front of a courthouse or prison and his look didn’t darken in the thought that he could be there as the culprit, then he did not live his time with integrity and dignity” 
 The attack on the Administrative Court is dedicated with all our fire to our brothers (G.Tsakalos, P.Argirou, H.Hajimihelakis) of the prisoner’s cell of the members of Conspiracy Cells of Fire. Our comrades and the honest minority of dignified revolutionary Persons political and civil, are not just a piec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[looking back over a lifetime, you see that love was the answer to everything]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/love-bradbury/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/love-bradbury/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes before I left home on Thursday one of my mom's coworkers pulled up on the driveway and handed me a plastic bag of zongzi as a going away gift. "Good luck with the move!" he said. "Go do what you love."
That last remark has been echoing in my head. It runs directly contrary to the advice I received from my parents and their friends growing up. Hearing my aunts now telling me to follow my dreams and not to worry about money makes me wonder how my mom's framed this new career shift of mine.
A large part of me is suspicious. Mom always told me growing up that being an adult was learning to do things you didn't want to do and that nobody would pay me to do a job I found fun. Why's she switching it up on me now? Did it take me crashing and burning in an actual job for her to realize I'm not cut out for a life in STEM? I try not to look back with regret, but how much further along would I be had I chased something I liked earlier?
In Zen in the Art of Writing Bradbury reflects and decides that "looking back over a lifetime, you see that love was the answer to everything." I've been thinking about that as I prepare mentally for a week (and month) of writing and teaching writing for fifty hours a week, things my parents have been telling everyone are things I like to do. At the risk of speaking too soon (knocks on wood), this is the first Sunday I'm not actually dreading the coming week, if not ever then at least for a very long time. I'm nervous and well aware that my schedule will test me, but a strong undercurrent of appreciation for what I'm doing (and not doing) buoys me now and that is nothing short of a revelation for me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Rose Anarchist Federation - Turning the Tide]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-rose-anarchist-federation-turning-the-tide?v=1717936810</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-rose-anarchist-federation-turning-the-tide?v=1717936810"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T12:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Black Rose Anarchist Federation
Title: Turning the Tide
Subtitle: An Anarchist Program for Popular Power
Date: May 1, 2023
Notes: Written and approved by the membership of Black Rose / Rosa Negra. First edition released May 1, 2023, available at blackrosefed.org. Cover illustration by Dinelli: dinelliarte.com.
Source: Retrieved on 2023-05-23 from blackrosefed.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/brrn-program-2023.pdf

General Introduction
 This is the political program of our organization, Black Rose Anarchist Federation / Federación Anarquista Rosa Negra (BRRN). The writings it contains are the result of nearly two years of collective analysis, discussion, and debate. The content of the program is divided into three parts: sections that detail our understanding of the social, political,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: wisteria at Iford]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52751</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/09/sunday-photoblogging-wisteria-at-iford/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T09:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>