<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-30T18:34:57.468Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-30T18:34:57.468Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Wirklich, ich lebe in finsteren Zeiten!”, some random thoughts on our responsibility as intellectuals / poets / writers / researchers / teachers]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53329</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/30/wirklich-ich-lebe-in-finsteren-zeiten-some-random-thoughts-on-our-responsibility-as-intellectuals-poets-writers-researchers-teachers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T18:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“We live in an age which silence is not only criminal but suicidal”, wrote James Baldwin in his “Open Letter to My Sister, Angela Y. Davis”. The year was 1970. I wonder if there has ever been a time when silence was not only criminal but also suicidal. I would like to live there and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Macarena Marey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281358</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T18:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Biden does call Trump supporters "garbage"; About exit polling; Boeing contract talks resume ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify and enhance Amazon S3 static website hosting with AWS Amplify Hosting]]></title>
        <id>ccdba42ff38124d2621c7b1dee7250dda057dd2d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-and-enhance-amazon-s3-static-website-hosting-with-aws-amplify/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T17:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy static sites with streamlined configuration, custom domains, SSL, CDN, and one-click updates using Amazon S3 with AWS Amplify Hosting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by carlgreene in "M4 MacBook Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41996119</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41996119"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:28:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s amazing is that in the past I’ve felt the need to upgrade within a few years.
New video format or more demanding music software is released that slows the machine down, or battery life craters.
Well, I haven’t had even a tinge of feeling that I need to upgrade after getting my M1 Pro MBP. I can’t remember it ever skipping a beat running a serious Ableton project, or editing in Resolve.
Can stuff be faster? Technically of course. But this is the first machine that even after several years I’ve not caught myself once wishing that it was faster or had more RAM. Not once.
Perhaps it’s my age, or perhaps it’s just the architecture of these new Mac chips are just so damn good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>carlgreene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia conducts large-scale nuke drills + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/russia-conducts-large-scale-nuke-drills-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/russia-conducts-large-scale-nuke-drills-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T15:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel bans UNRWA operations, threatening aid; Putin conducts nuclear drills simulating attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 2 | A global overview of political, social and economic situations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-2-A-global-overview-of-political-social-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-2-A-global-overview-of-political-social-and"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday, October 8, 2024, marked the second day of the CADTM network's international council. On the agenda: the political, economic and social situation, and the state of struggles in sub-Saharan Africa, the Middle East and North Africa, South Asia and Latin America. Sub-Saharan Africa: Mali, Niger, Burkina Faso, the new deal 
English

/ 
Latin America, 
Africa, 
Illegitimate debt, 
South Asia, 
North Africa and the Middle East, 
South, 
CI 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Broulaye Bagayoko, CADTM International, Maxime Perriot, Omar Aziki, Sushovan Dhar, Veronica Carrillo Ortega</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeremy F. Walton: &ldquo;Tangled Legacy&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/tangled-legacy</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/tangled-legacy"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fethullah Gülen (1941-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wolf Richter: Boeing Launches $22 Billion Share Offering to Get Breathing Room, Dodge Junk Credit Rating, after Having Wasted $64 Billion on Share Buybacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281353</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/wolf-richter-boeing-launches-22-billion-share-offering-to-get-breathing-room-dodge-junk-credit-rating-after-having-wasted-64-billion-on-share-buybacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T14:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the equity raise as outlined today, the company will have some limited financial breathing room, and will likely avert a near-term down grade to junk, so one day at a time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: On Maintaining Streaks]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/re-on-maintaining-streaks/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/re-on-maintaining-streaks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About six weeks ago, I opened up a Duolingo account. I don’t have a great desire to become bilingual, but I’ve read about all the benefits of learning a new a language and I figured, what the heck. I started with Latin, which I was enjoying, but decided I should switch to something a bit more practical. Being in the United States, Spanish was the logical choice, and so I moved my lessons over to Spanish.
Every day, I take three or four minutes to do my little challenges. It’s been a fun little distraction, but one that occasionally irritates me. For example, I’ve mistyped and lost hearts, which of course, prompts the app to sell me a membership, something I’m not interested in at this time. I don’t allow many notifications from apps on my phone, so Duolingo sends me emails to remind me to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning From The Inside Out]]></title>
        <id>https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/learning-from-the-inside-out/</id>
        <link href="https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/learning-from-the-inside-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve come to realize that education works best when it’s built around the learner. Not just teaching someone information but lighting a fire in them to seek out knowledge on their own.
That’s when it all changes. When students are genuinely curious, and they’re allowed the freedom to explore that curiosity, they become teachers to themselves.
They’re learning not because they have to but because they want to. That inner motivation is what takes learning beyond just facts and assignments—it makes it something exciting and meaningful.

But how do we actually make this shift? I’ve been thinking a lot about that, especially when I look back on how much public schooling is still rooted in traditional “chalk and talk” methods. A teacher at the front, lecturing while students sit passively—it has…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing Lasts Forever]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/nothing-lasts-forever/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/nothing-lasts-forever/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the central tenets of Buddhism is that everything is decaying. Eventually, everything falls apart. One just has to buy a home to see the truth in this. Trust me. Today, lots of people were disappointed that a well-liked Internet service, Omnivore, which allowed you to save articles to read later, subscribe to newsletters without using your personal email, and have some articles automatically archived, was turning off its servers on November 15. Some folks had just transitioned to using Omnivore, only to find that their efforts were now wasted. It was my favorite way to read a couple of my favorite writers, so I had to scramble to come up with an alternative.
People have seen it happen time and again. Huge, popular websites and companies have just disappeared or changed so completely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281341</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our always interesting daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obesity: Sociogenic Disease and the Next Generation of Blockbuster Drugs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281339</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/obesity-sociogenic-disease-and-the-next-generation-of-blockbuster-drug.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The only good way to deal with the obesity epidemic is to go back to the future and eat real food, close to home, wherever that may be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As German Industry Implodes, Country’s Wealthiest Make Out Like Bandits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281323</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/as-german-industry-implodes-countrys-wealthiest-make-out-like-bandits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blame cannons for the fall of Germany ignore Atlanticist elite and are increasingly being set on China in addition to Russia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hydrogen Stocks Crash as Hype Faces Reality Check]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281336</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/hydrogen-stocks-crash-as-hype-faces-reality-check.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T09:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU and especially Germany were relying on the fantasy that green hydrogen could save their industry, which is dying after governments cut off Russian pipeline gas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time to Put an End to World Bank Impunity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Time-to-Put-an-End-to-World-Bank-Impunity</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Time-to-Put-an-End-to-World-Bank-Impunity"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T08:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
World Bank, 
Illegitimate debt, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“I Am the Face of AIDS:” Ryan White and the Politics of Innocence in the History of HIV/AIDS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340658</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/i-am-the-face-of-aids-ryan-white-and-the-politics-of-innocence-in-the-history-of-hiv-aids/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T06:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While Ryan’s “innocence” pushed the federal government to act on AIDS, the “guilt” of marginalized groups fueled the urge “to punish sick people for their alleged lack of moral purity,” as one Philadelphia Daily News editorial put it. Specifically, the CARE Act contained punitive HIV criminalization and notification statutes and prohibited federal funding for needle-exchange programs. More
The post “I Am the Face of AIDS:” Ryan White and the Politics of Innocence in the History of HIV/AIDS appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul M. Renfro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Family Lived the Horrors of Native American Boarding Schools: Why Biden’s Apology Doesn’t Go Far Enough]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340331</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/my-family-lived-the-horrors-of-native-american-boarding-schools-why-bidens-apology-doesnt-go-far-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Oct. 25, 2024, Joe Biden, the first U.S. president to formally apologize for the policy of sending Native American children to Indian boarding schools, called it one of the most “horrific chapters” in U.S. history and “a mark of shame.” But he did not call it a genocide. Yet, over the past 10 years, many historians and Indigenous scholars have said that what happened at the Indian boarding schools “meets the definition of genocide.” More
The post My Family Lived the Horrors of Native American Boarding Schools: Why Biden’s Apology Doesn’t Go Far Enough appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rosalyn R. LaPier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Duty to Warn America: A Face-off with a Future of Fascism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340617</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/a-duty-to-warn-america-a-face-off-with-a-future-of-fascism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is it a time of historical reckoning for America, in this social media dominated age, riddled by lots of gaslighting hyperbole and rabbit-holed halls full of meme-filled mirrored walls? Is it just a caricatured stage play of days long political games with a crazy old man on one side telling people the country is like  More
The post A Duty to Warn America: A Face-off with a Future of Fascism? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Drake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s at Stake in 2024 — from (My) Rural America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340483</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/whats-at-stake-in-2024-from-my-rural-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Images of homes that collapsed under mudslides or falling trees, waterlogged farms, and debris-filled roads drove home (yes, home!) to me recently the impact of Hurricane Helene on rural areas in the southeastern United States. That hurricane and the no-less-devastating Hurricane Milton that followed it only exacerbated already existing underlying problems for rural America. Those would include federal insurance programs that prioritize rising sea levels  More
The post What’s at Stake in 2024 — from (My) Rural America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Mazzarino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frost and Fire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340572</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/frost-and-fire/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:54:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The season winds down. Yesterday morning I picked lettuce as yet undamaged by frosty nights alongside staked tomatoes not-so-fortunate. This is the shoulder season when life still clings to some crops while others surrender to bitter cold reality. So too in the political season, where the frosty (though minor) squabbles over “policy” between members of  More
The post Frost and Fire appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Rhames</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cattle Dog Gusto: How Bluey Conquered the United States]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340576</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/cattle-dog-gusto-how-bluey-conquered-the-united-states/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For decades, the cultural phenomenon known as Americanisation has taken place with diffusing ease.  Momentum was gained with the retreat of communism from Europe’s eastern states with the end of the Cold War and the eventual termination of the Soviet Union in 1991.  Global brands of Americana from fizzy drinks to Dallas became pervasive cultural presences.  Not even children’s programming  More
The post Cattle Dog Gusto: How Bluey Conquered the United States appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: An Ocean Apart?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340178</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/letter-from-london-an-ocean-apart/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Betty Boop is not the only remarkable figure on show in Florida. Henry McLeish is visiting professor of UK and European politics at the University of South Florida. As a wee boy the talented Scot once signed for Leeds United football club. Even more remarkable is the fact that for one year and 12 days  More
The post Letter from London: An Ocean Apart? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hamas Without Sinwar: a Setback or a Catalyst?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340325</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/hamas-without-sinwar-a-setback-or-a-catalyst/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T05:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since the October 7 attack last year, Israeli intelligence claimed that Yahya Sinwar, Hamas’s military leader, was hiding deep within Gaza’s complex underground tunnels, using Israeli hostages as a strategic shield. They alleged that he was using these hostages as a deterrent to complicate any rescue attempt or targeted strike. Sinwar’s elusiveness became almost  More
The post Hamas Without Sinwar: a Setback or a Catalyst? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween: Five Flash Fictions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340574</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/halloween-five-flash-fictions/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T04:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. The House of the Seven Gables When you open the door on Halloween you never know what you’ll get.  Could be the Monkey’s Paw — some victim of a multicar event dripping gore and having just a horrible Here day, and standing there now, his head with red hair in hand, saying trick or treat.  And you  More
The post Halloween: Five Flash Fictions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Facts About the Fearless Writer Sanora Babb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340207</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/ten-facts-about-the-fearless-writer-sanora-babb/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T04:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iris Jamahl Dunkle, author of Riding Like the Wind: The Life of Sanora Babb, shares ten intriguing facts about intrepid writer Sanora Babb — peerless author of midcentury American literature and remarkable rebel who challenged the era’s social and political norms. In 1939, when John Steinbeck’s The Grapes of Wrath was published, it became an instant  More
The post Ten Facts About the Fearless Writer Sanora Babb appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Iris Jamahl Dunkle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photoshoot at El Mozote, El Salvador (Population 901 in 1981)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340347</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/30/photoshoot-at-el-mozote-el-salvador-population-901-in-1981/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-30T04:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– In memory of Rufina Amaya It’s a formal occasion. She has on gloves. She holds the infant’s dress before her like she’s choosing something for a baptism. It is, after all, a christening of sorts, a whole village to be assembled. It takes time to lay them all out, an array of special tools,  More
The post Photoshoot at El Mozote, El Salvador (Population 901 in 1981) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desiree Hellegers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marianne Enckell - Ronald Creagh, an appreciation]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marianne-enckell-ronald-creagh-an-appreciation?v=1730240392</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/marianne-enckell-ronald-creagh-an-appreciation?v=1730240392"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Marianne Enckell
Title: Ronald Creagh, an appreciation
Date: 2024
Notes: Scanned from original.
Source: Anarchist Studies 32.1 (2024)

 An ‘inimitable singularity’: this is how Ronald Creagh described the American utopian communities he studied for his doctoral thesis. [1] But Ronald himself was also an inimitable singularity. 
 A cosmopolitan by family and culture, with British, Italian, Egyptian roots, he had studied in France and written his MA on the free thought periodicals in nineteenth century North America – after having been a priest for many years. He then turned towards the early anarchist movement; this led him to visit the CIRA library (Centre international de recherches sur l’anarchisme) in Lausanne, in the early ’70s. My mother, who was in charge at that time, sugges…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Clark - Ronald Creagh (1929-2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-clark-ronald-creagh-1929-2023?v=1730239852</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-clark-ronald-creagh-1929-2023?v=1730239852"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Clark
Title: Ronald Creagh (1929-2023)
Date: 2024
Notes: Scanned from original
Source: Anarchist Studies 32.1 (2024)

 Ronald Creagh took great satisfaction from the fact that he was born in Alexandria, Egypt, a historic city that was the centre of ancient learning. He grew up in a multicultural milieu in Port Said, Egypt. He was the offspring of a British-Sicilian father and a Franco-Lebanese mother and was taught Sicilian by his paternal grandmother. He said that Sicilian was his first language. 
 In 1947, his family migrated to Australia, while Ronald moved to France to become a Roman Catholic priest. He took a degree in sociology at the Sorbonne, a masters’ degree at the École Pratique des Hautes Études, and then taught at the Institute of Human Sciences and Techniques and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0xFACEFEED in "GitHub cuts AI deals with Google, Anthropic"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989925</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989925"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:08:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a programmer of over 20 years - this is terrifying.
I'm willing to accept that I just have "get off my lawn" syndrome or something.
But the idea of letting an LLM write/move large swaths of code seems so incredibly irresponsible. Whenever I sit down to write some code, be it a large implementation or a small function, I think about what other people (or future versions of myself) will struggle with when interacting with the code. Is it clear and concise? Is it too clever? Is it too easy to write a subtle bug when making changes? Have I made it totally clear that X is relying on Y dangerous behavior by adding a comment or intentionally making it visible in some other way?
It goes the other way too. If I know someone well (or their style) then it makes evaluating their code easier. The more time I spend in a codebase the better idea I have of what the writer was trying to do. I remember spending a lot of time reading the early Redis codebase and got a pretty good sense of how Salvatore thinks. Or altering my approaches to code reviews depending on which coworker was submitting it. These weren't things I were doing out of desire but because all non-trivial code has so much subtlety; it's just the nature of the beast.
So the thought of opening up a codebase that was cobbled together by an AI is just scary to me. Subtle bugs and errors would be equally distributed across the whole thing instead of where the writer was less competent (as is often the case). The whole thing just sounds like a gargantuan mess.
Change my mind.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0xFACEFEED</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fifth Estate Collective - Remembering Ronald Creagh]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fifth-estate-collective-remembering-ronald-creagh?v=1730239379</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fifth-estate-collective-remembering-ronald-creagh?v=1730239379"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T22:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fifth Estate Collective
Title: Remembering Ronald Creagh
Date: 2023, Fall
Notes: Accessed October 21, 2024 at https://www.fifthestate.org/archive/414-fall-2023/remembering-ronald-creagh/
Source: Fifth Estate #414, Fall 2023

 Longtime French anarchist scholar and activist Ronald Creagh died on September 8 at age 94. 
 He was in touch with anarchists and anti-authoritarians on several continents. Those who knew him personally appreciated his broad-minded openness and supportive spirit. 
 Some Fifth Estate staffers were among those who found him engaging and attentive in conversations on many subjects. In recent years he was a regular reader of our online current and past articles and enjoyed discussing them. 
 Ronald was born in Egypt in 1929, the son of a Lebanese mother and an Eng…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by onlyrealcuzzo in "OpenAI builds first chip with Broadcom and TSMC, scales back foundry ambition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989707</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989707"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As anyone with 2 brain cells should have.
You don't just acquire $7T.
The ENTIRE US domestic Net Investment isn't even $1T: https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/W790RC1Q027SBEA
Gross Fixed Capital Formation (Net Investment + Deprecation) isn't much more: https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/NFIRSAXDCUSQ
Google, Apple, and Microsoft together don't even spend $100B on CapEx per year. And they're worth almost $10T put together.
Asking for $7T when you're a $100B company is so ridiculous it's beyond belief.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>onlyrealcuzzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "OpenAI builds first chip with Broadcom and TSMC, scales back foundry ambition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989594</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41989594"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> OpenAI considered building everything in-house and raising capital for an expensive plan to build a network of factories known as "foundries" for chip manufacturing. The company has dropped the ambitious foundry plans for now due to the costs and time needed to build a network
That framing massively undersells how insane Sams ambitions were there, he was floating the idea of somehow raising seven trillion dollars to build thirty six fabs dedicated to making AI silicon. The TSMC execs reported more or less laughed in his face when he brought it up it them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[El Libertario editorial collective - Neither Chavez nor Carmona: Self-management is the way]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/el-libertario-collective-neither-chavez-nor-carmona-self-management-is-the-way?v=1730236456</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/el-libertario-collective-neither-chavez-nor-carmona-self-management-is-the-way?v=1730236456"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: El Libertario editorial collective
Title: Neither Chavez nor Carmona: Self-management is the way
Date: April 21, 2002
Source: Retrieved on October 24, 2024 from https://www.nodo50.org/ellibertario/descargas/folleto-abril-02.txt

 Given the political crisis that Venezuela is going through and that was manifested in the events before, during and after April 11, we anarchists consider it necessary to state our position. In this regard, therefore: 
 1) Hugo Chavez's contradictory policies have not benefited the most disadvantaged sectors of the country, increasing in three years of management the rates of poverty, unemployment and social insecurity. In addition, his government repeats errors and vices characteristic of previous ones. But in no way do the sectors of the current oppositi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Barnard - Primitive communism and mutual aid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/primitive-communism-and-mutual-aid?v=1730236264</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/primitive-communism-and-mutual-aid?v=1730236264"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alan Barnard
Title: Primitive communism and mutual aid
Subtitle: Kropotkin visits the Bushmen
Date: December 17, 1992
Source: Socialism (ASA Monographs); Ideals, Ideologies and Local Practice. Chris M. Hann (editor). <routledge.com/Socialism-Ideals-Ideologies-and-Local-Practice/Hann/p/book/9780415083225>

 But still we know that when the Europeans came, the Bushmen lived in small tribes (or clans), sometimes federated together; that they used to hunt in common, and divided the spoil without quarrelling; that they never abandoned their wounded, and displayed strong affection to their comrades. 
 Peter Kropotkin (1987a [1902]:83) 
 Concepts such as ‘anarchist’, ‘communist’, ‘socialist’, and even ‘Bushman’, are artificially constructed. This does not mean that they have no meaning. On…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nohara Shirõ - Anarchists and the May 4 Movement in China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nohara-shiro-anarchists-and-the-may-4-movement-in-china?v=1730236095</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nohara-shiro-anarchists-and-the-may-4-movement-in-china?v=1730236095"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nohara Shirõ
Title: Anarchists and the May 4 Movement in China
Date: January 1975
Notes: Translated by Philip Billingsley.
Source: Momoyama Gakuin University Library, Japan: <stars.repo.nii.ac.jp/record/7177/files/KJ00004276158.pdf> & <libcom.org/library/anarchists-may-4-movement-china>

Translator’s Note
 Until the post-Cultural Revolution thaw that began in 1979, Chinese readers found it next to impossible to gain access to information about the strong anarchist influence within their country’s revolutionary movement. From the point of view of the ruling Communist Party, in whose favour historical materials were invariably rewritten, this was a necessity borne out by the fact that, when people took to the streets in 1989 to demand a degree of control over their own lives, among t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mr Big police stings: true crime that reads like crime fiction]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8755</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mr-big-police-stings-true-crime-fiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T21:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A police method of prosecuting people suspected of being responsible for committing a serious crime, almost reads like something from a crime novel: Police manufacture a chance meeting with the suspect, then offer them paid work of a non-criminal nature before introducing jobs that appear to break the law. Through a series of interactions over […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When you miss the moment, watching it pass…]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8757</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/when-you-miss-the-moment-watching-it-pass/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The time 30 October once fell on a Saturday. The stop here had been unintentional. Unplanned. But that’s how it is for a lot of these stories. I hadn’t been to this place before, yet here I was. At ten minutes to midnight. It would be Sunday in eleven minutes. Not twenty minutes earlier, the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thih9 in "GitHub cuts AI deals with Google, Anthropic"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41988665</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41988665"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T19:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use cursor and its tab completion; while what it can do is mind blowing, in practice I’m not noticing a productivity boost.
I find that ai can help significantly with doing plumbing, but it has no problems with connecting the pipes wrong. I need to double and triple check the updated code - or fix the resulting errors when I don’t do that. So: boilerplate and outer app layers, yes; architecture and core libraries, no.
Curious, is that a property of all ai assisted tools for now? Or would copilot, perhaps with its new models, offer a different experience?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thih9</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Semantic Versioning to Simplify Release Management]]></title>
        <id>d6504957efc7f48d4d5fdb9ca03252f8f24e605b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/using-semantic-versioning-to-simplify-release-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any organization that manages software libraries and applications needs a standardized way to catalog, reference, import, fix bugs and update the versions of those libraries and applications. Semantic Versioning enables developers, testers, and project managers to have a more standardized process for committing code and managing different versions. It’s benefits also extend beyond development teams […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Kindred</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage Amazon Q Developer and AWS Chatbot within Slack]]></title>
        <id>348872cb14a26271b8eae4c0424f149ec4aace0d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/leverage-amazon-q-developer-and-aws-chatbot-within-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of Amazon Q Developer and its ability to be integrated into AWS Chatbot allows users who use Microsoft Teams or Slack to stay within their communication platform and interact with a conversational generative artificial intelligence (AI) AWS expert. Amazon Q Developer is a conversational generative AI chatbot that provides AWS assistance in the form of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281285</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Kamala campaign begins closing argument; The Fascist Question; Pennsylvania round-up; Memories of Richard Scarry ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code October 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_95</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_95"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code October 2024 Release (1.95)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by altbdoor in "GitHub cuts AI deals with Google, Anthropic"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41986040</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41986040"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://archive.is/Il4QM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>altbdoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless ML: Lessons from Capital One]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4b262f848e25</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/serverless-ml-lessons-from-capital-one-4b262f848e25?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T16:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for migrating an ML model to serverless for scalability and manageability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Impressions: Lamy Safari and Midori Notebook]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/first-impressions-lamy-safari-and-midori-notebook/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/first-impressions-lamy-safari-and-midori-notebook/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bought a Lamy Safari, my first fountain pen, a couple of weeks ago. I tend to get obsessed over things when I first get into them, and thus end up in an endless rabbit hole of research. I knew this would happen.
I go back and forth between purely taking digital notes for work and using pen and paper. For the past few years, I’ve switched to digital note taking because it’s easier to cmd + f to find what I’m looking for. However, with the constant game of musical chairs that is my dual-laptop setup for work, I end up using different applications for notes and, in turn, losing them anyway1.
And so, armed with this new pen I wanted to practice writing with, I decided to switch back to pen-and-paper mode, and back to the work notebook I’ve used on and off since 2017 2.
This is where I ran in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving Deeper into Projen: Exploring Advanced Features]]></title>
        <id>a94bc5a3754a86fa5518650bbc94d6f15d679528</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/diving-deeper-into-projen-exploring-advanced-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:31:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We will be highlighting Projen’s powerful features that cater to various aspects of project management and development. We’ll examine how Projen enhances polyglot programming within Amazon Web Services (AWS) Cloud Development Kit constructs. We’ll also touch on its built-in support for common development tools and practices. In our previous blog, we introduced you to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by exmicrosoldier in "Steve Ballmer was an underrated CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41984166</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41984166"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I disagree with Dan due to my experience as an low level employee under Ballmer. He encouraged political infighting and backstabbing and dog eat dog internal competition, while praising and desiring tight integration between teams.
He wanted "cloud first, moblie first" - two firsts! The culture at the time was built around RAID - the internal bug datadbase and that there should be clear prioritization for everything.
The inability to decide between enterprise cloud and consumer client devices held Microsoft back.
Ballmer had customers asking for enterprise cloud in 2000 but he kept listening to people talking about lifting windows sales by 10 percent with search integrated to the desktop.
And then they chose the bloated  SQL server for that and wondered why that couldn't run on normal consumer hardware in Longhorn.
The fundamental tradeoffs between something that sacrifices generalization for specialization and efficiency meant that what is good for running server rack NASDAQ didn't work for low powered laptops.
From a low level employee perspective Ballmer was the ruthless guy that wanted people to hate each other at work as they fought for survival lord of the flies style but was pikachu surprised that we could never deliver integrated experiences that worked together.
Satya's two key abilites to me were the ability to actually prioritize in a coherent way and the decision to bring the rank and file infighting down because integrated experiences are hard to build when you want your brother and sister departments to fail so yours gets more budget because thats how Ballmer worked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>exmicrosoldier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating billions of records: moving our active DNS database while it’s in use]]></title>
        <id>24rozMdbFQ7jmUgRNMF4RU</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/migrating-billions-of-records-moving-our-active-dns-database-while-in-use"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DNS records have moved to a new database, bringing improved performance and reliability to all customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Fattouche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Lies and Little Progress: Reviewing Four Years of Biden National Security Advisor Jake Sullivan’s “Foreign Policy for the Middle Class”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281255</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/big-lies-and-little-progress-biden-national-security-advisor-jake-sullivans-foreign-policy-for-the-middle-class.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sullivan went from a professed focus on the middle class to overseeing a system of mass slaughter and tried to wed the two.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the next-level of AI-powered workflows with Amazon Q Developer inline chat]]></title>
        <id>009a040a805940f8fc8938b162d51952a92ec7fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-inline-chat/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, Amazon Q Developer announced support for inline chat. Inline chat combines the benefits of in-IDE chat with the ability to directly update code, allowing developers to describe issues or ideas directly in the code editor, and receive AI-generated responses that are seamlessly integrated into their codebase. In this post, I will introduce the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Yapur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forced offline: the Q3 2024 Internet disruption summary]]></title>
        <id>3xoUhxvPcDFTiYCT9CjHhs</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/q3-2024-internet-disruption-summary"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third quarter of 2024 was particularly active, with quite a few significant Internet disruptions. Underlying causes included government-directed shutdowns, power outages, hurricane damage, terrestrial and submarine cable cuts, military action, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Meditation on Nice People]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/a-meditation-on-nice-people/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/a-meditation-on-nice-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A long time ago, a friend of mine told me that in life, you find what you look for. I believe that to be true most of the time. I'm always on the lookout for nice people. Thinking about them is a tool I use in my personal gratitude practice, a daily exercise where I record three things I'm grateful for. I have been doing it for years. There's never been a time in my life when I couldn't find some folks with kindness in their heart. Even during the years when I worked as a prison guard, there were inmates who did kind things in a non-manipulative way. I used to drink coffee continually on that job. You could buy a packet of Taster's Choice in the canteen for a dime in those days. An old con who cleaned the area around my desk gave me some sage advice one day. "Mr Plummer," he said, "Don't e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/29/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281231</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-29-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Central Bank Digital Currency (CBDC) Projects Are Foundering in Five-Eye Nations. What Gives?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281222</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/central-bank-digital-currency-cbdc-projects-are-foundering-in-all-five-eye-nations.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T10:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canada and Australia shelve plans for retail CBDCs while the US could soon become the first country to explicitly ban the central bank from issuing a CBDC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can America’s ‘Self-Made’ Men Make a President?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340150</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/can-americas-self-made-men-make-a-president/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new Biden-era federal refusal to automatically do Big Tech’s bidding has energized billionaires once content to pay relatively little attention to politics. Elon Musk has come to symbolize that new energy — and stands to gain the most from it. Trump has already promised to name Musk the head of a new “government efficiency commission” he plans to create once back in the White House. More
The post Can America’s ‘Self-Made’ Men Make a President? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Settler Colonial Contagion: A Long Simmering Plague]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340155</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/settler-colonial-contagion-a-long-simmering-plague/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ownership entitlement barrels into neighboring bodies and lands. The literal tanks that crush bodies move forward. It is as if the world couldn't understand the figurative so the gods decided on a visual you couldn't deny. Tanks running over bodies. Yet, the people still say (in the manner of abusers everywhere)......well, it's a shame they made those soldiers do that. Beware, however, of the risks involved with such behaviors-- you might get PTSD and not want to eat meat if you engage in running over other humans with your tank. More
The post Settler Colonial Contagion: A Long Simmering Plague appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Gaza Catastrophe — Checking Israeli and Western Elites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340254</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/the-gaza-catastrophe-checking-israeli-and-western-elites/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel is determined to take over North Gaza. This explains its destruction of residential areas in the region. Schools and hospitals have also been targeted. People have been forced to flee their homes. Many who have chosen to stay behind have been killed. Although some food and other essentials are now available, they are far  More
The post The Gaza Catastrophe — Checking Israeli and Western Elites appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chandra Muzaffar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dream of a “Promised Land”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340369</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/the-dream-of-a-promised-land/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve years ago, I joined an interfaith group on a trip to Israel and Palestine. My essay about the trip even won the first prize of a contest sponsored by the Unitarian Universalist Association. (link) Sadly, the escalation of horrors visited on the region today could be anticipated even then: no serious measures were taken  More
The post The Dream of a “Promised Land” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Galina DeRoeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Endorsement Isn’t “Neutrality” or “Objectivity”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340400</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/non-endorsement-isnt-neutrality-or-objectivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In late October, the Los Angeles Times published its list of candidate/issue endorsements for this year’s general election. Missing from the list: Any endorsement for president. Semafor reports that the paper’s owner, Dr. Patrick Soon-Shiong, nixed the Times editorial board’s planned endorsement of Kamala Harris over Donald Trump. A few days later, the Washington Post similarly announced that it won’t endorse for president this  More
The post Non-Endorsement Isn’t “Neutrality” or “Objectivity” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Matos, Friend and Comrade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340405</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/willie-matos-friend-and-comrade/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Willie Matos, who worked his entire adult life for Puerto Rican liberation and freedom for working class people everywhere, passed away on October 14. He was 84. Willie was participating in a panel discussion for Hispanic Heritage Month at Albertus Magnus College in New Haven marking the 60th anniversary of the passage of the 1964 Civil  More
The post Willie Matos, Friend and Comrade appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Piascik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Elon Musk Supporting Trump? Tax Avoidance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340154</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/why-is-elon-musk-supporting-trump-tax-avoidance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk, the New York Times reports, has gone all in for Donald Trump. His pro-Trump America PAC, has already spent $118 million and has the budget to spend tens of millions more, almost all of that coming from Musk himself. Musk has based his efforts on Trump’s behalf in Pennsylvania, the state he sees  More
The post Why is Elon Musk Supporting Trump? Tax Avoidance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Lord</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Playbook to Win Regardless of Election Night Results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340153</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/29/trumps-playbook-to-win-regardless-of-election-night-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T05:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Election deniers (defined by USA Today as those who have publicly denied the legitimacy of the 2020 election) are positioned as election officials to scan the ballots to challenge their validity. If Donald Trump loses to Kamala Harris, the election denier’s objections will become material for lawyers filing lawsuits to challenge state or county results.  More
The post Trump’s Playbook to Win Regardless of Election Night Results appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by addicted in "Steve Ballmer was an underrated CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978723</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978723"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T02:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article doesn’t understand what was fundamentally wrong with Ballmer’s leadership and what Nadella actually changed.
The specific technologies that were successful is irrelevant. Microsoft has and continues to invest in nearly every computer related technology that may come around the corner or they got late on.
The problem with Microsoft was everything went through Windows. The entire company was designed to promote Windows.
This was the fundamental flaw with Microsoft that Nadella changed. He quickly not just made Windows just another part of Microsoft’s business, to a great extent he actively devalued it.
The fact that Ballmer invested in Azure, etc before Nadella would all be irrelevant because under Ballmer Azure would have remained a red headed step child to Windows, so it’s unlikely to have seen much success under him anyways. Same goes for pretty much everything else Microsoft is doing right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>addicted</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by not_a_bot_4sho in "Steve Ballmer was an underrated CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41978402"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T01:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Funny story. I used to see Steve almost every weekday for a couple of years.
I can't speak to his business skills, but I can attest that he never once offered a tip for his daily black iced tea. We'd even have it ready for him before he showed up so he never had to wait! He would pay with cash, and I'd hand him his change and drink, and that was that.
It's funny to me now: one of the richest men in the world and he never once offered a tip.
Frugality aside, he was always very polite and warm so I can't be mad. Makes for a good ice breaker story.
Edit: holy moly, this is a sensitive subject. Please remember this was from a time before tipflation. Tipping meant you left your change behind once in a while only if you felt the desire to show appreciation. It wasn't an obligation. Yes, I still do think it's a funny story. Roast me for being entitled lol]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>not_a_bot_4sho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post cancellations]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53321</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/29/washington-post-cancellations/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T00:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until last Friday, I subscribed to two newspapers: the Washington Post and the Neue Zürcher Zeitung. As of Friday, I only subscribe to NZZ. I shared my cancellation on Facebook and was surprised by how many people in my network commented that they had done the same. This included people who almost never comment or […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eszter Hargittai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 1st1 in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977945</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977945"/>
        <updated>2024-10-29T00:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> How large is the Flutter team, today? Google doesn't publish this information, but my guess is that the team is about 50 people strong.
> That's 50 people serving the needs of 1,000,000. Doing a little bit of division, that means that every single member of the Flutter team is responsible for the needs of 20,000 Flutter developers! That ratio is clearly unworkable for any semblance of customer support.
This is a weird exercise. Python, for example, is a #1/#2 language in the world and there's only 50 active core devs, 90% of which don't even work on Python full time. Somehow we make that work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>1st1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pbreit in "HTML Form Validation is underused"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977759</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41977759"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T23:36:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest, easiest to implement underutilization is:
"Using specific type attribute values, such as "email", "number", or "url""
These can significantly improve user experience on mobile by triggering the optimal keyboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pbreit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by deergomoo in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41976613</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41976613"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Most people don't realize how many apps written in Flutter they use daily, simply because it's impossible to tell
You can't be serious. Maybe on Android, but on other platforms—especially iOS—they stick out like a sore thumb.
A number of them just look like Material Design Android apps awkwardly transplanted over, but I know that's down to the developer so I won't hold that against Flutter. But scrolling through the Flutter showcase[0] and calling those apps up to look at screenshots on the App Store—none of them look like native iOS apps. They don't look bad (mostly), but they don't fit in.
Don't get me wrong, I don't expect anyone else to care or even notice. But for those of us that do care, you can absolutely tell.
[0] https://flutter.dev/showcase]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deergomoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 economic laureates and more Nobel nonsense]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45693</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/28/the-2024-economic-laureates-and-more-nobel-nonsense/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Steven Klees I am quite sure that this year’s three Nobel Laureates in economics — Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson – are very competent new institutionalist economists.  Lars Syll offers a thoughtful critique of their substantive arguments, but he misses the main point for me.  New institutional economics, by and large, is nonsense.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From thousands to millions: the film budgets of Stanley Kubrick]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8750</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/thousands-millions-film-budgets-stanley-kubrick/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late American filmmaker Stanley Kubrick made his first feature, Fear and Desire, on a budget of a little over fifty-thousand dollars (US), in 1952. Almost thirty-years later, Kubrick had a budget of nineteen million dollars to make The Shining. I expect many successful filmmakers move along a similar budget trajectory. But it sounds like Kubrick […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by maxrmk in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975382</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975382"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> That's 50 people serving the needs of 1,000,000. Doing a little bit of division, that means that every single member of the Flutter team is responsible for the needs of 20,000 Flutter developers! That ratio is clearly unworkable for any semblance of customer support.
Back when I worked on .net we had fewer than 50 people maintaining a product that shipped to over a billion machines. If you opened an issue on github we'd usually reply that day.
It's getting a bit long in the tooth, but I feel like 'the mythical man month' should still be required reading for software devs. More devs != better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maxrmk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by plorkyeran in "We're forking Flutter"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975288</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41975288"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> That's 50 people serving the needs of 1,000,000. Doing a little bit of division, that means that every single member of the Flutter team is responsible for the needs of 20,000 Flutter developers! That ratio is clearly unworkable for any semblance of customer support.
If "only" 50 people working on a project used by one million people was unworkably low then every single successful project out there would be doomed. I've certainly worked on things with much worse ratios than that.
> one has to critically assess why a team that loves external contributions has only managed to merge contributions from 1,500 developers over a span of nearly a decade.
External contributions from 1500 developers over a decade is a lot. That is an unusually high number, not a low one, and backs up Flutter's claim to love external contributions.
The fact that this person thinks that they can just magically conjure up dozens of volunteer PR reviewers is wild. Everything about this post makes it pretty clear that they don't have the slightest clue of the scope of what they're trying to do. This feels like one of the standard examples of an ex-bigco person setting off on their own with no understanding how just how much the bigco did in the background to facilitate their job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>plorkyeran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ttul in "So long WordPress"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974901</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974901"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T19:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It gets so much worse. Today, my sales guy was trying to register for WordCamp, a conference that we have been attending for years as an essential place to meet customers. And then he encountered the registration form for a WordPress.org login, which neatly specifies that you affirm you have no “affiliation with WP Engine, whether financial or otherwise.” [1]
Of course, my company does have an affiliation with WP Engine. We use their service to host our website. Therefore, nobody on my team can register for a WordPress.org account.
I wrote an open letter to Matt Mullenweg complaining about the requirement and stating that I believe it violates the Sherman Act and Section 3 of the Clayton Act by being an overly broad prohibition that is clearly anti-competitive and has no clear business justification (aside from limiting competition).
Matt and the rest of the people backing Automattic should take note: Moves like this that destroy your community will eventually usher in a replacement. WordPress is pretty neat, but it only got that way because thousands of people put millions of hours into building add-ons and hosting services to make it blossom into what it is today. If their efforts are redirected in another direction, WordPress will wither away to nothing in a few years.
https://www.linkedin.com/posts/ksimpson_open-letter-to-matt-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ttul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SurgeArrest in "New iMac with M4"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974651</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41974651"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:48:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reading this on 2017 iMac 27" - is the first 5k iMac that couldn't be used as a monitor after the computer inside is irrelevant. 
I hope EU will push for some law that requires all AIO computers to work in monitor-only mode if internal hardware is no longer good enough or no longer supported by software updates.
I love the 5k screen on this iMac but the CPU is too old for photo or video editing as software got so much slower over the years. 
I could have used this screen for many more years, but now it will hit landfill... Apple is only "green" in their presentations - in reality they care more about inifite sales only.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SurgeArrest</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[rock bottom]]></title>
        <id>https://flecha248.bearblog.dev/rock-bottom/</id>
        <link href="https://flecha248.bearblog.dev/rock-bottom/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rock bottom is very often where we begin our healing journey. This is not because we suddenly see the light, nor because our worst days are magically transmuted into some type of epiphany, and not because someone saves us from our own madness. Rock bottom becomes a turning point because it is only at that point that most people think: I never want to feel this way again.
That thought is not just an idea. It is a declaration and a resolution. It is one of the most life-changing things you can ever experience. It becomes the foundation upon which you build everything else.
When you decide you truly do not ever want to feel a certain way again, you set out on a journey of self-awareness, learning, and growth that leads you to radically reinvent who you are.
In that moment, fault becomes irrel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating 10 Years of Amazon ECS: Powering a Decade of Containerized Innovation]]></title>
        <id>a104b5e60ff355bb5245b7686517b8829f9bfefc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/celebrating-10-years-of-amazon-ecs-powering-a-decade-of-containerized-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:28:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade of AWS innovation: Amazon ECS evolved from simplifying container orchestration to powering massive operations like Prime Day and enabling customers like SmugMug to seamlessly migrate petabytes of data and scale efficiently with "blazingly-fast" performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New code editor in AWS Lambda console, Amazon Q Business analytics, Claude 3.5 upgrades, and more (October 28, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>d2bccde1d7f3d42d9e6a3a70e09425042cd11315</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-code-editor-in-aws-lambda-console-amazon-q-business-analytics-claude-3-5-upgrades-and-more-october-28-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T17:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks ago, I had the wonderful opportunity to host subject matter experts from across Asia Pacific in the global 24 Hours of Amazon Q live stream event. This continuous 24-hour stream offered insights from AWS experts on Amazon Q Developer and Amazon Q Business, featuring use cases, product demos, and Q&A sessions. The highlight for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Literature Review on Sampling Techniques for Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.njkumar.com/literature-review-sampling-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://www.njkumar.com/literature-review-sampling-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is going to consist of my ongoing review of various sampling methods I’ve found through papers and online implementations. While samplers are relatively straightforward to create and combine, there is a challenge in trying to sample both high quality and diverse outputs. I'm particularly interested in finding samplers that are context-aware, resist hallucination, and can explore multiple reasoning paths in language models. For most of the samplers below I link their corresponding papers, implementations, and default parameter settings.
Basics
Logits and Logprobs
Language models generate text by predicting one token at a time. First, the process starts with tokenizing input text and converting these tokens into embeddings. Then, we feed them through the model’s layers and get logi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raphael Sassaki - Moore on Jerusalem, Eternalism, Anarchy and Herbie!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/raphael-sassaki-moore-on-jerusalem-eternalism-anarchy-and-herbie?v=1730130515</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/raphael-sassaki-moore-on-jerusalem-eternalism-anarchy-and-herbie?v=1730130515"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Raphael Sassaki
Title: Moore on Jerusalem, Eternalism, Anarchy and Herbie!
Date: January 2017
Notes: Originally published in Folha de São Paulo.
Source: Retrieved on 28th October 2024 from alanmooreworld.blogspot.com

Raphael Sassaki: How did you come up with the idea of Jerusalem, which tells a story that spreads through 1000 years in Northampton? How was the writing of it?
Alan Moore: Rather than originating from a single idea, Jerusalem is more the convergence of several different impulses and concepts. Foremost amongst these were the growing need to talk about the tiny but historically peculiar district I was raised in, and the simultaneous urge to talk about my family in a way that included both its history and its mythology. This, I soon realised, would require the proposed b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Moore - Fandom has toxified the world]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alan-moore-fandom-has-toxified-the-world?v=1730130220</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alan-moore-fandom-has-toxified-the-world?v=1730130220"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alan Moore
Title: Fandom has toxified the world
Subtitle: On superheroes, Comicsgate and Trump
Date: 26 October 2024
Source: Retrieved on 28th October 2024 from www.theguardian.com

About a decade ago, I ventured my opinion that the adult multitudes queueing for superhero movies were potentially an indicator of emotional arrest, which could have worrying political and social implications. Since at that time Brexit, Donald Trump and fascist populism hadn’t happened yet, my evidently crazy diatribe was largely met with outrage from the fan community, some of whom angrily demanded I be extradited to the US and made to stand trial for my crimes against superhumanity – which I felt didn’t necessarily disprove my allegations. 
 Ten years on, let me make my position clear: I believe that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by minimaxir in "New iMac with M4"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41971971</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41971971"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T15:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[16GB base RAM, they finally did it.
They also did move the Magic Keyboard and Magic Mouse to USB-C.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>minimaxir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 CAIRFI fellowships & research awardees announced]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2f650898e71e</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/2024-cairfi-fellowships-research-awardees-announced-2f650898e71e?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T12:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One announces 2024 award recipients out of the Center for Responsible Financial Innovation at Columbia University RFP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There’s Gold in Them Thar Reels]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53316</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/28/theres-gold-in-them-thar-reels/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T11:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of the gold rush is deeply rooted in the American psyche. “There’s gold in them thar hills.” Anyone can abandon his family and community to gamble big on themselves. Thanks to this rugged individualism and the natural bounty of our territory, there’s a chance that you can strike it rich. More than American, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thomasfl in "Ask HN: What are you working on? (October 2024)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41969858</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41969858"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T11:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For me the most important issue that needs to be solved right now is the increasing urban sprawl and the car dependent neighborhoods. It causes social isolation. Maintaining infrastructure like roads and electricity, is causing a strain on the economy for local municipalities. Not to mention the disastrous effect car based transportation has on the environment.
I am a fullstack developer living in Norway. Last year I registered the Norwegian branch of the Architectural Uproar as a not for profit organization. With the support from paying members, I have been able to go on tour to most of the major cities in Norway. We organize large meetings were we discuss architecture and city planning with politicians, architects and property developers on stage.
I am strongly inspired by Create Streets in UK and Strong Towns in the US. I want to improve people’s quality of life, help saving the planet and make Norway beautiful again while doing it.
https://arkitekturopproret.no edit: typos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thomasfl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody Owns CounterPunch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340171</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/nobody-owns-counterpunch/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please support our annual fall fund drive.
The post Nobody Owns CounterPunch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathaniel St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of US democracy: a flowchart]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53310</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/28/the-end-of-us-democracy-a-flowchart/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:39:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s not much I can do about it, but I still spend a lot of time thinking about what I, and others outside the US, should do if that country ceases to be a democracy. But, it doesn’t seem as if lots of other people are thinking this way. One possibility is that people just […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vldmrs in "Ask HN: What are you working on? (October 2024)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41968277</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41968277"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've noticed that my son spends way too much time on YouTube or playing Minecraft and one of the few offline activities he enjoys doing on his own is coloring. And since he comes to me every time he wants a new coloring book and we spend about 10 minutes together searching for each picture, I made a website with a collection of coloring books for him. The site is very simple, but to be honest, I haven't had so much fun with the process of creation for a long time.
https://colorango.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vldmrs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Latest Absurdities From the Columnists of the New York Times]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340198</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/the-latest-absurdities-from-the-columnists-of-the-new-york-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T06:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Both Friedman and Stephens argue that it is up to the Palestinians to take the lead in building a more politically moderate Middle East and to create conditions for the start of real diplomacy.  Neither Friedman nor Stephens acknowledges the difficult task of getting access to a new Hamas leadership or the even more difficult task of getting a notoriously right-wing Israeli government to compromise on any aspect of an Arab-Israeli peace plan.  Stephens risibly refers to the possibility of Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu “living up to his Churchillian self-image,” (whatever that could possibly mean). More
The post The Latest Absurdities From the Columnists of the New York Times appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnam Chemical Warfare’s Secret Toxic Legacies: Agent Blue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340104</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/vietnam-chemical-warfares-secret-toxic-legacies-agent-blue/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For over 50 years, US news about chemical warfare during the American Vietnam War has been dominated by the story of Agent Orange and its devastating impacts. During the Vietnam War period, however, another diabolical concoction called Agent Blue was also used extensively in Vietnam. This arsenic-based herbicide was used to kill rice and the public knew little about its use. In fact, the first news reference to this chemical weapon was a simple letter to the editor sent by Arthur H. Westing in 1971 and published by the New York Times under the headline “‘Agent Blue’ in Vietnam.” More
The post Vietnam Chemical Warfare’s Secret Toxic Legacies: Agent Blue appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Olson – Bryan R. Higgins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Violent Rhetoric Rising: an Analysis of Nine Years of Trump’s Speeches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340167</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/violent-rhetoric-rising-an-analysis-of-nine-years-of-trumps-speeches/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:56:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s political career has been marked by a unique and often controversial rhetorical style. Since 2015, his rhetoric has evolved significantly, attracting attention for its direct, often violent tone. Analyzing his speeches offers a revealing look at how his language has shaped both his political persona and the broader landscape of American politics. We  More
The post Violent Rhetoric Rising: an Analysis of Nine Years of Trump’s Speeches appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Savin – Daniel Treisman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crippling UNRWA: The Knesset’s Collective Punishment of Palestinians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340208</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/crippling-unrwa-the-knessets-collective-punishment-of-palestinians/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The man has a cheek.  Having lectured Iranians and Lebanese about what (and who) is good for them in terms of rulers and rule (we already know what he thinks of the Palestinians), Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has been keeping busy on further depriving access and assistance to those in Gaza and the West Bank.  This  More
The post Crippling UNRWA: The Knesset’s Collective Punishment of Palestinians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Western Distortions of the Palestinian Struggle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/western-distortions-of-the-palestinian-struggle/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Western colonialism and imperialism are the roots of the Palestinian struggle. A common characteristic of western powers is their shared history of colonization and oppression of indigenous populations. This distinction is important because it is clear that there is heavy bias against Palestinians in both western political policy and western mainstream media. The United States and Israel  More
The post Western Distortions of the Palestinian Struggle appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lamees Hijazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reality and Mainstream Media Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340164</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/reality-and-mainstream-media-reporting/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early October 2024, Professor Joseph Massad of Columbia University gave an interview to the online news site Electronic Intifada. In it he explained that there is a “huge gap” between the academic (evidence-based) understanding of aspects of the Palestinian-Israeli conflict (such as the Jewish supremacist nature of Israeli society and its resulting apartheid policies) and the mainstream media assumptions about (a “democratic” and “progressive”) Israel. The latter define the popular and official reporting about that country and its Zionist ideology.  More
The post Reality and Mainstream Media Reporting appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide to Climate Action in Your Local Community]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340210</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/guide-to-climate-action-in-your-local-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to have a voice in how policy decisions are made and resources are distributed in your local community, the data you collect will be critical. Generally, before they commit to spending tax dollars on a new program or policy, local government agencies want to understand the scope and scale of the problem  More
The post Guide to Climate Action in Your Local Community appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cate Mingoya-LaFortune</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women and Children Pay the Highest Price]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340183</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/women-and-children-pay-the-highest-price/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israel Defense Forces (IDF) are widely considered one of the most powerful armies in the world. And, according to Israeli leaders, they are “the most moral army in the world.” How, then, to reconcile these statements with what is happening now in Gaza and Lebanon, where tens of thousands of women and children have  More
The post Women and Children Pay the Highest Price appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is This Any Way to Stop Fascism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340256</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/is-this-any-way-to-stop-fascism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Vice President Kamala Harris was hoping the New York Times’ interview with John Kelly, Trump’s former Chief of Staff and retired Marine Corps General, would be the “October surprise” that would shift prospective voters against Trump, it has not played out that way, so far. Published on October 22, Kelly’s interview is a shocking read. Trump, according to  More
The post Is This Any Way to Stop Fascism? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tales From the Sargasso Sea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=340101</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/28/tales-from-the-sargasso-sea/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T05:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we step into the music… creation can sing free. — Murray Kyle Growing up in Athens, Greece I remember vividly the fascination my high school classmates and I shared about “the Bermuda Triangle.” In hushed tones, we spoke about this mysterious remote region where ships and airplanes—if they made the grave error of wandering  More
The post Tales From the Sargasso Sea appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eileen Crist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rudolf Rocker - The Truth About Spain]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-rocker-the-truth-about-spain?v=1730091464</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/rudolf-rocker-the-truth-about-spain?v=1730091464"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T04:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Rudolf Rocker
Title: The Truth About Spain
Date: 1936
Source: This text was retrieved on 2024-10-16 from https://www.scribd.com/document/292981558/Rocker. Clarifications for text which was obscured in the original source were retrieved on 2024-10-27 from https://stars.library.ucf.edu/prism/

 If there is any event that can bring about a rediscovery of inner strength on the part of organized labor and the libertarian elements of the world, it is the grand struggle against Fascism now being waged in Spain. After the unresisting defeat of the labor movement in Germany the effect of the heroic battle of the Spanish workers, peasants, and intellectuals against the Fascist bandits is that of a refreshing thunderstorm. It is the first time since Fascism made its appearance in Europe that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End of October 2024 update]]></title>
        <id>https://damien.zone/end-of-october-2024-update/</id>
        <link href="https://damien.zone/end-of-october-2024-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T04:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, little blog, it's been a while! The past two weeks have been uncharacteristically busy for me so, huh, I didn't write much here, oops!
I spent a week of vacation in Reno for definitely normal reasons. Turns out, being mostly offline with your friends and other freaks (complimentary) for a whole week is good??? Someone should look into this.
Then, as soon as I came back, my friend Joanna was in town to visit the Internet Archive, so I tagged along. I saw a bunch of very cool shit. Like, look at all this stuff!! Tell me this isn't cool as hell!!
Excuse the shoddy photography job lmao.
Servers!! A few of the many (I was told) servers that the Internet Archive HQ in San Francisco houses




A Petabox!! I didn't know the Internet Archive had one of these so early (2004!) but it makes sen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can’t Figure Out Your Personality Type?]]></title>
        <id>https://josephlee.bearblog.dev/cant-figure-out-your-personality-type/</id>
        <link href="https://josephlee.bearblog.dev/cant-figure-out-your-personality-type/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T04:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to struggle with explaining why some of my friends or family members didn’t quite fit into any of the 16 MBTI personality types. A friend of mine seemed like an INFP but had traits of an ISTJ, and my cousin felt like an ESFP, yet was as considerate as an ESFJ.
Then I stumbled upon Personality Ninja (or "NXT"), which uses 32 types instead of just 16. Suddenly, things started to make sense.
At first, I thought, “What? There are only 16 types!” But after trying it out with friends, I realized their new descriptions actually felt accurate. This system offered flexibility and depth the original 16 types didn’t seem to capture.
Curious, I dove deeper into whether 32 types could really work—and found out there’s no reason they can’t! If you look back at Carl Jung, who created the concept of cognitive functions, he didn’t enforce the rigid stacks we see in MBTI or the Harold Grant function model.
Personality Ninja’s approach allows both the first and second functions to be in the same attitude (both extraverted or both introverted), unlike MBTI’s requirement for them to be opposites.
This flexibility means types don’t have to follow TeSi or SiTe formats—they can be TeSe or SiTi. It was the answer I’d been looking for: my friend turned out to be FiSi, while my cousin was FeSe.
So if you’ve ever felt stuck trying to fit yourself or others into the 16 types, it might be worth exploring the 32-type approach!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[is the sky still blue?]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/sky-blue/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/sky-blue/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-28T01:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today was a good day. Even though I had trouble enjoying it and probably will for a while, I want to write about it so I can remember it as such. The sky is still blue and life beautiful!
I woke up at 7 and had my first morning workout in a long time, just to keep my mind off things. I'm hoping I can get into a routine with exercise again — I've spent most of the the past few weeks in bed (injuries, mood, medical reasons) and my muscles have gotten noticeably weaker. I missed it. Exercise has always been therapeutic for me; I like being able to focus on something external and feeling a pain that you know will fade.


chuta, the fall colors are so stubbornly beautiful here
I met J and E for a walk around Central Park and lunch at Sala Thai. I don't often eat Thai food because my opinion of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No one stopped writing diaries, they started publishing blogs instead]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8747</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/personal-websites-blogs-replaced-written-diaries/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mali Waugh, writing for The Age: I also think that keeping a written diary is not really done any more. I wonder whether part of this is that people are much more accepting of traditionally private things being put in the public domain. For the most part, this is a good thing but also sometimes […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[october]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/october/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/october/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[what a month.
cohost went read-only on the first. i went to a user meetup / wake in northampton the following weekend. i continued my job hunt (successful, btw). i tried (and largely failed) to rest. i learned that i am extremely bad at being unemployed.
everyone i talked to told me that it's pretty normal to not do anything in that window, that it's normal and reasonable to need a break. unfortunately, it did not feel like i was resting, it just felt like i couldn't do anything (distinct! not fun!).
anyway. tomorrow i start a new job, which will give me some structure in my day again. i get novelty—meeting new people, working on new things, experiencing and solving new problems. i'm looking forward to it.
weird, rough month. i am tired. someday i will be able to rest, but it is not right now.
i want to actually keep up with this blog more. i hadn't really realized it had been nearly a month since my last post. time flies. when i have things to write about, i'll do it here. that's about all i can promise.
ok that's it bye]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i cut all my hair off]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/shaved-head/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/shaved-head/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, I finally did it. I talked about it already in this post about my hair troubles and finally went through with it and cut all my hair off.

I did it because my illness/medication related hair loss just didn't stop for months now and I didn't like any of it. The hair on all my clothes, on the floor, in the bed, the shower and sink drains. I never had especially voluminous hair; I was on the lower average of the amount, and it was fine hair. But with now less than half left and no signs of slowing down, it was shitty to style, was constantly stringy even when it wasn't greasy, and had no volume at all. The edges of where my face met my hair were really thinning as well; thankfully no bald spots. I like having very long hair, but not when it is so little.
I also thought about the regrowth …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Nîmes]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53308</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/27/sunday-photoblogging-nimes/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-27T09:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by satvikpendem in "How 'Factorio' seduced Silicon Valley and me"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41957259</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41957259"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T19:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know lots of people who play Factorio but for me, I guess it just feels too much like work? Whenever I play it, I get the distinct feeling that I could instead do the same thing but productively instead, such as by contributing to my OSS projects (sometimes, maybe even for profit instead). I never got into these types of programmatic games for precisely this reason but I'd like to understand other perspectives on this.
The games I play instead are wholly unrelated to my work life, such as FPS or RPG ones, where there is a clear distinction between what I can do and what I want to do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>satvikpendem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris conference raises $1 billion for Lebanon + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/paris-conference-raises-1-billion-for-lebanon-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/paris-conference-raises-1-billion-for-lebanon-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T15:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.N. warns of record greenhouse gas levels; Paris conference secures $1 billion for Lebanon]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The BRICS summit in Russia offers no alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-BRICS-summit-in-Russia-offers-no-alternative</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-BRICS-summit-in-Russia-offers-no-alternative"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T09:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 23 October 2023, the 16th BRICS summit issued a 134-point Kazan Declaration clearly stating that the BRICS bloc is not an alternative in the interests of the people. 
English

/ 
South, 
BRICS, 
Imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lefstathiou in "Before you buy a domain name, first check to see if it's haunted"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41951890</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41951890"/>
        <updated>2024-10-26T02:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened to me and I found this tool super helpful to get my site unblocked: https://dnsblacklist.org/
I purchased a valuable premium domain to host a personal art collection (of anime cels). For some bizarre reason, the site was inaccessible from my work computer and it was de-listed from Google even if I typed the url itself into search.
I hired a square space specialist to figure out why, to no avail. I then begged our company’s CISO to investigate and it turns out we had some firewall setting on UniFi that blocked the domain because it appeared on a list. Once I checked way back, it turns out that it was as an anime porn aggregator years back. I personally reached out to all the web filters out there (Google, Symantec, bing) and one by one filed tickets for them to mark it as art instead of pornography and it worked.  I am now properly crawled on Google but still MIA on Bing, search console is giving me some BS error that’s incomprehensible, typical of MSFT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lefstathiou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lapcat in "Jeff Bezos killed Washington Post endorsement of Kamala Harris"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41951079</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41951079"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Newspapers publish opinions for the same reason that they publish comic strips: people want to read them. Readers seek them out. Newspapers are a business and have to give their customers what they want.
The problematic aspect here is that the current business owner, Jeff Bezos, has a conflict of interest. Bezos is making a bad business decision for The Washington Post, sacrificing it and losing readers for the sake of his other business interests, i.e., government contracts. It's unlikely that an independent owner with no conflict of interest would make the same decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lapcat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "Wikipedia article blocked worldwide by Delhi high court"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41950796</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41950796"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 18 2012, Wikipedia went black to draw attention to SOPA [0], a bill they described as one that "could fatally damage the free and open Internet".
Since then, we've seen a slow and steady march in the direction we all dreaded. Country after country has decided that they have the right to block content on the "free and open Internet", and business after business (even those who joined the SOPA protests) has complied. Someone looking ahead from 2012 would barely recognize the internet today as being the same thing, the way we just roll over to the threats that used to cause global outrage and defiance.
Were we naive even at the time? Have governments become more authoritarian? Or has our energy for resistance just been slowly whittled away?
[0] https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protests_against_SOPA_and_PI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[studyin' art]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/studyin-art/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/studyin-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T23:04:03.618Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[as i've posted about before, i've been taking time off from creating art to recover from some Life Problems™️. so while i've got a lot of downtime - i spent like, a solid week and a half unable to leave my bed for very long - i thought i'd pass the time by studying art.
recently, i had hit a wall with art... the last "polished" drawings i had worked on were all the way back in August. and Life Problems™️ kicking my ass certainly didn't help. when this happens, i try to shift my focus to something else. which i did! i went into an absolute frenzy trying to get a site put together, set up this blog, etc etc.
... and then after burning out from all of that, my body begged for rest and i begrudgingly complied, not having a choice in the matter. i was eager to start studying, though... hitting …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by redrix in "Wikipedia article blocked worldwide by Delhi high court"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41950680</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41950680"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T22:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[http://archive.today/XIxZv]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>redrix</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wilhil in "Company named "><SCRIPT SRC=HTTPS://MJT.XSS.HT> LTD" forced to change it (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41949293</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41949293"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T20:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My fav "abuse" of the system was a car park terminal that was running some flavour of Windows with an antivirus software.
It had a scanner for the barcode of a ticket, but, it understood lots of other barcodes/encoding systems and must have been logging to the filesystem.
So... saw someone encode the EICAR test string to a QR Code and put it to the scanner... that caused the AV to popup which covered the entire screen and made the terminal unusable!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wilhil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by byefruit in "Company named "><SCRIPT SRC=HTTPS://MJT.XSS.HT> LTD" forced to change it (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41949244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41949244"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T20:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A troll so good it necessitated a change in the law: https://publications.parliament.uk/pa/bills/cbill/58-03/0154...
(Page 16, 57A)
"A company must not be registered under this Act by a name that, in the
opinion of the Secretary of State, consists of or includes computer
code."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>byefruit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Molitor5901 in "Jeff Bezos killed Washington Post endorsement of Kamala Harris"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41948896</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41948896"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T19:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To play Devils Advocate for a moment: Why do we need, or even want, a newspaper to endorse a President? How does it not undermine a paper's journalistic ethics to be neutral and fair?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Molitor5901</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Kong: &ldquo;Spellbound&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/spellbound</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/spellbound"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T18:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Victor Erice’s ‘Close Your Eyes’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diff Authoring Time: Measuring developer productivity at Meta]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21928</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/10/25/developer-tools/diff-authoring-time-dat-measuring-developer-productivity-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T16:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Meta, we’re always looking for ways to enhance the productivity of our engineers and developers. But how exactly do you measure developer productivity? On this episode of the Meta Tech Podcast Pascal Hartig (@passy) sits down with Sarita and Moritz, two engineers at Meta who have been working on Diff Authoring Time (DAT) – a [...]
Read More...
The post Diff Authoring Time: Measuring developer productivity at Meta appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dustin Illingworth: &ldquo;Glorious Delusion&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/glorious-delusion</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/glorious-delusion"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T15:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Augusto Monterroso.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I've never used cohost. But I miss it.]]></title>
        <id>https://plume.pink/blog-cohost/</id>
        <link href="https://plume.pink/blog-cohost/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's a strange feeling, missing something you've never been a part of or even saw. And yet, that is what the end of "cohost" makes me feel.
There has been an influx of Bear Blog users that are from cohost. Who transferred over their blog from there, and so on, and lots of them have that little stamp saying, I was on cohost. It's sad because reading them it feels like a bygone era. Something is over now and I'll never get to see it but it sounded amazing and people have such fondness for what it was. It's heartbreaking almost.
And the most beautiful aspect of it to me is that no one seems bitter. Everyone that I've read talking about cohost expressed the same feeling of, I'm glad it was a thing, I'm glad it happened. It feels like something that had space to grow and that ended relatively s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lily Lynch: &ldquo;Old News?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/old-news</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/old-news"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Austrian Elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lily Lynch: &ldquo;Old News?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/old-news</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/old-news"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Austrian elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the The Teach-In and its role in Academic Freedom. From Arnold Kaufman to Meena Krishnamurthy]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53292</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/25/on-the-the-teach-in-and-its-role-in-academic-freedom-from-arnold-kaufman-to-meena-krishnamurthy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before Rawls’ shadow in left-liberal political philosophy there was Arnold S. Kaufman (1927-1971), who died when his airplane collided with a military jet while traveling (recall this post). While there is no Wikipedia page devoted to him, Kaufman was rather famous during the 1960s because of his involvement with the student movement at the University […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elephants in tunnels: how Hyperdrive connects to databases inside your VPC networks]]></title>
        <id>5GK429XQHhFzVyKSXGZ2R6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/elephants-in-tunnels-how-hyperdrive-connects-to-databases-inside-your-vpc-networks"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperdrive (Cloudflare’s globally distributed SQL connection pooler and cache) recently added support for directing database traffic from Workers across Cloudflare Tunnels. We dive deep on what it took to add this feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Repp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Most Powerful Method For Personal Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/the-most-powerful-method-for-personal-growth/</id>
        <link href="https://circlesoflife.bearblog.dev/the-most-powerful-method-for-personal-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T12:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's the most effective way for one to become better? It’s a question that’s been on my mind for years, maybe even decades. With all the books, articles, and advice on personal growth that I’ve sifted through, it seems like there are endless ways to approach it, each promising the one and only answer you'll ever need.
But over time, I’ve noticed one thing that feels like a thread running through it all: the impact certain ideas have on me and, more importantly, my reactions to them.
I’ve come to believe that paying attention to these reactions might be the clearest guide to finding a growth path that feels genuinely “me.” When something strikes a nerve, when a passage or concept sticks with me long after reading it, it feels like a signal—an opportunity to dig deeper and uncover why it s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pathways to sustainability (2): a critical review]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45665</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/25/pathways-to-sustainability-2-a-critical-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T05:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Maria Alejandra and WEA Pedagogy Blog Jean-Baptiste Fressoz, professor at the School of Advanced Studies in Social Sciences in Paris, challenges our understanding of the current energy transition process. In his book “The Shock of the Anthropocene: The Earth, History, and Us,” co-authored with Christophe Bonneuil, Fressoz offers a critical history of the Anthropocene, the current geological […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Alejandra Madi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by danpalmer in "Bitwarden SDK relicensed from proprietary to GPLv3"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41941795</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41941795"/>
        <updated>2024-10-25T02:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Unfortunately, I no longer recommend Bitwarden for normal people because the built-in password manager in Firefox is too good
Interesting, I've always felt that browser-based password managers provided remarkably little value for most people. Using them on mobile is tricky and platform dependent, it's easy to have local-only, non-synced data and then lose it, and being multi-device is trickier, especially in a work context.
On the other hand, people generally understand installing an app on each device they own and that app doing it for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danpalmer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple said to be reducing production of Vision Pro headset]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8742</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/apple-reportedly-reducing-production-vision-pro/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hartley Charlton, writing for Mac Rumours: Citing multiple people “directly involved” in making components for the headset, the report says that the scaling back of production began in the early summer. My take here is people thought Vision Pro was going to be the next WOW Apple product, and units would fly off the shelves, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humane may licence CosmOS, the AI Pin operating system]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8740</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/humane-licence-cosmos-ai-pin-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T20:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humane’s AI Pin, launched to less than flattering fanfare last April, may not have lived up to expectations of being an “iPhone killer”. But CosmOS, the device’s operating system, is something else altogether, says Om Malik, writing for Crazy Stupid Tech: An AI-focused operating system is agent-driven instead of application-driven. The agents — tiny bits […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 101008 in "Show HN: 2048 turned 10 this year, I built an updated version to celebrate"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41938545</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41938545"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This may be buried in the comments and you will never see it, but thank you very much Gabriele. Your game helped me in a very weird circumstance.
I was afraid of flying, specially on the takeoff and landing (and turbulence as well, ha). So I read somewhere that if I focused on something else, it would help me. So for the past years, I played 2048 during takeoff and landing, and it worked. It helped me to focus on something else, not the airplane, and I started to enjoying more my trips.
Now I don't need to do it anymore, but just for the experience I still do it when I fly. So thank you for helping me with my fear!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>101008</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mordae in "Show HN: 2048 turned 10 this year, I built an updated version to celebrate"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41938356</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41938356"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T18:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This doesn't make any sense. We should be celebrating 8 years, 16 years and so on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mordae</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frozen Russian assets fund Ukraine's aid package + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/frozen-russian-assets-fund-ukraine-s-aid-package-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/frozen-russian-assets-fund-ukraine-s-aid-package-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T17:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[G7 allies approve a $50 billion loan for Ukraine using frozen Russian assets; BRICS summit features rare talks between Xi and Modi; France pledges €100 million aid for Lebanon's humanitarian crisis; ESA considers partnership with SpaceX to address space debris.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build durable applications on Cloudflare Workers: you write the Workflows, we take care of the rest]]></title>
        <id>1YRfz7LKvAGrEMbRGhNrFP</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-workflows-durable-execution-on-workers"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Workflows is now in open beta! Workflows allows you to build reliable, repeatable, long-lived multi-step applications that can automatically retry, persist state, and scale out. Read on to learn how Workflows works, how we built it on top of Durable Objects, and how you can deploy your first Workflows application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sid Chatterjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billions and billions (of logs): scaling AI Gateway with the Cloudflare Developer Platform]]></title>
        <id>2LUyKREpCJjJ5qGqwZyoAx</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/billions-and-billions-of-logs-scaling-ai-gateway-with-the-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How we scaled AI Gateway to handle and store billions of requests, using Cloudflare Workers, D1, Durable Objects, and R2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catarina Pires Mota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Durable Objects aren't just durable, they're fast: a 10x speedup for Cloudflare Queues]]></title>
        <id>41vXJNWrB0YHsKqSz6SGDS</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-we-built-cloudflare-queues"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how we built Cloudflare Queues using our own Developer Platform and how it evolved to a geographically-distributed, horizontally-scalable architecture built on Durable Objects. Our new architecture supports over 10x more throughput and over 3x lower latency compared to the previous version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Wheeler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Not Selling Myself Short]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/on-not-selling-myself-short/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/on-not-selling-myself-short/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was eighteen, I worked weekends at a local hospital doing registration for the emergency department. I spent my weekdays attending community college and my free time dreaming about making movies. Then one day that all came crashing down.
I got an unexpected call at work from my father. He told me not to come home. All I had was the scrubs I was wearing, my cell phone, and a few hundred dollars in the bank.
I didn't do anything wrong. I wasn't a troublemaker. I didn't drink or do drugs. I never caused any issues. I was a straight A student who graduated from high school early. So, to say this was unexpected would be an understatement.
To this day, I don't know the exact reasoning for this phone call. My father was abusing alcohol and prescription drugs and my stepmother was bitter th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My terrible blogging conundrum]]></title>
        <id>https://dm.bearblog.dev/my-terrible-blogging-conundrum/</id>
        <link href="https://dm.bearblog.dev/my-terrible-blogging-conundrum/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-24T08:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My blogging conundrum is as follows:
I want to blog.
But I don't want to pay.
I want to blog.
But I don't want people to read what I write.
I want to blog.
But I want people to read and engage with what I write.
I want to blog.
But I want my blog to have a comments facility.
I want to blog.
But I want my blog to be just my posts, with no input from anyone else.
I want to blog, but in secret.
I want to blog, but I want everyone to know about my blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>