<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-10-10T12:49:29.676Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-10-10T12:49:29.676Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“15 Best Economics Book Blogs and Websites in 2024”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45626</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/10/15-best-economics-book-blogs-and-websites-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Feedspot The best Economics Book blogs from thousands of Book blogs on the web and ranked by traffic, social media followers & freshness. Economics Book Blogs Here are 15 Best Economics Book Blogs you should follow in 2024 1. Real-World Economics Review Blog The Real-World Economics Review blog serves as a critical platform for economists, scholars, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Stock Markets’ Reactions to EU Climate Policy Shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32002</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/international-stock-markets-reactions-to-eu-climate-policy-shocks/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While policies to combat climate change are designed to address a global problem, they are generally implemented at the national level. Nevertheless, the impact of domestic climate policies may spill over internationally given countries' economic and financial interdependence. For example, a carbon tax charged to domestic firms for their use of fossil fuels may lead the firms to charge higher prices to their domestic and foreign customers; given the importance of global value chains in modern economies, the impact of that carbon tax may propagate across multiple layers of cross-border production linkages. In this post, we quantify the spillover effects of climate policies on forward-looking asset prices globally by estimating the impact of carbon price shocks in the European Union’s Emissions Trading System (EU ETS) on stock prices across a broad set of country-industry pairs. In other words, we measure how asset markets evaluate the impact of changes to the carbon price on growth and profitability prospects of the firms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian di Giovanni, Galina Hale, Neel Lahiri, and Anirban Sanyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280142</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T10:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our popular daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satyajit Das: US Presidential Politics – The More They Bicker, the More They Stay the Same]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280140</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/satyajit-das-us-presidential-politics-the-more-they-bicker-the-more-they-stay-the-same.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T08:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US presidential candidates promise policy choices but have little room to manoeuvre. Ergo, politics turns into a contest like American Idol]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study Warns of ‘Irreversible Impacts’ From Overshooting 1.5°C, Even Temporarily]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280138</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/study-warns-of-irreversible-impacts-from-overshooting-1-5c-even-temporarily.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T07:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new paper in Nature finds that exceeding a 1.5°C increase in global temperature  is more deadly and durable than previously thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Communications Rules for Activists to Live By]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280113</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/11-communications-rules-for-activists-to-live-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeking reader reactions to recommendations on how to engage in "media activism".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mounting Costs of Ennabling Israel’s War on Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336782</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/the-mounting-costs-of-ennabling-israels-war-on-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, 2023, around 42,000 Palestinians have been killed in Gaza, plus over 700 more in the West Bank. Over 1,100 Israelis have been killed, too. These tragedies are a direct consequence of Israel’s illegal, U.S.-backed occupation of Palestinian territory and its war on Gaza, which must both end immediately. From the mass killing and maiming of Palestinian civilians to the forced starvation and deliberate destruction of Gaza’s health infrastructure, Palestinians and international experts have warned from the start that Israel is committing a “textbook case of genocide” in Gaza. More
The post The Mounting Costs of Ennabling Israel’s War on Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Immigration State and its Everyday Accomplices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336798</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/the-immigration-state-and-its-everyday-accomplices/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T06:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a year of watching thousands of people suffer a genocide fueled in large part by U.S. dollars and technology, the usual order of life on university campuses has been upended. Students, staff and faculty have protested, picketed, rallied, and exercised a long tradition of “expressive activity” that has come to define the unique space that inhabits university life. To say that this is a novel upsurge would be to ignore the student mobilizations throughout the years, against the massacres in Vietnam, apartheid in South Africa, and racisms past and present in our backyard. Each of these struggles have become part of the glossy photos memorializing universities’ nostalgic past, and seeming proof of their reputations as bastions of free expression, even in the face of government oppression. More
The post The Immigration State and its Everyday Accomplices appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shannon Gleeson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11 Communications Rules for Activists to Live by]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336857</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/11-communications-rules-for-activists-to-live-by/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than 50 years, I have been a progressive media activist. During my half-century of activism, I’ve learned how to use the media for social change, starting in the late 1960s, an era when idealists, activists, and utopians did so brilliantly, even dominating popular culture. Alas, today that’s all changed. Reflecting back on a  More
The post 11 Communications Rules for Activists to Live by appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Fenton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[License to Muzzle: Taking Offence at Flag Wavers for Hezbollah]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336861</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/license-to-muzzle-taking-offence-at-flag-wavers-for-hezbollah/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was done for the Viet Cong in numerous countries during the US involvement in Vietnam.  It was done for the African National Congress (ANC). It was done for the Irish Revolutionary Army (IRA).  Across the United States, Europe and Australasia, all three organisations, demonised as terrorist outfits, received tacit, symbolic support from protestors.  In some cases, support  More
The post License to Muzzle: Taking Offence at Flag Wavers for Hezbollah appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the Collective Offering an Alternative to the ‘Mental Health Industrial Complex’ for Underserved Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336863</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/meet-the-collective-offering-an-alternative-to-the-mental-health-industrial-complex-for-underserved-communities/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2024, for the sixth consecutive year, the Trevor Project’s U.S. National Survey on the Mental Health of LGBTQ+ Young People found “a significant association between anti-LGBTQ+ victimization and disproportionately high rates of suicide risk.” The study stated that 50 percent of LGBTQ+ youth did not have access to the mental health care they sought. It also  More
The post Meet the Collective Offering an Alternative to the ‘Mental Health Industrial Complex’ for Underserved Communities appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genocide by Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336592</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/genocide-by-air/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An estimated 75,000+ tons of bombs have been dropped on Palestinians in Gaza since October 7th 2023. The Palestinian government, and armed groups, in Gaza have absolutely no air defences, whatsoever, and the Palestinian people have no air raid shelters, unlike the perpetrators of the genocide. What we have witnessed for over a year is  More
The post Genocide by Air appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Woodrow Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Killing Knowledge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336793</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/killing-knowledge/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henry Giroux’s recent article about Paulo Freire generated these thoughts: “that education and politics are inseparable”. The French and American revolutions initially highlighted the importance of knowledge in valuing the independence of the press. The Fourth Estate. Preeminent international law expert Richard Falk writes “If ever during the history of the human species did we  More
The post Killing Knowledge appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Judith Deutsch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kris Kristofferson: the Anti-War Veteran]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336791</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/kris-kristofferson-the-anti-war-veteran/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American country musician Kris Kristofferson was a military veteran and anti-war activist. He continued his advocacy against the Gulf Wars and benefit concerts for Palestinian children despite the negative impacts that both had on his career. Kristofferson died on September 28 at his home in Hawaii, aged 88. Kristoffer Kristofferson was born in 1936 in  More
The post Kris Kristofferson: the Anti-War Veteran appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Disuniting States of America?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336744</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/a-disuniting-states-of-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:48:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I think about all the changes triggered or excused by US “national security” policies that have taken hold in society since I arrived at the National Security Agency as a senior executive in 2001, the escalating damage to democracy is truly awful. The presidential election that’s now just weeks away will likely determine whether  More
The post A Disuniting States of America? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Drake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Assault on Democracy Goes Global]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336162</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/the-assault-on-democracy-goes-global/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:44:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much of the world looks bleak in the fall of 2024. Israel’s assault on Gaza, the world’s first livestreamed genocide, goes on unchecked, with  material and diplomaticsupport from powerful countries. Emboldened by this support, Israel is now attacking Lebanon as well. Large numbers of people in countries abetting the genocide are appalled at their own  More
The post The Assault on Democracy Goes Global appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Basav Sen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Newspaper Revolution Sparked Protesters and Influencers, Disinformation and the Civil War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336347</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/10/how-a-newspaper-revolution-sparked-protesters-and-influencers-disinformation-and-the-civil-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An image from Harper’s Weekly depicts the ‘Grand procession of Wide-Awakes at New York on the evening of October 3, 1860.’ Library of Congress Prints and Photographs Division There’s one question I get every time I give a talk. I’m a curator of political history at the Smithsonian Institution, and when I discuss the deep  More
The post How a Newspaper Revolution Sparked Protesters and Influencers, Disinformation and the Civil War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Grinspan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Maddie, be green tea" - a discussion about presentation]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/maddie-be-green-tea-a-discussion-about-presentation/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/maddie-be-green-tea-a-discussion-about-presentation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T01:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(CW: Fat-shaming, dysphoria, discussions about body image issues)
I spoke to my Taiwanese trans friend last night about how our emotions changed post transition, and how I--personally--don't get angry much (if at all) unless I'm severely stressed out, overstimulated, and then someone throws the final straw on the haystack.
...I may be talking about recent days, but hey.
My friend's interjection came with a wry smile. "You want to be likeable?"
Obviously I paused at this question. It sounded vain and shallow, but this is Asia. Results matter more than intentions, as our parents would oft prove by pointing to our tests. It's why so many Reincarnation and Cultivation stories exist. The proliferation of  skills in Asian fantasy exists to give you the result without hard work. And why would har…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending October 06, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241009</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241009"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T23:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So long, thanks for all the blog posts: Microsoft cans WordPad]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8647</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/thanks-blog-posts-microsoft-cans-wordpad/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T21:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is doing away with their old basic, but useful, word processor, WordPad, which has been bundled with Windows Operating Systems for nearly thirty-years. It will not be a feature at all in Windows 11. Yet another reason to migrate away from Windows all together, perhaps? Before switching to Word, I used to draft all […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by stego-tech in "US weighs Google break-up in landmark antitrust case"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41791020</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41791020"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loving the discourse in the comments here.  Speaking as someone who grew up alongside Google in a sense, I fall on the side of the "break it up" camp.  It was novel at the time to have a single company so nicely provide us with everything digitally that we could need - G Suite, YouTube, Search, Maps, Advertising, Books, Reader, etc - but in hindsight, we gave too much power to too unaccountable an entity, who in turn used it to choke off any avenues to challenge its dominance.
As for the rebuttal of "bUt ThE gDp", there's a counter-argument to be made that the GDP would have grown just as much with a higher diversity and stringent M&A regulations by spurring on new businesses and concepts, as opposed to mainstreaming fad after fad that seemingly solely benefits the established players.  There's another argument to be made equating GDP values to desirable targets creates a Goodhart's Law problem, thereby making GDP as a measure of growth or success a bad metric; the rise of income and wealth inequality these past few decades, when there was increased focus on GDP as a target of growth or success, could be viewed as evidence supporting said argument.
It's worth noting that this case against Google is likely to be the bellwether for future divestments and breakups.  Whatever comes next will be an invaluable learning experience for both sides, just like AT&T and Microsoft's own anti-trust woes were learning experiences for the current crop of companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stego-tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 10/9/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280101</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/200pm-water-cooler-10-9-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics; fun with maps: Helene and Milton could make Pennsylvania the key;  Kamala has a beer with Stephen Colbert; on hurricanes; Response to Helene in NC; Boeing talks break down as management walks away from the table. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kristjansson in "PEP 760: No more bare excepts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41789903</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41789903"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My concern, and IMO what should be the overwhelming concern of the maintainers, is not the code that is being written, or the code that will be written, but all the code that has been written, and will never be touched again. A break like this will force lots of python users to avoid upgrading to 3.17, jettison packages they may want to keep using, or deal with the hassle of patching unmaintained dependencies on their own.
For those Python users for whom writing python is the core of their work that might be fine.  For all the other users for whom python is an foreign, incidental, but indispensable part of their work (scientists, analysts, ...) the choice is untenable. While python can and should strive to be a more 'serious', 'professional' language, it _must_ have respect and empathy for the latter camp.  Elevating something that should be a linter rule to a language change ain't that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kristjansson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu Goes Even More Rogue, Announces Intent to Turn Lebanon into Gaza, Refuses to Inform US of Iran Strike Plans [Update]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280100</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/netanyahu-goes-even-more-rogue-announces-intent-to-turn-lebanon-into-gaza-refuses-to-inform-us-of-iran-strike-plans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T16:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu, drunk on his power and his love of destruction, keeps upping the ante.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Passion]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/power-passion/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/power-passion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of my job inspecting houses, I also assess the household's fire safety. Often, important products like fire extinguishers and smoke alarms are missing.
If the customer is missing something and wants to purchase it, I have those kinds of products in my car. The sales are secondary, as a service to the customer, but I'm usually one of the technicians who sells the most.
Do I get a good commission for that effort? No. Do I work my butt off to be at the top? Never. Are our products the cheapest? Nope.
The simple reason is that I enjoy doing it. It's a great feeling to leave a home safer than when I arrived. It feels satisfying and rewarding.
If I saw myself as a salesperson or recommended something I didn't believe in, I could just as well drive around with an empty car. I wouldn't sell a single product.
The same goes for my blog. I write about blogging because it interests and fascinates me. If I were to write about something just to be trendy or try to get more people to read my stuff, I'd get bored real fast. And my readers would too.
Regardless of what your goal is with your blog (if you have one), make sure it's something you're passionate about. Otherwise, both you and your readers will get tired of it.
No advertising or SEO beats genuine passion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving platform resilience at Cloudflare through automation]]></title>
        <id>2i9tHkPAfy7GxYAioGM100</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/improving-platform-resilience-at-cloudflare"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We realized that we need a way to automatically heal our platform from an operations perspective, and designed and built a workflow orchestration platform to provide these self-healing capabilities across our global network. We explore how this has helped us to reduce the impact on our customers due to operational issues, and the rich variety of similar problems it has empowered us to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opeyemi Onikute</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eig in "Chemistry Nobel: Computational protein design and protein structure prediction"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41787261</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41787261"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T12:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I disagree with most of the comments here stating it’s premature to give the Nobel to AlphaFold.
I’m in biotech academia and it has changed things already. Yes the protein folding problem isn’t “solved” but no problem in biology ever is. Comparing to previous bio/chem Nobel winners like Crispr, touch receptors, quantum dots, click chemistry, I do think AlphaFold already has reached sufficient level of impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fun Day on the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/a-fun-day-on-the-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/a-fun-day-on-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like a lot of people who enjoy blogging and tech, my social media drug of choice is Mastodon. For those who don't know, Mastodon is a platform where you can have (in my case) micro-blog posts of 500 words or less, as well as share photos. People can comment on what you wrote or repost it. They can also give you a little dopamine boost by clicking a star to indicate they liked what you posted. In that way, it is structured similarly to Twitter (X), Threads, and BlueSky.
Where Twitter and Threads are corporate-owned and centralized, Mastodon is just a platform, and anyone can get the software and set up their own server if they are tech-savvy. It can be confusing for newcomers to decide which server they want to join, but the good news is that you can join more than one, and you can also mov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Indicator of Labor Market Tightness for Predicting Wage Inflation]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32101</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/a-new-indicator-of-labor-market-tightness-for-predicting-wage-inflation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key question in economic policy is how labor market tightness affects wage inflation and ultimately prices. In this post, we highlight the importance of two measures of tightness in determining wage growth: the quits rate, and vacancies per searcher (V/S)—where searchers include both employed and non-employed job seekers. Amongst a broad set of indicators, we find that these two measures are independently the most strongly correlated with wage inflation. We construct a new index, called the Heise-Pearce-Weber (HPW) Tightness Index, which is a composite of quits and vacancies per searcher, and show that it performs best of all in explaining U.S. wage growth, including over the COVID pandemic and recovery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Heise, Jeremy Pearce, and Jacob P. Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 10/9/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280001</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/links-10-9-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T10:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our subversive daily links: painting is hard, Foxconn to Mexico, Milton freakout, FEMA-Helene censorship push, ocean heating, UK sees Rooskie spies, Aljazeera Israel war crimes doco, Zelensky ditches peace summit, Kamala hiding, Google breakup? satire censorship]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alzheimer’s: How Not to Study a Disease]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280085</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/alzheimers-how-not-to-study-a-disease.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T10:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLG returns to why the discredited amyloid thesis as the cause of Alzheimer's nevertheless persists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Stop Pretending That We Can Escape from Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280082</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/lets-stop-pretending-that-we-can-escape-from-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T10:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The search for safe places to hide from climate change impacts is already underway, yet is set to be largely futile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Digital Tech Moves Into Synthetic Biology: The Generative AI Rush / Black Box Biotech P1/2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=280080</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/10/big-digital-tech-moves-into-synthetic-biology-the-generative-ai-rush-black-box-biotech-p1-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T10:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report, Black Box Biotech, warns of the biodiversity and error risk of AI engineered proteins, aka synthetic or  "generative biology".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring global poverty]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Measuring-global-poverty</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Measuring-global-poverty"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T08:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To track progress towards its goal of eradicating extreme poverty by 2030., the UN relies on World Bank estimates of the share of the world population that fall below the so-called International Poverty Line (IPL). 
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Precarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mihaic in "John Carmack on inlined code (2014)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41785113</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41785113"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first heard the maxim that an intelligent person should be able to hold two opposing thoughts at the same time, I was naive to think it meant weighing them for pros and cons. Over time I realized that it means balancing contradictory actions, and the main purpose of experience is knowing when to apply each.
Concretely related to the topic, I've often found myself inlining short pieces of one-time code that made functions more explicit, while at other times I'll spend days just breaking up thousand line functions into simpler blocks just to be able to follow what's going on. In both cases I was creating inconsistencies that younger developers nitpick -- I know I did.
My goal in most cases now is to optimize code for the limits of the human mind (my own in low-effort mode) and like to be able to treat rules as guidelines. The trouble is how can you scale this to millions of developers, and what are those limits of the human mind when more and more AI-generated code will be used?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mihaic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by EvanAnderson in "European govt air-gapped systems breached using custom malware"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784970</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784970"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the discipline surrounding most "air gapped" machines I've seen I always find this quote appropriate:
"At best, an air gap is a high-latency connection" -Ed Skoudis - DerbyCon 3.0]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EvanAnderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Hell is Going On?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336581</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/what-the-hell-is-going-on/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please donate to our annual fund drive.
The post What the Hell is Going On? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Agony and Ecstasy of an Empire: The United States in the Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336556</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/the-agony-and-ecstasy-of-an-empire-the-united-states-in-the-middle-east/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economic hegemony has been the cornerstone of U.S. policy in the Persian Gulf since the end of the Second World War.  America’s “special relationship” with Israel, a term first coined by President John F. Kennedy in 1962, is founded on business.  Economic supremacy was also at the heart of the oil-for-security bargain that the United States sealed with oil-rich Saudi Arabia after World War II.   More
The post The Agony and Ecstasy of an Empire: The United States in the Middle East appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Conflagration of Lies: Mainstream Media, Political Theater, and the Hypocritic Oath]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336328</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/a-conflagration-of-lies-mainstream-media-political-theater-and-the-hypocritic-oath/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I tell my children there are two ways to lie. One is to tell me something that didn’t happen, and the other is not to tell me something that did happen.” –Al Tompkins “I’ve been a reporter for 20 years; the reporters of those who believe more sympathetically about Israel and its right to exist  More
The post A Conflagration of Lies: Mainstream Media, Political Theater, and the Hypocritic Oath appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John G. Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariffs and Government-Granted Patent Monopolies: Bad and “Good” Forms of Protectionism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336522</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/tariffs-and-government-granted-patent-monopolies-bad-and-good-forms-of-protectionism/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s promise to impose taxes of 10-20 percent on all imports (more for imports from China) has put protectionism front and center in U.S. policy debates. Economists are for the most part saluting the flag, saying that protectionism is bad, and we should look to promote free trade wherever possible, with some carve-outs for national  More
The post Tariffs and Government-Granted Patent Monopolies: Bad and “Good” Forms of Protectionism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asian-Americans Could Make the Difference in 2024 – and Not Just in Nevada]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336620</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/asian-americans-could-make-the-difference-in-2024-and-not-just-in-nevada/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s emerging as a major anomaly in the  2024 presidential swing states polls  While Donald Trump is gaining and slightly leading Kamala Harris in three of the most important swing states in the Sunbelt – AZ, GA and NC – Harris still clings to a stubborn polling lead in a fourth swing state, Nevada.  It’s just 1.2 points,  More
The post Asian-Americans Could Make the Difference in 2024 – and Not Just in Nevada appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside the World of Fossil Fuel Philanthropy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336164</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/inside-the-world-of-fossil-fuel-philanthropy/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, the fossil fuel industry has laundered false claims and junk science through allied think tanks and the media in an effort to slow public action on climate change. That scandal has attracted more and more attention over the years. But less well documented is how the funders of these efforts have used U.S.  More
The post Inside the World of Fossil Fuel Philanthropy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chuck Collins, Helen Flannery and Bella DeVaan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ask (Not) What You Can Do for Your Planet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336534</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/ask-not-what-you-can-do-for-your-planet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one wants a nuclear reactor in their backyard. It’s an eyesore and a health hazard, not to mention the hit to your property values. And don’t forget the existential danger. One small miscalculation and boom, there goes the neighborhood! In the 1970s, in the southwest corner of Germany, the tiny community of Wyhl was  More
The post Ask (Not) What You Can Do for Your Planet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Dimensional Reporting: Maintaining A Status Quo Storyline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336621</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/one-dimensional-reporting-maintaining-a-status-quo-storyline/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mainline media is managed by people acculturated to their society’s dominant storyline—and all the myriad prioritized sub-storylines that are supposed to explain events both domestic and foreign. What are the consequences of this deeply rooted attachment? Well, for one thing, the resulting reporting is predictable. Nine times out of ten, it will reinforce the  More
The post One Dimensional Reporting: Maintaining A Status Quo Storyline appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Warrants Should Be Public Records]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336641</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/all-warrants-should-be-public-records/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 7, the US Supreme Court rejected an appeal from X — formerly Twitter — concerning, among other issues, the use of “nondisclosure orders” when prosecutors serve search warrants. In this specific case, the prosecutor was special counsel Jack Smith, the target was former president Donald Trump, and the warrant was for Trump’s Twitter  More
The post All Warrants Should Be Public Records appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: 100 Years Ago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336157</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/letter-from-london-100-years-ago/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve always been interested in time tunnels. I should explain. The benefit of hindsight. The clarity of now from the knowledge of then. Bumping into someone not seen in years and gleaning in seconds what time has done. I began thinking about this in the context of the Stones album Goats Head Soup and the  More
The post Letter from London: 100 Years Ago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Dry Forest Management in a Warming Climate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336567</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/09/rethinking-dry-forest-management-in-a-warming-climate/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:49:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[La Cueva, Santa Fe National Forest. From left to right: Sam Hitt, president of the Santa Fe Forest Coalition, Joey Smallwood M.S., environmental studies and GIS, Cristina Salvador M.S., plant ecologist at the Santa Fe Botanical Garden, Sarah Hyden, co-founder and director of The Forest Advocate, Adam Rissien M.S., environmental studies, ReWilding Manager at WildEarth  More
The post Rethinking Dry Forest Management in a Warming Climate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Hyden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nullindividual in "Why the ISO format has to die"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784789</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41784789"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author could use a bit of humility.
ISO isn’t useful in the author’s use-case. That’s fine, it is their project to do as they will. ISOs may still have uses elsewhere, such as PXE boot or just a near universally mountable read only container.
The author’s point to the age of the original ISO standard is irrelevant. Many old technologies are reliable and widely adopted, which in and of itself may make it superior to more modern technologies.
Author’s project, author’s will. But that was difficult to read due to their attitude and beyond the author’s use case, didn’t provide a reason for universally retiring ISO.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nullindividual</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate Serverless Streamlit App Deployment with Terraform]]></title>
        <id>801c833117b120c017f34599470ae8bce1d0bf6e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-serverless-streamlit-app-deployment-with-terraform/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T05:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphic created by Kevon Mayers. Introduction As customers increasingly seek to harness the power of generative AI (GenAI) and machine learning to deliver cutting-edge applications, the need for a flexible, intuitive, and scalable development platform has never been greater. In this landscape, Streamlit has emerged as a standout tool, making it easy for developers to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevon Mayers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs. The great hope of 1997's indie web.]]></title>
        <id>https://escape.bearblog.dev/blogs-the-great-hope-of-1997s-indie-web/</id>
        <link href="https://escape.bearblog.dev/blogs-the-great-hope-of-1997s-indie-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T01:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time I think I'm out, they pull me back in.

The main problem with Blogs in 1997 is that it didn't take long to realize nobody else cared about it.
The good thing about Blogs in 2024 is that you go into it knowing nobody will care about it. How Fucking Refreshing.
These days there are places to connect in 300 characters or less, places to manage & moderate a growing community, and there are billionaire owned communities to help you become disappointed in your friends and family.
Sounds tedious AF.
I miss the ancient times when a simple RSS reader allowed people to lurk in the manner they preferred.
When an introvert could get a word in.
When you could fucking curse if it pleased you, because you're an adult and sometimes things suck.
Ya know?!?
So that's what I'll do here.
Curse.
But also share. With no pressure to be heard. And no pressure to respond.
If nothing else, a time capsule.
Of my journey in game development, and perhaps someday in setting up a studio. Video games have always been a wonderful escape for me. I'd call my game studio "Escape Element". So that'll be the blog's name too.
But don't be confused. This blog will be my personal take on things.
You could find all sorts of stuff here. It could be gamedev related stuff like art, music, or code (I dabble in all) ... or...
I may just need to rant about how stupid people are stupid.
Whatever is taking my attention at any given moment... I'm probably either in love with or pissed off at it, and it's well past time I let the universe know about it.
If following along sounds like it may provide you with an element of escape, come on back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Jedd in "Who died and left the US $7B?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41783447</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41783447"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T01:04:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fascinating reddit post was mentioned here about a month ago - about the mildly famous (if a little macabre) 'Buy, Borrow, Die' cycle used by the obscenely-wealthy to - multi-generationally - avoid tax obligations.
https://old.reddit.com/r/BuyBorrowDieExplained/comments/1f26...
HN comments:  https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41408772]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jedd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Compleat History of the Magic: the Gathering Metagame, Supplemental: Commander's Road to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://azhdarchid.com/a-compleat-history-of-the-magic-the-gathering-metagame-supplemental-commanders-road-to-hell/</id>
        <link href="https://azhdarchid.com/a-compleat-history-of-the-magic-the-gathering-metagame-supplemental-commanders-road-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 24 2024, the Commander Rules Committee put out their quarterly update detailing the newest batch of changes to the format. These changes consisted of banning four cards from the format: Dockside Extortionist, Jeweled Lotus, Mana Crypt, and Nadu, Winged Wisdom.
Less than a week later, the Commander RC – the independent group of fans who had controlled the game’s most popular format for over a decade – was no more.
What follows is an attempt at understanding how the world's most popular card game got to this point.
A brief explanation of Commander
If you're unfamiliar: Commander is a casual Magic variant that has, in the last 10 years, become the most popular and widespread form of the game. In Commander, players play free-for-all multiplayer games, typically with four players, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Amorymeltzer in "Who died and left the US $7B?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782989</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782989"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T23:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Levine touched on this briefly today, and I liked his two cents:
>It’s kind of cool? Like you could imagine a hierarchy, in roughly ascending order of wealth:
>Too poor to pay taxes.
>Rich enough to pay taxes.
>Rich enough to not pay taxes.
>Rich enough to not even bother with not paying taxes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amorymeltzer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.City here I come]]></title>
        <id>https://binarydigit.cafe/city-here-i-come/</id>
        <link href="https://binarydigit.cafe/city-here-i-come/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T22:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was mulling over the thought of renewing this domain's tld; ".cafe" is super cute but I kind of want a different vibe this year, and ".city" spoke to me. It's also have the cost of a cafe domain and I like the idea of tying all of my various sites into subdomains around my "city". Much like how folks have a ".town" or ".space". It's also better than constantly buying a million domains when I'm bored and want to start a new project. 😂 Three more are expiring this month; are you all proud of me?
By the end of the month I should have this Bear blog with the new domain and darker color themes more often than light color themes. I realize it's ok to just do what you want with a personal blog. I have other websites that I can focus on better readability (like a dev blog) with light and dark modes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by recursivedoubts in "A modest critique of Htmx"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782080</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41782080"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These all look reasonable to me.
I especially go back and forth on attribute inheritance (it can be disabled via the htmx.config.disableInheritance option)
Three of the criticisms boil down to the fact that client-side state doesn't always play well w/htmx swaps (especially the simple ones) which is absolutely true.
And events can get crazy.  They are powerful, but crazy and at times hard to debug.  Such is event-driven life.
The one thing I don't agree with is the default queuing mode: it is not to cancel an existing request and replace it.  Instead it is to keep the current request in flight and queue one and only one additional request.  I'd need to sit down w/them to see if they were misinterpreting something, using the hx-sync attribute to implement the behavior they mention, or if there is a bug.
I would also like to take this opportunity to market our mug for people who don't like htmx:
https://swag.htmx.org/products/htmx-sucks-mug]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>recursivedoubts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oxford Comma users: people may think AI does your writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8643</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/oxford-comma-users-people-think-ai-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T21:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frequent use of the Oxford Comma, also referred to as the Serial Comma, is — apparently — a tell-tale sign a written work was composed using an AI chatbot. The repeat use of punctuation mark is among seven indicators researchers at Cambridge University, in the United Kingdom, identified after studying AI generated articles and essays. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road Not Taken]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45623</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/08/the-road-not-taken/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T19:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We all heterodox economists who have chosen the road ‘less traveled by’ know that this choice comes at a price. Fewer opportunities to secure ample research funding or positions at prestigious institutes or universities. Nevertheless, yours truly believes that very few of us regret our choices. One doesn’t bargain with one’s conscience. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The art of forgetting about music for a bit]]></title>
        <id>https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/the-art-of-forgetting/</id>
        <link href="https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/the-art-of-forgetting/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a piece of advice I've heard thrown around to composers a lot. You've probably heard it too.
"You should try to write at least a little bit of music every day."
This is bad advice.
For a multitude of reasons that I won't get into here, I've had a terrible few months. Just awful. My creative output has suffered as a result. I've still been making music, but it's been a slow, painstaking process. Lots of staring at empty Cubase sessions, wondering why I can't come up with any ideas. And while I have been happy with what I have managed to make, I haven't had that feeling that happens when you make something you really, really love, like you've figured out how to transform a part of yourself into a track and release it to the world.
I didn't fully realize it, but what I needed was a bre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Netflix’s TimeSeries Data Abstraction Layer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/31552f6326f8</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/introducing-netflix-timeseries-data-abstraction-layer-31552f6326f8?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T17:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Rajiv Shringi, Vinay Chella, Kaidan Fullerton, Oleksii Tkachuk, Joey Lynch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Like a Painter]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-painter/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-painter/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a homeowner, you know how daunting it can feel to paint your entire house at once. Hiring someone to do it can be expensive, and doing it yourself can seem overwhelming.
But what if you painted one side every other year? It suddenly becomes a much more manageable task. It can even be enjoyable, perhaps combined with a barbecue with your neighbors. Plus, your house always looks beautiful.
Starting a blog can feel similarly overwhelming. We see other bloggers posting regularly, creating every possible slash page, and participating in every blogging challenge that comes along.
Let go of all that pressure. Start at your own pace, in your own way.
Begin with just one post. It doesn't have to be anything special, a paragraph or two is plenty. The main thing is to get started.
When the weekend comes, maybe you'll sit down and create an "About" page. Now you have both a blog post and a page that describes you and your blog.
Step by step, you'll build your blog on your own terms. No musts or deadlines. It's your blog, you set the rules – no one else.
Soon, you'll have painted a beautiful blog that looks great from every angle, year after year.
Community echoes
FW: Blog Like a Painter by Yordi
(I am) the painter with dried up paint cans by Jedda
Re: Blog Like a Painter by Helen Chong
Re: Blog Like a Painter by Dominik]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zubiaur in "Do U.S. ports need more automation?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41777960</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41777960"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T14:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation messes up the flow of illegal drugs. The big stuff does not come in a backpack but in container ships/trucks.
In LATAM, dock workers make sure this goes undetected. I know of an IE who was championing a dock worker scheduling optimization algo, typical Operations Management stuff. Dude was killed.
I'd like to think that this kind of things do not happen here. But every time I've thought along those lines, I've been mistaken. It's just happens at a different scale.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zubiaur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging Kubernetes virtual machines at Cloudflare with KubeVirt]]></title>
        <id>1149BgOuHn2l6ubvzlzHar</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/leveraging-kubernetes-virtual-machines-with-kubevirt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes team runs several multi-tenant clusters across Cloudflare’s core data centers. When multi-tenant cluster isolation is too limiting for an application, we use KubeVirt. KubeVirt is a cloud-native solution that enables our developers to run virtual machines alongside containers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Cichra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare acquires Kivera to add simple, preventive cloud security to Cloudflare One]]></title>
        <id>6e7vmGCa8tZRTNJWqYs1di</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-acquires-kivera"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The acquisition and integration of Kivera broadens the scope of Cloudflare’s SASE platform beyond just apps, incorporating increased cloud security through proactive configuration management of cloud services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noelle Kagan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by VHRanger in "Nobel Prize in Physics awarded to John Hopfield and Geoffrey Hinton [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41776411</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41776411"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T12:04:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoffrey Hinton wins the Nobel prize in physics for giving physics postdocs more reasonable job market options]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>VHRanger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unprecedented since 2019: over 200 people joined the CADTM Autumn Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Unprecedented-since-2019-over-200-people-joined-the-CADTM-Autumn-Meetings</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Unprecedented-since-2019-over-200-people-joined-the-CADTM-Autumn-Meetings"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T08:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From October 4–6, 2024, CADTM Europe organized its autumn meetings. Over 200 people took part. They included activists from India, Mali, Spain, Côte d'Ivoire, Morocco, Mexico, Brazil, Netherlands, France, Burkina Fasso, Togo and the Democratic Republic of the Congo. Many were activists from Liège, with a significant proportion being young people. It's an autumn festival unlike any we've seen since 2019, with a fighting, militant, anti-racist, and anti-fascist spirit. Friday, October 4: Screening (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
CADTM, 
Colonialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM Belgique, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sniper Man:  Quinn Buckner’s Assault on Free Speech and Academic Freedom at Indiana University]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/the-sniper-man-quinn-buckners-assault-on-free-speech-and-academic-freedom-at-indiana-university/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T06:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Buckner’s watch, the Bloomington campus made national headlines last spring with a viral photograph of a state police sniper atop the iconic Indiana Memorial Union building overlooking campus war protests. Three floors below the gunman’s sights, in the historic Free Speech Zone known as Dunn Meadow, armed Indiana State Police with riot shields advanced on peaceful protesters, evicted them, tore down their encampment, and arrested fifty six. More
The post The Sniper Man:  Quinn Buckner’s Assault on Free Speech and Academic Freedom at Indiana University appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Higgs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nuclear Warning From Hurricane Helene]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/a-nuclear-warning-from-hurricane-helene/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As no one can have failed to notice, our country has been ravaged once again by violent weather extremes, most recently by Hurricane Helene, which left areas in the south submerged and destroyed, and led to a significant number of deaths. The press has routinely been describing the extreme flooding, especially in places such as North Carolina, as “Biblical. But, as my partner and colleague at Beyond Nuclear Paul Gunter points out, it is nothing of the sort. As should be obvious by now, our ever more frequent climatic disasters are entirely human-caused.  More
The post A Nuclear Warning From Hurricane Helene appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Pentz Gunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nixon’s “War on Drugs” Was a Sham]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336460</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/nixons-war-on-drugs-was-a-sham/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times recently revealed that while Pres. Richard Nixon publicly referred to marijuana as “public enemy No. 1” he really felt it was “not particularly dangerous.” Kurtis Hanna, a Minnesota cannabis lobbyist and advocate for drug legalization, discovered revealing tape recordings while researching marijuana at the Nixon Library archive.  According to one source, he was startled by  More
The post Nixon’s “War on Drugs” Was a Sham appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raw Deals: The Continued Shafting of the Chagossians]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336450</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/raw-deals-the-continued-shafting-of-the-chagossians/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a spectacular example of a non-event, alloyed by pure symbolism and cynicism.  Here was a British government offering – how generous of them – to return sovereignty over the Chagos Islands, whose residents had been brutally displaced between 1965 to 1973, to Mauritius. In an October 3 joint statement between London and Port Louis, all but  More
The post Raw Deals: The Continued Shafting of the Chagossians appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Must Higher Education Always Genuflect Before America’s Highest Incomes?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336068</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/must-higher-education-always-genuflect-before-americas-highest-incomes/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[America’s wealthiest have towered over the rest of us for quite some time now, and most all of us have over recent decades gained at least a little sense of how awesome the purchasing power of our richest has become. Today’s awesomely affluent, we’ve come to understand, can afford to buy just about anything, from  More
The post Must Higher Education Always Genuflect Before America’s Highest Incomes? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation is Called “Productivity Growth”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336049</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/automation-is-called-productivity-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is more than a bit bizarre reading pieces that talk about automation or job-killing AI as something new and alien. These are forms of productivity growth. They allow more goods and services to be produced for each hour of human labor. Productivity growth is usually thought of as a good thing. It’s the reason  More
The post Automation is Called “Productivity Growth” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glyphosate and Neonicotinoids are Poisoning Honeybees (and the World)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336419</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/glyphosate-and-neonicotinoids-are-poisoning-honeybees/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prologue The twentieth century gave birth to honeybee neurotoxins – organophosphate, carbamate and neonicotinoid pesticides. It also gave birth to glyphosate, a weed killer that achieved global significance, being the biggest selling pesticide — ever. But where does this chemical come from? Rosemary Mason, a European physician, prolific science writer, and environmentalist, tracked down the  More
The post Glyphosate and Neonicotinoids are Poisoning Honeybees (and the World) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evaggelos Vallianatos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Middle East Shoah]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=336406</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/10/08/middle-east-shoah/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T04:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Shoah is taking place in the Middle East and few people seem to notice, certainly not those responsible for the thousands of bombs rained over innocent civilians, mostly women, children, old people and those with disabilities. Those who ordered it and made it possible Sit comfortably in their plump offices oblivious to the suffering  More
The post Middle East Shoah appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by MarkMarine in "Is the attack helicopter dead?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41772946</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41772946"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T01:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the war I fought in, there was a markedly different approach to combat air ops between even just the different service branches. The Army tended to use the Apache like it was a flying tank, hovering and delivering ordinance; the Marines (which is where I fought) flew as low and as quickly as possible even while sending rounds and hellfire missiles downrange. The marines were not losing aircraft in anywhere close to the numbers of the Army when I was there. You need a skilled operator to hit a helicopter moving at 100 knots when it's 15m over the buildings, and we mostly operated at night. I remember watching a ZPU gunner pointing the cannons directly at us and firing, and laughing as the rounds just flew behind the tail.
It's my understanding (and from watching the videos that I can get as a civilian) that the Russians still aren't operating their helicopters in a manner that I would be comfortable with if I was inside one. I certainly wouldn't be pumped flying in the environment they are in, with so many MANPADS out there, but there is no way a machine I was in would be hit with an anti-tank missile while we hovered (as was in the article.)
Lot of preamble to say: no, I don't think the attack helicopter is dead. Attack helicopters are nimble and can hide in terrain quite well, and even when an attacking force can see them it takes a skilled operator to actually hit them. The single use drones that operate like kamikaze vehicles may throw a winkle into the mix, but a helo flying at 150knots is going to be very challenging to hit for one of those. I expect there will be quite an arms race countering and then counter countering these in the future wars.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MarkMarine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pëtr Kropotkin - A Letter on the Present War]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/petr-kropotkin-a-letter-on-the-present-war?v=1728337063</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/petr-kropotkin-a-letter-on-the-present-war?v=1728337063"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T21:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Pëtr Kropotkin
Title: A Letter on the Present War
Date: October 1914
Notes: Published in Freedom vol. XXVIII, no. 306.
Source: Retrieved on 7th October 2024 from freedomnews.org.uk

[Our comrade P. Kropotkin, having been asked by the Swedish Professor G. Steffen[1] to give his opinion upon the present war, gave it in a letter which we reproduce, with the additions he made to it in the three last paragraphs.]
 DEAR STEFFEN, — You ask my opinion’ about the war. I have expressed it on several occasions in France, and the present events, unfortunately, only reinforce it. I consider that the duty of every one who cherishes the ideals of human progress altogether, and especially those that were inscribed by the European proletarians on the banner of the International Working Men’s Associ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jeffrey Zeldman: I stayed, and declined an Automattic severance]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8639</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/jeffrey-zeldman-declined-automattic-severance/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New York City based web designer, standards advocate, founder of A List Apart, and many other things, Jeffrey Zeldman: I stayed because I believe in the work we do. I believe in the open web and owning your own content. I’ve devoted nearly three decades of work to this cause, and when I chose to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ApolloFortyNine in "Google must open Android for third-party stores, rules Epic judge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770925</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770925"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T20:52:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If apple literally hadn't won their own case 2 years ago you'd be right.
If the company that literally doesn't allow users to install ANY application, yet alone a whole store, is in the clear, it's mind boggling that Google's situation is the one they took issue with.
Apple literally has a higher market share in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ApolloFortyNine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sneed_chucker in "Is the attack helicopter dead?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770724</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770724"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T20:34:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of a broader pattern in military technology right now.
All weapon systems that consist of an expensive vehicle and an expensive-to-train crew are being re-evaluated against drones right now.
If you're fighting a highly asymmetric conflict where your enemies can barely touch your expensive toys then it's less of a concern.
If you're fighting near-peer it's a different story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sneed_chucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Timshel in "Google must open Android for third-party stores, rules Epic judge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770458</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770458"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T20:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's not just allowing alternative stores, it's stuff like:
- Stop requiring Google Play Billing for apps distributed on the Google Play Store (the jury found that Google had illegally tied its payment system to its app store)
- Let Android developers tell users about other ways to pay from within the Play Store
- Let Android developers link to ways to download their apps outside of the Play Store
- Let Android developers set their own prices for apps irrespective of Play Billing
Removing those restriction on billing in the app will probably have way more impact in the end.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timshel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "Google must open Android for third-party stores, rules Epic judge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770338</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770338"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T20:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's probably not a great idea to point at a monopoly, as a defense of one's own monopoly, and claim "Yeah, but he did it worse."
Both Google and Apple's platforms need to be cracked open to competition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xnx in "Google must open Android for third-party stores, rules Epic judge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770223</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770223"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T19:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is ridiculous. From Google's reply (https://blog.google/outreach-initiatives/public-policy/epic-...): "These Epic-requested changes stem from a decision that is completely contrary to another court’s rejection of similar claims Epic made against Apple — even though, unlike iOS, Android is an open platform that has always allowed for choice and flexibility like multiple app stores and sideloading."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xnx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tmtvl in "Google must open Android for third-party stores, rules Epic judge"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770193</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41770193"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T19:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wait, so the Google Play Store, which you can install alternatives to (F-Droid, Aurora, Amazon,...), and where you can easily install apps through other means (such as downloading an APK through your browser and running it from the file manager) is an illegal monopoly while the Apple App Store isn't?
Well, I guess Google's market cap is only 2 trillion compared to Apple's 3 trillion, so I guess that's fair.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tmtvl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please write it, do not stream it]]></title>
        <id>https://rimarin.bearblog.dev/please-write-it-do-not-stream-it/</id>
        <link href="https://rimarin.bearblog.dev/please-write-it-do-not-stream-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T19:20:30.169Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I cannot help but notice an even stronger trend of content creators abandoning any written expression, in favour of untamed video or audio streams.
One guy had a very cool blog about FIRE and abandoned it completely to devote himself to video streams and become an entertainer; a week ago, a software engineering blogger started focusing on a podcast and I'm afraid it will end up the same way.
Writing forces you to organise your thoughts, divide them up logically and tell a coherent story. Ideas become condensed and accessible. Also easier to discuss, update and comment. Usually, you can go back and re-read at any time, streamed content seems doomed to be a one-off.
Of course reading is cognitively more demanding, but it is also the better option for learning and memory recognition. Not advocating against low-attention means of communication, but if the content is supposed to be educational, written content should be the default (possibly complemented by other mediums).
One annoying thing is the asymmetrical nature of time between creator and listener. When you write an article, you invest X time in writing it, but it only takes ~X/10 time to read it. It takes effort, but it pays off in terms of quality, while providing the best time-to-content ratio for the reader.
On the other hand, producing a video stream requires little effort and takes about the same time as the stream itself, but forces the watcher to invest much more time, while retaining less information.
While I cannot deny the power of videos to reach a wider audience, I wish they would more often consider the old-fashioned, forum-nostalgic boomers. These folks like to read ideas summarised in nice blog articles :)
P.S.: This article could have been a 20 minute video on YouTube or a 30 minute podcast, shall I switch?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;On the Brink&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/on-the-brink"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T18:53:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and escalation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by psunavy03 in "US antitrust case against Amazon to move forward"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41769457</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41769457"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T18:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruling at the below link, because apparently every US news reporter is allergic to actually providing source docs in court cases . . .
https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.wawd.32...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>psunavy03</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: HIPAA eligible with Amazon Q Business, Amazon DCV, AWS re:Post Agent, and more (Oct 07, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>238beac9f3f87197236d630385a99ae1acba128a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-q-business-is-hipaa-eligible-amazon-dcv-aws-repost-agent-and-more-oct-07-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last Friday, I had the privilege of attending China Engineer’s Day 2024(CED 2024) in Hangzhou as the Amazon Web Services (AWS) speaker. The event was organized by the China Computer Federation (CCF), one of the most influential professional developer communities in China. At CED 2024, I spoke about how AI development tools can improve developer […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kevin_thibedeau in "Nearly all of the Google images results for "baby peacock" are AI generated"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41768527</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41768527"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T17:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost all of the "product X vs Y" results are AI ramblings now. This growth of the dead Internet is making me want to sign up for Kagi. We're going to need a certification for human generated content at some point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kevin_thibedeau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cactacea in "Ask HN: What's the "best" book you've ever read?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41767392</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41767392"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T16:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> "The best book I've ever read was Atlas Shrugged in 8th grade. Changed my life."
"huh, ok"
> Really, I'm just looking for people who won't jump down my throat on a faux pas.
I think you're dismissing the people such as myself that would note you as an idiot without comment and move on wanting nothing to do with you.
Edit: tests and trick questions with people you just met is an ineffective way to navigate the world. My 2c]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cactacea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Kerrick in "What's New in Ruby on Rails 8"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41767185</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41767185"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T15:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby and Rails really seem to be going through a renaissance lately.
- The pickaxe book, Programming Ruby, has a new edition this year covering Ruby 3.3
- The Rails Way is being updated for Rails 8 and is available in pre-release, and will have two companion books
- A new title, Rails Scales, is being published by PragProg and is available in pre-release now
- YJIT has made Ruby fast. Like, _FAST_
- Rails has a bunch of new features that cover the "missing middle" levels of success
- Ruby has a bunch of new and new-ish features like Data (immutable Struct), pattern matching, Fibers and Ractors, and more.
I had largely moved on from ruby into the world of front-end applications by 2013, but now I'm excited about the prospects of diving back in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kerrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blog Your Way Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-way-forward/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-way-forward/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["But I don't know what to blog about."
I often hear that. Friends and acquaintances who know that I blog, and who are eager to start themselves, but don't know what to write about. My answer is always the same:
"Blog your way to the answer."
We can sit and ponder for eternity without coming to an answer. Or the answer might come to us in theory, but in practice it quickly turns out to be a false or misleading answer.
Blog, blog, blog – that's the solution.
We might come to realize that we don't need to blog about anything in particular. The writing becomes a meditation, and that rewarding sense of satisfaction is all we need.
Or maybe we'll realize that blogging isn't our thing at all. Then at least we've tried and gotten a truthful answer, and we didn't waste our time ruminating about it.
The only direction I had when launching this blog was that it should be in English. It's still a bit all over the place in terms of content, and might continue to be so. But lately, something of a concept has been tapping me on the shoulder from time to time.
Many of the posts here are about writing, blogging, and inspiration. These are things I'm really passionate about and love to share. Something that also permeates this blog's small side projects, such as the Bearming Theme and the Blog Inspiration section.
Who knows, maybe these will become the main focus of this blog someday. I don't have anything concrete planned, but this idea keeps coming up more often. I’m mainly mentioning it is yet another good example of how this idea came about:
Through blogging. Not through considering blogging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whatever1 in "Silicon Valley, the new lobbying monster"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41766990</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41766990"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T15:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like how they started with different values compared to the old American companies (oil, cigarettes, defense).
But they ended up exactly the same. Helping the worst regimes, all-in in military complex, taking advantage of screen addiction and teen insecurities.
But hey at least they don’t wear white collars like the old bad guys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whatever1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by intothemild in "Can you get root with only a cigarette lighter?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41765984</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41765984"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T13:47:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This reminds me of exploits we used to do to arcade cabinets back in Sydney in the 80's and 90s. The school gas heaters used to have what we called "clickers", piezoelectric ignition devices you could remove from the heaters.
You then took that clicker to your local arcade, and clicked one of the corners of the CRT, that would send a shock through the system and add credits to your game. I believe this was because the CRT was grounded on the same ground lines that the mechanism for physically checking a coin had gone through the system.
Suffice to say, they caught onto this over time, and added some form of an alarm into it. But up until then... Those were truly the best times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>intothemild</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by agentultra in "An e-waste dumping ground"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41765975</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41765975"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T13:46:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is one reason I believe "right to repair" laws are so important. The environmental damage of producing the device is already done. Make it last as long as possible. Reduce, reuse... then recycle.
Re-using devices helps us also reduce the number of new devices needed... which is what probably scares the corporate oligarchy. If we're not buying new phones every couple of years how will the stock prices keep going up?
Never the less, the devices we make these days can last a long, long time. I've been repairing and maintaining iPhone 5's, 7's, and 8's that are no where near their end of life. The iPhone has a couple of small electrolytic capacitors which should have a useful life of at least 20 years. And can be replaced! The batteries and screens can replaced. These devices can last much longer than we give them credit for.
But tech companies have been struggling to make it illegal or difficult to repair for a long time. I've been seeing photojournalist projects such as this since the late 90s at least (longer perhaps). In North America we had a culture that valued repairing and building things that lasted. It's as good a time as any to push for this to return! Support policy makers that are pushing for right-to-repair and environmental protection!
And pick up a new hobby if you are able. Support your local tech geeks if you can!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>agentultra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thermal design supporting Gen 12 hardware: cool, efficient and reliable]]></title>
        <id>5GRHH8385Hxg3UHjINuHz8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/thermal-design-supporting-gen-12-hardware-cool-efficient-and-reliable"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great thermal solutions play a crucial role in hardware reliability and performance. Gen 12 servers have implemented an exhaustive thermal analysis to ensure optimal operations within a wide variety of temperature conditions and use cases. By implementing new design and control features for improved power efficiency on the compute nodes we also enabled the support of powerful accelerators to serve our customers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leslye Paniagua</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real People]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/the-real-people/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/the-real-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern Internet era, where our interactions with other people can be primarily or exclusively online, I've stopped distinguishing between IRL and online human beings. You are all real people to me. In my professional life, a good portion of my customers are voices on the telephone or composers of emails. My job is to solve problems for those people and their very real issues. Lots of times, but not always, I get a verbal or written "thanks" for helping them out, but I'd help them even if all I got was silence. People with good manners are a bonus.
Even with folks I first met by sharing the same physical space, most interactions tend to come through a computer monitor or cell phone screen. This includes my own flesh and blood. I see more pictures of my grandchildren on Facebook than …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Philosophy & Public Affairs is not dead yet]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53257</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/07/philosophy-public-affairs-is-not-dead-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most interesting developments in the little world of political theory / philosophy in recent years has been the mass resignation of the editorial teams of both Philosophy & Public Affairs, and Journal of Political Philosophy. Public statements from both groups suggested they were disturbed by their existing publishers’ injunctions to publish in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do Climate Risk Indices Measure?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31740</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/10/what-do-climate-risk-indices-measure/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As interest in understanding the economic impacts of climate change grows, the climate economics and finance literature has developed a number of indices to quantify climate risks. Various approaches have been employed, utilizing firm-level emissions data, financial market data (from equity and derivatives markets), or textual data. Focusing on the latter approach, we conduct descriptive analyses of six text-based climate risk indices from published or well-cited papers. In this blog post, we highlight the differences and commonalities across these indices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hyeyoon Jung and Oliver Hannaoui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Austerity, dispossession and injustice: Facets of the debt crisis in Sri Lanka]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Austerity-dispossession-and-injustice-Facets-of-the-debt-crisis-in-Sri-Lanka</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Austerity-dispossession-and-injustice-Facets-of-the-debt-crisis-in-Sri-Lanka"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka defaulted on its external debt for the first time in its postcolonial history in April 2022. The International Monetary Fund (IMF)-led process of recovery that followed has not only been disastrous in terms of the economic policy package proposed by the Government. The underlying analysis of the causes of the debt crisis itself is also flawed. Sri Lanka provides lessons about both the broken global financial system and the widespread consequences of an unjust debt resolution (...)
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ahilan Kadirgamar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[twin cities metro communion]]></title>
        <id>https://theoptics.bearblog.dev/twin-cities-metro-communion/</id>
        <link href="https://theoptics.bearblog.dev/twin-cities-metro-communion/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T02:29:20.137Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[y'know when you're in a train car with exactly one other person (you've only glanced at them, if at all) and you fixate on the hidden enormity and complexity of your temporary companion's life and you wonder how more than two entire human beings could ever possibly fit in a train car]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automation is called “productivity growth”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45619</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/07/automation-is-called-productivity-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T00:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker It is more than a bit bizarre reading pieces that talk about automation or job-killing AI as something new and alien. These are forms of productivity growth. They allow more goods and services to be produced for each hour of human labor. Productivity growth is usually thought of as a good thing. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nimbius in "Congress fights to keep AM radio in cars"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41761219</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41761219"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T23:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There arent any alternatives for major catastrophes that can top amplitude modulated radio.
if you are in a car fleeing for your life from a wildfire, major storm, or war, AM radio is available sometimes hundreds of miles from your location to provide timely instruction and lifesaving updates. if you need electricity for a radio, your car has fuel and can provide a radio signal to you for quite some time.
AM radio can be transmitted with a roll of wire and a relatively simple transciever from an FOB or refugee camp. digital radio requires codecs, licenses, and specialty equipment. Satellite radio may, or may not be available as the ground stations that power it require even more advanced transcievers and software to operate and could take months to repair if attacked or destroyed. Cellular towers require special beamforming antenna that can take months to rebuild or procure in an emergency and rely on an advanced system of transcievers and software to provide a signal.
its not Dolby quality, but if you need clean water and shelter it will guide you. Arguably you could mandate a VHF receiver in every car for FM based NOAA/EAS alerts, but AM is still cheaper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nimbius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rout39574 in "Sq.io: jq for databases and more"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41761142</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41761142"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T23:06:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love JQ.  But ... I'd never considered its query language to be particularly admirable.  If I want to ask questions of some databases, I don't understand why I'd choose JQ's XPATH-like language to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rout39574</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance your website's security with Cloudflare’s free security.txt generator]]></title>
        <id>1uvkAn3IB6vSEO91XsPyAO</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/security-txt"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Cloudflare’s free security.txt generator, empowering all users to easily create and manage their security.txt files. This feature enhances vulnerability disclosure processes, aligns with industry standards, and is integrated into the dashboard for seamless access. Strengthen your website's security today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Moraru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by devjab in "Rust needs a web framework"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41760687</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41760687"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T22:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I like to make silly things, and I also like to put in minimal effort for those silly things. I also like to make things in Rust…
I think this part is perhaps the silliest part of a very silly article. If you really like to put in a minimal effort then why on earth would you use Rust? If you want efficiency, memory management and a compiled modern language just use Go. Then you won’t even need anything but the standard library for what you want to do. Or… use Django as you suggest?
Yes, yes we use Rust in production because we thought it would be easier (well safer) to teach to interpreted language OOP developers than c/c++ but why on earth would you ever use it for the web unless you are a member of the cult?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>devjab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Sniffnoy in "AVX Bitwise ternary logic instruction busted"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41759410</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41759410"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T19:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, I thought the title was saying that the instruction doesn't work properly!  (The article actually just explains how it works.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sniffnoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelnos in "XFCE 4.20 aims to bring preliminary Wayland support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41759223</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41759223"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To be clear here, we don't have a compositor yet. I've done a little work on it, but it won't be usable for at least a year, maybe (probably) longer.
4.20 will let you run some of our components on another compositor. We mostly test with Wayfire and Labwc, as our compositor will also be using wlroots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelnos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on blogging every day]]></title>
        <id>https://thebirdhouse.bearblog.dev/on-blogging-every-day/</id>
        <link href="https://thebirdhouse.bearblog.dev/on-blogging-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since discovering my favorite types of blog posts are essay-like in anatomy and length, I've dedicated a lot of time to both writing and reading such posts. Every morning, before I go on my phone and while I drink my coffee, I'll hop onto Bear Blog and start writing. About what? Well, anything! Usually, the first topic that pops into my head is the one I'll write about, and I can usually pop out a decently sized post within an hour. I have the luxury of working from home and my classes are all later than 10am, so I've really enjoyed crafting this relaxing and productive morning routine for myself. I don't always post what I write, but I always make sure to write every day, if only for a few minutes.
When I post something in the morning, I'll check back periodically to reread my post or look at the toasts. I don't have an email attached to this account as of yet, so the only feedback I get on the site (or evidence that my post reached anyone at all) is from the toasts. Seeing the number tick up can really make my day when it's a post I spent a lot of time on, or if it covers a subject I care about. I want to attach more functionality to my blog that makes it easier for people to reach me and interact with my writing, but I've also really enjoyed feeling like typing in this little blue box is something I only do for me. I feel really good after blogging, and I don't ever want that to change.
ʚ ═══･୨ ꕤ ୧･═══ ɞ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing as Meditation]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/writing-meditation/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/writing-meditation/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm sitting at one of my favorite coffee shops here in Stockholm. A friend reached out and asked if I wanted to meet up. She was just about to meditate first.
I've meditated myself in periods. I'm actually doing it right now. The meditation I practice is called writing.
Few things in life make me as present in the moment as writing. I've tried different types of meditation, gone on retreats around the world, read books on the subject, done online courses, tested various apps... Nothing has come close to the mindful presence I experience while writing.
Am I saying that traditional meditation is bad? No, of course not. I still do it myself occasionally, and I know that my dear friend finds it incredibly rewarding and valuable.
What I'm trying to say is that the "technique" isn't so important. The important thing is that it aligns with what suits us, whether it means sitting cross-legged or being out in the woods picking mushrooms.
If meditation becomes something that "should be done" - a task, an achievement - how much do we really get out of it? One conscious breath can be more precious than spending 30 minutes checking off the task 'meditation' on the to-do list.
I leave you with that to meditate on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Salt at Gruissan]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53254</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/10/06/sunday-photoblogging-salt-at-gruissan/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-06T06:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wulfinna - Black and Red Rags]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-black-and-red-rags?v=1728159612</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-black-and-red-rags?v=1728159612"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T20:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wulfinna
Title: Black and Red Rags
Date: 3 Oct 2024
Source: https://ignitedindark.wordpress.com/2024/10/03/black-red-rags/

 For me, I take the black rag over the red rag because I refuse to spill my blood for the right to be a worker, and instead practice negativity against every parcel of the world we have known for generations. 
 The black rag represents fighting spirit, critical self-thought and innovative audacity. The red rag represents a conservative principle of Work taken to its most political extreme wherein workers own and police their own sorrow. The red rag means sacrifice for the re-constitution of sacrifice for the economy and politics. The black one cannot soundly be joined with the red. 
 The black rag represents the potent intellect of midnight fury which prefaces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ş. Tekoşer PilingLorenzo Orsetti - Last Journals and Writings of Şehîd Tekoşer Piling]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/last-journals-and-writings-of-sehid-tekoser-piling?v=1728158761</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/last-journals-and-writings-of-sehid-tekoser-piling?v=1728158761"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T20:06:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ş. Tekoşer Piling
Lorenzo Orsetti
Title: Last Journals and Writings of Şehîd Tekoşer Piling
Date: 2024
Source: <tekosinaanarsist.noblogs.org/last-journals-and-writings-of-s-tekoser-piling-lorenzo-orsetti-5-years-anniversary>

Preface
 18th March 2019 Heval Tekoşer Piling fell şehîd in battle
 in Baghouz Fawqani, in Deir Ezzor region. 
 He was a great friend to all of us and an incredibly brave soldier.
 From Afrin to Deir Ezzor, he was always the last to leave. 
 We all carry the legacy of struggle from past times.
 Realizing our connection to our history and to fallen comrades
 gives us strength in present day. 
 Şehîd Tekoşer will always remind us of the fallen comrades,
 the beauty of struggle and the price of the defense of freedom.
 With our grief, we celebrate Lorenzo’s life …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlikely Upvote Button for Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/unlikely-upvote-button/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/unlikely-upvote-button/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T18:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlikely Upvote Button for Bear
Do you want to keep the upvote button on your Bear blog but find it stressful to see how many people have liked, or haven't liked, your posts?
Say hello to the "unlikely" button. It works like the standard button but doesn't display the upvote count. No more sleepless nights worrying about your post's popularity, but still keeping that trending post dream alive.
In your Beraming Theme, simply replace the current button with the following styles:
/* Unlikely button */
.upvote-button svg,
.upvote-count {
  display: none; 
}
button.upvote-button { 
  display: block !important;
  padding: 4px 9px;
  font-family: var(--font-secondary);
  font-size: 13px;
  color: var(--link-color);
  border: 1px solid var(--link-color);
  border-radius: 6px;
  cursor: pointer;
}
.upvote-button::before {
  content: "☆ ";
}
.upvote-button::after {
  content: "Like it?";
}
.upvote-button[disabled]::before {
  content: "★ ";
}
.upvote-button[disabled]::after {
  content: "Thank you!";
  cursor: default;
}
.upvote-button.upvoted {
  color: var(--link-color) !important;
  background-color: var(--accent-color);
}
.upvote-button:hover {
  background-color: var(--accent-color);
}

See the add-ons page for more Bear customizations.
Update: If you're not using the Bearming Theme or simply want a lighter version, ReedyBear has you covered. Thanks for the highlighting tip!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logan Marie Glitterbomb - Communizing Society With Consumer Cooperatives]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/logan-marie-glitterbomb-communizing-society-with-consumer-cooperatives?v=1728125462</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/logan-marie-glitterbomb-communizing-society-with-consumer-cooperatives?v=1728125462"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T10:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Logan Marie Glitterbomb
Title: Communizing Society With Consumer Cooperatives
Date: September 28th, 2024
Source: https://c4ss.org/content/59900

 Within anarchist circles, there is a split between those who advocate markets and those who advocate forms of decentralized planning such as participatory economics or federated communes. While the work of Ludwig von Mises and Friedrich Hayek has pointed out the numerous issues with centralized state planning, much of the same criticisms can apply to decentralized planning as well. Decentralized planning attempts to avoid the knowledge problem by including participation from both producers and consumers directly in the planning process rather than relying on centralized planners to make decisions on their behalf. While worker cooperatives…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elisha Moon Williams - Feet On The Ground!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elisha-moon-williams-feet-on-the-ground?v=1728106421</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/elisha-moon-williams-feet-on-the-ground?v=1728106421"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T05:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Elisha Moon Williams
Title: Feet On The Ground!
Subtitle: Anarchism and the Labor Struggle Today
Date: October 2nd, 2024
Source: https://medium.com/@elisha1542/feet-on-the-ground-3182bd113c6f

 When I first started my journey as an anarchist, I was incredibly privileged in both my environment and upbringing. I had grown up in a very upper-middle class suburb, neither knowing economic struggle nor of want when it came to my basic needs. I was, at that point in my life, a young 20 year old ‘man’ living with their parents as I started my doomed college career. That was when I got into the package industry. 
 Being a warehouse worker within the package industry was the most radicalizing job you could have given me. The sheer amount of naked disregard for safety and the well-being of my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to identify inactive users of Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>3c8053df1e60e8c4552906f954b9aabc2c5c8d81</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-to-identify-inactive-users-of-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T22:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI is leading to many new features and capabilities. As a result, your employees may not know about all the new tools you are deploying. I was recently working with a customer that had deployed Amazon Q Developer for all their software developers. However, many developers didn’t know they had access to the productivity […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Beach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grand final day: when some introverts must leave the house]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8631</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/grand-final-day-some-introverts-must-leave-house/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T21:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No posts about sport, hardly ever, then two in a week. But the NRL football (rugby league) grand final (Penrith Panthers versus Melbourne Storm) is on this long weekend, and since I wrote about the AFL the other day, this seems right. More a personality/psychology post though: a profile of Nathan Cleary, the Panthers halfback, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All IndieWeb participants need to be vocal, not just developers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8628</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/indieweb-participants-vocal-not-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evan Sheehan, writing at The Darth Mall: I think Jeremy Keith is right, that all that really matters is having your own website. However big or small, however you make it, whatever you choose to put on it. I just don’t think that this is what the IndieWeb is actually focused on. The IndieWeb feels […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use the latest AWS innovations with the new AWS Cloud Control provider for Pulumi]]></title>
        <id>956d52eea644a70dfc8ebceae873bac6346bbd13</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-the-latest-aws-innovations-with-the-new-aws-cloud-control-provider-for-pulumi/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T20:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of the AWS Cloud Control provider for Pulumi, an modern infrastructure management platform, which allows our customers to adopt AWS innovations faster than ever before. AWS has consistently expanded its range of services to support any cloud workload, supporting over 200 fully featured services and introducing more […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marina Novikova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Jäger: &ldquo;National Lockstep?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/national-lockstep</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/national-lockstep"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Belgium.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Escaping the jungle: Rethinking land ownership for a sustainable Future]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45613</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/10/04/escaping-the-jungle-rethinking-land-ownership-for-a-sustainable-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog Introduction: Beyond the Jungle For centuries, capitalism has told us that land is a commodity to be bought, sold, and exploited for profit. It has also sold us a dangerous myth: that humans are inherently competitive, isolated individuals, destined to fight for survival in a brutal world. According […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asad Zaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[my dsa prep plan]]></title>
        <id>https://minami.bearblog.dev/dsa-prep-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://minami.bearblog.dev/dsa-prep-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18-Week Deep Dive FAANG Interview Prep Plan
Week 1: Foundations and Problem-Solving Intuition
Python essentials for coding interviews (1 day)
Time and space complexity analysis (1 day)
Problem-solving strategies and intuition building (2 days)
Breaking down problems
Pattern recognition
Approaching problems from multiple angles
Introduction to game theory in algorithms (1 day)
Practice: Solve 20 easy LeetCode problems (2 days)
Week 2-4: Linked Lists (Deep Dive)
Linked list fundamentals and implementation (1 day)
Two-pointer techniques in linked lists (2 days)
Reversing linked lists (variations and applications) (2 days)
Detecting and removing cycles (2 days)
Intersection and merging of linked lists (1 day)
Deep copy of linked lists with random pointers (1 day)
LRU Cache implementation using…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Subtle Art of Always Quitting Your Hobbies]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/the-subtle-art-of-always-quitting-your-hobbies/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/the-subtle-art-of-always-quitting-your-hobbies/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, it's been a while. Where do I start?
Let’s start at the beginning.
I’ve been writing for most of my life. As a kid, I wrote stories, though they never went beyond a few pages. I even started a neighborhood newspaper, but that didn’t last long. I wrote about football matches during big tournaments like the World Cup, but once the tournament ended, so did my writing. Not that I felt really sad about that, by the way. Most of the time I was glad it was over, because I could finally stop the forced writing.
I also wrote for a fairly big gaming website for a couple of years, but I always dreaded writing long reviews. Enjoyment was far away.
Then, in June of this year, I rediscovered my love for writing — this time, on my personal blog. I found a community of fellow writers on Mastodon and r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Banfico built an Open Banking and Payment Services Directive (PSD2) compliance solution on AWS]]></title>
        <id>5aedbbd23e8bd759d82d3999de0db5fb2461fbaa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-banfico-built-an-open-banking-and-payment-services-directive-psd2-compliance-solution-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T14:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Paulo Barbosa, the COO of Banfico.  Introduction Banfico is a London-based FinTech company, providing market-leading Open Banking regulatory compliance solutions. Over 185 leading Financial Institutions and FinTech companies use Banfico to streamline their compliance process and deliver the future of banking. Under the EU’s revised PSD2, banks can use application […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Otis Antoniou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art You Cannot See]]></title>
        <id>https://austinmwav.com/the-art-you-cannot-see/</id>
        <link href="https://austinmwav.com/the-art-you-cannot-see/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T02:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a child, I grew up in a hoarder home. My mother had me at 16. We lived with my grandmother and her then wife, who kept everything she ever received. I have vivid memories of two things in that house.
The first is the kitchen table. There were no chairs around the table, it was never used to eat meals. Instead it was filled to the edges with things left unused.
 

The second was the piano. It was old, out of tune. The wood was peeling and no one in the home knew how to play the instrument. It sat in the front of the house and I was the only one to ever touch it. Like the table, the top of the piano was a menagerie of unwanted items and dust. I would toy around on it, pressing the keys down and creating out of tune melodies that have been lost to time.
 

When I was 11, my mother …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>