<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-12-14T18:34:26.911Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-12-14T18:34:26.911Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283839</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-14T11:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daunting daily links: inflammation stokes Alzheimers? wood burning, Yoon impeached, Macron new PM, UK food shortages? Russia big strikes in Ukraine, Biden in Hiller bunker mode? Texas sues NY doctor over abortion, terrorism charge over health care worker threat, AI chatbots lie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Neuburger: The Media’s Bizarre Treatment of the Mangione Case]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283901</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/tom-neuburger-the-medias-bizarre-treatment-of-the-mangione-case.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-14T10:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The press hesitates to fully report the alleged Mangione murder. Class interests at work?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Democratic Party Faces Its Day of Reckoning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283896</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/the-democratic-party-faces-its-day-of-reckoning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-14T09:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good recap of how the Democratic Party sold out the working class to become the fake opposition. But what comes next?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JPKab in "McKinsey and Company to pay $650M for role in opioid crisis"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42414181</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42414181"/>
        <updated>2024-12-14T02:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My mom got hooked in 99 after she slipped on ice at her house in Bluefield, WV.
Became a full blown addict after getting prescribed for the subsequent back injury.
She lost everything, disappeared, became a homeless addict drifting from DC to Baltimore to NYC and back, until she died of an overdose of heroin in a parking lot of a 7-11 in DC in December 2015.  Her story and the impact on me and my 4 siblings is a drop in an ocean of suffering these smug assholes inflicted on this country.
This slap on the wrist is an insult to all of us, especially us Appalachians, who saw this starting in the 90s and got ignored because “hillbillies are genetically prone to addiction” as Purdue told the FDA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JPKab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DevX101 in "OpenAI whistleblower found dead in San Francisco apartment"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42413238</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42413238"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T23:18:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I'm a whistleblower in an active case and I end up dead before testifying, I absolutely DO want the general public to speculate about my cause of death.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DevX101</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by BillFranklin in "OpenAI whistleblower found dead in San Francisco apartment"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42413204</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42413204"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T23:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some pretty callous comments on this thread.
This is really sad. Suchir was just 26, and graduated from Berkeley 3 years ago.
Here’s his personal site: https://suchir.net/.
I think he was pretty brave for standing up against what is generally perceived as an injustice being done by one of the biggest companies in the world, just a few years out of college. I’m not sure how many people in his position would do the same.
I’m sorry for his family. He was clearly a talented engineer. On his LinkedIn he has some competitive programming prizes which are impressive too. He probably had a HN account.
Before others post about the definition of whistleblower or talk about assassination theories just pause to consider whether, if in his position, you would that want that to be written about you or a friend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>BillFranklin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 12/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283851</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/200pm-water-cooler-12-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T19:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; RFK, Trump, and vax; Covid "viral reservoir" theory recieves support; Where oil profits went; New Covid charts: Good news, but positivity uptick ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effect of positional encoding on graph transformer models]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2e601169de3e</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/effect-of-positional-encoding-on-graph-transformer-models-2e601169de3e?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T17:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s research on how graph models are used in finance and how positional encodings affect different graph transformers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Bulgarian Dreams&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bulgarian-dreams</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bulgarian-dreams"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T15:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Victor Petrov’s ‘Balkan Cyberia’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Adams Trying to Wriggle Free from Sanctuary City Restrictions; Has “Same Desire” as Trump Border Czar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283840</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/nyc-mayor-adams-trying-to-wriggle-free-from-sanctuary-city-restrictions-has-same-desire-as-trump-border-czar.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T15:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Adams will work with the Trump Administration to remove illegal aliens who have committed crimes. What about sanctuary city laws?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simlevesque in "Test"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42408390</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42408390"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T13:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my province in Canada (Quebec) some IT worker in the government made a template .doc document that's widely used. They exported it with the document title "sdf fdsfdsfg". This title isn't in the actual printed document but it's in the metadata. If you Google that string in quotes you'll find tons of official documents with that title.
https://www.google.com/search?q=%22Sdf+fdsfsdfg%22]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simlevesque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283768</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T11:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our cussed daily links: death by bed, opposition to synthetic bacteria, Arctic ice fix? China bars key materials to US, Soros India meddling, EU farmers betrayed, debate over The Resistance future, Russia retaliation? moar NJ flying object, Trump Perestroika? health industry breakups? more Brian Thompson criticism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Year of Javier Milei’s Economic “Miracle”: Plunging Inflation, Surging Poverty, Rising Inequality and Slumping Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283669</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/the-first-year-of-javier-mileis-economic-miracle-plunging-inflation-surging-poverty-slumping-industry.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T11:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["The deep chainsaw is coming" in the second year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cihan Tuğal: &ldquo;Erdoğan&#8217;s Syria?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/erdogans-syria</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/erdogans-syria"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T11:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turkey and the region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Anti-Western or Non-Western? The Nuanced Geopolitics of BRICS”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283830</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/anti-western-or-non-western-the-nuanced-geopolitics-of-brics.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T10:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More on how much and what kind of influence BRICS might wield when it grows up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by m000 in "Show HN: I designed an espresso machine and coffee grinder"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42407396</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42407396"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T10:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Congrats! The design looks nice, but I'm not very fond of the website design. There isn't a single picture of Trefolo that doesn't crop-out some part of it. Also, every picture is in a "sterile" environment. It would be nice to have a picture of it on a real kitchen counter or coffee corner to put its dimensions into perspective, and also demonstrate how it "fades back into the environment".
Also, IMHO, the sustainability pitch is a nice one but needs to be put down in more precise terms. It is good as it is for people who would otherwise buy a Nespresso machine, but anyone who has bought something above that level would need more convincing.
Overall, a good espresso machine already scores pretty high sustainability-wise. Apart from the used of sustainable/premium materials, a key factor to that is the replacement parts and repairability. So, how does Trefolo do in terms of replacement parts and compatibility with 3rd party parts?
For me, the future lack of replacement parts is especially concerning for the Turbina coffee grinder. The use of bespoke grinding burrs adds a wow factor and may be functionally superior to other types of burrs. But this is the one part in the whole setup that is guaranteed to need replacement down the road. What are the provisions for that? How much would it cost? And if you decide to stop selling it, would you e.g. be willing to commit to releasing the burr design so owners or some independent manufacturer can machine replacements?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>m000</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Heart Attack and Stroke Drug That Saves Lives Exists—But American Patients May Be Left Behind by Profit-Driven Healthcare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283828</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/a-heart-attack-and-stroke-drug-that-saves-lives-exists-but-american-patients-may-be-left-behind-by-profit-driven-healthcare.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T09:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An example of medical industry inertia and profit priorities thwarting better treatments, here new clot-busters for heart attacks and strokes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syria at the Crossroads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346699</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/syria-at-the-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T07:01:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assad’s fall is undeniably worth celebrating — it’s a rare unifying force for a deeply fractured country. But after decades of oppression and 14 years of war, it will take much more to heal these wounds and guarantee a new era of freedom, justice, prosperity, and reconciliation. More
The post Syria at the Crossroads appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farrah Hassen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: All a Friend Can Say is, “Ain’t It a Shame?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346729</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/roaming-charges-all-a-friend-can-say-is-aint-it-a-shame/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lame duck senators Joe Manchin and Kyrsten Sinema cast decisive votes against Biden's NLRB nominee, Lauren McFarren, ensuring that the Democrats will not secure control of the national labor regulator through 2026 and handing Trump effective control of the board when his term begins. The petulant Sinema, who hadn't cast a vote since 11/21/24, seemed to enjoy making a final twist of the knife. More
The post Roaming Charges: All a Friend Can Say is, “Ain’t It a Shame?” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fall of the Assad Government in Syria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346631</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/the-fall-of-the-assad-government-in-syria/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the rebel forces led by Hayat Tahrir al-Sham (Syria Liberation Committee) seized Damascus, Syria’s capital, on December 7, 2024, the president of Syria, Bashar al-Assad boarded a flight to Moscow, Russia. It was the end of the rule of the Assad family that began when Hafez al-Assad (1930-2000) became president in 1971, and continued through his son Bashar from 2000—a 53-year period of rule. Hayat Tahrir al-Sham (HTS), which seized Damascus, was formed out of the remnants of the al-Qaeda affiliate in Syria, Jabhat al-Nusra (Front for the Conquest of Syria) in 2017, and led by its emir Abu Jaber Shaykh and its military commander Abu Mohammed al-Jolani. More
The post The Fall of the Assad Government in Syria appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Gets Burnt in the Politics of Passion?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346829</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/who-gets-burnt-in-the-politics-of-passion/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key question here is whether the destruction that Trump will rain on wage earners, while at the same time nurturing dividend recipients, will dampen the passion of the former for Trump. Counter-passions may erupt. Donald Trump isn't playing paddle ball with us. His is a knife fight in a phone booth (the last one on the planet) politics. Reason isn't in there. Historical parallels of reason evacuated, or gone mad, reveal the extreme potentialities of the politics of passion. More
The post Who Gets Burnt in the Politics of Passion? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Syrian Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346496</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/on-the-syrian-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t remember when I began studying the Syrian revolution in any detail.  I know that in its early years I pretty much accepted what had been handed down to me from commonplace sources on the left. I formed a quite typical image; Assad, for all his faults – was a secular leader in the image  More
The post On the Syrian Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Return of Anti-Capitalist Vigilantism is Proving Surprisingly Popular]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346762</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/a-return-of-anti-capitalist-vigilantism-is-proving-surprisingly-popular/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose a company is operating on a business model that demonstrably depends on letting people die through intentional neglect. Is it murder for someone who becomes aware of that crime to take violent action to try to prevent more deaths? Take, for example, a nursing home that decides to save money by leaving elderly inmates  More
The post A Return of Anti-Capitalist Vigilantism is Proving Surprisingly Popular appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Change Trial at The Hague]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346703</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/climate-change-trial-at-the-hague/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stakes are extremely high as the impact of fossil fuels on climate change goes to The Hague for hearings December 2-13, 2024 to determine whether nations are obligated to phase out fossil fuels. Will the esteemed court issue an opinion that truly impacts climate change? More
The post Climate Change Trial at The Hague appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Return of War to the Home Front]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346714</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/the-return-of-war-to-the-home-front/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early 1990s, doctors in Hiroshima, Japan, discovered a stress-induced syndrome they called Takotsubo cardiomyopathy, or “broken heart syndrome” — a condition in which the heart’s left ventricle, responsible for pumping blood, loses its capacity in response to extreme stressors like war, natural disaster, and the loss of loved ones. Prevalent among older women, that  More
The post The Return of War to the Home Front appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Mazzarino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington’s Third World War Scores Another “Victory”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346840</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/washingtons-third-world-war-scores-another-victory/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While I am certainly not one to begrudge those residents of Syria who are celebrating the end of Assad’s ultimately brutal regime, I am hesitant to accept the overthrow of that government as either a democratic uprising or even as a quantum step forward for the people of that region of the world.  Indeed, the  More
The post Washington’s Third World War Scores Another “Victory” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shattered Lands: A Short History of the Syrian Conflict]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346717</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/shattered-lands-a-short-history-of-the-syrian-conflict/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This piece was first published on CounterPunch in March 2021. When the Arab Spring came to the Middle East ten years ago, most on the left welcomed the protests, except in Libya and Syria largely out of geopolitical concerns. If the world was made up of opposing camps, you had to support Washington’s enemies even  More
The post Shattered Lands: A Short History of the Syrian Conflict appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louis Proyect</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holiday Season Nostalgia: Are We All on Fascism’s Side?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346583</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/holiday-season-nostalgia-are-we-all-on-fascisms-side/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The re-election of Donald Trump raises a simple question: Are you willing to protest? With the new year approaching and start of the year resolutions forthcoming, the question challenges a specific generation. For Baby Boomers like me, the Age of Aquarius has not arrived, and the Age of Selfishness seems ubiquitous. We tried to let  More
The post Holiday Season Nostalgia: Are We All on Fascism’s Side? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Americans Appear to Love the UnitedHealthcare Assassin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346719</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/why-americans-appear-to-love-the-unitedhealthcare-assassin/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On X, Luigi Mangione’s been dubbed the Claims Adjuster, or simply the Adjuster. The memes suggest a Punisher-style comic-book hero, hooded and masked, in a black jacket, with a silenced pistol. The narrative is about justice against the corporate elite and redemption and regeneration through violence. In this narrative, the villain is a sociopath deserving  More
The post Why Americans Appear to Love the UnitedHealthcare Assassin appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christopher Ketcham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syria: Hopes and Pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346706</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/syria-hopes-and-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid collapse of Bashar al-Assad’s regime has taken both intelligentsia and analysts by surprise. It was a repeat of the unexpected speedy fall of the Afghan government during the U.S. military withdrawal from Afghanistan. Both events share notable similarities: in Afghanistan, the government unraveled when its primary sponsor—the United States—decided to withdraw. Similarly, in  More
The post Syria: Hopes and Pitfalls appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Aims to Go Out With a Bellicose Bang]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346742</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/biden-aims-to-go-out-with-a-bellicose-bang/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having failed thus far to ignite Nuclear Armageddon, what’s up next for the U.S. military industrial complex? I’ll tell you: New bases in Europe, 47 of them, to be exact, in Scandinavia in coming years. That’s Joe Biden’s legacy, a blood transfusion to NATO’s moribund carcass by adding Finland and Sweden and thereby ballooning the  More
The post Biden Aims to Go Out With a Bellicose Bang appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Boss, Same as the Old: Brian Mast as Foreign Policy Indicator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346744</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/new-boss-same-as-the-old-brian-mast-as-foreign-policy-indicator/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, Donald Trump ran for president as a kinda-sorta, maybe-a-little-bit, “antiwar” candidate. Once in office, however, he escalated every war he had inherited, ending none of them, “surging” US troops into Syria and Afghanistan, making a public head-fake at withdrawing from Syria before changing his mind, abrogating the Iran “nuclear deal,” and negotiating a  More
The post New Boss, Same as the Old: Brian Mast as Foreign Policy Indicator appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anger Explodes at Health Care CEOs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346738</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/anger-explodes-at-health-care-ceos/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:53:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over 8,000 Americans die every day, many of them unnecessarily. Why? Because the United States still doesn’t have a national health care system that guarantees everyone adequate medical attention. One particular American’s death has driven that point home. On December 4, a gunman murdered Brian Thompson, UnitedHealthcare’s 50-year-old CEO. The bullet casings from the shooting read  More
The post Anger Explodes at Health Care CEOs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly Half of Older Americans Can’t Afford Basic Needs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346737</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/nearly-half-of-older-americans-cant-afford-basic-needs/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked hard my whole career and retired feeling secure. Then I lost every last dime in a scam. I was left with $1,300 a month in Social Security benefits to live on in an area where monthly expenses run about $3,700. I’m a smart woman, but scams against older Americans are increasing in number and sophistication. Whether  More
The post Nearly Half of Older Americans Can’t Afford Basic Needs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sherlea Dony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Pancho Villa and the Fall of Dictators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346752</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/reflections-on-pancho-villa-and-the-fall-of-dictators/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:53:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dictators – whether in Spain, South Africa, Romania or Syria —retain power for decades. They can seem impregnable and invulnerable. But they always fall, and when they do fall the world acts surprised. It ought not to be. The demise of dictators is woven into the fabric of history. In his massive, exhaustive, definitive new  More
The post Reflections on Pancho Villa and the Fall of Dictators appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Martial Law Defeated, Now Is a Decisive Moment for Change in South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346749</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/with-martial-law-defeated-now-is-a-decisive-moment-for-change-in-south-korea/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Late at night on December 3, soldiers stormed into South Korea’s National Assembly in armored vehicles and combat helicopters. Assembly staff desperately blocked their assault with fire extinguishers and barricades. South Korea’s President Yoon Suk Yeol had just declared martial law to “eliminate ‘anti-state’ forces.” Outside the National Assembly, people gathered from all over Seoul and beyond.  More
The post With Martial Law Defeated, Now Is a Decisive Moment for Change in South Korea appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did Netanyahu set a Trap for Genocide?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346745</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/did-netanyahu-set-a-trap-for-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are told by the mainstream media as well as Israeli sources that October 7 came as a complete surprise to Netanyahu and that he underestimated Hamas’ military capability and had no indication that Hamas had constructed a massive tunnel system in preparation for their attack.  As a challenge to this account, as a follow up  More
The post Did Netanyahu set a Trap for Genocide? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Schwartzman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Rafael Barrett: A Radical Voice in a Dispossessed Land]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346511</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/on-rafael-barretts-a-radical-voice-in-a-dispossessed-land/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rafael Barrett was born in Torrelavega in northern Spain, close to the Bay of Biscay. Eldest of two sons, he grew up in a well-to-do, though not extremely wealthy, family and enjoyed the privileges that such families took for granted: travel, good education, social and cultural capital. For reasons made clear in William Costas’s Introduction  More
The post On Rafael Barrett: A Radical Voice in a Dispossessed Land appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Costa – Michael D. Yates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mocking the Disabled is Cruel and Immoral, Especially When a President Does It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346740</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/mocking-the-disabled-is-cruel-and-immoral-especially-when-a-president-does-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most people, verbal communication is a seamless, unthinking act. But for individuals with communication disorders — such as stuttering, aphasia, or other speech and language impairments — speech is anything but automatic. They must not only consider what they say but also how they say it, knowing their manner of speaking might elicit judgment, dismissal, or ridicule. And  More
The post Mocking the Disabled is Cruel and Immoral, Especially When a President Does It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Eric S. Jackson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Great Trump Escape on Night Trains to Armenia: A Habsburg Suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346611</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/a-great-trump-escape-on-night-trains-to-armenia-a-habsburg-suicide/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth part in a series about riding night trains across Europe and the Near East to Armenia — to spend some time in worlds beyond the pathological obsessions of President-elect Donald Trump. (This week Trump threatened to imprison those from the January 6th Committee who had challenged his supreme being, especially its  More
The post A Great Trump Escape on Night Trains to Armenia: A Habsburg Suicide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wilderness Act’s Next 60 years: Elevating Earth’s Community of Life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346520</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/the-wilderness-acts-next-60-years-elevating-earths-community-of-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fall, Wilderness Watch and other wilderness advocates gathered at the feet of the Selway-Bitterroot Wilderness, in the trees and away from computer screens, to reflect on the 60th anniversary of the Wilderness Act and talk about where we might go in the years ahead. The conservation movement has excelled at Power Point presentations and  More
The post The Wilderness Act’s Next 60 years: Elevating Earth’s Community of Life appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dana Johnson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate Income Tax Collections Rise When They are Not Voluntary]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346630</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/corporate-income-tax-collections-rise-when-they-are-not-voluntary/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Donald Trump prepares to embark on another round of MAGA tax cuts it is worth a quick review of the corporate side of the last one, and the Biden administration’s efforts to reverse the revenue loss. One of the unheralded successes of the Biden administration was increasing corporate income tax collections as a share  More
The post Corporate Income Tax Collections Rise When They are Not Voluntary appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arab Writers: Pain, Perseverance and Prizes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346529</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/arab-writers-pain-perseverance-and-prizes/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arab writers have a tough job these days. Here, I’m talking only about those of us in the US. (Although this affects us all.) Whether poets, journalists, novelists or comedians, we have an extra responsibility to record our pain, unite our fractured people, and celebrate our existence and endurance. We must continue to celebrate while  More
The post Arab Writers: Pain, Perseverance and Prizes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>B. Nimri Aziz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part One: Resisting Authoritarian Populism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346722</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/part-one-resisting-authoritarian-populism/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last four years, Joe Biden and his anointed but defeated successor, Kamala Harris, attempted to refurbish U.S. capitalism and reassert U.S. hegemony over the world system, particularly against China, but also Russia and a host of regional powers. Their program of liberal reform at home failed to address the economic grievances of the  More
The post Part One: Resisting Authoritarian Populism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Smith -</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund: an ABC 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346586</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/the-international-monetary-fund-an-abc-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like the World Bank, the International Monetary Fund (IMF) was created in 1944 at Bretton Woods. Its official purpose was to stabilize the international financial system by regulating the circulation of capital. What it has become is the main international institution whose task is to impose inhuman neoliberal policies all over the planet. It is clearly an anti-democratic  More
The post The International Monetary Fund: an ABC 2.0   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Old Country New Again: Revisiting Keith Jarrett]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346595</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/the-old-country-new-again-revisiting-keith-jarrett/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the mid-70s I had a friend who attended the New England Conservatory, a school for future musicians of all ilks — jazz, classical, guitar, sax, orchestration, composition, etc.  My friend, Mark, was an Army brat whose father was a colonel stationed at Ft. Devens just 40 miles from Boston. He had shown great  More
The post The Old Country New Again: Revisiting Keith Jarrett appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silenced Night: The Unheard Lesson of Lessons and Carols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346858</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/13/silenced-night-the-unheard-lesson-of-lessons-and-carols/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-13T06:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Festival of Nine Lessons and Carols fills King’s College Chapel at Cambridge University every year on the afternoon of Christmas Eve. The service is broadcast by the BBC and heard, according to some estimates, by 400 million worldwide listeners. Expats, Anglophiles, far-flung members of the so-called Commonwealth and countless others tune in to hear  More
The post Silenced Night: The Unheard Lesson of Lessons and Carols appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pj_mukh in "Assisted dying now accounts for one in 20 Canada deaths"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42403388</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42403388"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T21:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My dad (age 75) got diagnosed with ALS and within a month of the diagnosis opted for MAID. He had only just lost control of one leg, but he knew what was coming. As much as we begged him for more time, he didn't want any of it.
Till his dying breath he kept repeating how thankful he was that he lived in a country that didn't force him to live on when he didn't want to.
He was a clear Track 1 case, and I realize Track 2 cases are more complicated, but just wanted to add my story as reporting on MAID spins out of control in our culture war milieu.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pj_mukh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mocha Mousse 17-1230 selected as the PANTONE colour of year 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8952</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mocha-mousse-17-1230-pantone-colour-year-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re twelve days out from the big one, and high in the silly season, as the brevity of recent posts here may allude to. Otherwise, the major highlight has to be the annual announcement of the PANTONE colour of the year. As I wrote two years ago, this was a big deal during my web […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by guyzero in "Assisted dying now accounts for one in 20 Canada deaths"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42402467</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42402467"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T19:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Canadian parents are in their 80's so naturally a lot of their friends of the same age are dying. And two of them have been via MAID.
In one case, which was surprising to me, a man who had survived cancer - he was not terminal but certainly wasn't getting any better - elected to die via MAID after his wife died. She passed, he called his doctor and less than a week later he was also dead. He got a chance to visit his family, apparently drive around his hobby farm one more time and then that was it. He didn't want to deal with being alone and seriously ill.
Another friend was in renal and congestive heart failure and possibly could have lived longer but they were driving 100km daily to get to the nearest dialysis clinic and again, this person was definitely dying. So made and appointment and decided to go sooner rather than suffer along for an indeterminate amount of time.
It's quite surprising to me, but these people are in their mid to late 80's and of sound mind and know what they want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>guyzero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 12/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283776</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/200pm-water-cooler-12-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T19:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Trump: Time's "Person of the Year"; Why Ernst changed her mind on Hegseth (some speculation); Thumbs down on  UCLA's AI-designed textbook cover ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Confidence: A Case Study in How to Create Confidence Scores for GenAI Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7294</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/12/building-confidence-a-case-study-in-how-to-create-confidence-scores-for-genai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T17:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Getting a response from GenAI is quick and straightforward. But what about the confidence level for that response? In [...]
The post Building Confidence: A Case Study in How to Create Confidence Scores for GenAI Applications appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alexandrawei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a mixed reality headset]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=22052</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/12/12/virtual-reality/how-to-build-a-mixed-reality-headset/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T17:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do you take a mixed reality (MR) headset from idea to finished product? Alfred Jones, VP of hardware engineering at Meta Reality Labs, joins Pascal Hartig (@passy) on the latest episode of the Meta Tech Podcast for a discussion on the realities (no pun intended) of building MR hardware. Jones shares his strategy for [...]
Read More...
The post How to build a mixed reality headset appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NeurIPS 2024: Capital One showcases leading AI research]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/207d989b64ad</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/neurips-2024-capital-one-showcases-leading-ai-research-207d989b64ad?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T16:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore our contributions to the world’s premier AI research conference, from papers and workshops to expert presentations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power of Decision Model and Notation (DMN)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/976de4f9d35e</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/the-power-of-decision-model-and-notation-dmn-976de4f9d35e?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T14:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How and when to use DMN as a business logic solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Bonham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nomilk in "Gukesh becomes the youngest chess world champion in history"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42399317</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42399317"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T14:21:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was struck by Ding's thoughtfulness, objectivity and humility when asked how he felt after the match (while clearly utterly dejected):
> How do you feel?
> I think I played my best tournament of the year. I think it was a fair tournament in the end. I have no regrets.
> Any message for fans?
> Thank you, I will continue to play, I hope I can show strength like this time.
Gukesh was equally as objective, humble, and gentlemanly in victory.
These attributes are what makes chess and its superstars so appealing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by seanhunter in "Gukesh becomes the youngest chess world champion in history"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42399237</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42399237"/>
        <updated>2024-12-12T14:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That was a absolutely horrible finish to a really exciting championship if you ask me.
For anyone who doesn't know, there was a lot of drama because Gukesh was playing amazingly coming into this (eg winning the gold medal on board 1 at the olympiad in crushing style) and Ding had been playing terribly. Then there were 13 games of back and forth with stalwart defending and imaginative computer preparation by both sides, playing a lot of fresh chess and both of them going for the most critical and challenging moves in each position. Ding was playing a lot better than a lot of people had expected and the previous game had been one of the best games in a world championship for a long time. Everything was tied going into the last game of the classical portion and the "bar room consensus" was that since Gukesh was so young and doesn't focus at all on the faster forms of chess (rapid and blitz) and is therefore much lower rated than Ding in those formats, that if this game was a draw then Ding would be a substantial favourite in the ensuing tiebreaks.
The final game was a complex struggle, with Ding keeping everything in lockdown with the white pieces so as not to give Gukesh a ghost of a chance. Most of the pieces had been traded and it was the most drawish of drawn endgames. Gukesh was up a pawn, but they both had a rook and bishop and all Ding had to do was hang on to his pieces and keep them well away from the enemy king. On the stream I was watching IM David Pruess had just been asked by someone in chat whether Gukesh could win and he said "1% chance".
Then all of a sudden Ding made 3 bad moves in a row. The first two were just poor endgame technique, putting his rook and bishop both on bad squares too close to the enemy king, then the real blunder. Completely inexplicably he traded off the pieces.  Now he was in an endgame that was just dead lost. After 14 games of 4+ hours each It had gone from being a dead draw with him a big favourite in tie breaks to all over in a few seconds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>seanhunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now Available – Second-Generation FPGA-Powered Amazon EC2 instances (F2)]]></title>
        <id>823f176c71ff36d802a6912c8db66ae3c79403cf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/now-available-second-generation-fpga-powered-amazon-ec2-instances-f2/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T23:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate genomics, multimedia, big data, networking, and more with up to 192 vCPUs, 8 FPGAs, 2TiB memory, and 100Gbps network – outpacing CPUs by up to 95x.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Y2K, a film by Kyle Mooney, the Y2K bug seriously strikes back]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8946</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-y2k-kyle-mooney-y2k-bug-strikes-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure if this horror re-imagining, trailer, of the Y2K “bug” will have a cinematic run in Australia, or is going straight to streaming. Two high school nobodies make the decision to crash the last major celebration before the new millennium on New Year’s Eve 1999. The night becomes even crazier than they could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jen Cardello Q&A: Advancing design research and operations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9cab17c9071b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/jen-cardello-q-a-advancing-design-research-and-operations-9cab17c9071b?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T18:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting to know Capital One’s Head of Research and Design Operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code November 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_96</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_96"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code November 2024 Release (1.96)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmward01 in "Bankruptcy judge rejects sale of Infowars to The Onion"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42385358</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42385358"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T06:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is clear that Jones and his relatives have moved money and assets around in order to shield them from the verdict. Now, money that should have been already given to the victims is being used to steal back the megaphone that caused harmed in the first place. The end effect will probably be even more subscribers and money for Jones which he will use with even less restraint since he knows there are no consequences. There are no words for the evil going on here. What recourse is left when the legal system is this broken?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmward01</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alwa in "Bankruptcy judge rejects sale of Infowars to The Onion"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42385137</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42385137"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T05:44:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Isn't it a little strange, though, that the system notionally decided that the families are owed an enormous amount of economic power as compensation for the nasty behavior of Alex Jones' media company, but at the same time it's obliging them not to use that economic power to prevent the sale of the media company to a "new owner" still affiliated with an unrepentant Alex Jones, who will undoubtedly continue the nasty behavior? Just in order to get cash to compensate them at pennies on the dollar for his previous round of nasty behavior?
I have to say, just as a matter of gut instinct, it sure feels like when the court finds that Alex Jones damaged people—at a value orders of magnitude beyond that of his company—those people should be allowed to decide that, to them, there's value in snuffing out his ill-behaving company altogether.
Is the issue that there are other creditors who are unhappy with this, who would get paid before the aggrieved families' damages would? The lawyers seem to be fine with it, as they're the ones advocating for this plan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from x86 to AWS Graviton on Amazon EKS using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>e5dc8b7d430b19b64ca0e6442d0af0464c387b94</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/migrating-from-x86-to-aws-graviton-on-amazon-eks-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-11T05:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog was authored by Johannes Brück, Senior Staff Engineer (Personio), Donald Dragoti, Lead Platform Engineer (Personio), Steve Flinchbaugh, Lead Platform Engineer (Personio), Maximilian Schellhorn, Senior Solutions Architect (AWS) and Dionysios Kakaletris, Technical Account Manager (AWS). Migrating your Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) nodes to use AWS Graviton based Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pmm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending December 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241210</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241210"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nsxwolf in "The Google Willow Thing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42382006</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42382006"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T21:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man, reading this makes me feel so small. Being a "software engineer" consuming APIs and updating database rows seems laughably childish compared to whatever the hell it is I just read. I can't even imagine why I should bother trying to understand it. It's completely inaccessible. Only an elite few get to touch these machines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nsxwolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can learn a lot about work when working at an art gallery]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8944</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/learn-about-work-working-art-gallery/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T20:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henrik Karlsson worked for several years at an art gallery in Denmark. The work seems more varied, and entrepreneurial, than some of us might think: Ie. you don’t say, “This is my job and that thing is outside my area”—no, if the value you are trying to promote requires you to go outside your role […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nspeller in "Ask HN: Those making $500/month on side projects in 2024 – Show and tell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42380418</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42380418"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T19:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I built an interactive Music Theory course 8 years ago over a winter break and it continues to bring in enough to pay my rent each month.
I just thought there had to be a more intuitive way to learn music theory than the very boring and jargon-heavy alternatives.
It uses Tone.js to include little interactive pianos, guitars, and other demos.
I've done no marketing, it hit the HN front page for a day, and after that initial spike in traffic has been fairly consistent over the past 8 years.
It uses Stripe for payments and for the first few years it was only Stripe. 3 years in I decided to add PayPal support... revenue doubled overnight, mostly from international customers.
https://www.lightnote.co/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nspeller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "From where I left"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379400</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379400"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T18:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For me, the license change upset me mainly for two reasons:
1. Many people had contributed their efforts to the Redis project for free - both in terms of code but also in advocacy, writing tutorials, publishing example code etc - and when they did that it was under the understanding that project would remain under the same open source license. It honestly felt like a betrayal of trust.
2. From a purely selfish point of view, my favourite thing about open source licenses is that they let me know exactly what I'm allowed to do and build on that software without having to consult a license. Licenses like the new Redis one leave me potentially needing to get my own legal advice depending on what I'm building on the software. I don't want to spend my time, energy or money on that stuff!
I do also see these kinds of license trends as harmful to open source generally. It used to be that you could pick an open source project and build a business on it and expect that the project would stay available to you under those well understood terms. That's not the case any more - not just because of Redis, there are a number of other high-profile license rug-pulling projects. I'm sad about that.
(And yes, I do understand and dislike the trend of businesses building on open source without contributing back. There are no clearly correct answers here.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by munificent in "From where I left"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379377</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379377"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T18:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> However, during the “writing years” (I’m still writing, by the way), I often returned to coding, as a way to take breaks from intense writing sessions (writing is the only mental activity I found to be a great deal more taxing than coding)
This has been my experience too. With both "Game Programming Patterns" and "Crafting Interpreters", writing the code was a joy while writing the prose was hard work. Gratifying, but mentally draining in a way that programming isn't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>munificent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China deploys historic naval fleet near Taiwan + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-deploys-historic-naval-fleet-near-taiwan-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-deploys-historic-naval-fleet-near-taiwan-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T18:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global advertising revenue is projected to exceed $1 trillion; garment workers face increased heat risks; Taiwan raises alert over China's largest naval fleet deployment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From South Africa to Syria, rising perils for Palestine solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/From-South-Africa-to-Syria-rising-perils-for-Palestine-solidarity</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/From-South-Africa-to-Syria-rising-perils-for-Palestine-solidarity"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T17:52:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sudden regime overthrow in Syria and the long-delayed opportunity to confront the legacy of Bashar al-Assad's tyranny are either being celebrated or condemned, as explored below, but they come at a time that poses profound problems for solidarity with Palestine. 
English

/ 
South Africa, 
Palestine, 
Israel, 
Syria]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gkoberger in "Firefox removes "do not track" feature support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379074</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42379074"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T17:37:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was at Mozilla when this was implemented.
It was completely optional for websites to support this. A few did at first.
A lot of people internally wanted it to be on-by-default, but the argument was that if it was, nobody would respect it – after all, what tracking platform would willingly only track the 0.1% of people who went into the settings to enable it? (Internet Explorer did eventually enable it by default, which got them good press but ultimately killed the feature since everyone stopped respecting it.)
Overall, I'm happy to see this sunsetted. I don't think it actually did anything – in fact, I think it implies that it did way more than it did, so it was just a faux feeling of security.
(All that being said, I would love if the cookie modals on each site became browser-level, but I'm sure there's many reasons that hasn't happened yet. And I suspect a bit reason starts with a G and ends with an Oogle.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gkoberger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Facebook’s video delivery system]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=22037</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/12/10/video-engineering/inside-facebooks-video-delivery-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T17:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re explaining the end-to-end systems the Facebook app leverages to deliver relevant content to people. Learn about our video-unification efforts that have simplified our product experience and infrastructure, in-depth details around mobile delivery, and new features we are working on in our video-content delivery stack. The end-to-end delivery of highly relevant, personalized, timely, and responsive [...]
Read More...
The post Inside Facebook’s video delivery system appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotcop: enforcing your robots.txt policies and stopping bots before they reach your website]]></title>
        <id>6Bi6mGvw8vrskNZ7Mmp73F</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-audit-enforcing-robots-txt/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, the AI Audit dashboard gets an upgrade: you can now quickly see which AI services are honoring your robots.txt policies and then automatically enforce the policies against those that aren’t.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Celso Martinho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The International Monetary Fund: an ABC 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-International-Monetary-Fund-an-ABC-2-0</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-International-Monetary-Fund-an-ABC-2-0"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T09:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
Debt

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break Stuff on Purpose]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17310</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/break-stuff-on-purpose/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-10T09:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A complex system can fail in an infinite number of ways.” -“Systemantics” by John Gall   Incidents are stressful but inevitable. Even services designed for availability will eventually encounter a failure. Engineers naturally find it daunting to defend their systems against the “infinite number of ways” things can go wrong.  Our team found ourselves in…
The post Break Stuff on Purpose appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Madden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by breadwinner in "What we know about CEO shooting suspect"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42370958</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42370958"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T21:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He was carrying all of the evidence with him, including the fake ID he used at the hostel, the gun & suppressor, mask, and even a handwritten manifesto that points to his motivation. It seems he wanted to be found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>breadwinner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious, deadly, flu-like disease outbreak in Congo]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8939</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mysterious-deadly-flu-like-disease-outbreak-in-congo/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T20:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The details are pretty scant at the moment. So far the flu-like disease killed close to one-hundred-and-fifty people in the south west of the Democratic Republic of the Congo, in November. Infected people had flu-like symptoms including high fever and severe headaches, Remy Saki, the deputy governor of Kwango province, and Apollinaire Yumba, the provincial […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;The Roads to Damascus&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-roads-to-damascus</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-roads-to-damascus"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T19:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assad’s fall from power.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yeknoda in "Sora is here"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368718</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368718"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T18:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've found using these and similar tools that the amount of prompts and iteration required to create my vision (image or video in my mind) is very large and often is not able to create what I had originally wanted. A way to test this is to take a piece of footage or an image which is the ground truth, and test how much prompting and editing it takes to get the same or similar ground truth starting from scratch. It is basically not possible with the current tech and finite amounts of time and iterations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yeknoda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by codeulike in "Willow, Our Quantum Chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368381</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368381"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They opened the API for it and I'm sending requests but the response always comes back 300ms before I send the request, is there a way of handling that with try{} predestined{} blocks? Or do I need to use the Bootstrap Paradox library?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>codeulike</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vessenes in "Willow, Our Quantum Chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368186</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42368186"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m a quantum dabbler so I’ll throw out an armchair reaction: this is a significant announcement.
My memory is that 256 bit keys in non quantum resistant algos need something like 2500 qubits or so; and by that I mean generally useful programmable qubits. To show a bit over 100 qubits with stability, meaning the information survives a while, long enough to be read, and general enough to run some benchmarks on is something many people thought might never come.
There’s a sort of religious reaction people have to quantum computing: it breaks so many things that I think a lot of people just like to assume it won’t happen: too much in computing and data security will change -> let’s not worry about it.
Combined with the slow pace of physical research progress (Schorrs algorithm for quantum factoring was mid 90s), and snake oil sales companies, it’s easy to ignore.
Anyway seems like the clock might be ticking; AI and data security will be unalterably different if so. Worth spending a little time doing some long tail strategizing I’d say.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vessenes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Slack Audit Logs and Anomalies]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17321</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/slack-audit-logs-and-anomalies/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are Slack Audit Logs? Like many Software as a Service (SaaS) offerings, Slack provides audit logs to Enterprise Grid customers that record when entities take an action on the platform. For example, when a user logs in, when a user updates their profile, when an app downloads a file, etc. The actual list of…
The post Slack Audit Logs and Anomalies appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Katkov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Typed Python in 2024: Well adopted, yet usability challenges persist]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=22026</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/12/09/developer-tools/typed-python-2024-survey-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T17:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ten years after the introduction of PEP 484, we surveyed the current state of the Python type system and the tools developers are using.
Read More...
The post Typed Python in 2024: Well adopted, yet usability challenges persist appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare 2024 Year in Review]]></title>
        <id>4oLkLHLIZ1vibq8dtPJP6F</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2024-year-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Cloudflare Radar Year in Review is our fifth annual review of Internet trends and patterns at both a global and country/region level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From ChatGPT to Temu: ranking top Internet services in 2024]]></title>
        <id>1bFqI2J5pfAs7dEpRp8auV</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2024-year-in-review-internet-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 popular Internet services landscape highlights rising generative AI, e-commerce shifts, and the continued dominance of platforms like Google and Facebook, as revealed by Cloudflare’s rankings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leafo in "Itch.io Taken Down by Funko"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42364033</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42364033"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T08:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm the one running itch.io, so here's some more context for you:
From what I can tell, some person made a fan page for an existing  Funko Pop video game (Funko Fusion), with links to the official site and screenshots of the game. The BrandShield software is probably instructed to eradicate all "unauthorized" use of their trademark, so they sent reports independently to our host and registrar claiming there was "fraud and phishing" going on, likely to cause escalation instead of doing the expected DMCA/cease-and-desist. Because of this, I honestly think they're the malicious actor in all of this. Their website, if you care: https://www.brandshield.com/
About 5 or 6 days ago, I received these reports on our host (Linode) and from our registrar (iwantmyname). I expressed my disappointment in my responses to both of them but told them I had removed the page and disabled the account. Linode confirmed and closed the case. iwantmyname never responded. This evening, I got a downtime alert, and while debugging, I noticed that the domain status had been set to "serverHold" on iwantmyname's domain panel. We have no other abuse reports from iwantmyname other than this one. I'm assuming no one on their end "closed" the ticket, so it went into an automatic system to disable the domain after some number of days.
I've been trying to get in touch with them via their abuse and support emails, but no response likely due to the time of day, so I decided to "escalate" the issue myself on social media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leafo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by KingOfCoders in "Itch.io Taken Down by Funko"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42363906</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42363906"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T07:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Phishing report to our registrar, iwantmyname, who ignored our response and just disabled the domain"
One registrar off the list of registrars you wanna use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KingOfCoders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GuB-42 in "Pat Gelsinger was wrong for Intel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42362945</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42362945"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T03:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The real issue? The board. Full of people like Boeing execs.
Literally, Gregory Smith, former Boeing CFO is a member of the board.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GuB-42</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CodeHorizon in "Pat Gelsinger was wrong for Intel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42362565</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42362565"/>
        <updated>2024-12-09T02:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bring back Pat.
Was Pat perfect, no. But Pat acknowledged Intel’s problems - something Otellini, Krzanich, and Swan never did. These CEOs, all non-technical, focused on dividends, buybacks, and next-quarter results while Intel fell behind in advanced nodes and innovation.
Gelsinger inherited a disaster: 10nm delays, TSMC pulling ahead, and no GPU strategy. He had the courage to cut buybacks and slashed dividends. He poured billions into fabs in Arizona, Ohio, Germany, and Ireland. He delivered Intel 18A, powered on first silicon, released PDK 1.0 for Microsoft, and secured Microsoft and Amazon as customers. There were even rumors Apple might join.
Contrast this with Nadella at Microsoft back in 2014. He didn’t reboot the company by tearing everything down. Instead, he built on Ballmer-era wins like Azure, Office 365 while shifting Microsoft’s focus to the cloud. Gelsinger had to start from scratch in many ways, tackling years of neglect while facing harsher challenges.
Yes, Intel’s stock dropped $150 billion, but Gelsinger was upfront - it wouldn’t turn around before 2025. He was trained by Gordon Moore and Andy Grove, and while some saw him as arrogant, that confidence came from decades of technical leadership.
The real issue? The board. Full of people like Boeing execs. They don’t get engineering. Trusting them to fix Intel is like hoping a plane door won’t pop open mid-flight. They’re the ones who should be replaced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CodeHorizon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nikeee in "JSON5 – JSON for Humans"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42361282</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42361282"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T22:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it allows for too much. I was glad that JSON only supports double-quoted strings. It is a feature that removes discussions about which quotes to use. Or even whether to use quotes at all (we still need them for keys with colons or minus in it, so what gives?).
The only thing that JSON is really missing are comments and trailing commas. I use JSONC for that. It's what VSC uses for the config format and it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nikeee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "UK bans daytime TV ads for cereals, muffins and burgers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42360161</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42360161"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T20:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can we do gambling ads next? We banned tobacco ads and then seemingly forgot the lesson that it's actually bad to let advertisers shove addictive and self-destructive products in the publics face, including to former addicts at risk of relapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Australian social media users need ID to prove their age? Maybe not]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8929</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/will-australian-social-media-users-need-id-prove-age/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in 2025, Australians under the age of sixteen will no longer be able to operate social media accounts. I thought up to high school age, about thirteen, seemed sensible, but lawmakers decided otherwise. Anyway, I imagine the new regulations will require, eventually, those of us sixteen or over, to verify, or certify, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by keiferski in "Show HN: Cut the crap – remove AI bullshit from websites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42357831</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42357831"/>
        <updated>2024-12-08T15:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I bookmarked this comment a few months ago because I thought it was hilarious and increasingly accurate:
It's approaching a very strange situation where people make overly wordy and bloated AI generated content and other people try to use AI to compress it back into useful pellets vaguely corresponding to the actual prompts used to generate the initial content. Which were the only bits anybody cared about in the first place.
One guy pays the AI to dig a hole, the other guy pays the AI to fill in the hole. Back and forth they go, raising the BNP but otherwise not accomplishing anything.
https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41635079
More seriously though; I wonder if/when we will reach a point at which asking for a Neuromancer-esque précis summary video of a topic will replace the experience of browsing and reading various sources of information. My gut feeling is that it will for many, but not all scenarios, because the act of browsing itself is desirable and informative. For example, searching for books on Amazon is efficient but it doesn’t quite replace the experience of walking through a bookstore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>keiferski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>