<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-07T01:30:45.865Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2024-05-07T01:30:45.865Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nationalism rots your brain]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895988168/0/themoneyillusion~Nationalism-rots-your-brain/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895988168/0/themoneyillusion~Nationalism-rots-your-brain/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don&#8217;t think people realize how profoundly nationalism distorts their view of the world. Consider a recent comment in response to my complaint about people&#8217;s obsession with the Gaza War: I suggest you ask a Palestinian for their views. Maybe he was joking, as from a certain perspective this is an amusing response to my [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/895988168/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/895988168/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/895988168/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/895988168/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/895988168/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/nationalism-rots-your-brain/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/nationalism-rots-your-brain/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of the last internet cafe on Earth]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7523</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/search-last-internet-cafe-earth/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Homepages and personal websites may be on the way back, but what of that other venerable staple of the early web: internet cafes? In the late 1990’s they were everywhere. Venture onto any suburban shopping strip, and there’d be at least one net cafe in amongst the other shops. When I first acquired the disassociated.com.au […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271135</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T18:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics, Trump faces jail, Hope Hicks testifies (and cries), Texas dairies refuse to allow Federal epidemiological field studies ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by apitman in "Alternative clouds are booming as companies seek cheaper access to GPUs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40277479</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40277479"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the weekend a coworker was helping someone in our lab prepare data for an important conference talk.
We accidentally ran up a rather large bill because while the EFS storage pricing was simple enough, the usage pricing bit us.
It seems like AWS' entire business model is making the pricing so confusing that you don't know what it will cost until after you've used it. It feels weirdly similar to the US healthcare/insurance situation.
More competition in this space can only be a good thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>apitman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortgage Rate Lock‑In and Homeowners’ Moving Plans]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29544</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/mortgage-rate-lock-in-and-homeowners-moving-plans/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. housing market has had a tumultuous few years. After falling to record lows during the pandemic, the average 30-year mortgage rate rapidly increased in 2022 and 2023 and now hovers near a two-decade high of 7.2 percent. For those that locked in a low mortgage rate prior to 2022, this steep increase has significantly increased the cost of moving, as taking out a mortgage at current rates would potentially increase their monthly housing payment by hundreds or thousands of dollars, even if the amount they borrowed remained unchanged. As shown by Ferreira et al. (2011), this lock-in effect has the potential to reduce geographic mobility and turnover in the housing market and has gained the attention of  Federal Reserve leaders. In this post, we utilize special questions from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s 2023 and 2024 SCE Housing Surveys to estimate the extent to which mortgage rate lock-in is suppressing U.S. household’s moving plans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Aidala, Andrew Haughwout, Ben Hyman, Jason Somerville, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q, Amazon QuickSight, AWS CodeArtifact, Amazon Bedrock, and more (May 6, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>92e15e319c82446cbaf197341c7d570da966e378</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-q-amazon-quicksight-aws-codeartifact-amazon-bedrock-and-more-may-6-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T14:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April has been packed with new releases! Last week continued that trend with many new releases supporting a variety of domains such as security, analytics, devops, and many more, as well as more exciting new capabilities within generative AI. If you missed the AWS Summit London 2024, you can now watch the sessions on demand, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting to know Amy Lenander, Chief Data Officer]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/2d5259b58eb5</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/getting-to-know-amy-lenander-chief-data-officer-2d5259b58eb5?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T13:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reflecting on Amy’s first year as Chief Data Officer, her 20+ year tenure at Capital One and how data powers innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lenerdenator in "NYU professors who defended vaping didn't disclose ties to Juul"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40273996</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40273996"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T12:46:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It really is amazing. We were thiiiiiiis close to having a generation that wasn't addicted to nicotine for the first time in hundreds of years (like, since trade between North America and Europe really became a thing) and these guys pulled this thumb drive that tastes like cotton candy out of nowhere and every young person is just jonesing.
And the regulatory/public opinion environment isn't what it was in the 80s and 90s when we decided to take on cigarettes. Imagine a company being told today that they now have to stop advertising on billboards, can't advertise to kids, and have to pay a fifth of a trillion dollars over 25 years for the harms they caused to Medicaid. Can't, can you?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lenerdenator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run, Bezos, Run]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52649</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/06/run-bezos-run/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T11:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A transcript from memory of an evening conversation with my two older sons: “I heard that Jeff Bezos could run through the streets every day, throwing hundred dollar bills in the air, and he’d still be making money.” “I wonder if that’s true?” “Okay, how much is Jeff Bezos worth?” “Uh [googling]… wow, it says […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271114</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our sure-footed daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remembering A Day the West Wants to Forget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271098</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/remembering-a-day-the-west-wants-to-forget.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia celebrates its victory over Nazism on May 9 while in the West decades of historical revisionism blaming the USSR for WWII has helped rehabilitate Nazis and lead us to the New Cold War crisis today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuberculosis Emergency in California After Death in Homeless Shelter Outbreak; Follows Chicago Migrant Shelter Cluster and Earlier IM Doc Anecdata]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271074</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/tuberculosis-emergency-in-california-after-death-in-homeless-shelter-outbreak-follows-chicago-migrant-shelter-cluster-and-earlier-im-doc-anecdata.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T08:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rise in tuberculosis cases as an indictment of US public health and immigration policy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Apocalypse’ Became a Secular as Well as a Religious Idea]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271124</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/how-apocalypse-became-a-secular-as-well-as-a-religious-idea.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T06:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meaning of “apocalypse” has expanded in recent decades from an exclusively religious idea to include other, more human-driven apocalyptic scenarios]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student Demands for Divestment Are Not New]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321249</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/student-demands-for-divestment-are-not-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T06:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Divestment can mean different things depending on the nature of the institution’s financial ties. But the idea behind it is simple: It means removing all financial ties, such as withdrawing investments, and therefore ending direct complicity in criminal and unjust actions. American institutions of higher learning are economic powerhouses with massive endowments, and ultimately can be described as “big businesses.” Many of them use their funds to directly or indirectly invest in Israel. Harvard University, for example, was found in 2020 to have invested nearly $200 million of its $40 billion endowment in companies with ties to Israel’s occupation of Palestine. More
The post Student Demands for Divestment Are Not New appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standing with Professor Nadera Shalhoub-Kevorkian: Upholding Justice, Dignity and Academic Freedom]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321340</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/standing-with-professor-nadera-shalhoub-kevorkian-upholding-justice-dignity-and-academic-freedom/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:58:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The circumstances surrounding Professor Shalhoub-Kevorkian's detention are deeply troubling. She was apprehended on meritless grounds, stemming from a gross distortion of statements made in her scholarly articles and during a podcast hosted by reputable university professors in the United States. During her detention, she endured degrading and dehumanizing treatment, including a humiliating strip search, tight restraints causing physical harm, denial of essential medication, and exposure to inhumane conditions in a cold and insect-infested prison cell. More
The post Standing with Professor Nadera Shalhoub-Kevorkian: Upholding Justice, Dignity and Academic Freedom appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Palestine-Global Mental Health Network</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Shrewsbury Says His Senate Campaign in West Virginia is Bigger Than Party Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321438</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/zach-shrewsbury-says-his-senate-campaign-in-west-virginia-is-bigger-than-party-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we first reached Zach Shrewsbury to interview the former Marine about his U.S. Senate campaign in West Virginia, he was trying to navigate the mountain roads of his home state amid a severe weather advisory. There was high water throughout Kanawha River Valley, due to creeks and streams over-flowing. Near Charleston, the state capital,  More
The post Zach Shrewsbury Says His Senate Campaign in West Virginia is Bigger Than Party Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Early</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Safety is a Fiction: Passing the UK’s Rwanda Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321417</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/when-safety-is-a-fiction-passing-the-uks-rwanda-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What a stinking story of inhumanity.  A country intent on sending asylum seekers to one whose residents have actually applied for asylum and sanctuary in other states.  But the UK-Rwanda deal, having stalled and stuttered before various courts and found wanting for reasons of human rights, has become law with the passage of the Safety of Rwanda  More
The post When Safety is a Fiction: Passing the UK’s Rwanda Bill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Golden Age for Shareholders Ever End?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321414</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/will-the-golden-age-for-shareholders-ever-end/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 3, 2024, Disney CEO Bob Iger officially fended off the attempt by institutional investor Nelson Peltz and his hedge fund Trian Partners to secure two board seats. During the affair, Disney faced pressure from proxy advisory firm Institutional Shareholder Services to support Peltz’s initiative. While Iger prevailed, the costliest board fight in history underscores the significant influence of  More
The post Will the Golden Age for Shareholders Ever End? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Craven Opportunism of John Fetterman]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321412</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/the-craven-opportunism-of-john-fetterman/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was disappointed, but not surprised to read Democratic Senator John Fetterman express his support for Republican Governor Ron DeSantis’ ban on cultivated meat in Florida. For those who don’t know, cultivated meat is grown from livestock cells, without slaughter. It has the potential to dramatically reduce our greenhouse gas emissions, pandemic risk and the  More
The post The Craven Opportunism of John Fetterman appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem of Feeding a Still-Growing Population: Nitrogen, Agrochemical Corporations and International Trade: A Perilous Mix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271080</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/the-problem-of-feeding-a-still-growing-population-nitrogen-agrochemical-corporations-and-international-trade-a-perilous-mix.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial farming, with its international trade and specialization, has disturbed the nitrogen cycle, undermining the feeding of the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Analysts Leave Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321437</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/what-the-analysts-leave-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:47:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conservative columnist George Will wrote a very welcome column calling attention to a book, Nuclear War: A Scenario by historian Annie Jacobsen, a riveting must-read that details just how easily deterrence could unravel, how fast and irreversibly escalation would occur, and how compete the destruction would be. But Will undercut the value of his  More
The post What the Analysts Leave Out appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Winslow Myers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India, Israel, and America’s Double Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/india-israel-and-americas-double-standard/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[India is hailed as the world’s biggest democracy, and Israel as the only democracy in the Middle East. Yet both are led by authoritarian rulers who are far more interested in crushing opponents than in promoting democracy. This reality should be sobering for US presidents who, whether Democrats or Republicans, have consistently given both countries  More
The post India, Israel, and America’s Double Standard appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza and Humboldt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321248</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/gaza-and-humboldt/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No books were burned this time in early May. But there were ironic parallels, some all too alarming! It was May 10th in Germany’s terrible year 1933, Hitler had been in power for hardly three months, when students and staff emptied the university libraries of forbidden books and threw them, an estimated 20,000 books by  More
The post Gaza and Humboldt appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victor Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nowheresville]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321245</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/06/nowheresville/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowhere Land: Journeys Through a Broken Nation. Ron Jacobs, Burlington, Vt: Formite Press, 132pp, $12.00 The literature of itinerant travel, “on the road,” has been a search for the Lost Highway of American life as soon as turnpikes (often based on Indigenous people’s trails) offered escape. Escape from what? Or in hopes of discovery, what?   More
The post Nowheresville appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Buhle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by willvarfar in "Social engineering takeovers of open source projects"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40271299</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40271299"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So next the attackers playing the long game will just set out to develop the next great everybody-uses-it open-source library, so they control it from inception?
Great that we'll finally get state-sponsored open-source development :D]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>willvarfar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sensanaty in "MIT abandons requirement of DEI statements for hiring and promotions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40270369</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40270369"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T01:44:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The western idea of DEI has always puzzled me ever since I first came across it (or at least the D portion of DEI, which in my mind is the most important one).
I'm a Serb by blood and grew up in and have lived in Indonesia for the majority of my life, and I went to an international school with kids from quite literally every single corner of the earth, many of them being some exotic mix of various ethnicities.
Despite that, many of us are actually amazingly similar in many ways - We have a very distinct int'l kid accent that we all share, we grew up with extremely similar experiences, listening to the same music, being exposed to all the same things. Despite the superficial differences, I actually wouldn't call us a very diverse group at all when you really look at us. Some years later whe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sensanaty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by notatoad in "Bollards: Why and What"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269520</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269520"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T23:18:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i'm not entirely sure what the author intended, but what i took from the article is that there should be a general consensus that some sort of physical separation between cars and pedestrians is necessary to protect pedestrians from cars, and failing to build that protection means you're failing to protect pedestrians.
it's up to each individual jurisdiction to decide how much they want to protect pedestrians, but when a pedestrian is killed by a car it should be acknowledged that a bollard probably could have prevented that, and not doing the thing that would have protected a pedestrian was a decision that was made for reasons such as "it's expensive" or "it's ugly".  The people or organizations making decisions to not protect pedestrians should be held liable for choosing to endanger pedestrians.
too often, the response to a car running into a person or building is to either claim nothing can be done about it, or to blame the driver.  no protections from cars is seen as a road designer following best practices, and they've done their job acceptably well.  and that should be corrected.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>notatoad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Aurornis in "MIT abandons requirement of DEI statements for hiring and promotions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269356</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269356"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve heard this same argument for DEI statements every time the topic has been debated: They sidestep arguments about DEI statements and instead retreat to safer arguments about how advancing DEI is a good thing.
On one hand, I get it. Arguing for DEI in an abstract sense is much easier than arguing for specific interventions.
On the other hand, this is the textbook example of a Motte-and-bailey fallacy, where the debater conflates two topics and then retreats to the safer position while hoping that the audience will accept it as an argument for the more difficult position.
DEI statements have been quite unpopular as specific interventions, as noted in the article by the way that the majority of staff disagreed with them when polled privately. However, speaking out against them publicly was viewed as a very risky move and serious career mistake, so they slowly slipped into mainstream acceptance.
It’s interesting to see how they’re now quietly being removed from processes with as little attention as possible. Nobody wants to be known as the person who campaigned against them publicly, but I suspect there are a lot of people feeling relief in this case as they’re being quietly removed from the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aurornis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by afruitpie in "“Meta spent almost as much as the Manhattan Project on GPUs in today's dollars”"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269243</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40269243"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m surprised how “cheap” the Manhattan Project and Apollo Program were.
It’s bizarre we put people on the Moon in the ‘60s for an amount of money similar to Apple’s recent stock buybacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>afruitpie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by crazygringo in "Bollards: Why and What"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268948</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268948"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a bit difficult to read, as it seems to be written with a heavy dose of sarcasm/irony.
I genuinely can't tell what the author is arguing for, as it's extremely difficult to tell if he's quoting things because he agrees or disagrees with them.
My biggest question is: is the author arguing that there should be spaced bollards along literally every sidewalk in the country/world, and around all edges of every parking lot?
If so, it's an interesting idea, but I also can't help but think that would not just be expensive, but also possibly extremely ugly.
I'm curious if there are estimates of both installation cost as well as lives saved and other damage to buildings avoided.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>crazygringo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bsuvc in "Social engineering takeovers of open source projects"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268920</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268920"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a maintainer (one of many) of an open source project, and this topic has been on my mind a lot lately as I review PRs.
I am more suspicious of PRs from new contributors by default now. Of course I keep these suspicions to myself, but besides simply reviewing code for all the regular things, I now ask myself "what sort of sneaky thing could they be doing that appears benign on the surface?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bsuvc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Review: Wolves Upon the Coast as a System]]></title>
        <id>https://reaverswutc.bearblog.dev/a-review-wolves-upon-the-coast-as-a-system/</id>
        <link href="https://reaverswutc.bearblog.dev/a-review-wolves-upon-the-coast-as-a-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T21:37:35.441Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have played a lot of Wolves Upon the Coast. I love it and recommend this system to anyone that wants the vibes of Iron Age Warriors seeking to make great stories. So if this is what you are looking for is just "is it worth it" I would say Yes. Past that I am going to do a review of my favorite and least favorite bits of this system. I also am going to review Wolves the system before Wolves the setting I will do the setting in the future but for now I wanted to talk about this system.
The Good:
Boasting - Wolves did away with traditional levels and moved to a more diegetic method of advancement that still provides a solid framework for players to look at when they question how else to advance. Pure diegetic systems can leave players feeling a bit lost as to what they are expected to do an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by suddenexample in "Israel shuts down local Al Jazeera offices"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268542</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268542"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T21:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The US White House press secretary issued a weak statement condemning Israel's action, but it was on April 1st and the costumed Easter Bunny overshadowed that statement.[7]
Wow you can't make this stuff up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suddenexample</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cjk2 in "Israel shuts down local Al Jazeera offices"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268421</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268421"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T21:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just a point about Al Jazeera that is worth mentioning. There are two Al Jazeeras. One which is presented to Western audiences and one which is presented to Middle-Eastern audiences. The media and articles are politically aligned in each region. Don't assume what you read in the US/UK/wherever is the same as over there.
In the case of Israel, the Middle-Eastern unit were literally showing videos demanding further uprising against Israel across the region directly from Hamas. Also the entire point of Al Jazeera was for Qatar to provide political influence through media, not as an unbiased news agency.
It's even banned in some Arab countries for being a security risk.
Why would you allow that to continue in your country?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cjk2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The personal website returns: the good, the bad, and the ugly of it]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7515</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/personal-website-returns-good-bad-ugly/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T21:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kyle Chayka, writing for the New Yorker, in an article heralding the demise of the platform era: Now digital-distribution infrastructure is crumbling, having become both ineffective for publishers and alienating for users. Social networks, already lackluster sources for news, are overwhelmed by misinformation and content generated by artificial intelligence. A.I.-driven search threatens to upend how […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Israel shuts down local Al Jazeera offices"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268301</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40268301"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["and block its websites." So this keeps Israelis from reading Al Jazeera.
Now that's new. Israel started Internet censorship in 2017.[1] Initially it was limited to "terror group websites, online illegal gambling, prostitution services, hard drug sales". At the time, "due to warnings from rights groups that the law poses a slippery slope toward additional censorship, the final version of the legislation dictates that rights groups may appeal the decisions."
Then, in 2021, there was the "Facebook bill", authorizing very broad censorship.[2] That does not seem to have passed. It was first proposed in 2016, almost passed in 2018 [3], tried in 2021, and tried again in 2022. It doesn't seem to have passed.
But something new happened recently. Wikipedia has a note at Censorship in Israel: "This article needs to be updated. The reason given is: New ban issued by the knesset on foreign media channels. Please help update this article to reflect recent events or newly available information. (April 2024)"[4]
The Knesset gave the government the authority to ban foreign media on April 1, 2024.[5]
This isn't just about preventing outside media from reporting from Israel. It keeps Israelis from viewing media the government doesn't like. Haarez has good coverage.[6]
The US White House press secretary issued a weak statement condemning Israel's action, but it was on April 1st and the costumed Easter Bunny overshadowed that statement.[7]
[1] https://www.timesofisrael.com/to-tackle-online-crime-israel-...
[2] https://www.timesofisrael.com/proposed-censorship-bill-more-...
[3] https://www.timesofisrael.com/how-israel-nearly-destroyed-fr...
[4] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Censorship_in_Israel
[5] https://www.msn.com/en-us/news/world/israels-knesset-approve...
[6] https://www.haaretz.com/israel-news/2024-05-05/ty-article/is...
[7] https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/press-briefings/202...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by afavour in "Israel shuts down local Al Jazeera offices"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267846</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267846"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:14:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not sure about “dark day for the media” but it does feel like a dark day for Israel.
Once you’ve established that the government can unilaterally ban a voice for reasons of “national security” you’ve essentially given them a free pass. As Americans living post-9/11 will know, “national security” is a deliberately elastic term that can cover anything required in the moment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>afavour</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Israel shuts down local Al Jazeera offices"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267756</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267756"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:04:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: if you're about to comment in this thread, please review https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html and make sure your post is in the intended spirit of the site. If it isn't, please edit it until it is; or simply remember that the internet is usually wrong and refrain from posting.
The intended spirit is curious, respectful conversation in which we learn from each other. Yes, that is hard when emotions run strong, but hard != impossible, and it's what the site rules ask: "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could WHO’s Technical Report on “Pathogens That Transmit Through the Air” Already Be Obsolete, Two Weeks After Its Release?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271078</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/whos-technical-report-on-pathogens-that-tranmit-through-the-air-already-rendered-obsolete-by-advancing-aerosol-science.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WHO's terminology and WHO's science are both questionable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "MIT abandons requirement of DEI statements for hiring and promotions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267547</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267547"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the spirit of trying to learn something from the community: while I can certainly understand the rationale and goals behind DEI programs (many of which I agree with, others not), I honestly can't understand these "DEI statements" at all. They always seemed very "1984" to me, and almost designed to engender resentment in a way that would ultimately backfire. So perhaps I'm in a like-minded echo chamber, but is there anyone that actually defends these DEI statements with a coherent argument, or can you point me to one online? If so, I'd honestly love to hear it, and I mean this quite genuinely. I did some googling beforehand and found loads of "how to write a good DEI statement" articles, but literally every single one of them just took it at face value that these were a good thing to begin with (or, perhaps in their defense, that "academic jobs require it", so you better learn how to write one in any case).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ship to oblivion is finished]]></title>
        <id>https://frings.space/ship-to-oblivion-is-finished/</id>
        <link href="https://frings.space/ship-to-oblivion-is-finished/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:36:32.020Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post goes something like this: I was really happy yesterday.
It feels extraordinarily silly to write about that, but I think it matters.
I should've written this yesterday! Whilst feeling the emotions and thinking the thoughts! But alas, I did not.
Part of the reason why I didn’t is the same reason why I’ve never been able to keep a journal, no matter how many of those my mother gifted me when I was a child in an attempt to encourage the habit. (Same goes for a blog, ironically, or at least one that is about myself.)
That reason is that I think in words. Not in the sense of hearing them, not quite in the sense of saying them either, but I think the way I write: the words, sentences, just kind of come to me. I don’t exactly conjure them. But I do almost see them, like you would see a h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "MIT abandons requirement of DEI statements for hiring and promotions"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267353</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40267353"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: Please don't use HN for ideological battle. There are too many low-quality/predictable comments here. We want curious conversation, not sharp recitals.
I know it's hard when the topic is itself an ideological battle, but that's a good time to review the site guidelines,  including this one: "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."
https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Amazon EKS Deployments with GitHub Actions and AWS CodeBuild]]></title>
        <id>927b83b65f21454ba5bd50a68ec8f8d9aea30edc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/simplify-amazon-eks-deployments-with-github-actions-and-aws-codebuild/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T19:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we will explore how to simplify Amazon EKS deployments with GitHub Actions and AWS CodeBuild. In today’s fast-paced digital landscape, organizations are turning to DevOps practices to drive innovation and streamline their software development and infrastructure management processes. One key practice within DevOps is Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD), which […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepak Kovvuri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sph in "Take a look at Traefik, even if you don't use containers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40265558</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40265558"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T15:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traefik is pretty cool, but suffers from the same, terrible problem of Ansible: there is a lot of documentation, and a lot of words written, yet you can never find anything you need.
I have used it since v1 and I routinely get lost in their docs, and get immensely frustrated. I have been using Caddy for smaller projects simply because its documentation is not as terrible (though not great by any stretch)
Technical writers: documentation by example is good only for newbies skimming through. People familiar with your product need a reference and exhaustive lists, not explanation for different fields spread over 10 tutorial pages. Focus on those that use the product day in and day out, not solely on the "onboarding" procedure.
This is my pet peeve and the reason why I hate using Ansible so damn much, and Traefik to a lesser extent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sph</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a contemplation on death and a quick update]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/death-and-an-update/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/death-and-an-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T12:57:00.734Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[how many people die in a year?
we visited my a-ma on may 1st, a day before her birthday. while waiting for my dad to finish placing the flowers by her vault, i looked around the room. it seemed so empty, yet so full at the same time. everyone in her room was old, unsurprisingly.
when we went to the temple to visit my taima and taikong1, i looked around again. just on the column that housed my great grandparents was the resting place of what seemed like a young child.
the slot is packed with calico critters and a lone sonny angel, sugary sweet snacks and drinks and a cute candle. in another slot, cigarettes and a can of coke. further down the temple, in slot L-28: baby formula and a bottle, alongside a new pink onesie. the name on the slot is yellowed. the baby has been here a while. two sl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which Industries Lost Jobs, Which Gained Jobs: Longer-Term Employment Trends in Charts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271058</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/which-industries-lost-jobs-which-gained-jobs-longer-term-employment-trends-in-charts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T11:29:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Which Industries Lost Jobs, Which Gained Jobs: Longer-Term Employment Trends in Charts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271045</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T10:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our breezy daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: pink salt lake at Gruissan]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52666</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/05/sunday-photoblogging-pink-salt-lake-at-gruissan/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T09:27:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Colonialism in the Empire State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321230</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/05/green-colonialism-in-the-empire-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T05:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November of last year, the Tonawanda Seneca Nation sued the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service (USFWS) over its illegal approval of a wastewater disposal pipeline that would service STAMP. According to the Tonawanda Seneca Nation, the USFWS approved the Genesee County Economic Development Center’s (GCEDC) construction of the 9.5-mile pipeline without conducting a sufficient environmental review and without a government-to-government consultation with the Nation—in direct violation of their sovereign rights.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Green Colonialism in the Empire State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cecilia Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pitzer College Becomes First in US to Call for Academic Boycott of Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320535</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/05/pitzer-college-becomes-first-in-us-to-call-for-academic-boycott-of-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T05:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Photo: Student protest against BlackRock Vice Chairman and then Pitzer Trustee Robert Fairbairn, on the wall of a Pitzer College dorm in Fall 2019. | Donnie Denome – The Student Life.
On April 1, the administration of Pitzer College in Claremont, California, outside of Los Angeles, announced that it would be suspending its student exchange program with the University of Haifa in Israel. The following day, the Dean of Faculty’s Office claimed in a statement that the decision to suspend the program did not “reflect an academic boycott,” but “lack of enrollments for at least five years, exchange imbalance, or curricular overlap.” The statement could have passed for a belated April Fool’s Day joke, seeing as how students and faculty at Pitzer and other schools belonging to the consortium of Claremont Colleges had been demanding their institutions sever ties with the Israeli economy and academia due to the ongoing Israeli genocide in Gaza, which has killed at least 34,488 Palestinians, including 14,500 children and 8,400 women, according to Al Jazeera at the time of this writing.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Pitzer College Becomes First in US to Call for Academic Boycott of Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what i've been reading]]></title>
        <id>https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/what-ive-been-reading/</id>
        <link href="https://monocyte.bearblog.dev/what-ive-been-reading/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T21:08:51.114Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hey! i haven't posted for a while now. i wanted to talk about more manga but couldn't justify making a whole post dedicated to one series. so here is a post where i talk about a couple of them briefly. this one will be less edited and more chaotic than usual so enjoy!
cigarette and cherry

i know i know, the last manga i reviewed also had a smoking theme and was a romance manga. the similarities were actually how i found this one.
it has a simple plot of a student enrolling to a university and trying to find a girlfriend but you slowly get invested in the characters and enjoy their banter. most of the story is centered around a cafe and gives me a sort of friends vibe. i enjoyed my time with it, i think it's worth checking out.
the fable

the deadliest assassin of japan gets an order from …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading is much more better than watching]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/reading-is-much-more-better-than-watching/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.bearblog.dev/reading-is-much-more-better-than-watching/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T19:11:36.558Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven't been able to watch anything lately like animes, youtube videos, dramas, movies, documentaries etc.
Watching feels just too slow for me. If I read, I can consume the content with my preference of pace. That's something I can't do with watching. Yes, I can speed up the video most of the time but it is still not enough.
It is not like I read super fast by the way. I'm a quite average reader in terms of speed. Reading just feels more personal, internalizable and absorbable.
It's probably because reading is an active process while watching is a passive process.
The important thing is that I realized this reality within myself and I decided to reduce watching videos. So I've been purposely avoiding watching videos for awhile now. I can say that consuming contents in reading format is much more better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Writing when nothing to write]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.bearblog.dev/writing-nothing-write/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.bearblog.dev/writing-nothing-write/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T18:26:36.546Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while I write even though I have nothing to write. This is one of those times.
Sometimes something comes out of it, sometimes it doesn't. But I keep doing it in one form or another. Because...
It's easier to keep going than to get started.
I find it more motivating to do it publicly - even if no one reads it. It adds a bit of healthy "pressure". And it's more fun, especially with nice tools like Bear blog.
But it doesn't matter how you do it.
Write on a piece of paper, your phone, a computer, or whatever. Write spontaneously or thoughtfully, in depth or effective, personal or general. Write a sentence, 500 characters, or three pages.
It doesn't matter. It's all up to you. There's no contest, and there's no right or wrong.
Just keep writing...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the fragility of all we hold dear]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/farewell-uncle/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/farewell-uncle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T16:49:02.289Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday during my brother's graduation my mom told me that her older brother (my uncle) was admitted to the hospital and diagnosed with late stage lung cancer.
I don't know exactly when this happened, but I think things haven't been good for a while now. My mom and her siblings are intentionally very vague; they haven't even told my grandparents. I understand not wanting to spook the parents but don't know if I agree. I know I would want to know as soon as possible if my firstborn were on death's doorstep.
My uncle's been smoking since before I was born, so it's not like we couldn't have foreseen this coming. But I think my grandpa doing the same without issue well into his eighties lulled us all into a false sense of security. The timing stunned me, not least because we found out at com…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a rocking horse and a thinking chair: an entry better left unfinished]]></title>
        <id>https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-rocking-horse-and-a-thinking-chair/</id>
        <link href="https://bowlofmisua.bearblog.dev/a-rocking-horse-and-a-thinking-chair/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T15:24:17.785Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[all of us strangers, dir. andrew haigh

may has arrived at my doorstep, bringing about a new wave of loneliness that doesn’t scream, but thrums.
twenty-three-almost-twenty-four lonely years.
there’s a deep longing for a partner; someone to share everything with. yes, I can do that with my friends, but there’s a line of intimacy that i can’t quite seem to breach. it’s thin, but sturdy. a reminder that the people in my life right now are platonic.
there are dreams of a figure, never a face, that holds me in my sleep. dreams of the hazy silhouette of a five year old running down the stairs; of a home full of laughter and silly tiles and stained glass. dreams of someone who sits beside me on a hot day, complaining about the heatwave that has southeast asia in a vice grip.
there’s never a face.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by akudha in "I don't want to fill out your contact form"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40258200</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40258200"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T15:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I become older (and grumpier) I have realized that not engaging is the best thing to do, wherever possible. Dirty  restaurant / rude staff? Don't go there. Don't like dark patterns on a website? Contact forms don't work? Don't use those sites. And so on. Two reasons - first, most of the time, these businesses know their shit is broken or they're doing low quality work etc. They just don't care. Second, it is good for our own stress levels to avoid dealing with shitty stuff.
Obviously this can't be applied to essential services like healthcare etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>akudha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rachel’s Children]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321113</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/04/rachels-children/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T14:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Had she not been murdered in Rafah protecting Palestinian homes from demolition, Rachel Corrie could have become the mother of today’s protesters on US campuses. They’re certainly the inheritors of her fierce moral spirit and unflinching courage…
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Rachel’s Children appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Absurd!’: US Billionaires Pay Lower Tax Rate Than Working Class for First Time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271041</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/absurd-us-billionaires-pay-lower-tax-rate-than-working-class-for-first-time.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T13:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's time to tax the billionaires," economist Gabriel Zucman argues in a new analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The singularity and importance of the 1st World Anti-Fascist Conference to be held in Porto Alegre from 17 to 19 May 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-singularity-and-importance-of-the-1st-World-Anti-Fascist-Conference-to-be</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-singularity-and-importance-of-the-1st-World-Anti-Fascist-Conference-to-be"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T09:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is so special about the conference taking place in Porto Alegre from 17 to 19 May 2024? 
English

/ 
Brazil, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Environment Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/environment-matters/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/environment-matters/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T08:33:54.829Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best advice I got in college was from a senior. "Pick the teacher not the course" he told me. This was contrary to the general method. Everyone picked a course based on how lenient the grading was or interest.
I respected the guy so decided to follow his advice. I chose 'Computational Complexity' as an elective. A subject I had no interest in. The Prof was known for strict grading and the material was supposed to be really tough. It was all theory. No practical coding. On paper it was the worst choice I could have made. It turned out to be the best course I ever took.
In my college you can sit for am elective course for first week or two before committing to it. Kind of like window shopping for knowledge. So I decided to check the course out. I knew nothing about it. Had no interest as well. It quickly changed. The Prof teaching it had a passion that was infectious. He would encourage doubts. If someone asked something silly he would say "ah! it seems trivial on the face of it but reveals deeper complexities" with a happy glint in his eyes. There were no stupid questions in his class. So I chose the teacher not the course. Going with my gut and my seniors advice against all common sense. Only 11 other people in the entire college took the course.
I had the most fun in those classes. Learned so much. Fell in love with formal proof writing. Had my mind blown several times. The extra class hours spend absorbing the material, making my way through new proofs felt effortless.
It taught me a lesson that I always keep in mind. Environment matters. The people you surround yourself with matter. Whether in work or personal life. Anything can become interesting, profound and world changing if done with right people.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by surfingdino in "AI copilots are changing how coding is taught"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40255488</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40255488"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T06:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am skeptical.
Well before AI co-pilots something happened to the good old admins--they started to disappear only to be replaced by "AWS devops" (their job titles) who have never wired a network using routers, switches, and cables. I noticed that they started lacking basic networking knowledge and couldn't set up networking inside AWS. They just didn't know what a gateway, NAT, or subnet is.
Similar things are happening with AI co-pilots. We have an increasing number of people who "write code", but the number of people who can understand and review code is not increasing. There is also a problem of injecting ethics and politics into those tools, which can produce silly results. I asked Bard to write me a Python function to turn the US Constitution into a palindrome. Bard refused and gave ma a lecture on how the US Constitution is too important to be played with in such trivial fashion. I then asked it to produce code that turns the US national anthem into a palindrome, it refused again. So I asked it do the same but with the Russian national anthem and it spat out code without telling me off. I then asked it to generate code for simple tasks and it did an OK job, except the formatting and the fonts used were different every time, because it just lifted code from different webpages and recombined it like a massively hungover student waking up to realise he's supposed to hand in the assignment in one hour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>surfingdino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A traumatizing layover in Mexico airport]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.bearblog.dev/a-traumatizing-layover-in-mexico-airport/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.bearblog.dev/a-traumatizing-layover-in-mexico-airport/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T01:48:27.960Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm soon traveling to Seattle for work. Surprisingly, I'm more anxious about this trip than seems reasonable, and I'm not sure why. It's not the first time I've traveled, nor is it even the first time I've gone to Seattle for work. It's actually the second time I'm going there. Now that I think about it, I can see how the first time was kind of traumatizing in some ways. Perhaps talking about it would help me work through it.
Let's start from the beginning...
Last time I went, I flew from my country to Mexico City, and then from there to Seattle. I took the same route on the way back. Overall, it was fairly quick and was by far the best option offered by the travel agency that the company I work for uses (all the other routes were waaay longer or had a lot more legs).
My way there was... o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sasaf5 in "AI copilots are changing how coding is taught"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40254012</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40254012"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T01:13:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early 2023, when everyone started using chat GPT for coding, I thought it would be a big boost because it enabled us to quickly employ a large number of people in a project regardless of language or framework.
An year into the project I am forced to revise my opinion. When browsing my code-base I often stumble in abstruse niche solutions for problems that should not have existed. It was clearly the work of someone inexperienced walking through walls in an AI-fuelled coding frenzy.
Having an oracle that knows all answers is useless if you don't know what to ask.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sasaf5</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dgacmu in "How hard can generating 1024-bit primes be?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40252687</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40252687"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T21:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Related, there are a few cryptocurrencies that used things related to finding large primes as part of their proof of work functions. It turns out that ~8 years ago, a really fast primality test implementation could make you a lot of money. (For some period of time I was the author and maintainer of mining software for riecoin. Why, I have no idea, except that I like prime numbers.)
This article omits the number one optimization for fast primality testing: Montgomery multiplication
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montgomery_modular_multiplic...
It forms the basis of fast practical modular exponentiation implementations.
Niall Emmart, then in academia and now I believe at Nvidia, released a really, spectacularly fast GPU bigint library, CGBN: https://github.com/NVlabs/CGBN
It's still the fastest batch modexp implentation that I'm aware of. It's breathtaking, if I can gush in geek for a moment.
(Someday I should write up the story of how that helped me dominate production of a small cryptocurrency for about 5 years. Thanks, Niall - owe you a beer if we ever cross paths!)
Also worth noting that python includes an entirely fine modexp in the three-argument form of pow(x, y, m) --> compute x^y % m
With that, you can very easily implement a fermat or miller-rabin primality test if you want to roll your own, which is quite fun. If you don't, the gmp library provides a very nice mpz_probab_prime() function. Gmp is obviously faster, but it's hard to beat the fun of a two liner fermat test for playing with big primes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dgacmu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Immigration, wages, and the Phillips Curve]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715483/0/themoneyillusion~Immigration-wages-and-the-Phillips-Curve/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715483/0/themoneyillusion~Immigration-wages-and-the-Phillips-Curve/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:52:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As you may know, the actual Phillips Curve is about the relationship between unemployment and wage inflation. That&#8217;s the relationship A.W. Phillips actually identified, and it&#8217;s still the correct version. Price inflation doesn&#8217;t correlate well with unemployment. Painful disinflation is and always has been about getting wage inflation down. Forget payroll employment, the big news [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/895715483/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/895715483/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-03-at-2.46.30-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/895715483/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/895715483/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/895715483/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comment-6821360">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comment-6821359">Bobster, Yes, lags. And the recent downward trend in wage ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comment-6821343">Scott, you said, “It looks to me like wages are about 8% ...</a> <i>by Travis Allison</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comment-6821148">Scott,   “..as you may know, the actual Phillips Curve is ...</a> <i>by Viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comment-6821047">@MD Sandifer:   The problem, which you allude to, is that the ...</a> <i>by msgkings</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/immigration-wages-and-the-phillips-curve/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Odds and ends]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715492/0/themoneyillusion~Odds-and-ends/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715492/0/themoneyillusion~Odds-and-ends/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Commenter Floccina directed me to a video showing Matt Yglesias&#8217;s ideal city. 2. A back issue of Harpers had an article discussing the possibility of legalizing drugs. This comment caught my eye: At the time, I was writing a book about the politics of drug prohibition. I started to ask [former Nixon aide] Ehrlichman [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/895715492/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/895715492/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-27-at-12.41.30-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/895715492/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/895715492/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/895715492/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comment-6821379">I did a quick check of the immigrant statistics to the EU and ...</a> <i>by Carl</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comment-6821128">Gabbard is also a finalist.</a> <i>by sara</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comment-6820840">EHarding, You said:   “she is a moderate Republican” ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comment-6820814">The irony of you denigrating Trump as 'exceedingly dumb,' and ...</a> <i>by DBrooks</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comment-6820739">sumner never has evidence. he is all polemics and poetry, and ...</a> <i>by agrippa postumus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/odds-and-ends-8/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The question is the problem]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715498/0/themoneyillusion~The-question-is-the-problem/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/895715498/0/themoneyillusion~The-question-is-the-problem/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You: What do you think of the Gaza situation? Me: That&#8217;s the problem. You: What do you mean? I asked for your view on the situation. Me: My view is that the question you asked is the problem. The problem is that we are asking questions about Gaza. If we were not asking those questions, [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/895715498/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/895715498/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/895715498/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/895715498/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/895715498/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comment-6821484">msgkings, I mostly agree with both comments, but would replace ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comment-6821444">Let me add, the Israelis are pretty bad guys in general, ...</a> <i>by msgkings</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comment-6821442">@ssumner:   Great post right above…would use like button if ...</a> <i>by msgkings</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comment-6821385">Camden, The term genocide is like “racism”, it's been so ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comment-6821378">I suggest you ask a Palestinian for their views. The US is ...</a> <i>by Camden</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-question-is-the-problem/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by minusLik in "As private equity dominates wheelchair market, users wait months for repairs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40252212</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40252212"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T20:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What the article does not seem to mention is that an usual electric wheelchair costs about $65,000 (and is intended to be replaced every six years or so). This and the non-availability of replacement parts is why some wheelchair users started a project to open-source a wheelchair from standard parts:
https://themif.org/
Louis Rossmann interviewed the founder of the project here:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eaAj59025Kk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>minusLik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nickff in "As private equity dominates wheelchair market, users wait months for repairs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40251683</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40251683"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T19:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private equity discovered that regulations, compliance requirements, & other similar barriers to entry are the most effective 'moats' which allow businesses to raise prices and have little impact on demand; they are now exploiting this 'hack' ruthlessly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nickff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tombert in "AI copilots are changing how coding is taught"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40250835</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40250835"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T18:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm all for moving to higher-level skills, when I was an adjunct professor I usually didn't put a huge emphasis on syntax unless I thought it was important to explain a concept, and I very rarely took off points for syntax.
That said, I don't know that I would allow AI for learning to code in the class.  I do not consider "prompt engineering" to be a substitute for programming, and it's very easy to get AI to write some code and copypaste it, not understand anything it said, and be done.
Last year, when I was administering a test, I said that they were allowed to use any IDE they wanted, but they could not use any AI assistance.  I am pretty convinced one student just copypasted my test questions into ChatGPT or BingAI and then copied the answers. I didn't have a way to prove it so I had to give him the benefit of the doubt and grade it assuming he did it honestly.
Before someone says "YOU SHOULD TEACH THEM TO USE THE AI TOOLS LOL THAT'S THE FUTURE!!!", stop.  That's not true, not yet at least.  Just because I can call an Uber doesn't mean I get to say I know how to drive.  Just because I can go to McDonalds doesn't mean I get to say I know how to cook. I was teaching them how to write Java and Python, the goal of the class was for them to learn Java and Python, it wasn't learning how to copypaste into OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tombert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vegetablepotpie in "Lithium-free sodium batteries exit the lab and enter US production"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40249330</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40249330"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re undergoing a Cambrian explosion of battery chemistries at the moment. Other startups, such as From Energy is scaling up production of Iron Air batteries in West Virginia, which will be an order of magnitude cheaper than lithium ion and will provide grid scale power [1]. North Harbour Clean Energy Promised to build a manufacturing facility in Australia to build Vanadium Flow batteries, which have very high charge cycle in their lifetime and can store energy for longer durations [2].
The advantage with Sodium Ion is that, although energy densities are lower than Lithium Ion, it could still be used to power mobile devices and electric vehicles.
[1] https://www.wesa.fm/environment-energy/2024-02-19/weirton-fo...
[2] https://www.abc.net.au/news/science/2023-02-02/vanadium-redo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vegetablepotpie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Slack adopted Karpenter to increase Operational and Cost Efficiency]]></title>
        <id>511682252fe50ea5a72ea086e585c18b81e75fe9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-slack-adopted-karpenter-to-increase-operational-and-cost-efficiency/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T16:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bedrock – Slack’s internal Kubernetes platform Slack is the AI-powered platform for work that connects people, conversations, apps, and systems together in one place. Slack adopted Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon ) to build “Bedrock,” the codename for an internal compute orchestration platform that simplifies container deployment and management. Bedrock handles build, deploy, and runtime […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vikram Venkataraman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking Hard-work]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/hacking-hard-work/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/hacking-hard-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T14:37:32.675Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always been lazy and ambitious. My life mostly has been a weird experiment in combining the two. Being ambitious means I want to achieve a lot, something that required hard work. Being lazy means, well I would rather not work hard.
And no this is not some post about smart work. I never understood smart work anyways. It assumes people are dumb and don't know how to approach problems from high leverage points. I am not sure if any of these people even exist when you are competing at a high level.
Competing at a high level means you are up against smart crazy human beings willing to burn everything including themselves. You have to grind hard to have a shot. So I had to solve my hard work issue.
I soon realised that my issue was not hard work. It was work that 'felt' like hard work. I can just program the wet squishy computer between my skull to change the 'feeling' settings. So hard work feels like a breeze. Even extremely enjoyable.
How can this programming be done? Well the key insight is you can bore yourself to a point that anything is enjoyable. Also you can gaslight yourself into making any mundane task feel grand. So what looks like mundane paperwork to someone on the outside could feel like the holy act of putting ink on paper and rewriting history to you. You get my point right?
Everyone has a different brain and how you programme this squishy thing will be personal to you. Just spend time with yourself. Introspect to read the documentation.
Be the cracked self programmer you need to be!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pqdbr in "DNS traffic can leak outside the VPN tunnel on Android"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40248095</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40248095"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T14:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blog posts like this (instead of endless YouTube sponsorships like their competitors do) are what made me choose them as my VPN service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pqdbr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nazgulsenpai in "DNS traffic can leak outside the VPN tunnel on Android"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40247762</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40247762"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T14:01:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't use Mullvad, but I respect the shit out of them. This is a good, information dense explanation of the problem, their short term workaround and potential workarounds for others, as well as what will need to be fixed in Android. Good stuff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nazgulsenpai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Have Bad Days Too]]></title>
        <id>https://meowen.bearblog.dev/we-have-bad-days-too/</id>
        <link href="https://meowen.bearblog.dev/we-have-bad-days-too/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:36:37.156Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I may be a cat, but I am not immune to bad days.
This afternoon, I miscalculated the the jump from the ground to the bench. It ended up me looking like a rabbit standing on his hind legs with my front paws reaching out.
Unluckily, a child who passed by the park noticed my failure and told his mother.
"Mother, look! That cat couldn't jump properly!" He pointed out to his mother while giggling and laughing on their way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has Market Concentration in U.S. Manufacturing Increased?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29400</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/has-market-concentration-in-u-s-manufacturing-increased/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The increasing dominance of large firms in the United States has raised concerns about pricing power in the product market. The worry is that large firms, facing fewer competitors, could increase their markups over marginal costs without fear of losing market share. In a recently published paper, we show that although sales of domestic firms have become more concentrated in the manufacturing sector, this development has been accompanied by the entry and growth of foreign firms. Import competition has lowered U.S. producers’ share of the U.S. market and put smaller, less efficient domestic firms out of business.  Overall, market concentration in manufacturing was stable in recent decades, though import penetration has greatly altered the makeup of the U.S. manufacturing sector.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary Amiti and Sebastian Heise</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mhaberl in "Woodworking as an escape from the absurdity of software"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40246243</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40246243"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Even my last team leader sent me a message out of the blue saying “I think I’ll run a bar. I want to be a bartender and listen to other people’s stories, not figure out why protobuf doesn’t deserialize data that worked JUST FINE for the past three years”.
I worked at a bar when I was young, listened to the stories; the most annoying protobuf deserialization issues or 'Agile meetings' are freaking fun compared to the most of the stories you can hear.
This is just comparing apples to oranges. Woodworking or any other hobby that you enjoy will be more pleasing than any real job you will do. Programming is fun, that is why you started doing it. Working as software developer can be less so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mhaberl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sukruh in "Woodworking as an escape from the absurdity of software"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40246033</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40246033"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the people I know who pursue creative/crafting hobbies alongside a software development job have chosen to work for well-known big companies, for prestige and safety, and ended up unfulfilled in their jobs.
Most big companies are not good if you want to solve problems and build stuff. Especially "the enterprise", where software is seen as a cost center so the less of it the better. The effort of managing up eats a creative person's soul.
I want the clarity of being able to talk to "the boss/the customer" and solve their problems and get paid the market rate for my skills. Not prepare endless PowerPoints for my skip-level, who has no ownership but has to act in their own best interests in a swamp of principal-agent problems.
This is why I am very happy at a fast-growing small tech company where one can have honest conversations about the customer and the product. How do other people deal with this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sukruh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letters of Protest: Colleges Suppress Dissent While Closing Their Eyes to Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320861</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/letters-of-protest-colleges-suppress-dissent-while-closing-their-eyes-to-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T06:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Israel began its genocide in Gaza, those who manage U.S. colleges and universities also commenced to issue statements of outrage at what Hamas had done. And as campus protests erupted in condemnation of the slaughter of Gazans, and especially children, and the destruction of homes and every major institution, including hospitals, these same institutions of higher learning began to disrupt these protests and bring them to an end. As a former college teacher, one who witnessed the attacks on those who protested against the War in Vietnam and who studied the repression on campuses during the McCarthy period, I became so appalled at what was being done to our brave and courageous college students that I began to write letters to the leaders of what are, in reality, academic enterprises. More
The post Letters of Protest: Colleges Suppress Dissent While Closing Their Eyes to Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael D. Yates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Tin Cops and Biden Coming…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320563</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/roaming-charges-tin-cops-and-biden-coming/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T06:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As America's liberal elites declare open warfare on their own kids, it's easy to see why they've shown no empathy at all for the murdered, maimed and orphaned children of Gaza. Back-of-the-head shots to 8-year-olds seem like a legitimate thing to protest in about the most vociferous way possible...But, as Dylan once sang, maybe I'm too sensitive or else I'm getting soft. More
The post Roaming Charges: Tin Cops and Biden Coming… appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post’s David Ignatius Declares Victory in Ukraine…Once Again!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/washington-posts-david-ignatius-declares-victory-in-ukraineonce-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s David Ignatius, the mainstream media’s leading apologist for the Pentagon’s use of force and the Central Intelligence Agency’s covert action, has done it once again.  For the past two years, he has regularly predicted victory for Ukraine because the United States or the European members of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization have delivered one particular weapons system or another.  This time around, Ignatius’ oped argues that the “game changer” in the war is the “newly arriving ATACM-300 long-range missile.” More
The post Washington Post’s David Ignatius Declares Victory in Ukraine…Once Again! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Iron Heel of the State at UCLA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321092</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/the-iron-heel-of-the-state-at-ucla/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Biden Biden, Whattaya Say? How Many Kids You Kill Today?” This was one of the militant chants of hundreds of students on May 1 at UCLA. I went to the university after covering the May Day rally in Hollywood, arriving around 4:00 p.m., and this is what I witnessed at the frontlines of the class struggle  More
The post The Iron Heel of the State at UCLA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s More Than Just Protests for Palestine, It is Existential Hope for the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320695</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/its-more-than-just-protests-for-palestine-it-is-existential-hope-for-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's comforting to think in simplistic terms, to avoid confronting the ugliness of history and actively opposing that same unhinged supremacy that created this world that we currently live in. A world of massive inequality, increasing existential threat, and a misery index on the rise. To bring about something radically different for humankind would be to address the violence inherent to settler colonialism and, in a clear-eyed manner, address the very much ongoing philosophy that the deranged ruling elite have decided is worth continuing at the cost of the vast majority of humanity. More
The post It’s More Than Just Protests for Palestine, It is Existential Hope for the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Heat’s On – Big Time!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320848</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/the-heats-on-big-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Nearly nineteen thousand (19,000) weather stations have notched record high temperatures since Jan. 1.” (Source: Earth’s Record Hot Streak Might be a Sign of a New Climate Era, The Washington Post, April 19, 2024) A blistering start to the 2024 year is breaking all-time global temperature records of 2023 and bringing to the forefront a  More
The post The Heat’s On – Big Time! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uncommitted Campaign in New Jersey: The Fight To End Genocide Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320691</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/the-uncommitted-campaign-in-new-jersey-the-fight-to-end-genocide-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sense of urgency loomed over Fatima Mughal, one of the leading organizers behind the uncommitted campaign in New Jersey. Some emotional containment was necessary in the midst of an ongoing genocide. “The people who’ve lost so much in Gaza don’t have the time to sit with their feelings,” she expressed, referring to the 40,000  More
The post The Uncommitted Campaign in New Jersey: The Fight To End Genocide Continues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudip Bhattacharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University Investments: Divesting from the Military-Industrial Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320858</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/university-investments-divesting-from-the-military-industrial-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rage and protest against Israel’s campaign in Gaza, ongoing since the October 7 attacks by Hamas, has stirred student activity across a number of US university campuses and beyond.  Echoes of the Vietnam anti-war protests are being cited.  The docile consumers of education are being prodded and found interested.  University administrators and managers are, as they always  More
The post University Investments: Divesting from the Military-Industrial Complex appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cruelty is the Point]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320850</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/the-cruelty-is-the-point/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acts of cruelty to animals are more than a slight personality flaw. A history of animal torture and abuse has been linked repeatedly to serial killers and mass shooters. Which brings us to the deranged animal-killer Kristi Noem, the South Dakota governor who is running to be the fascist leader Donald “Take Down the Metal  More
The post The Cruelty is the Point appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Southern Autoworkers Can Reverse Decades of Job Quality Decline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320977</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/how-southern-autoworkers-can-reverse-decades-of-job-quality-decline/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United Auto Workers recently scored the largest union victory in decades in the South. Their success at a Tennessee Volkswagen plant could be a turning point for labor in a region long known for governmental hostility to unions. The next test will be a UAW election scheduled for the week of May 13 at  More
The post How Southern Autoworkers Can Reverse Decades of Job Quality Decline appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Bayard - Dev Wakeley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reactionaries and US Military Backers Prevail in Latin America – for Now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321018</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/reactionaries-and-us-military-backers-prevail-in-latin-america-for-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Southern Command Chief Laura Richardson was visiting Argentina for the third time. On April 4 in Ushuaia, Tierra del Fuego – the world’s southernmost city – she and U. S. Ambassador Marc Stanley were received by President Javier Milei, his chief-of-staff, his cabinet chief, the defense minister, the interior minister, a military band, and an honor guard –  More
The post Reactionaries and US Military Backers Prevail in Latin America – for Now appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Let Congress Widen the Digital Divide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320974</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/dont-let-congress-widen-the-digital-divide/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a third of Americans who don’t have broadband say the reason is because it costs too much — and unfortunately, Congress is prepared to let that figure rise dramatically. Lawmakers have yet to renew funding for the federal government’s Affordable Connectivity Program, or ACP, which is being rolled back as of today and will fully come  More
The post Don’t Let Congress Widen the Digital Divide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Claude Cummings Jr.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overcoming Whiteness: A Matter for Imagination, Not Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321020</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/overcoming-whiteness-a-matter-for-imagination-not-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whiteness [is] the ownership of the Earth forever and ever, Amen.                          –W.E.B. Dubois, The Souls of Black Folk whiteness is the world’s most dangerous cult today.                                                –Pankaj Mishra, The Religion of Whiteness Modern neuroscience solidly supports Freud’s notion that many of our conscious thoughts are complex rationalizations for the flood of instincts, reflexes, motives and deep-seated memories  More
The post Overcoming Whiteness: A Matter for Imagination, Not Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim C. Domenico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has the War Against Palestine Killed Jewish Comedy?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320702</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/has-the-war-against-palestine-killed-jewish-comedy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Curb Your Enthusiasm, “Palestinian Chicken,” season 8, episode 3, Robert W. Weide dir. Screenshot Long decline, sudden end To be sure, morbid symptoms were apparent for decades. Woody Allen hasn’t been funny since 1987 (Radio Days). Rodney Dangerfield is long gone. Al Franken moved from SNL to the U.S. Senate — where he was often  More
The post Has the War Against Palestine Killed Jewish Comedy? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore: Lawrence Wong to Lead Amid Economic and Political Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320969</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/singapore-lawrence-wong-to-lead-amid-economic-and-political-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore has announced that Deputy Prime Minister Lawrence Wong will take over as the country’s next leader on May 15. Wong, 51, has garnered unanimous support from lawmakers within the People’s Action Party (PAP). He will succeed Lee Hsien Loong, who has held the top job for 20 years. Wong, who earned praise for his  More
The post Singapore: Lawrence Wong to Lead Amid Economic and Political Challenge appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burning Plastic Waste is Not an Energy Solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320865</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/burning-plastic-waste-is-not-an-energy-solution/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world has a plastics problem. Never mind the horrifying pictures of a seahorse riding a cotton swab or a beached whale found with hundreds of plastic bags in its stomach. Plastic pollution has now progressed up the food chain to our diets, ingested as microplastic particles and even transferred from mother to fetus. Each  More
The post Burning Plastic Waste is Not an Energy Solution  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John K. White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Oil, the U.S. Election and Opening the Cash Spigot for Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=320874</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/03/russian-oil-the-u-s-election-and-opening-the-cash-spigot-for-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know the White House has wrapped itself into a pretzel, when it beseeches its Ukrainian attack dog to stop assaulting Russian oil refineries, while simultaneously going bananas over the need for more weapons for Kiev. Droning Russian refineries boosts the price of oil in an election year – a big no no for the  More
The post Russian Oil, the U.S. Election and Opening the Cash Spigot for Ukraine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[recounting a dream]]></title>
        <id>https://passerine.bearblog.dev/recounting-a-dream/</id>
        <link href="https://passerine.bearblog.dev/recounting-a-dream/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:52:53.039Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[in this world, we met much later than usual. college roommates, at the cusp of graduation, in an apartment that resembled the 2nd floor of one the many homes i've left behind. i don't remember what you were studying this time around, but your room was always filled with music and the murmur of your friends' voices.
we lived like strangers for the most part. our schedules never coincided. we were never home at the same time. we spoke infrequently and only via alphabet magnets on our fridge.
"fod here", "tysm", "rain tom", "ok", "was loud?", "no", "ok"
then finally — an intersection. carpooling home from a mutual friend's party, squished together in the back seat. i was nodding off and you guided my head to your shoulder. i tell you that it's been a while since i've seen you, so you promise to develop a habit of forgetting your keys.
from there, it blurs together. the bump of the road, the hair on my cheek, the itch of your sweater, the gentle hand on my thigh.
i know i'm meant to love you in every lifetime we meet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Sorkin penning a sequel to The Social Network in response to January 6]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7500</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/aaron-sorkin-penning-a-sequel-to-the-social-network-in-response-to-january-6/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T21:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I squeezed in two screenings of The Social Network — the 2010 film by David Fincher and Aaron Sorkin, dramatizing the founding of Facebook — on the day it was released in Australia. I went up to the local cinema the morning it opened, so I could write about it here, then returned to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 market share declining… in favour of Windows 10]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7495</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/windows-11-market-share-declining-windows-10/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, this is something: According to Statcounter, in April 2024, Windows 11 lost 0.97 points, going down from 26.68% to 25.65%. All those users seemingly went for Windows 10 since the OS, which will soon turn nine, crossed the 70% mark for the first time since September 2023, gaining 0.96 points. A nine year old […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Praiseworthy by Alexis Wright, wins the 2024 Stella Prize]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7509</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/praiseworthy-alexis-wright-wins-2024-stella-prize/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T20:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Queensland/Waanyi author Alexis Wright, has been named winner of the 2024 Stella Prize for Australian literature, for works by women and non-binary writers, with Praiseworthy, a novel set in the north of Australia. In a small town dominated by a haze cloud, which heralds both an ecological catastrophe and a gathering of the ancestors, a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by megraf in "Microsoft bans U.S. police from using enterprise AI tool for facial recognition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40240262</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40240262"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T19:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of course they did. They have to pay separate licensing for the use of DAS – which is developed by M$ and resold from NYPD.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Domain_Awareness_System]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>megraf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code April 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_89</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_89"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code April 2024
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Towards the 6th International Ecosocialist Meeting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Towards-the-6th-International-Ecosocialist-Meeting</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Towards-the-6th-International-Ecosocialist-Meeting"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 9, 10 and 11 May 2024, the 6th International Ecosocialist Meeting and the 1st Latin American and Caribbean Ecosocialist Meeting will be held in Buenos Aires, Argentina.. 
th to the 21st century and articulates the fundamental ideas of Marxist (...)
English

/ 
Argentina, 
Ecological debt, 
Capitalism, 
Ecology/Climate, 
Colonialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maria Elena Saludas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build RAG applications with MongoDB Atlas, now available in Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>b969f642374dd7b33aee58f7ddd2a41df8d86392</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-rag-applications-with-mongodb-atlas-now-available-in-knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T13:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foundational models (FMs) are trained on large volumes of data and use billions of parameters. However, in order to answer customers’ questions related to domain-specific private data, they need to reference an authoritative knowledge base outside of the model’s training data sources. This is commonly achieved using a technique known as Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate Terraform Deployments with Amazon CodeCatalyst and Terraform Community action]]></title>
        <id>685ceb3b28139e7768d8b2e600ca25a67cb1ae04</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/automate-terraform-deployments-with-amazon-codecatalyst-and-terraform-community-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T21:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CodeCatalyst integrates continuous integration and deployment (CI/CD) by bringing key development tools together on one platform. With the entire application lifecycle managed in one tool, CodeCatalyst empowers rapid, dependable software delivery. CodeCatalyst offers a range of actions which is the main building block of a workflow, and defines a logical unit of work to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vineeth Nair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget WhatsApp and Messenger, contact me via my website]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7489</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/forget-whatsapp-messenger-contact-website/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite their convenience, ease of sharing content, and even security, I steadfastly resist using the likes of WhatsApp, Messenger, Signal, Telegram, Wire, Viber, and whatever else is out there. I probably infuriate friends and family by refusing to assimilate, but really feel I can only keep up with a certain number of communication channels: chiefly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[euphoria]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/euphoria/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/euphoria/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T19:27:07.366Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday Kendrick Lamar responded to Drake by dropping a diss track called euphoria. Naturally my two friends who listen to hip-hop freaked out. Drama on a Tuesday morning! We weren't the only ones, because the Genius site for the song crashed from all the traffic. The internet is having a field day with it.

I'm not a Kendrick fan but this is far and away the best diss I've ever heard. Kendrick's high-pitched voice inflections shine through. Over six minutes and three wildly different beats he rips Drake's biracialism, reputation as a deadbeat, and inauthenticity, all in rhyme.
I can't choose which lyrics to point out — they're all good! Just listen and admire the wordplay.
Amidst all the carnage, you get the sense that Kendrick's not even trying. He raps,
I make music that electrify 'em, you make music that pacify 'em
I can double down on that line, but spare you this time, that's random acts of kindness
and later,
We ain't gotta get personal, this a friendly fade, you should keep it that way
I know some shit about n- that make Gunna Wunna look like a saint
It's lyrical homicide. I really hope this rap beef doesn't end here, because I want more of this.
The other songs in this beef up to this point:
First Person Shooter (Drake ft. J Cole)
Like That (Future, Metro Boomin, Kendrick Lamar)
Like That REMIX (Kanye West)
7 Minute Drill (J Cole, later deleted)
Push Ups (Drake)
Taylor Made Freestyle (Drake)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 tips to supercharge your developer career in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-05-01-5-tips-to-supercharge-your-developer-career-in-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-05-01-5-tips-to-supercharge-your-developer-career-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T16:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From mastering prompt engineering to leveraging AI for code security, here’s how you can excel in today's competitive job market.  </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-05-01-5-tips-to-supercharge-your-developer-career-in-2024/">5 tips to supercharge your developer career in 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop the CNAME chain struggle: Simplified management with Route 53 Resolver DNS Firewall]]></title>
        <id>86dd5735fb76719fae3fa6f0aa4e8a5a846c0583</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/stop-the-cname-chain-struggle-simplified-management-with-route-53-resolver-dns-firewall/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:39:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updated 2 May 2024: I removed the reference to Route53 Alias that was incorrectly referred as a chain Starting today, you can configure your DNS Firewall to automatically trust all domains in a resolution chain (such as aCNAMEor DNAMEchain). Let’s walk through this in nontechnical terms for those unfamiliar with DNS. Why use DNS Firewall? […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Water Flowing Upwards: Net financial flows from developing countries]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45345</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/01/water-flowing-upwards-net-financial-flows-from-developing-countries/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T12:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from C. P. Chandrasekhar and Jayati Ghosh Once again, low and middle income countries (LMICs) are at the brutal receiving end of the fickle trajectory of international capital flows. As Figure 1 indicates, net financial flows to such countries, which increased rapidly after the Global Financial Crisis that began and was created by advanced economies, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mexican debt crisis and the World Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Mexican-debt-crisis-and-the-World-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Mexican-debt-crisis-and-the-World-Bank"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
Mexico, 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machines and tools]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52657</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/01/52657/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T05:52:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s International Workers Day, still celebrated as the May Day public holiday here in Queensland, at least when the Labor party is in office. So, it’s a good day for me to set out some tentative thoughts on work and its future. Via Matt McManus, I found this quote from Marx ‘Fragment on Machines”. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[no i don't drink coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://lili.bearblog.dev/no-i-dont-drink-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://lili.bearblog.dev/no-i-dont-drink-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T03:51:52.997Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I'm visiting Atlanta on a work trip with my coworkers.
In the morning we went out to a breakfast place, courtesy of our host. When the waitress took our orders, I watched as my coworkers and hosts each ordered a cup of coffee along with their food. During breakfast, they talked about how important coffee is to a scientific workplace.
At our institute, there is a single set of coffee machines on the top floor, set up to encourage interactions among scientists.
When scientists take social breaks, it's often coded as "coffee break". One scientist even wrote an opinion piece encouraging more socialization in science through coffee breaks.
The problem is that I don't drink coffee. Honestly, I barely take in caffeine. I used to drink black tea in the morning irregularly, then I tried …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container Runtime Interface streaming explained]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/01/cri-streaming-explained/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/01/cri-streaming-explained/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes Container Runtime Interface (CRI)
acts as the main connection between the kubelet
and the Container Runtime.
Those runtimes have to provide a gRPC server which has to
fulfill a Kubernetes defined Protocol Buffer interface.
This API definition
evolves over time, for example when contributors add new features or fields are
going to become deprecated.
In this blog post, I'd like to dive into the functionality and history of three
extraordinary Remote Procedure Calls (RPCs), which are truly outstanding in
terms of how they work: Exec, Attach and PortForward.
Exec can be used to run dedicated commands within the container and stream
the output to a client like kubectl or
crictl. It also allows interaction with
that process using standard input (stdin), for example if users want t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TheSmallWay.txt]]></title>
        <id>https://library.xandra.cc/the-small-way/</id>
        <link href="https://library.xandra.cc/the-small-way/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the Small Web for Connection
i might do things the hard way, according to some folks. on my personal website:
i don't use bootstrap or other frameworks, even though i know how to;
i'm not using SEO, even though i've studied it throughout my career and used it professionally;
i code things by hand in notepad, despite other code editors being easier and more efficient;
i use graphics from other places on the web as well as making my own, in order to participate in the sharing culture of the small web.
i didn't really set out to do this initially, but it turns out i'm using the practice of coding and creating webpages to meditate, be more intentional with my actions, and feel like i'm putting effort into sharing with others who i am, even if i'm not racking up likes, comments, or pa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add your Ruby gems to AWS CodeArtifact]]></title>
        <id>0775d12391b11338b1a7e4a6ec8ed43cde3d78ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/add-your-ruby-gems-to-aws-codeartifact/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T22:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby developers can now use AWS CodeArtifact to securely store and retrieve their gems. CodeArtifact integrates with standard developer tools like gem and bundler. Applications often use numerous packages to speed up development by providing reusable code for common tasks like network access, cryptography, or data manipulation. Developers also embed SDKs–such as the AWS SDKs–to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It is a mistake to think all mistakes have a silver lining]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7481</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mistake-think-mistakes-have-silver-lining/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media is awash with motivational quotes extolling the virtues of making mistakes. I probably glanced sideways at some quote or other on Instagram — like, five years ago — because now my search tab is full of the things. Daily I’m reminded that experience is simply the name we give our mistakes, or remember […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Text Embeddings V2 now available in Amazon Bedrock, optimized for improving RAG]]></title>
        <id>ccf9cb1edfcf2e819e0bac0a313a9025d5a63946</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-titan-text-v2-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock-optimized-for-improving-rag/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T20:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan foundation models (FMs) offer a comprehensive suite of pre-trained image, multimodal, and text models accessible through a fully managed API. They're designed for a range of applications while adhering to responsible AI practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The destruction of Argentina’s higher education and science system]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52654</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/30/the-destruction-of-argentinas-higher-education-and-science-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T19:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientific research, academic knowledge production, and higher education are under an obscene and direct attack today in Argentina. Milei’s attack is not an isolated case. To a certain extent, it is part of a global phenomenon, i.e. the rampant anti-intellectualism of the “new” right-wing movements and governments, which has certainly accelerated its spread with the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Macarena Marey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending April 28, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240430</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240430"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Business, now generally available, helps boost workforce productivity with generative AI]]></title>
        <id>4fbfa8a4b103697fdc4535c845ba79aa75c59031</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-business-now-generally-available-helps-boost-workforce-productivity-with-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Business is now available with many new features, including custom plugins, and a preview of Amazon Q Apps, generative AI–powered customized and sharable applications using natural language in a single step for your organization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer, now generally available, includes previews of new capabilities to reimagine developer experience]]></title>
        <id>61f7326bca5a32b68ab7d5d0e766ef742ab6f30e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-developer-now-generally-available-includes-new-capabilities-to-reimagine-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T12:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This generative AI–powered assistant helps developers build applications on AWS, research best practices, perform troubleshooting, and resolve errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharged Developer Portals]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7053</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/04/supercharged-developer-portals/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T09:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we announced Spotify’s latest products and services for companies adopting Backstage, the open source framework for building IDPs.
The post Supercharged Developer Portals appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Preventing unauthorized volume mode conversion moves to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/30/prevent-unauthorized-volume-mode-conversion-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/30/prevent-unauthorized-volume-mode-conversion-ga/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Kubernetes 1.30, the feature to prevent the modification of the volume mode
of a PersistentVolumeClaim that was created from
an existing VolumeSnapshot in a Kubernetes cluster, has moved to GA!
The problem
The Volume Mode of a PersistentVolumeClaim
refers to whether the underlying volume on the storage device is formatted into a filesystem or
presented as a raw block device to the Pod that uses it.
Users can leverage the VolumeSnapshot feature, which has been stable since Kubernetes v1.20,
to create a PersistentVolumeClaim (shortened as PVC) from an existing VolumeSnapshot in
the Kubernetes cluster. The PVC spec includes a dataSource field, which can point to an
existing VolumeSnapshot instance.
Visit Create a PersistentVolumeClaim from a Volume Snapshot
for more detail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extraterrestrials may arrive in 500 years, but not in flying saucers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7470</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/extraterrestrials-arrive-500-years-not-flying-saucers/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T21:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the late 1960’s, former United States President Jimmy Carter, reported seeing an Unidentified Flying Object (UFO). Today unexplained objects, or phenomena, seen in the skies, are referred to as Unidentified Anomalous Phenomenon (UAP). Carter, however, was not expecting to participate in any historic close encounter of the third kind: While puzzled by the object […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run scalable, enterprise-grade generative AI workloads with Cohere Command R & R+, now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>9791e9f8c9a7a599b65609f5477868e565fc3a6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/run-scalable-enterprise-grade-generative-ai-workloads-with-cohere-r-r-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T18:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In November 2023, we made two new Cohere models available in Amazon Bedrock (Cohere Command Light and Cohere Embed English). Today, we’re announcing the addition of two more Cohere models in Amazon Bedrock; Cohere Command R and Command R+. Organizations need generative artificial intelligence (generative AI) models to securely interact with information stored in their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Know, It’s Ok to Talk About It]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/you-know-its-ok-to-talk-about-it/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/you-know-its-ok-to-talk-about-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:52:51.383Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[{{ post_description }}
I thought that instead of typing up another rant, I'd do something a bit different. I want to share a little anecdote with you.
Around 20 years ago, I joined the British Army; right at the height of the Iraq and Afghan conflicts.
Yeah, I've never been the sharpest tool in the box.
Anyway, Iraq was shit. I lost a couple of friends, more were badly hurt, and I myself suffered a minor shrapnel wound.
It's fair to say that I saw shit out there that no-one should ever see. I finished my tour of Iraq and less than a year later I found myself in Afghanistan.
For me, Afghan was marginally better than Iraq. I won't go into detail as to why as that could reveal who I am, but suffice to say, it wasn't quite as shit as Iraq.
I got back from Afghan and I was fucked. Not physically though. Mentally. The Army might spin this yarn that they give their troops the help they need, but the fact of the matter is, if you went to the "Med Centre" claiming you were having mental health problems, you'd quickly become a laughing stock of the battalion.
You'd be labelled a pussy. A fanny. Not tough enough be a soldier.
Note: This might not be the case anymore. It's been a long time since I served, but that's what it was like then I was serving.
So I didn't get help, and it utterly fucked me. I was having nightmares. I was taking it out on my loved ones. I was all over the show.
Then my (now) wife convinced me to go see a professional to help me process some of this baggage.
I did, and it really helped. Actually, it was one of the best things I've ever done. Do I still have demons? Yes. Do I let them affect my life? For the most part, no.
So, my message to you is - whether you're a soldier, a police officer, a fire fighter, a janitor, an office worker, or anything else - if you have shit going on upstairs, don't let it fester. Go and see someone about it. Someone impartial, who can just listen and help you process that shit.
You can thank me later.
Peace. ✌️
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Upstox built NextGen trading platform using Amazon EKS, Karpenter, and spot instances]]></title>
        <id>deee4e5d917bc248aeaa698812bcfed749cb9381</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-upstox-built-nextgen-trading-platform-using-amazon-eks-karpenter-and-spot-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a guest post by Pranav Kapoor, Head of DevOps at Upstox co-authored with Jayesh Vartak, Solutions Architect at AWS and Jitendra Shihani, Technical Account Manager (TAM) at AWS. Upstox is India’s largest investech, a multi-unicorn valued at $3.5 billion. It allows you to buy and sell stocks, mutual funds, and derivatives, and is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranav Kapoor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Bedrock, AWS CodeBuild, Amazon CodeCatalyst, and more (April 29, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>646f6c7158c987ccad244324a7df5b137acafb74</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-bedrock-aws-codebuild-amazon-codecatalyst-and-more-april-29-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T15:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This was a busy week for Amazon Bedrock with many new features! Using GitHub Actions with AWS CodeBuild is much easier. Also, Amazon Q in Amazon CodeCatalyst can now manage more complex issues. I was amazed to meet so many new and old friends at the AWS Summit London. To give you a quick glimpse, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[De-risk releases with AWS CodePipeline rollbacks]]></title>
        <id>28260cddb3b9e9f8b6a318bec59783bad5c1256a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/de-risk-releases-with-aws-codepipeline-rollbacks/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s an established practice for development teams to build deployment pipelines, with services such as AWS CodePipeline, to increase the quality of application and infrastructure releases through reliable, repeatable and consistent automation. Automating the deployment process helps build quality into our products by introducing continuous integration to build and test code as early as possible, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Laver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q1 2024 Internet disruption summary]]></title>
        <id>662b80e17c0f59000a6a925a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/q1-2024-internet-disruption-summary"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first quarter of 2024 kicked off with quite a few Internet disruptions. Perhaps most interestingly, RPKI, DNS, and DNSSEC issues were among the technical problems that disrupted connectivity for subscribers across multiple network providers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do not comment on another website, when you can write on your own]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7457</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/do-not-comment-another-website-when-you-can-write-your-own/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T21:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The more things change, the more they stay the same, perhaps? Manuel Moreale writing the other week about blog post comments: I’m not a fan of comments in general and I think commenting on something should be done in one of two ways: 1. Privately via email or via direct messaging. 2. Publicly by posting […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Pézenas]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52650</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/28/sunday-photoblogging-pezenas-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T15:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India : popular movements, not elections, will bring transformative change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/India-popular-movements-not-elections-will-bring-transformative-change</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/India-popular-movements-not-elections-will-bring-transformative-change"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T08:38:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the exception of a brief period, India has been more fortunate than many other nations in being able to maintain parliamentary rule over the last 77 years. With 900 million voters—more than the populations of Europe and Australia put together—the Indian elections are hailed as the largest exhibition and celebration of democracy. The nation's economic growth over the past 30 years —one of the fastest in the world—also makes the elections noteworthy on a global scale. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
India, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sushovan Dhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Blogs Do We All Really Need?]]></title>
        <id>https://liesofd.bearblog.dev/how-many-blogs-do-we-all-really-need/</id>
        <link href="https://liesofd.bearblog.dev/how-many-blogs-do-we-all-really-need/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T05:03:55.038Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I was going over my RSS feeds list in Feedly. I've noticed that I barely see new posts now from bloggers I've been following. So I decided to check their blogs to see what they're up to. First one I checked shows that he has switched blogging platforms. Okay...
I checked out his new blogging platform and it is pretty neat. Beautiful design, nice layouts, makes me want to use it too. Checked it out some more and found that they have something like the Discover feed on Bearblog. Decided to click the first post on the list and it turns out to be from some other blogger that I follow. He's also on this new platform. What the heck is going on?!
And to think I gave Bearblog a try because I saw him blogging on here. Now he's packed up and moved on and left us all here.
Checked out the other blogs/bloggers on this new platform. There was one guy that had 4-5 active blogs, on different platforms it seems. Dude, how are you even maintaining all of those.
If you told me before that I would get FOMO from following blogs, I will tell you you're crazy. But what is this I'm feeling now? I feel like I can't keep up and that maybe I should try this other blogging platform too. Christ, I just started on this new blog months ago. I cannot keep up with all these other bloggers. I somewhat feel like I'm on Facebook again, except the newsfeed is filled with bloggers touting their new blogs. It makes me want to go offline.
How many blogs do we all really need? Apparently, the answer is not enough. It makes me wander what we are really trying to get out of blogging.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India: Modi and the rise of the billionaire Raj]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/India-Modi-and-the-rise-of-the-billionaire-Raj</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/India-Modi-and-the-rise-of-the-billionaire-Raj"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T09:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A general election in India starts today. 970m Indians, more than 10% of the world's population, will head to the polls in what will be the largest election in history for the Lok Sabha (House of the People) parliamentary elections. The poll will spread across India and take up to 4 June to complete. Opinion polls suggest that Prime Minister Narendra Modi, leader of the Hindu nationalist Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), and his coalition will win a third successive 5-year term, and win by (...)
English

/ 
India, 
Capitalism, 
Inequality]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Launching the Capital One Hub at UVA School of Data Science]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/085e3e050d14</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/launching-the-capital-one-hub-at-uva-school-of-data-science-085e3e050d14?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T18:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Capital One Hub will advance data science at UVA and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Isabella Trimboli: &ldquo;Resonances&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/resonances</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/resonances"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T17:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Carla Lonzi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The non-existence of economic laws]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45342</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/26/the-non-existence-of-economic-laws-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T16:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll In mainstream economics, there’s — still — a lot of talk about ‘economic laws.’ The crux of these laws — and regularities — that allegedly exist in economics, is that they only hold ceteris paribus. That fundamentally means that these laws/regularities only hold when the right conditions are at hand for giving rise […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build APIs using OpenAPI, the AWS CDK and AWS Solutions Constructs]]></title>
        <id>0125d7293c46e299397121afaad6b8d5ed7f517c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/build-apis-using-openapi-the-aws-cdk-and-aws-solutions-constructs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T13:49:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction APIs are the key to implementing microservices that are the building blocks of modern distributed applications. Launching a new API involves defining the behavior, implementing the business logic, and configuring the infrastructure to enforce the behavior and expose the business logic. Using OpenAPI, the AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK), and AWS Solutions Constructs […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Biff Gaut</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Lavery: &ldquo;Europe&#8217;s Core&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/europes-core</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/europes-core"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T09:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logics of integration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Meta on Culture Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52645</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/26/going-meta-on-culture-wars/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T09:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Culture wars have two main functions. First, to split an existing, dominant social or political coalition apart by the clever use of wedge-issues. (Not all wedge-issues are a part of a culture war.) So, a culture war reveals a latent or induces real divergence in a pre-existing coalition. So, for example, how to think about trans-issues […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Schliesser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Further thoughts on the economics of imperialism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Further-thoughts-on-the-economics-of-imperialism</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Further-thoughts-on-the-economics-of-imperialism"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T05:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2021, Guglielmo Carchedi and I published a paper in Historical Materialism called The Economics of Modern Imperialism. The paper focused exclusively on the economic aspects of imperialism. We defined that as the persistent and long-term net appropriation of surplus value by the high-technology advanced capitalist countries transferred from the low-technology dominated countries. We identified four channels by which surplus value flows to the imperialist countries: currency (...)
English

/ 
BRICS, 
Imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Multi-Webhook and Modular Authorization Made Much Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/26/multi-webhook-and-modular-authorization-made-much-easier/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/26/multi-webhook-and-modular-authorization-made-much-easier/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Kubernetes 1.30, we (SIG Auth) are moving Structured Authorization
Configuration to beta.
Today's article is about authorization: deciding what someone can and cannot
access. Check a previous article from yesterday to find about what's new in
Kubernetes v1.30 around authentication (finding out who's performing a task,
and checking that they are who they say they are).
Introduction
Kubernetes continues to evolve to meet the intricate requirements of system
administrators and developers alike. A critical aspect of Kubernetes that
ensures the security and integrity of the cluster is the API server
authorization. Until recently, the configuration of the authorization chain in
kube-apiserver was somewhat rigid, limited to a set of command-line flags and
allowing only a single webhook in th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has a book in them, but not every book has a reader]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7451</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/everyone-has-book-in-them-but-not-every-book-has-reader/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has a book in them, or so they say. It’s a pithy turn of phrase, one that’s possibly inspired the writing of a billion plus manuscripts. Slightly less inspiring though, is the revelation that ninety-six percent of books sell less than one thousand copies. Everyone has a book in them, but how many readers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Amazon EC2 Spot Instances with Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>0f65cb4e31baf551e75bb5e5e3aafe0fbc65b084</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-amazon-ec2-spot-instances-with-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T17:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog was updated by Irene Garcia Lopez, Solutions Architect, and Mehdi Yosofie, Solutions Architect, in April 2024 to reflect Karpenter beta changes. Overview Karpenter is a dynamic, high performance, open-source cluster autoscaling solution for the Kubernetes platform introduced at re:Invent 2021. Customers choose an autoscaling solution for a number of reasons, including improving the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Raja Ganesan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;Rules of the Game&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/rules-of-the-game</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/rules-of-the-game"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T12:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran versus Israel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Structured Authentication Configuration Moves to Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/25/structured-authentication-moves-to-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/25/structured-authentication-moves-to-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Kubernetes 1.30, we (SIG Auth) are moving Structured Authentication Configuration to beta.
Today's article is about authentication: finding out who's performing a task, and checking
that they are who they say they are. Check back in tomorrow to find about what's new in
Kubernetes v1.30 around authorization (deciding what someone can and can't access).
Motivation
Kubernetes has had a long-standing need for a more flexible and extensible
authentication system. The current system, while powerful, has some limitations
that make it difficult to use in certain scenarios. For example, it is not
possible to use multiple authenticators of the same type (e.g., multiple JWT
authenticators) or to change the configuration without restarting the API server. The
Structured Authentication Configurati…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More articles]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407957/0/themoneyillusion~More-articles/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407957/0/themoneyillusion~More-articles/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. Tyler linked to an interesting article on Portugal. This caught my eye: Then, in 2023, the Immigration Control Agency was dissolved, ostensibly in response to an extremely uncharacteristic display of violence where, in March 2020, two officers beat a Ukrainian man to death in the airport of Lisbon. No protests followed the unjust death [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/882407957/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/882407957/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-18-at-2.26.00-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/882407957/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/882407957/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/882407957/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comment-6819143">#5 seems like it is clearly a reflection of the stereotype of ...</a> <i>by derek</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comment-6817966">Can, I wonder if “flight to liquidity” is a better ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comment-6817930">Justin: Despite his career with statistics, Scott relies on an ...</a> <i>by art andreassen</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comment-6817608">I'm finally reading “The Money Illusion” the book and had a ...</a> <i>by Can</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comment-6816500">I thought this moron retired, no?   Nobody at Bentley ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/more-articles-2/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I don&#8217;t wanna be &#8220;rich&#8221;]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407960/0/themoneyillusion~I-dont-wanna-be-%e2%80%9crich%e2%80%9d/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407960/0/themoneyillusion~I-dont-wanna-be-%e2%80%9crich%e2%80%9d/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eventually, I&#8217;ll get to price indices. But first, a long boring digression on why I don&#8217;t want to be &#8220;rich&#8221; (but do want to have a billion dollars.) I recently read a WSJ story about how a $200 million St. Louis skyscraper had sold for only $4 million. That got me wondering what house prices [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/882407960/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/882407960/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-18-at-8.36.41-AM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/882407960/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/882407960/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/882407960/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comment-6817295">Jeff, Interesting article, but I don't buy the claim that ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comment-6817285">Interesting theory on decline of midwest cities using St. Louis ...</a> <i>by Jeff</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comment-6815142">David, I agree.   Tsergo, The mistake was not in buying the ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comment-6815118">Would you have made more money investing in stocks rather than ...</a> <i>by Tsergo Ri</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comment-6815040">Good article in the recent Economist on population changes ...</a> <i>by David S</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/i-dont-wanna-be-rich/#comments">Plus 3 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yes!  We have no core values]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407963/0/themoneyillusion~Yes-We-have-no-core-values/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/882407963/0/themoneyillusion~Yes-We-have-no-core-values/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T23:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans remind me of the old song &#8220;Yes, we have no bananas&#8221;. They really, really like to agree with the assertions in poll questions. Should pot be legalized? Yes!! Should people selling pot be executed? Yes? Should Roe v. Wade be reversed? Yes? Should abortion be banned? Yes! Should the corporate tax rate be raised? [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/882407963/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/882407963/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-24-at-4.44.00-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/882407963/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/882407963/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/882407963/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comment-6818792">You are inching closer to admitting the gravity of digital ...</a> <i>by Morgan Warstler</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comment-6816289">Trina, Good quote.</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comment-6815347">Apparently you agree with Masha Gessen. From Sam Harris Episode ...</a> <i>by Trina Halppe</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comment-6815144">“Considering the general public was against the Iraqi war, ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/yes-we-have-no-core-values/#comment-6815082">Considering the general public was against the Iraqi war, ...</a> <i>by Sara</i></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Discovering Generative AI on AWS]]></title>
        <id>4bf356a9759a6d15d6fdc1bb91138569ae9f37af</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T20:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative artificial intelligence (generative AI) is a type of AI used to generate content, including conversations, images, videos, and music. Generative AI can be used directly to build customer-facing features (a chatbot or an image generator), or it can serve as an underlying component in a more complex system. For example, it can generate embeddings […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genomics workflows, Part 6: cost prediction]]></title>
        <id>5341ba5a07a4dc54add94b35bc7bbfe29a35740e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/part-6-genomics-workflows-cost-prediction/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T16:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genomics workflows run on large pools of compute resources and take petabyte-scale datasets as inputs. Workflow runs can cost as much as hundreds of thousands of US dollars. Given this large scale, scientists want to estimate the projected cost of their genomics workflow runs before deciding to launch them. In Part 6 of this series, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rostislav Markov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM Denounces the Lack of Action on Climate Change and the Neoliberal Approach of the Bretton Woods Institutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-Denounces-the-Lack-of-Action-on-Climate-Change-and-the-Neoliberal</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-Denounces-the-Lack-of-Action-on-Climate-Change-and-the-Neoliberal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T14:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spring Meetings of the IMF and World Bank ended on Saturday 20 April 2024. As expected, there were no changes to the neoliberal policies promoted and imposed by the Bretton Woods institutions. A demonstration was held in front of the headquarters of the two institutions, and the present call to put an end to austerity policies was delivered. 
Press releases

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“The Olympic flame, a wonderful idea from Dr. Goebbels”!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Olympic-flame-a-wonderful-idea-from-Dr-Goebbels</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Olympic-flame-a-wonderful-idea-from-Dr-Goebbels"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T09:32:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overflowing with national pride, the Greek media, seconded by the country's grandiloquent authorities, don't miss the opportunity to present this veritable re-enactment of a Nazi ceremony, namely the so-called “Olympic flame lighting ceremony” in Olympia... as proof of the greatness and historical continuity of the Greek nation. And with it, to present its accessories too, such as “the first Olympic torch” which, as we read, was handed over to the mayor of Marathon, “in a magnificent ceremony (...)
English

/ 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank saw the debt crisis looming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-saw-the-debt-crisis-looming</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-saw-the-debt-crisis-looming"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Validating Admission Policy Is Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/24/validating-admission-policy-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/24/validating-admission-policy-ga/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On behalf of the Kubernetes project, I am excited to announce that ValidatingAdmissionPolicy has reached
general availability
as part of Kubernetes 1.30 release. If you have not yet read about this new declarative alternative to
validating admission webhooks, it may be interesting to read our
previous post about the new feature.
If you have already heard about ValidatingAdmissionPolicies and you are eager to try them out,
there is no better time to do it than now.
Let's have a taste of a ValidatingAdmissionPolicy, by replacing a simple webhook.
Example admission webhook
First, let's take a look at an example of a simple webhook. Here is an excerpt from a webhook that
enforces runAsNonRoot, readOnlyRootFilesystem, allowPrivilegeEscalation, and privileged to be set to the least permissive va…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending April 21, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240423</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240423"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from building an automated SDK pipeline]]></title>
        <id>66277eb37c0f59000a6a8dfa</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/lessons-from-building-an-automated-sdk-pipeline"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During Developer Week 2024, we announced the revamped SDKs that are automatically generated using our OpenAPI schemas. Today, we’re taking a deeper look at how the pipeline works and share lessons we’ve learned along the way]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Bednarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Llama 3 models are now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>f95adfe97ec5996905b98d693588b5d607ececfd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/metas-llama-3-models-are-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The instruction-tuned large language models have been pre-trained on over 15 trillion tokens of data—a training dataset seven times larger than that used for Llama 2 models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock now available with new safety filters and privacy controls]]></title>
        <id>4c0f2591932fcda01bb3e6c08523ac0726981cc3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/guardrails-for-amazon-bedrock-now-available-with-new-safety-filters-and-privacy-controls/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock, you can implement safeguards in your generative artificial intelligence applications that are customized to your use cases and responsible AI policies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock: Introducing a simplified creation and configuration experience]]></title>
        <id>180a9a30a03c4d19eb46cdde6bc2c05f64830fc8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/agents-for-amazon-bedrock-introducing-a-simplified-creation-and-configuration-experience/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Agents for Amazon Bedrock, applications can use generative artificial intelligence (generative AI) to run tasks across multiple systems and data sources. Starting today, these new capabilities streamline the creation and management of agents: Quick agent creation – You can now quickly create an agent and optionally add instructions and action groups later, providing flexibility […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock model evaluation is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>4efd0cbd0640b3c92182260a34c2fa5cbf691076</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-bedrock-model-evaluation-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new capability helps you to incorporate generative AI into your application by letting you select the foundation model that gives you the best results for your particular use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Import custom models in Amazon Bedrock (preview)]]></title>
        <id>9b3467e3b47c60f7e737180a4bb3eea62b609e10</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/import-custom-models-in-amazon-bedrock-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon Bedrock, you have access to a choice of high-performing foundation models (FMs) from leading artificial intelligence (AI) companies that make it easier to build and scale generative AI applications. Some of these models provide publicly available weights that can be fine-tuned and customized for specific use cases. However, deploying customized FMs in a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Image Generator and watermark detection API are now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>bce2b6392c224fa0474554ef68cf029b2525a220</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-titan-image-generator-and-watermark-detection-api-are-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:25:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All images generated by Titan Image Generator contain an invisible watermark to help reduce the spread of misinformation by providing a mechanism to identify AI-generated images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Read-only volume mounts can be finally literally read-only]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/23/recursive-read-only-mounts/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/23/recursive-read-only-mounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read-only volume mounts have been a feature of Kubernetes since the beginning.
Surprisingly, read-only mounts are not completely read-only under certain conditions on Linux.
As of the v1.30 release, they can be made completely read-only,
with alpha support for recursive read-only mounts.
Read-only volume mounts are not really read-only by default
Volume mounts can be deceptively complicated.
You might expect that the following manifest makes everything under /mnt in the containers read-only:
---
apiVersion: v1
kind: Pod
spec:
 volumes:
 - name: mnt
 hostPath:
 path: /mnt
 containers:
 - volumeMounts:
 - name: mnt
 mountPath: /mnt
 readOnly: true


However, any sub-mounts beneath /mnt may still be writable!
For example, consider that /mnt/my-nfs-server is writeable on the host.
Inside the c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unify DNS management using Amazon Route 53 Profiles with multiple VPCs and AWS accounts]]></title>
        <id>75632917a9827f42f888158e1c5fcff0d8f243c2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/unify-dns-management-using-amazon-route-53-profiles-with-multiple-vpcs-and-aws-accounts/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T21:08:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are managing lots of accounts and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) resources, sharing and then associating many DNS resources to each VPC can present a significant burden. You often hit limits around sharing and association, and you may have gone as far as building your own orchestration layers to propagate DNS configuration […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Anthropic’s Claude 3 Opus in Amazon Bedrock, Meta Llama 3 in Amazon SageMaker JumpStart, and more (April 22, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>2d82454837371065ef760d6f4a06cdd3d0a7ea75</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-anthropics-claude-3-opus-in-amazon-bedrock-meta-llama-3-in-amazon-sagemaker-jumpstart-and-more-april-22-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T17:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summits continue to rock the world, with events taking place in various locations around the globe. AWS Summit London (April 24) is the last one in April, and there are nine more in May, including AWS Summit Berlin (May 15–16), AWS Summit Los Angeles (May 22), and AWS Summit Dubai (May 29). Join us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In search of radical alternatives]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45339</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/22/in-search-of-radical-alternatives/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T17:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Crelis Rammelt and current issue of RWER Our presumed dominion over nature is an illusion. No matter how clever technological innovations may seem, they remain subject to the laws of thermodynamics. Consequently, a growth-centered capitalist economy finds itself trapped in futile attempts to completely decouple itself from nature – aiming for a 100% circular, service-oriented and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.30: Beta Support For Pods With User Namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/22/userns-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/22/userns-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux provides different namespaces to isolate processes from each other. For
example, a typical Kubernetes pod runs within a network namespace to isolate the
network identity and a PID namespace to isolate the processes.
One Linux namespace that was left behind is the user
namespace. This
namespace allows us to isolate the user and group identifiers (UIDs and GIDs) we
use inside the container from the ones on the host.
This is a powerful abstraction that allows us to run containers as "root": we
are root inside the container and can do everything root can inside the pod,
but our interactions with the host are limited to what a non-privileged user can
do. This is great for limiting the impact of a container breakout.
A container breakout is when a process inside a container can break out
o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the BRICS and their New Development Bank offering alternatives to the World Bank, the IMF and the policies promoted by the traditional imperialist powers?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Are-the-BRICS-and-their-New-Development-Bank-offering-alternatives-to-the-World</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Are-the-BRICS-and-their-New-Development-Bank-offering-alternatives-to-the-World"/>
        <updated>2024-04-21T12:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, the rightful rejection of the policies promoted by the traditional imperialist powers (North America, Western Europe and Japan), followed by the announcements made by the BRICS (Brazil, Russia, India, China and South Africa), have aroused great interest and expectations of major changes, including the creation of a common currency to challenge the US dollar as the dominant currency. But what has actually happened? What has been achieved by the New Development Bank and the (...)
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Banks, 
BRICS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: crossroads]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52639</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/21/sunday-photoblogging-crossroads/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-21T05:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About Me]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/about-me/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/about-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-20T19:03:27.073Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You clicked at least 2 links with the desire to know me better to get here. I am flattered. So here is the spiel.
I was born and raised in Delhi, India. I have always had this sense of wonder about the world. I grew up reading a lot. Mostly fiction. Hard SciFi, High Fantasy, you get the idea. I was good at academics and my parents kinda lemme do whatever I wanted. Ever since I was 10 I had my own room ,no oversight and an internet connection(yeah ik could have been a disaster). I discovered so much. From the VlogBrothers to Richard Feynman. Changed so much. For the better. Mostly.
I recently graduated with a CS degree. It was challenging and fun tbh. Mostly cuz of the absolutely cracked people I met here and a few passionate profs. These days I write firmware for enterprise servers. Servers you definitely have interacted with unless you live under a rock(how are you reading this then?).
This blog is just me. I decided to put myself out there more. Share my honest thoughts and opinions. Who knows maybe I will say something profound that changes someones life? If not at least a part of my consciousness will be in the future AGI training dataset. Not bad eh?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Online talks]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52629</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/20/online-talks/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-20T01:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been doing a bunch of talks and events online, mostly not CT related, but a couple that might be interesting to readers. One that certainly is is this conversation with Francis Spufford, which is a coda to Red Plenty. Some of my bits of the conversation build on this Long Now talk from a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expertise and naval power]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52627</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/20/expertise-and-naval-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-20T00:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert Farley has replied to my recent post on the obsolescence of naval power. Unlike our previous exchange, a pile-on where I was (as he points out) in a minority of one, Robert’s tone is mostly civil this time, and I intend to reciprocate. Our disagreements have narrowed a fair way. On many points, it’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quickly go from Idea to PR with CodeCatalyst using Amazon Q]]></title>
        <id>648c07be1d442126da52ebb69ccb250845e66ddc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/quickly-go-from-idea-to-pr-with-codecatalyst-using-amazon-q/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T18:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q feature development enables teams using Amazon CodeCatalyst to scale with AI to assist developers in completing everyday software development tasks. Developers can now go from an idea in an issue to a fully tested, merge-ready, running application code in a Pull Request (PR) with natural language inputs in a few clicks. Developers can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matt Schierz: &ldquo;Gaining Ground&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaining-ground</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaining-ground"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T17:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in South Korea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying Generative AI to CVE remediation – early vulnerability patching in Continuous Integration Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>da6c0a2e28bb41c458599e8b0fcafa8e609496aa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/applying-generative-ai-to-cve-remediation-early-vulnerability-patching-in-continuous-integration-pipelines/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T16:25:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud technologies are a rapidly evolving landscape. Securing cloud applications is everyone’s responsibility, meaning application development teams are needed to follow strict security guidelines from the earliest development stages, and to make sure of continuous security scans throughout the whole application lifecycle. The rise of generative AI enables new innovative approaches for addressing longstanding challenges with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Soriano Alves Duarte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the internet became shit]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-the-internet-became-shit/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-the-internet-became-shit/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T14:01:32.424Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently replaced the battery on my iPhone 8 (it's the perfect smartphone; fight me) in an attempt to prolong its life by a few more years. However, the iStore service centre required that the phone be wiped to comply with the POPIA act prior to any kind of service work commencing. This was annoying, but being a thin client with good backup hygiene it was just inconvenient and not a major issue.
Once I had my phone back up and running with all my apps re-installed I found myself browsing Hacker News and followed a link to an article on one of the bigger news sites. And there were ads EVERYWHERE. I'd forgotten to re-install my adblocker.
Having not been on the internet without an adblocker in over 10 years, this was eye-opening. It was literally impossible for me to read the article due t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federico Perelmuter: &ldquo;In the Basement&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-the-basement</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/in-the-basement"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Osvaldo Lamborghini’s literary revolt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cutting-edge macroeconomics …]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45337</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/19/cutting-edge-macroeconomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll No sooner had I finished my comment on the irrelevancy of economics but I had confirmation — albeit unwittingly — in this morning’s Financial Times.  There on the editorial page was a short column by Soumaya Keynes talking about the rise of Hank. For those of you not on the cutting edge, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rippling’s journey migrating to the new VPC CNI Network Policy Engine]]></title>
        <id>aab29ee572c302768f346f709423642206cc67a4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/ripplings-journey-migrating-to-the-new-vpc-cni-network-policy-engine/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T04:50:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was coauthored by Venkatesh Nannan, Sr. Engineering Manager at Rippling Introduction Rippling is a workforce management system that eliminates the friction of running a business, combining HR, IT, and Finance apps on a unified data platform. Rippling’s mission is to free up intelligent people to work on hard problems. Existing Stack Rippling uses […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashok Srirama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Llama 3 available on Cloudflare Workers AI]]></title>
        <id>6621846827e210000ab2a303</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/meta-llama-3-available-on-cloudflare-workers-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T20:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to give developers around the world the ability to build AI applications with Meta Llama 3 using Workers AI. We are proud to be a launch partner with Meta for their newest 8B Llama 3 model]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michelle Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare named in 2024 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Security Service Edge]]></title>
        <id>6620c18227e210000ab29f16</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-sse-gartner-magic-quadrant-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T14:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gartner has once again named Cloudflare to the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Security Service Edge (SSE) report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Olly Haynes: &ldquo;First Priorities&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/first-priorities</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/first-priorities"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T14:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paths for the French left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Built Slack AI To Be Secure and Private]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16574</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/how-we-built-slack-ai-to-be-secure-and-private/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T05:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Slack, we’ve long been conservative technologists. In other words, when we invest in leveraging a new category of infrastructure, we do it rigorously. We’ve done this since we debuted machine learning-powered features in 2016, and we’ve developed a robust process and skilled team in the space. Despite that, over the past year we’ve been […]
The post How We Built Slack AI To Be Secure and Private appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kelly Moran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wenar on why you shouldn’t try to help poor people]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52621</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/17/wenar-on-why-you-shouldnt-try-to-help-poor-people/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T22:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In all the discussion of Leif Wenar’s critique of Effective Altruism , I haven’t seen much mention of the central premise: that development aid is generally counterproductive (unless, perhaps, it’s delivered by wealthy surfers in their spare time). Wenar is quite clear that his argument applies just as much to official development aid and to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamically create repositories upon image push to Amazon ECR]]></title>
        <id>6fc0557e15ad361fb4e9e29b287e0bcafed78eaf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/dynamically-create-repositories-upon-image-push-to-amazon-ecr/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T19:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Container Registry (Amazon ECR) provides a fully managed container registry service, offering high-performance hosting for reliably deploying application images anywhere. Amazon ECR service requires repositories to pre-exist before pushing container images. In this post, we explore a dynamic solution that leverages AWS CloudTrail, Amazon EventBridge, and AWS Lambda functions to automatically create Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Madhu Neelaiahgari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The eclipse part wo]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45330</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/17/the-eclipse-part-wo/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T15:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford What are we to say of a discipline that steadfastly ignores reality in its pursuit of ever more formality in its methods? Wow. Steve Levitt has really shaken me. I come not to mock, but to follow up … Stand up and take a bow Ben Moll!  You daring soul. Clearly I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending April 14, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240417</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240417"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T14:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Academic Freedom, State Legislatures and Public Universities (Wisconsin edition).]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52615</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/17/52615/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gina’s post on Indiana’s DEI-related law came at a fortuitous time for me, because last week I participated in a panel about State Legislatures, Academic Freedom and Public Universities. The panelists were given about 6 minutes to present some prepared remarks’ and discussion ensued. As far as I could tell there was just one state […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cloudflare Cloud Email Security protects against the evolving threat of QR phishing]]></title>
        <id>661e652327e210000ab299b4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-cloud-email-security-protects-against-the-evolving-threat-of-qr-phishing"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about how Cloudflare's Cloud Email Security tackles QR phishing, why attackers favor QR codes, and Cloudflare's proactive defense strategy against evolving threats]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Pang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Fed Consumer Credit Panel: A Foundational CMD Data Set]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29259</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/the-new-york-fed-consumer-credit-panel-a-foundational-cmd-data-set/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Great Financial Crisis and associated recession were unfolding in 2009, researchers at the New York Fed joined colleagues at the Board of Governors and Philadelphia Fed to create a new kind of data set. Household liabilities, particularly mortgages, had gone from being a quiet little corner of the financial system to the center of the worst financial crisis and sharpest recession in decades. The new data set was designed to provide fresh insights into this part of the economy, especially the behavior of mortgage borrowers. In the fifteen years since that effort came to fruition, the New York Fed Consumer Credit Panel (CCP) has provided many valuable insights into household behavior and its implications for the macro economy and financial stability. 
The CCP was one of the first data sets drawn from credit bureau data, one of the earliest features of the Center for Microeconomic Data (CMD), and the primary source material for some of the CMD’s most important contributions to policy and research. Here we review a few of the main household debt themes over the past fifteen years, and how our analyses contributed to their understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle Scally, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crooked Timberish books and other writings]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52612</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/17/crooked-timberish-books-and-other-writings/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T07:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m sure Crooked Timber readers would been keen to learn of exciting new books out just now from Daniel Davies and Kieran Healy. Marion Fourcade and Kieran Healy have published The Ordinal Society , arguing that “argue that technologies of information management, fueled by the abundance of personal data and the infrastructure of the internet, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.30: Uwubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/17/kubernetes-v1-30-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/17/kubernetes-v1-30-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editors: Amit Dsouza, Frederick Kautz, Kristin Martin, Abigail McCarthy, Natali Vlatko
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.30: Uwubernetes, the cutest release!
Similar to previous releases, the release of Kubernetes v1.30 introduces new stable, beta, and alpha
features. The consistent delivery of top-notch releases underscores the strength of our development
cycle and the vibrant support from our community.
This release consists of 45 enhancements. Of those enhancements, 17 have graduated to Stable, 18 are
entering Beta, and 10 have graduated to Alpha.
Release theme and logo
Kubernetes v1.30: Uwubernetes
Kubernetes v1.30 makes your clusters cuter!
Kubernetes is built and released by thousands of people from all over the world and all walks of
life. Most contributors are not being paid …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudWatch Internet Weather Map – View and analyze internet health]]></title>
        <id>53cc82790d2ebf7528517c5f1c4e151b7b1218da</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudwatch-internet-weather-map-view-and-analyze-internet-health/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T23:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet has a plethora of moving parts: routers, switches, hubs, terrestrial and submarine cables, and connectors on the hardware side, and complex protocol stacks and configurations on the software side. When something goes wrong that slows or disrupts the Internet in a way that affects your customers, you want to be able to localize […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The hawkish case]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407241/0/themoneyillusion~The-hawkish-case/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407241/0/themoneyillusion~The-hawkish-case/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T14:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future course of the economy always involves a bit of guesswork. But it seems to me that the following two claims are pretty likely to be true: 1. Over the past three years, monetary policy has been far too expansionary. 2. It is likely that monetary policy is still a bit too expansionary, although [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/881407241/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/881407241/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-16-at-9.30.19-AM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/881407241/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/881407241/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/881407241/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comment-6815304">Thomas, GDP growth was 4.7% in Q1, that's still too strong. ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comment-6815268">The yield curve inversion first appeared in Jul22, and I’ve ...</a> <i>by Thomas Novak</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comment-6813826">Harding, So the fact that Trump often says pro-Putin things and ...</a> <i>by Scott Sumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comment-6813760">“Republican fans of Putin don’t seem to understand that he ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comment-6813541">By: Michael Sandifer		</a> <i>by Michael Sandifer <a href="http://www.exactmacro.substack.com">http://www.exactmacro.substack.com</a></i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-hawkish-case/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is African politics inferior to American politics?]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407244/0/themoneyillusion~Is-African-politics-inferior-to-American-politics/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407244/0/themoneyillusion~Is-African-politics-inferior-to-American-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T14:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Financial Times has a story that points to some disturbing features of South African politics: It is the kind of fervent devotion that has driven a wave of support for the former president [Jacob Zuma] ahead of a critical general election on May 29. Yet as recently as January, the 82-year-old African National Congress [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/881407244/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/881407244/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/881407244/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/881407244/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/881407244/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comment-6812451">the circumstances have changed, the past is a different ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comment-6812237">Viennacapitalist, For most of my life, the US political system ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comment-6812192">Scott,   got it, but I was uncertain of what exactly you are ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comment-6811685">Viennacapitalist. I'm stunned that people think this post is ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comment-6811497">Scott,   “…Perhaps Africans cannot handle democracy?..” ...</a> <i>by viennacapitalist</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/is-african-politics-inferior-to-american-politics/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven!  (Trump is on a roll)]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407247/0/themoneyillusion~Seven-Trump-is-on-a-roll/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/881407247/0/themoneyillusion~Seven-Trump-is-on-a-roll/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T14:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent post, I listed 6 ways that Trump intends to reduce inflation: Trump has a 6-part plan to bring down inflation: 1. Favors&#160;NIMBY policies&#160;to prevent housing construction in the suburbs. 2. Expel all the illegal workers that pick our food and provide other key services. 3. Put heavy tariffs on imported food and [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/881407247/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/881407247/themoneyillusion,"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/881407247/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/881407247/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/881407247/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comment-6811688">“pro liberty politician in Bolsonaro”   Liberty? The guy ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comment-6811466">The only person being exposed as a “moron” is you.   You're ...</a> <i>by Sara</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comment-6810674">And for the record… the exchange between Longstreet (and ...</a> <i>by Student</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comment-6810588">Michael,   If Biden were up 3-5 points in the polling averages, ...</a> <i>by Student</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comment-6810581">>What do the people in the audience think   They think a Trump ...</a> <i>by foosion</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/seven-trump-is-on-a-roll/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3 Opus model is now available on Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>fdd6785a94c9a9a811184ccfce887e43d73ef200</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-opus-model-on-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T14:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are living in the generative artificial intelligence (AI) era; a time of rapid innovation. When Anthropic announced its Claude 3 foundation models (FMs) on March 4, we made Claude 3 Sonnet, a model balanced between skills and speed, available on Amazon Bedrock the same day. On March 13, we launched the Claude 3 Haiku […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoS threat report for 2024 Q1]]></title>
        <id>661e462727e210000ab298ff</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2024-q1"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 started with a bang. Cloudflare’s autonomous systems mitigated over 4.5 million DDoS attacks in the first quarter of the year — a 50% increase compared to the previous year. 
Read the full coverage]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Yoachimik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Survey of Consumer Expectations: A Look Back at the Past Decade]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29150</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/the-survey-of-consumer-expectations-a-look-back-at-the-past-decade/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a little over ten years since we started releasing findings from the Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s Survey of Consumer Expectations (SCE). In this post, we review some of the headline findings from the first decade of the survey’s history, highlighting the evolution of consumers’ expectations about inflation and labor market outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivier Armantier, Gizem Koşar, Giorgio Topa, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chang’s “Edible Economics”]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45324</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/15/changs-edible-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T20:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Junaid Jahangir and current issue of RWER [Ha-Joon] Chang’s latest book Edible Economics (2022) crystallizes the narrative that he has developed through his popular books over the years. . . . I have reviewed the salient ideas as follows in a bid to draw out lessons I could share with my ECON 101 students. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the PartyRock generative AI hackathon winners]]></title>
        <id>66f7500aa15dc6083b08a0dc3ae5aae8291ef5d9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/congratulations-to-the-partyrock-generative-ai-hackathon-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T18:22:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PartyRock Generative AI Hackathon wrapped up earlier this month. Entrants were asked to use PartyRock to build a functional app based on one of four challenge categories, with the option to remix an existing app as well. The hackathon attracted 7,650 registrants who submitted over 1,200 projects, and published over 250 project blog posts […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I joined Cloudflare as Chief Partner Officer]]></title>
        <id>66192d5fa5fcdf000a091f4b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/tom-evans-chief-partnership-officer"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T16:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Evans is joining Cloudflare as our first ever Chief Partner Officer, continuing a great career in scaling channel partner programs in the tech sector. Read more about why he’s excited about his new role in this blog post]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can I Speak to Your Supervisor? The Importance of Bank Supervision]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28767</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/can-i-speak-to-your-supervisor-the-importance-of-bank-supervision/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In March of 2023, the U.S. banking industry experienced a period of significant turmoil involving runs on several banks and heightened concerns about contagion. While many factors contributed to these events—including poor risk management, lapses in firm governance, outsized exposures to interest rate risk, and unrecognized vulnerabilities from interconnected depositor bases, the role of bank supervisors came under particular scrutiny. Questions were raised about why supervisors did not intervene more forcefully before problems arose. In response, supervisory agencies, including the Federal Reserve and Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, commissioned reviews that examined how supervisors’ actions might have contributed to, or mitigated, the failures. The reviews highlighted the important role that bank supervisors can play in fostering a stable banking system. In this post, we draw on our recent paper providing a critical review and summary of the empirical and theoretical literature on bank supervision to highlight what that literature tells us about the impact of supervision on supervised banks, on the banking industry and on the broader economy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beverly Hirtle and Anna Kovner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code Day 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/04/15/vscode-day</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/04/15/vscode-day"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Internet traffic analysis during Iran's April 13, 2024, attack on Israel]]></title>
        <id>661c44d3115505000a3f608a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/internet-traffic-analysis-iran-israel-april-attack"/>
        <updated>2024-04-14T21:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 13, 2024, Iran launched a retaliatory attack on Israel. We examined its potential impact on Internet traffic and attacks. While there were some shifts in traffic, we haven't observed any large-scale cyberattacks on Israeli domains protected by Cloudflare.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Canal Saint-Martin, Paris (3)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52608</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/14/sunday-photoblogging-canal-saint-martin-paris-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-14T07:38:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Limitarianism update]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52544</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/13/limitarianism-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T14:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since my book Limitarianism: The Case Against Extreme Wealth came out, first in Dutch at the end of November, and then in the US and in the UK a few weeks later, I’ve given more than 60 media interviews and talks. Among them was a long interview in The Observer, a summary of the argument […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using OPA to validate Amazon EKS Blueprint Templates]]></title>
        <id>eabeffc7f9c1f847b229f17e45fddc0e5f7db70b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/using-opa-to-validate-amazon-eks-blueprint-templates/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T23:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As organizations adopt containerization technologies, such as Kubernetes, the challenge of making sure of security and compliance becomes increasingly complex. With Kubernetes environments that span Infrastructure-as-Code (IaC) and Kubernetes clusters, maintaining a secure posture can be a daunting task. To tackle this complexity and reduce risk, many teams are turning to standardized tooling. Organizations that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Mattoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chicago economics — nothing but pseudo-scientific cheating]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45316</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/12/chicago-economics-nothing-but-pseudo-scientific-cheating/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T20:15:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll Unlike anthropologists … economists simply invent the primitive societies we study, a practice which frees us from limiting ourselves to societies which can be physically visited as sparing us the discomforts of long stays among savages. This method of society-invention is the source of the utopian character of economics; and of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huda Awan: &ldquo;Possibilities&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/possibilities</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/possibilities"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T16:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Susan Taubes and form.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Frédéric Lordon: &ldquo;End of Innocence&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/end-of-innocence</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/end-of-innocence"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gaza and fantasy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving authoritative DNS with the official release of Foundation DNS]]></title>
        <id>66126c36a5fcdf000a090ccf</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/foundation-dns-launch"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are launching Foundation DNS – our new enterprise-grade authoritative DNS offering. As our new enterprise authoritative DNS offering, Foundation DNS was designed to enhance the reliability, security, flexibility, and analytics of our authoritative DNS service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hannes Gerhart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we ensure Cloudflare customers aren't affected by Let's Encrypt's certificate chain change]]></title>
        <id>661847dda5fcdf000a091ee1</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/shortening-lets-encrypt-change-of-trust-no-impact-to-cloudflare-customers"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Encrypt’s cross-signed chain will be expiring in September. This will affect legacy devices with outdated trust stores (Android versions 7.1.1 or older). To prevent this change from impacting customers, Cloudflare will shift Let’s Encrypt certificates upon renewal to use a different CA]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The making of Icehenge]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52584</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/04/12/the-making-of-icehenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, I received an email asking if I would write an introductory essay for the Tor Essentials reissue of Kim Stanley Robinson’s novel Icehenge. It took me approximately thirty seconds to convince myself that this was not some kind of hallucination, and another three or four to type YES! OF COURSE!!! and hit reply. It […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Anatomy of Export Controls]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29122</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/the-anatomy-of-export-controls/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments increasingly use export controls to limit the spread of domestic cutting-edge technologies to other countries. The sectors that are currently involved in this geopolitical race include semiconductors, telecommunications, and artificial intelligence. Despite their growing adoption, little is known about the effect of export controls on supply chains and the productive sector at large. Do export controls induce a selective decoupling of the targeted goods and sectors? How do global customer-supplier relations react to export controls? What are their effects on the productive sector? In this post, which is based on a related staff report, we analyze the supply chain reconfiguration and associated financial and real effects following the imposition of export controls by the U.S. government.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Crosignani, Lina Han, Marco Macchiavelli, and André F. Silva</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joshua Rahtz: &ldquo;Hand and Mind&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hand-and-mind</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hand-and-mind"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T19:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rothko at the Fondation Louis Vuitton.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building new custom silicon for Meta’s AI workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21183</id>
        <link href="https://www.metacareers.com/life/building-custom-silicon-for-the-future-of-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T16:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]
Read More...
The post Building new custom silicon for Meta’s AI workloads appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an infrastructure for AI’s future]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21103</id>
        <link href="https://www.metacareers.com/life/behind-gen-ai-building-an-infrastructure-for-the-future"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T16:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]
Read More...
The post Building an infrastructure for AI’s future appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One & USC Partner to Drive Responsible AI (CREDIF)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cb1e80b00d26</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-one-usc-partner-to-drive-responsible-ai-credif-cb1e80b00d26?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T14:22:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One & USC launch the Center for Responsible AI and Decision Making in Finance (CREDIF) to advance the future of AI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The increasing collusion between . . . . . .]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45311</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/11/the-increasing-collusion-between/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from a comment by Ikonoclast “A truth is permitted only a brief victory celebration between the two long periods where it is first condemned as paradoxical and later disparaged as trivial.” – Arthur Schopenhauer. As they break new ground, the Capital as Power theoreticians will encounter the “Schopenhauer Effect” over and over. When you point […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetary Policy and Money Market Funds in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28848</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/monetary-policy-and-money-market-funds-in-europe/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As shown in a past Liberty Street Economics post, in the United States, the yields of money market fund (MMF) shares respond to changes in monetary policy rates much more than the rates of bank deposits; in other words, the MMF beta is much higher than the deposit beta. Consistent with this, the size of the U.S. MMF industry fluctuates over the interest rate cycle, expanding during times of monetary policy tightening. In this post, we show that the relationship between the policy rates of the European Central Bank (ECB) and the size of European MMFs investing in euro-denominated securities is also positive—as long as policy rates are positive; after the ECB introduced negative policy rates in 2015, that relationship broke down, as MMFs received large inflows during this period.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Cipriani, Daniel Fricke, Stefan Greppmair, Gabriele La Spada, and Karol Paludkiewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Architecture: Code Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/11/sig-architecture-code-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/04/11/sig-architecture-code-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third interview of a SIG Architecture Spotlight series that will cover the different
subprojects. We will cover SIG Architecture: Code Organization.
In this SIG Architecture spotlight I talked with Madhav Jivrajani
(VMware), a member of the Code Organization subproject.
Introducing the Code Organization subproject
Frederico (FSM): Hello Madhav, thank you for your availability. Could you start by telling us a
bit about yourself, your role and how you got involved in Kubernetes?
Madhav Jivrajani (MJ): Hello! My name is Madhav Jivrajani, I serve as a technical lead for SIG
Contributor Experience and a GitHub Admin for the Kubernetes project. Apart from that I also
contribute to SIG API Machinery and SIG Etcd, but more recently, I’ve been helping out with the work
that is needed to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-04-10-github-availability-report-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-04-10-github-availability-report-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T20:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In March, we experienced two incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services. </p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-04-10-github-availability-report-march-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: March 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Snap Inc. secures its services with Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>62e68358fd3ac058abd5310ee101c0e417b5f63b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-snap-inc-secures-its-services-with-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T17:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Snapchat is an app that hundreds of millions of people around the world use to communicate with their close friends. The app is powered by microservice architectures deployed in Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) and datastores such as Amazon CloudFront, Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3), Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon ElastiCache. This post […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shrikant Pandhare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Storage using OpenEBS on EKS Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>4667e1b8928db4acd8948adb78e5c2a49bfdeefd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/adding-storage-using-openebs-on-eks-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T17:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Amazon EKS Anywhere (EKS Anywhere) is an opinionated and automated deployment of the Amazon EKS Distro that enables users to create and operate Kubernetes clusters on user-managed infrastructure. EKS Anywhere does not include a Container Storage Interface (CSI) driver for persistence. In this post, we setup OpenEBS to provide persistence using the disks available in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Krueger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wealth catapulted up]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45300</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/10/wealth-catapulted-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T16:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Blair Fix and current issue of RWER Speaking of competition and losers, Ronald Reagan set the tone of the neoliberal era when, in 1981, he fired 11,000 striking air-traffic controllers (Houlihan, 2021). The message? Workers were losers who would be subjected to the discipline of competition. Reagan called it ‘morning in America’. But really, it was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending April 07, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240410</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240410"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the next-gen Meta Training and Inference Accelerator]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21177</id>
        <link href="https://ai.meta.com/blog/next-generation-meta-training-inference-accelerator-AI-MTIA/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T15:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]
Read More...
The post Introducing the next-gen Meta Training and Inference Accelerator appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Retrospective on the Life Insurance Sector after the Failure of Silicon Valley Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29163</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/a-retrospective-on-the-life-insurance-sector-after-the-failure-of-silicon-valley-bank/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the Silicon Valley Bank collapse, the stock prices of U.S banks fell amid concerns about the exposure of the banking sector to interest rate risk. Thus, between March 8 and March 15, 2023, the S&P 500 Bank index dropped 12.8 percent relative to S&P 500 returns (see right panel of the chart below). The stock prices of insurance companies tumbled as well, with the S&P 500 Insurance index losing 6.4 percent relative to S&P 500 returns over the same time interval (see the center panel below). Yet, insurance companies’ direct exposure to the three failed banks (Silicon Valley Bank, Silvergate, and Signature Bank) through debt and equity was modest. In this post, we examine the possible factors behind the reaction of insurance investors to the failure of Silicon Valley Bank.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fulvia Fringuellotti and Saketh Prazad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Making of VES: the Cosmos Microservice for Netflix Video Encoding]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/946b9b3cd300</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/the-making-of-ves-the-cosmos-microservice-for-netflix-video-encoding-946b9b3cd300?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T22:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liwei Guo, Vinicius Carvalho, Anush Moorthy, Aditya Mavlankar, Lishan Zhu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways GitHub engineers use GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-04-09-4-ways-github-engineers-use-github-copilot/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-04-09-4-ways-github-engineers-use-github-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T19:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>GitHub Copilot increases efficiency for our engineers by allowing us to automate repetitive tasks, stay focused, and more.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-04-09-4-ways-github-engineers-use-github-copilot/">4 ways GitHub engineers use GitHub Copilot</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The need for a new economic paradigm]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45287</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/04/09/the-need-for-a-new-economic-paradigm/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T10:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Giandomenico Scarpelli and current issue of RWER As documented in the previous paragraph, in recent years it finally seems that most orthodox economists have become more aware of the catastrophic outcomes of climatic disturbances; but at this point the traditional policy they recommend could be insufficient to meet the goals set at international level. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total eclipse of the Internet: traffic impacts in Mexico, the US, and Canada]]></title>
        <id>66147ebda5fcdf000a0912db</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/total-eclipse-internet-traffic-impacts-mexico-us-canada"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T00:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s data shows a clear impact on Internet traffic from Mexico to the US, and Canada, following the path of totality of the total solar eclipse that occurred on April 8, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major data center power failure (again): Cloudflare Code Orange tested]]></title>
        <id>660fd4d7a5fcdf000a0908cd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/major-data-center-power-failure-again-cloudflare-code-orange-tested"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T13:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just four months after a complete power outage at a critical data center we were hit with the exact same scenario.  Here’s how we did this time, and what’s next]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Prince</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Week 2024 wrap-up]]></title>
        <id>66131e15a5fcdf000a090cfc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/developer-week-2024-wrap-up"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer Week 2024 has officially come to a close. Here’s a quick recap of the announcements and in-depth technical explorations that went out last week]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Internal Liquidity’s Value in a Financial Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=28786</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/04/internal-liquiditys-value-in-a-financial-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A classic question for U.S. financial firms is whether to organize themselves as entities that are affiliated with a bank-holding company (BHC). This affiliation brings benefits, such as access to liquidity from other affiliated entities, as well as costs, particularly a larger regulatory burden. This post highlights the results from a recent Staff Report that sheds light on this tradeoff. This work uses confidential data on the population of broker-dealers to study the benefits of being affiliated with a BHC, with a focus on the global financial crisis (GFC). The analysis reveals that affiliation with a BHC makes broker-dealers more resilient to the aggregate liquidity shocks that prevailed during the GFC. This results in these broker-dealers being more willing to hold riskier securities on their balance sheet relative to broker-dealers that are not affiliated with a BHC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cecilia Caglio and Adam Copeland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>