<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-11T18:30:33.003Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-11T18:30:33.003Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274819</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T18:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics; syndemics; festival of Biden! ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing software version consistency for Amazon ECS services]]></title>
        <id>804df1297f07a7ffb6fbd385fd1a1a2bdb03636f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-software-version-consistency-for-amazon-ecs-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Container image tags offer a user-friendly way to manage and keep track of different versions of container images. However, they also present a security risk to organizations due to their mutable nature. Without protections in place, a container image tag can be changed in a container image repository to point to a different container […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS announces workspace context awareness for Amazon Q Developer chat]]></title>
        <id>27c05c55cfcfa7555a9de914dce5f0bcd0e5f0b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/aws-announces-workspace-context-awareness-for-amazon-q-developer-chat/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, Amazon Web Services (AWS) announced the release of workspace context awareness in Amazon Q Developer chat. By including @workspace in your prompt, Amazon Q Developer will automatically ingest and index all code files, configurations, and project structure, giving the chat comprehensive context across your entire application within the integrated development environment (IDE). Throughout the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Matos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chat about your AWS account resources with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>1ebdbeac0365214c30b3bebba744123a5e7c6ad4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/chat-about-your-aws-account-resources-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T17:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traditional way customers had to interact with AWS account resources was through the AWS Management Console, SDKs, or command line interface (CLI) calls. However, these methods do not provide a quick way to gather information about AWS resources without writing scripts or navigating thought the AWS Management Console. The ability to use natural language […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Euro 2024’s impact on Internet traffic: a closer look at finalists Spain and England]]></title>
        <id>6690086858eb3b000a367cdd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/euro-2024s-impact-on-internet-traffic-a-closer-look-at-finalists-spain-and-england"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we examine how UEFA Euro 2024 football matches have influenced Internet traffic patterns in participating countries, with a special focus on the two finalists, Spain and England, on their journey to the final]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[country diary]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/country-diary/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/country-diary/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My apartment doesn't have power.
They're doing some kind of maintenance.
The air is hot and thick, and I'm pining for some AC.
Took the doggo out for our morning walk and stopped at Timmies to get a coffee and breakfast sandwich, then remembered I had to walk up four flights of stairs bc—no power.
K drove me back to the city last night, and as much as I miss being in the country...coming home to my own apartment and bed felt nice.
As I was falling asleep, I saw the tiniest of ants crawling up my arm, and immediately murder, death, kill for that little guy and of course I then googled what would happen if an ant crawled into your ear and nothing good came out of that.
I distracted myself by watching some ASMR and fell asleep in my perfectly temperature-controlled bedroom (K's apartment is a veritable icebox).
** his mom crocheted me a shawl(!!!), and I think my heart imploded. Nothing says i love you more than here...I made you something.
&nbsp
country sunsets & trails






the trail where I got devoured by an army of carnivorous mosquitos

out-the-car-window photographs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Agenda of Russia-India Relations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274818</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/new-agenda-of-russia-india-relations.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modi and Putin had a bear hug earlier this week. Some context on India-Russia dealings and US upset about them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application Security report: 2024 update]]></title>
        <id>668ea1544f58a9000ada525d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/application-security-report-2024-update"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s updated 2024 view on Internet cyber security trends spanning global traffic insights, bot traffic insights, API traffic insights, and client-side risks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Tremante</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mysterious Slowdown in U.S. Manufacturing Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30531</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/07/the-mysterious-slowdown-in-u-s-manufacturing-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout the twentieth century, steady technological and organizational innovations, along with the accumulation of productive capital, increased labor productivity at a steady rate of around 2 percent per year. However, the past two decades have witnessed a slowdown in labor productivity, measured as value added per hour worked. This slowdown has been particularly stark in the manufacturing sector, which historically has been a leading sector in driving the productivity of the aggregate U.S. economy. What makes this slowdown particularly puzzling is the fact that manufacturing accounts for the majority of U.S. research and development (R&D) expenditure. Despite several recent studies (see, for example, Syverson [2016]), much remains to be uncovered about the nature of this slowdown. This post illustrates a key facet of the mystery: the productivity slowdown appears to be pervasive across industries and across firms of various sizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danial Lashkari and Jeremy Pearce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274799</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T10:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our safely grazing daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Twists in the Wind as Big Donors Close Wallets, Party Criticism Persists Despite Clampdown, and Pelosi Questions His Decision to Continue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274797</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/biden-twists-in-the-wind-as-big-donors-close-wallets-party-criticism-persists-despite-clampdown-and-pelosi-questions-his-decision-to-continue.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T10:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite reports of ruthless Biden efforts at containment, calls for him to withdraw from the 2024 race grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Tariffs Don’t Protect Jobs. Don’t Be Fooled.”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274795</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/tariffs-dont-protect-jobs-dont-be-fooled.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More discussion of tariffs as the US is using to whack Chinese imports, above all EVs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Something Rotten in the State of Albion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274772</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/something-rotten-in-the-state-of-albion.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at Britain's image versus its conduct.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Les métamorphoses du moi]]></title>
        <id>https://florentbasch.fr/metamorphose/</id>
        <link href="https://florentbasch.fr/metamorphose/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lectures
Oliver Sacks -- L'homme qui prenait sa femme pour un chapeau -- Le marin perdu
Greg Egan -- En apprenant à être moi
Diapo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Settler Colonialism and the Engineering of Historical Amnesia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327770</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/settler-colonialism-and-the-engineering-of-historical-amnesia/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T06:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It should come as no surprise to those of us with even a cursory understanding of the history of U.S. imperialism that the once sovereign Kingdom of Hawai’i became the very first state in the nation to call for an immediate and permanent ceasefire in Gaza. Hawai’i is an occupied nation, and has been since 1893 when the U.S. launched a coup to overthrow the sovereign rule of Queen Liliʻuokalani. We don’t need to dive that far back into historical memory to discover that even this imperialist overthrow was acknowledged by none other than then president Bill Clinton, who, in 1993 (on the centennial of the coup) issued an official apology to the Hawaiian Kingdom—an apology that notably did not include a return of the land to the people of this occupied island nation. More
The post Settler Colonialism and the Engineering of Historical Amnesia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donalyn White - Anthony Ballas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Collapse of the “Vital Center” and the Return of Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327690</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/the-collapse-of-the-vital-center-and-the-return-of-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T06:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is what politics looks like today: a president-elect in Mexico pushes big minimum wage hikes amid unsettled financial markets. In Budapest people queue to vote in local and European elections not for liberals to oppose Orban’s nationalist FIDESZ party, but for an alternative conservative party to it. In Germany the rightwing AfD swept elections along political geographic lines almost questioning whether Germany ever fully re-united in 1989. Meanwhile, the centrist faction of Labour sent Tories packing while simultaneously seeing the return to Parliament of Jeremy Corbyn and Nicholas Farage. More
The post The Collapse of the “Vital Center” and the Return of Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Sommers, Cosmin Marian and Daniel Pop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fascism at the Gates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327594</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/fascism-at-the-gates/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T06:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Now is the time of monsters.” – Antonio Gramsci Two recent events have shattered complacency about the specter of a fascist takeover globally that a number of us have been warning about for some time now. In Europe, far-right parties scored impressive gains in the elections to the European Parliament in June.  In Germany, the  More
The post Fascism at the Gates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to a Massive Mobilization of the Left in France, the Far Right Cannot Control the Government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327780</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/thanks-to-a-massive-mobilization-of-the-left-in-france-the-far-right-cannot-control-the-government/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the results of the parliamentary elections in France on 7 July 2024? In the second round of France’s parliamentary elections on 7 July 2024, the National Rally (Rassemblement National -RN-) suffered a political defeat, even though it increased its number of MPs. The wager of the far-right party was to win a  More
The post Thanks to a Massive Mobilization of the Left in France, the Far Right Cannot Control the Government appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Burgum is Trump’s Likely VP Choice.  Here’s Why]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327821</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/doug-burgum-is-trumps-likely-vp-choice-heres-why/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two, maybe three, good reasons to believe that Donald Trump will choose North Dakota Governor Doug Burgum as his vice-presidential running mate over more popular MAGA-oriented choices like Ohio Senator J.D. Vance or Florida senator Marco Rubio, whose Cuban-American working class roots might appeal to Hispanics. First, and foremost, because Burgum appears to  More
The post Doug Burgum is Trump’s Likely VP Choice.  Here’s Why appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trendy Appointments: Australia’s Special Antisemitism Envoy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327824</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/trendy-appointments-australias-special-antisemitism-envoy/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was there any need for this?  Australia’s Albanese government, harried by the conservative opposition for going soft on pro-Palestinian protests and the war in Gaza while allegedly wobbling on supporting Israel, has decided to bring a touch of bureaucracy to the show.  Australia now has its first antisemitism envoy, a title that sits in that odd constellation  More
The post Trendy Appointments: Australia’s Special Antisemitism Envoy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: 9 Songs (with apologies to Michael Winterbottom)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327642</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/letter-from-london-9-songs-with-apologies-to-michael-winterbottom/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. David Bowie: ‘We’ve got five years, stuck on my eyes / Five years, what a surprise / We’ve got five years, my brain hurts a lot / Five years, that’s all we’ve got…’ Our son, as it happened, was first in the neighbourhood to vote at our local polling station on who will run  More
The post Letter from London: 9 Songs (with apologies to Michael Winterbottom) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Swedish Unions in Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327748</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/11/swedish-unions-in-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a truism that capitalism is not a democracy; capitalism means economic dictatorship, which is most evident in our workplaces. But truisms have the merit of being true and as long as workers live under the employers’ dictatorship, there is every reason to repeat this truth and fight for democracy. Another truism is that the  More
The post Swedish Unions in Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rasmus Hästbacka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warzone Distro, Susaron 4 - MORE THAN JUST A DIET]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-more-than-just-a-diet?v=1720659191</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/warzone-distro-more-than-just-a-diet?v=1720659191"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Warzone Distro, Susaron 4
Title: MORE THAN JUST A DIET
Subtitle: A Conversation Between Warzone Distro & the Susaron 4
Date: July 7 2024
Source: https://warzonedistro.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/04/more-than-just-a-diet-a-conversation-between-warzone-distro-the-susaron-4/

So first and foremost, could you give us and the readers an update? Last many of us heard, one of you was released.
 So for those who don’t already know about our case and a small update: 
 On November 3, 2022 we four comrades were arrested, accused of the arson attack to the meat company Susaron, a national industry that has been supplying the whole country with beef, pork and poultry meat for years. 
 On November 4, we were remanded in custody for the duration of the investigation. Accused of burning six trucks, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics (Continued)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics-continued?v=1720657195</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics-continued?v=1720657195"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics (Continued)
Subtitle: Problem of "Anjin" (安 心, Peace of Mind)
Date: 1965
Source: Retrieved on 07/10/2024 from https://noselvesnomasters.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/hakugen_ethics_2.pdf

 By "Anjin" is meant here spiritual calmness created by Prajna. Prajna is a unique intuition that sees the true nature of things as they are (Yathabhutam). "Zazen-shin" (坐 禅 箴, Instruction in Zazen) by Dogen (1200 -1253) reads: "A bird flies as a bird does; a fish swims likes a fish!" The essence of things seen by Prajna or Yathatathyadarsana (如 実 見, seeing into the truth as it is) is named "Suchness" (tathata) or "Emptiness" (sunyata), because it is beyond our daily expression which is the result of discriminative consciousness …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 07, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240710</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240710"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spellcheck, autocorrect: the end of Notepad as a simple text editor]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7981</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/spellcheck-autocorrect-end-notepad-simple-text-editor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s go back in time. Way back in time. To about this time in 2000. I had, or was just about, to start my first job as a web designer, at an exciting, multidisciplinary design studio, on Sydney’s trendy urban fringe. Ok: Surry Hills. I’m pleased to say I was headhunted into the role, thanks […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taming the tail utilization of ads inference at Meta scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21421</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/10/production-engineering/tail-utilization-ads-inference-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T20:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tail utilization is a significant system issue and a major factor in overload-related failures and low compute utilization. The tail utilization optimizations at Meta have had a profound impact on model serving capacity footprint and reliability.  Failure rates, which are mostly timeout errors, were reduced by two-thirds; the compute footprint delivered 35% more work for [...]
Read More...
The post Taming the tail utilization of ads inference at Meta scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wsay in "AMD to buy Silo AI for $665M"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40931097</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40931097"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T20:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who has designed and taught those courses, my experience (admittedly only one persons) is that you pick what will work with the least hassle - because you'll have plenty of hassle elsewhere and probably no real time to deal with any of it without making more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wsay</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The conjuncture in the crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-conjuncture-in-the-crisis</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-conjuncture-in-the-crisis"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T18:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Aaranchiya Subhai!” (‘Await Good News') read posters plastered across the country recently. It was the build-up to Ranil Wickremesinghe's televised speech on June 26, passing off a bad deal with official creditors on debt servicing as “Sri Lanka has won”. 
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Crisis, 
Debt crisis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274773</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Trump VP picks; Biden's wall of Black support; Pelosi: "Not so fast!" ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alakaʻi Kapānui and Fatima Abed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327778</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/alaka%ca%bbi-kapanui-and-fatima-abed/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join Counterpunch Radio contributor Rebecca Maria Goldschmidt, in conversation with activists and community organizers, Alakaʻi Kapānui and Fatima Abed, to discuss the Palestinian Solidarity movement in Hawai’i.
From being the first “state” to call for an immediate and permanent ceasefire, to the #CancelRIMPAC campaign against the world’s largest Navy exercises, Hawai’i organizers are drawing deeper connections between the military occupations of Hawai’i, Palestine, and the Israeli apartheid state. Decades of Native Hawaiian-led demilitarization efforts and current Palestinian and Jewish-led grassroots community are finding ways to collaborate towards genuine security.
Alakaʻi Kapānui is a Kanaka ʻŌiwi and Jewish activist and community organizer. She is the poʻo (head) of Kona 4 Palestine …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vector search for Amazon MemoryDB is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>a2931bd0421d69f5d03ea0b81d6deb2d21e7adfa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/vector-search-for-amazon-memorydb-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Store, index, retrieve, and search vectors with in-memory performance for use cases like retrieval augmentation, semantic caching, and anomaly detection through single-digit millisecond queries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build enterprise-grade applications with natural language using AWS App Studio (preview)]]></title>
        <id>675e924e6be607327f2b94aa9a414b0452cc18b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-custom-business-applications-without-cloud-expertise-using-aws-app-studio-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:32:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effortlessly build apps with AI-powered low-code tools, enabling organizations to create secure custom apps in minutes without dev teams - streamlining processes like claims, inventory, and approvals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Apps, now generally available, enables users to build their own generative AI apps]]></title>
        <id>58d223451397f47b42448e9f3d0eb7a68ab67077</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-apps-now-generally-available-enables-users-to-build-their-own-generative-ai-apps/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:20:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craft generative AI apps from conversations using natural language and approved data sources. Customize securely shared apps, specifying data sources per card and new APIs for programmatic app management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize Amazon Q Developer (in your IDE) with your private code base]]></title>
        <id>dbb8742329cd1fae053e5dd3ea9c6f968b17483f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/customize-amazon-q-developer-in-your-ide-with-your-private-code-base/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock hyper-relevant code suggestions tailored to your codebase; enhance productivity with Amazon Q Developer's private customization while maintaining robust data privacy and security standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock now support memory retention and code interpretation (preview)]]></title>
        <id>cb2425b75e646718c827c993d8716db44573e98a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/agents-for-amazon-bedrock-now-support-memory-retention-and-code-interpretation-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T16:04:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agents for Amazon Bedrock now offer Memory to retain user context and Code Interpreter to dynamically execute code snippets—whether for data analysis, visualization, or complex problem-solving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical Decision-Making in a Fragmented Space: Spotify In-Car Case Study]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7142</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/07/technical-decision-making-in-a-fragmented-space-spotify-in-car-case-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Car rides have become connected and interactive these days with drivers jamming to music or catching up on podcasts or [...]
The post Technical Decision-Making in a Fragmented Space: Spotify In-Car Case Study appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock can now detect hallucinations and safeguard apps built using custom or third-party FMs]]></title>
        <id>e71f10193867cd708459006c696412bbd9e25212</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/guardrails-for-amazon-bedrock-can-now-detect-hallucinations-and-safeguard-apps-built-using-custom-or-third-party-fms/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock adds hallucination detection and an independent API to fortify generative AI applications with customized guardrails across any model, ensuring responsible and trustworthy outputs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Knowledge Bases for Amazon Bedrock now supports additional data connectors (in preview)]]></title>
        <id>d1ac6c04af654f43a3f18f82c30276aa6defb928</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/knowledge-bases-for-amazon-bedrock-now-supports-additional-data-connectors-in-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance company knowledge bases with new Amazon Bedrock connectors for Confluence, Salesforce, SharePoint, and web domains - empowering RAG models with contextual data for more accurate and relevant responses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon Q Developer in SageMaker Studio to streamline ML workflows]]></title>
        <id>2f43e4416aa370a33fa9f2f85b61010b3aa3c5d8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-q-developer-in-sagemaker-studio-to-streamline-ml-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline your ML workflows with this generative AI assistant providing tailored guidance, code generation, and error troubleshooting, to build, train, and deploy models efficiently.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: Thanks to a massive mobilization of the Left the Far Right cannot control the government]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-Thanks-to-a-massive-mobilization-of-the-Left-the-Far-Right-cannot</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-Thanks-to-a-massive-mobilization-of-the-Left-the-Far-Right-cannot"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What are the results of the parliamentary elections in France on 7 July 2024? 
English

/ 
France, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life Update]]></title>
        <id>https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/life-update/</id>
        <link href="https://kylevallans.bearblog.dev/life-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enter your email if you'd like to get inside our overnight momentum trading chat for a free month.
I started writing about Going Infinite about the highly autistic Sam Bankman-Fried, Alameda Research, FTX and its downfall. However, I couldn't do it justice. I recommend picking up the book and reading it for yourself. FWIW, after reading it, your pov should remain the same of "crypto is highly retarded".
Instead of going down that rabbit hole, I decided to go for a feel-good post with a little update since deciding to step away from my former profession...
Okay, so I left on April 3rd, 2024 so it's been a total of 97 days and during that time I have:
Severely reduced the stress and anxiety I was dealing with day to day by no longer making my life revolve solely around work.
Started to enjoy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hudson: Russia and China CRUSH NATO’s Plan as Ukraine FALLS Apart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274756</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/michael-hudson-russia-and-china-crush-natos-plan-as-ukraine-falls-apart.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NATO is looking wobbly and many of its woes are self inflicted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[grammar aggression]]></title>
        <id>https://junejuice.bearblog.dev/grammar-aggression/</id>
        <link href="https://junejuice.bearblog.dev/grammar-aggression/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[you sound so aggressively passionate about grammar. i get it. don't worry. being passionate about something you want everyone to follow through. order.
and then there's these people who are going against that order yuck
oh no ! no ! no ! /stomps three times i'll curse you out! >:(
or
oh no the world will end if i don't use grammar right. /dramatically flops on the ground tongue lolling to the side
come on now, don't get your knickers in a twist
let people write what they want, post what they want and however they want. because guess what?
it's their blog /dramatic gasp
the reader also, also, guess again, have the choice to click away. shocker
also don't cuss people out that's not nice]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mastax in "AMD to buy Silo AI for $665M"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40927114</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40927114"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’d argue that a factor in CUDA’s success is their army of in-house researchers which use CUDA to do novel things. Sometimes those things get turned into products (OptiX) other times they are essentially DevRel to show off what the hardware can do and documentation for how to do it. Additionally I’m sure they use pre-release hardware and software and give feedback about how to improve it.
I don’t know what AMD has in mind for this acquisition but I could see there being a lot of value having an in house LLM team to create models for customers to build on, run in benchmarks, and improve their products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mastax</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radioactive Real Estate: Finding a Forever Home for Nuclear Waste]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274761</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/radioactive-real-estate-finding-a-forever-home-for-nuclear-waste.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Castoffs from U.S. nuclear weapons get buried at one site in New Mexico. But what happens when that facility fills up?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TrueGeek in "Girls in Tech closes its doors after 17 years"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40926856</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40926856"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Better article with more information:
https://www.bizjournals.com/nashville/news/2024/07/08/girls-...
> In an email Monday, founder and CEO Adriana Gascoigne said “Girls in Tech will be closing its doors due to a lack of funding in 2023 and 2024.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TrueGeek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Zaraz adds support for server-side rendering of X and Instagram embeds]]></title>
        <id>667d9546a4598c000bd7062b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/zaraz-supports-server-side-rendering-of-embeds"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce Cloudflare Zaraz support for server-side rendering of embeds from X and Instagram. This allows for secure, privacy-preserving, and performant embedding without third-party JavaScript or cookies, enhancing security, privacy, and performance on your website]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yair Dovrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s approach to machine learning prediction robustness]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21437</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/07/10/data-infrastructure/machine-learning-ml-prediction-robustness-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s advertising business leverages large-scale machine learning (ML) recommendation models that power millions of ads recommendations per second across Meta’s family of apps. Maintaining reliability of these ML systems helps ensure the highest level of service and uninterrupted benefit delivery to our users and advertisers. To minimize disruptions and ensure our ML systems are intrinsically [...]
Read More...
The post Meta’s approach to machine learning prediction robustness appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Girls in Tech closes its doors after 17 years"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40926350</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40926350"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T12:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: if you're going to post on a topic like this please make sure you're not just commenting out of reflexive activation. That's not what HN is for, as the site guidelines try to make clear: https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html.
On HN, we want comments that are thoughtful—i.e. that come from reflection, not reflex [1]; and specific—i.e. that have to do with what's different about a story, not what's generic. This is not particular to any topic; it's an optimization problem: we're trying to optimize the site for intellectual curiosity [2].
The trouble with reflexive comments is that they repeat responses that have already happened many times—rather as if they're being served from cache [3]. The trouble with generic comments is that the generic level is too abstract to say anything new or interesting. Put those together and you get repetition, the arch-enemy of curiosity [4].
[1] https://hn.algolia.com/?dateRange=all&page=0&prefix=true&sor...
[2] https://hn.algolia.com/?dateRange=all&page=0&prefix=true&sor...
[3] This, btw, is why such comments always show up quickly: cached responses are the fastest to arise. The kind of thoughtful comments we're looking for take longer to "compute".
[4] https://hn.algolia.com/?dateRange=all&page=0&prefix=false&so...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Confessions - My Life on the High Seas]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/true-confessions-my-life-on-the-high-seas/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/true-confessions-my-life-on-the-high-seas/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those of us whose online life began with 2400 bps modems or slower remember what life was like when viewing an image online meant downloading it line by line over a 10- or 15-minute period. One image. The early editions of CompuServe, Prodigy, and AOL were all text-based, as were local BBSs. When the real Internet, the kind you access through a browser, or rather through Netscape 1.0, became available, for me in 1996, most of us had 14.4 modems; we quickly upgraded to 28.8 and then 56.6 bps. When things were still super slow, I remember downloading Netscape 2.0 like it was the birth of another child. It was about 6 MB in size, and it took 45 minutes of "NOBODY CAN USE THE PHONE." I paced back and forth outside on my lawn, smoking cigarettes and trying to imagine what the new web would look…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=274681</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T10:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our fastidious daily links: dog rescue, long sepsis? climate change v. semen, views of US v. China, EU v. Orban, moar Israel atrocities, WSJ: Russia beating US wunderwaffen, backbone data harvest, NATO wobbly, press piling on v. Biden, gunz, AI heath coaching scam? PBM markups]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Some Zapatista Principles & Practices...]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-zapatista-principles-practices?v=1720605560</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-some-zapatista-principles-practices?v=1720605560"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Some Zapatista Principles & Practices...
Date: 2009
Source: Scanned from “Sharing Leadership Series Handout 5.6.09”

 The Zapatista indigenous movement in Chiapas, México has summarized many of their principles into short, accessible sayings that convey big ideas about a different way of leading and building power, which contrast greatly with repressive/oppressive methods of holding power and authority. 
Mandar Obedeciendo (Lead by Obeying)
 PRINCIPLE: True leaders follow the will of the people, the desires of the larger community. 
 PRACTICE: This principle challenges authoritarianism in the communities, and representatives who are not accountable to the widespread desires of the community will be ousted from their positions. In many of the communities, an oversig…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TheOffer.txt]]></title>
        <id>https://library.xandra.cc/the-offer/</id>
        <link href="https://library.xandra.cc/the-offer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're Buying a House
i am absolutely exploding inside with this news, but i have no way to scream it, so this will have to do.
we've put an offer in on a house on sunday, and they accepted it today! i cannot believe it! i cried all the two hours it took for us to get home; partially because this is a dream that i have worked so hard for and never thought i'd actually get.
the house is deeply within our budget, thank goodness; but it's pushing the limits of commute for my boyfriend, which is unfortunate. i wish it was still affordable to live within reasonable commuting distance of a major city like seattle, but i'm just so thankful that we're staying in the pacific northwest. i'm really loving every second of being here, and it feels as though i was always meant to be here in this moment—i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The UK’s Major Political Shifts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327579</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/the-uks-major-political-shifts/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T06:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tories had their worst performance in their 190-year history, losing almost half their share of the vote and 252 parliamentary seats in the 650-seat House of Commons, surpassing their previously greatest electoral catastrophe, when the Balfour government went under in 1906, losing 246 seats. There are now 121 Conservative MPs, and no Tory MPs in Central London, Wales, Oxfordshire (one of the leafy shires that were previous Tory strongholds), and Cornwall (which has had at least one Tory MP since 1924). More
The post The UK’s Major Political Shifts appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenneth Surin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Judgment Day for America’s Worst Supreme Court Justice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327710</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/judgment-day-for-americas-worst-supreme-court-justice/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least I had the courage to do the deed myself. That counts for something here on the other side of death, where I wait for you, Clarence Thomas, and your sharp-toothed wife Ginni, and someday the others whose decrees and rulings from afar have aided and abetted the mayhem and the massacres. Cowards all of you, and boring and petty to boot, at such a safe distance from the volleys, the salvos, the gunfire. Oh, the names I have had to learn — Sandy Hook and Columbine and Uvalde and so many hundreds more and even more after that, while you were careful to stay at a safe distance from the children as they fell. More
The post Judgment Day for America’s Worst Supreme Court Justice appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ariel Dorfman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Westminster at Last: The Threat of Nigel Farage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327727</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/in-westminster-at-last-the-threat-of-nigel-farage/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“This is the inflection point,” warned Nigel Farage last month as he assumed the reins of power at the incarnated Reform UK party, standard bearer of the often inchoate group known as the hard right of British politics.  “The only wasted vote is a Conservative one.  We are the challengers to Labour.  We are on our way.” On July 4,  More
The post In Westminster at Last: The Threat of Nigel Farage appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside China-Focused Congressional Hearings, Panic, Paranoia, and Hypocrisy Reign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327707</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/inside-china-focused-congressional-hearings-panic-paranoia-and-hypocrisy-reign/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 26th, the Committee on Oversight and Accountability sat down for a Congressional Hearing titled, “Defending America from the Chinese Communist Party’s Political Warfare.” This was one of many Congressional hearings aimed at tackling the “China threat.” As a general premise, I didn’t have a lot of hope for the hearing. Language is crucial,  More
The post Inside China-Focused Congressional Hearings, Panic, Paranoia, and Hypocrisy Reign appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Megan Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time for the Fed to Cut Interest Rates]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327593</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/time-for-the-fed-to-cut-interest-rates/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Board Chair Jerome Powell has been saying for some time that he needs to see more evidence that inflation is under control before he lowers interest rates. We can never be certain of where the economy is going, so it’s understandable that he remains worried that inflation could reaccelerate. However, there are risks  More
The post Time for the Fed to Cut Interest Rates appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open letter to the President of Switzerland, Ms Viola Amherd]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327732</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/open-letter-to-the-president-of-switzerland-ms-viola-amherd/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Madame President of the Swiss Confederation, Ms Viola Amherd Dear Federal Councillor and Minister of Foreign Affairs, Mr Ignazio Cassis The proposal to house a liaison office of the North Atlantic Treaty Organization in Geneva is ill-advised.  Switzerland is a neutral country since the Congress of Vienna of 1815[1].  Its well-earned reputation as a responsible State  More
The post Open letter to the President of Switzerland, Ms Viola Amherd appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deference to Joe Biden from Bernie Sanders Has Become Nonsensical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327730</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/deference-to-joe-biden-from-bernie-sanders-has-become-nonsensical/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love Bernie Sanders. By most measures, he’s the greatest senator in the last 50 years. I was very glad to be a Sanders delegate to the 2016 and 2020 Democratic National Conventions. But when Bernie screws up, his progressive base should say so. That happened during the first months of Israel’s war on Gaza  More
The post Deference to Joe Biden from Bernie Sanders Has Become Nonsensical appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Ryan] Grim News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327735</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/ryan-grim-news/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grim said he’d leave The Intercept “in a box,” but he’s very much alive and launching a new outlet. When I got back to writing earlier this year, I wasn’t expecting AIPAC to be a recurring theme. But then the right-wing group went and dropped over $4 million on a nearby congressional primary. I was able to write  More
The post [Ryan] Grim News appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This Absurd Election Choice Should Have Us Thundering in the Streets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327736</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/this-absurd-election-choice-should-have-us-thundering-in-the-streets/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Eugene Ionesco’s 1959 play “Rhinoceros,” a staple of the post-war absurdist repertoire, the cast of characters discuss the sudden news that one or more rhinoceros have been seen running through their small French town. In the play, the local villagers parse trivial, speculative and tangential points—the rhinoceros, seen on two occasions, might have been  More
The post This Absurd Election Choice Should Have Us Thundering in the Streets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the New Popular Front Won]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327702</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/why-the-new-popular-front-won/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the evening of our stunning victory, I listened to the speeches of our politicians: “Glory to the people!”, “We must stay mobilized to push forward the program!”, &c. And then as the orators turned to depart the stage, Jean-Luc Mélenchon paced back up to the microphones and addressed the crowd, “I have heard that  More
The post Why the New Popular Front Won appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Wallis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passing Fancy: Wilt Chamberlain as Distributor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327581</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/passing-fancy-wilt-chamberlain-as-distributor/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nikola Jokić is one of my favorite NBA players.  Since he entered the league in 2015, his multiple talents, uncanny skill set, and high basketball IQ have helped to transform the way we conceptualize the “center” position.  Among his many skills is his brilliant passing, which commentators have long noted.  In their tributes to another  More
The post Passing Fancy: Wilt Chamberlain as Distributor appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter A. Coclanis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stop the ‘Lesser of Two Evils’ Syndrome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327743</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/stop-the-lesser-of-two-evils-syndrome/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:12:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Liberals vote Democrat. Conservatives vote Republican. Most progressives vote Democrat. So has it been. That landscape is changing.  This election debate revolves around “lesser of evils” as always, but the presidential candidates are more unpopular than ever. What issues matter most? Greater possibility for world war with nuclear weapons. Mother Earth enraged. Racism and inequality. Republican  More
The post Stop the ‘Lesser of Two Evils’ Syndrome appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Ridenour</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cows in a National Park? How Can That Be?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327506</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/10/cows-in-a-national-park-how-can-that-be/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cattle grazing, a practice that dates back to the creation of Grand Teton National Park and is also observed in a dozen other parks, is a part of the park’s historical legacy. However, that legacy is still creating conflicts between park values and livestock interests.  A current controversy is over a $700,000 fence in the  More
The post Cows in a National Park? How Can That Be? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - A Short and Incomplete Guide For New Activists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-a-short-and-incomplete-guide-for-new-activists?v=1720577930</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-a-short-and-incomplete-guide-for-new-activists?v=1720577930"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: A Short and Incomplete Guide For New Activists
Subtitle: or: how to get started by getting started
Date: May 22, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 4th July 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 A couple weeks ago, I was talking to my friends who run the podcast It Could Happen Here. “Summer is coming, and an awful lot of people are newly radicalized. You all should put out an episode about what the next steps are,” I told them. 
 “Perfect,” someone replied. “Write it and record it by May 20th.” 
 So I wrote a short and incomplete guide for new activists. You can hear me present it in audio format if you’d like. 
 I’m coming with my own biases which I want to get out right up front: I’m an anarchist, and it’s also been decades since I broke into the movement, beca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.) - The Direct Urgency of Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-the-direct-urgency-of-attack?v=1720577766</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-the-direct-urgency-of-attack?v=1720577766"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.)
Title: The Direct Urgency of Attack
Date: 2013
Notes: A contribution by the CCF member, Christos Tsakalos, to the Nihilistic March zine and the counter-information blog Parabellum. Continuing the conversation, started by Italian comrade Nicola Gai. 
 Translated by Inter Arma.
Source: <interarma.info/2014/02/13/ellada-amesh-anagkaiothta-ths-epithsis-chts/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

I. The miracle workers of social salvation
 We live in a dull, predictable and mechanical age. We live in the dictatorship of numbers of the financial crisis, of unemployment statistics, stock market analysis and of generalized social fear. 
 At the same time, the humanist merchants of “progressive” ideologies are seeking new clients. The wandering…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.), Giorgos Nikolopoulos (C.C.F.) - Text in Relation to the Summons for the Inflammatory Parcel That Was Sent to Berlusconi]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-giorgos-nikolopoulos-c-c-f-text-in-relation-to-the-summons-they-receive?v=1720577098</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/christos-tsakalos-c-c-f-giorgos-nikolopoulos-c-c-f-text-in-relation-to-the-summons-they-receive?v=1720577098"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T02:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Christos Tsakalos (C.C.F.), Giorgos Nikolopoulos (C.C.F.)
Title: Text in Relation to the Summons for the Inflammatory Parcel That Was Sent to Berlusconi
Date: 2011
Source: <interarma.info/2011/06/23/keimeno-x-tsakalos-g-nikolopoulos-dema-berlusconi/?lang=en>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

‘Through the sadness of endless mediocrity that suffocates us from everywhere, I console myself that somewhere in a closet several stubborn people struggle to counteract the spoilage.’ [Odysseas Elytis]
 We are summoned to appear before the Prosecutor’s Office of Bologna, Italy, on June 28th in order to participate in a preliminary investigation in regard to the ‘punishable offense under Articles 110, 280 of the Criminal Code (attempt with terrorist and subversive purposes)’ of t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - A Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-a-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics?v=1720575200</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-a-preliminary-conception-of-zen-social-ethics?v=1720575200"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T01:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: A Preliminary Conception of Zen Social Ethics
Date: 1963
Source: Retrieved on 7/4/2024 from <jstage.jst.go.jp/article/ibk1952/11/1/11_1_359/_pdf/-char/ja>

 A short poem “Adoring Naivety” by a Christian poet Jukichi Yagi (1827–1927) runs as follows: 
 Rice bread, 
 Whole-rice bread, 
 Fresh and steaming! 
 Whole-rice bread! 
 A bread seller goes about a “Non-acting” (Mu-i 無 爲 akarma) path singing cries of wares, as if in ecstacy over his singing.[1]
 This verse seems to suggest the aesthetic character of the Japanese folks. In the early days, Japanese peddlers, such as gold-fish vendors, beancurd dealers and seedling-peddlers used to peddle by crying in rythmical voices. Mood, relish, flavour and atmosphere carry great weight in a Japanese life. “Japanese ph…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gerasimos Tsakalos (C.C.F) - Individuality and the Anarchist Group]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gerasimos-tsakalos-c-c-f-individuality-and-the-anarchist-group?v=1720573604</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gerasimos-tsakalos-c-c-f-individuality-and-the-anarchist-group?v=1720573604"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T01:06:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gerasimos Tsakalos (C.C.F)
Title: Individuality and the Anarchist Group
Date: December 2015
Source: Web archive capture on 13 Sep 2016 from <web.archive.org/.../325.nostate.net/.../>

Instead of a Prologue
 About the subject of “Individuality and the anarchist group”, one could say that it’s a timeless issue within the anarchist milieu… Is an anarchist individuality subjugated or liberated within a group? How does the individual encounter the collective? Can disagreements between comrades of the same collective be creative or do they inevitably lead to disputes, rivalries, intrigues, competitions and end up in rupture? 
 How are friendships and cliques able to bring about a cancellation of an anarchist group? 
 What is the relationship of an anarchist organization to the expulsions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kostas Sakkas - Political statement at the terror-trial of Koridallos prison]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kostas-sakkas-political-statement-at-the-terror-trial-of-koridallos-prison?v=1720569724</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kostas-sakkas-political-statement-at-the-terror-trial-of-koridallos-prison?v=1720569724"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T00:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kostas Sakkas
Title: Political statement at the terror-trial of Koridallos prison
Date: January 14, 2015, anarchists in trouble
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=18709>. Retrieved on 03/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 I am sending the following text to Athens lawyer Dimitrios Katsaris in order for him to deliver it to his client and my co-accused Giorgos Karagiannidis, in order to read it out in the courtroom during the testimony procedure. 
 I realize absolutely that what a relative of mine testified during the witnesses’ testimonies was done with the best of intentions. However I must clarify that a large part of it does not reflect reality and does not express me as an individual. Unfortunately the conditions in which I find myself in, my inability to communicate and the restr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clarence Lee Swartz, in collaboration with The Mutualist Associates - What Is Mutualism?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/clarence-lee-swartz-in-collaboration-with-the-mutualist-associates-what-is-mutualism?v=1720568727</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/clarence-lee-swartz-in-collaboration-with-the-mutualist-associates-what-is-mutualism?v=1720568727"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T23:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Clarence Lee Swartz, in collaboration with The Mutualist Associates
Title: What Is Mutualism?
Date: 1927
Notes: This is a very interesting and valuable text on Mutualism. It is slightly dated in some points and a bit off the target when dealing with monetary matters. Nevertheless it remains a powerful exposition of the main tenets of Mutualism and a sincere plea in favour of the freedom and autonomy of the individual.
Source: <c4ss.org/wp-content/uploads/2009/06/what-is-mutualism.pdf>

MUTUALISM — A Social System Based on Equal Freedom, Reciprocity, and the Sovereignty of the Individual Over Himself, His Affairs, and His Products; Realized Through Individual Initiative, Free Contract, Cooperation, Competition, and Voluntary Association for Defense Against the Invasive and for the P…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitor data events in Amazon S3 Express One Zone with AWS CloudTrail]]></title>
        <id>08f8205391b4f54c420072e762445c6a8d490a15</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/monitor-data-events-in-amazon-s3-express-one-zone-with-aws-cloudtrail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T22:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudTrail data event logging enables auditing for governance and compliance of object operations like PutObject and GetObject. Leverage high performance and low cost for latency-sensitive workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Announcements of the AWS Summit in New York, 2024]]></title>
        <id>8ed151291b1f97b46f2655d37b994f085e5bd6eb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/top-announcements-of-the-aws-summit-in-new-york-2024-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Along with a plethora of new launches, read about the latest models in Amazon Bedrock and new features for Amazon Q.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate your data and collaborate using data preparation in AWS Glue Studio]]></title>
        <id>3dbcc75ef8554e17d4ce640b34987f60e1ed5ea5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/integrate-your-data-and-collaborate-using-data-preparation-in-aws-glue-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With AWS Glue's new visual interface, data teams can collaboratively build ETL pipelines, bridging the gap between analysts and engineers through an intuitive, shareable canvas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COVID-19: third most lethal cause of death in Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7977</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/covid-19-third-most-lethal-cause-death-australia-2022/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From The Daily Aus. Aside from being linked to a slight decrease in life expectancy, COVID-19 was the third highest cause of death in Australia in 2022, claiming almost ten-thousand lives: COVID-19 was the third leading cause of death in Australia in 2022, according to AIHW. It was the first time in more than 50 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by munificent in "Judge dismisses DMCA copyright claim in GitHub Copilot suit"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40920723</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40920723"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T20:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Indeed, last year GitHub was said to have tuned its programming assistant to generate slight variations of ingested training code to prevent its output from being accused of being an exact copy of licensed software.
If I, a human, were to:
1. Carefully read and memorize some copyrighted code.
2. Produce new code that is textually identical to that. But in the process of typing it up, I randomly mechanically tweak a few identifiers or something to produce code that has the exact same semantics but isn't character-wise identical.
3. Claim that as new original code without the original copyright.
I assume that I would get my ass kicked legally speaking. That reads to me exactly like deliberate copyright infringement with willful obfuscation of my infringement.
How is it any different when a machine does the same thing?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>munificent</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Graviton4-based Amazon EC2 R8g instances: best price performance in Amazon EC2]]></title>
        <id>07a71bd7ce6b0c97862edd3bdcb3b2e5005fcf1c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-graviton4-based-amazon-ec2-r8g-instances-best-price-performance-in-amazon-ec2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover the price performance and sustainability benefits of Graviton4 with Amazon EC2 R8g instances, ideal for memory-intensive workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reminder to Take a Walk and Breathe]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-reminder-to-take-a-walk-and-breathe/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-reminder-to-take-a-walk-and-breathe/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A non-stressful day at work is hard to come by. I am constantly straddling the fine line between being burnt out, and just flipping a table and walking away. At the end of the day, those two feelings are basically the same side of a coin.
I work remotely full-time, for the most part. Sometimes I travel for workshops, but that’s mostly just at the beginning of kicking off a new product that I’ve been asked to build. Any other time, I’m mostly working in my home office, which has become my favorite place in the house, yet the place where I stress out the most.
I spend a lot of time in front of a computer. I’m in meetings probably 5-6 hours a day. With a majority of my current team in Central and Eastern time zones (2-3 hours ahead of me), sometimes I also forget to take a break and eat. It’s easy to lose track of time when I’m focused on solving this problem or that.
I also forget to breathe.
The weather finally cooled down yesterday, and a little bit today before we hit another heat wave. LSC constantly encourages me, and at times pushes me to go for a walk. Take a walk around the block, and just breathe. We practice breathing together, inhaling and exhaling. Inhale the fresh air slowly, keep it in for a few seconds, exhale slowly. Then we go back in the house, and I feel a tiny bit better.
Sometimes we get into what we’re doing so deeply that we forget the essentials. We forget to breathe. We don’t notice it until we’re drowning, and it’s even harder to get back to the surface. Sometimes all it takes is a reminder to stop what you’re doing, take a walk if you can, and breathe.
So hey, let this be a reminder.
Go for a walk. Inhale that fresh air. Hold it in. Exhale.
7/100
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the challenges in creating an accessible sortable list (drag-and-drop)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T19:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Drag-and-drop is a highly interactive and visual interface. We often use drag-and-drop to perform tasks like uploading files, reordering browser bookmarks, or even moving a card in solitaire.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-07-09-exploring-the-challenges-in-creating-an-accessible-sortable-list-drag-and-drop/">Exploring the challenges in creating an accessible sortable list (drag-and-drop)</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by miki123211 in "Google Chrome has an API accesible only from *.google.com"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40919040</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40919040"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T18:01:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I think the explanation is quite mundane
> There’ll be plots of various stats, including CPU utilization. I think meet will also helpfully suggest closing tabs if your machine is overloaded
This is not mundane at all, it's a perfect example of giving your product an unfair competitive advantage.
If Meet users are told why their meeting isn't working correctly but Zoom, Teams and Slack, Meet users are going to have a better experience that Zoom, Teams or Slack has no way of replicating.
No wonder every other meeting provider pushes you aggressively into using their desktop app, Google Meet's desktop app is just Chrome!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miki123211</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by padenot in "Ask HN: How do browsers isolate internal audio from microphone input?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40918539</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40918539"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T17:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way this works (and I'm obviously taking a high level view here) is by comparing what is being played to what is being captured. There is an inherent latency in between what is called the capture stream (the mic) and the reverse stream (what is being output to the speakers, be it people taking or music or whatever), and by finding this latency and comparing, one can cancel the music from the speech captured.
Within a single process, or tree of processes that can cooperate, this is straightforward (modulo the actual audio signal processing which isn't) to do: keep what you're playing for a few hundreds milliseconds around, compare to what you're getting in the microphone, find correlations, cancel.
If the process aren't related there are multiple ways to do this. Either the OS provides a capture API that does the cancellation, this is what happens e.g. on macOS for Firefox and Safari, you can use this. The OS knows what is being output. This is often available on mobile as well.
Sometimes (Linux desktop, Windows) the OS provides a loopback stream: a way to capture the audio that is being played back, and that can similarly be used for cancellation.
If none of this is available, you mix the audio output and perform cancellation yourself, and the behaviour your observe happens.
Source: I do that, but at Mozilla and we unsurprisingly have the same problems and solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>padenot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;Damage Control&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/damage-control</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/damage-control"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T16:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran’s ‘reformist’ president.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jonplackett in "Linksys Velop routers send Wi-Fi passwords in plaintext to US servers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40918007</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40918007"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T16:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just reading these comments - is everyone OK with them sending your password to a server, but not with the lack of encryption?
I would not expect my password to be sent to the server in the first place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jonplackett</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by xapata in "PySkyWiFi: Free stupid wi-fi on long-haul flights"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916892</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916892"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the author wrote, "This is satire," it'd ruin the satire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>xapata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[morning commute]]></title>
        <id>https://passerine.bearblog.dev/morning-commute/</id>
        <link href="https://passerine.bearblog.dev/morning-commute/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! it’s been a while since anything at all. june wasn’t uneventful or anything (quite the opposite, really!). i was just lost for words and it’s taken me some time to find them again – life lately has felt like a lot, when it really shouldn’t have been.
i’ve finally started a new job after my month-long vacation in europe. i’m still working in design, which is still not really my ideal (even if my high-school self was convinced it was)1. either way, it’s fun and i like it better than my previous one.
my last job was 100% remote. (they were changing this policy just as i was leaving though). i enjoyed having so much free time, of course. the commute in the philippines eats away up to 4 hours of your day, if you’re lucky. that’s not including time you spend getting ready, or time spent s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by justusthane in "PySkyWiFi: Free stupid wi-fi on long-haul flights"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916315</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916315"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Agreed. I applaud the initiative of figuring out they could access reddit via the CDN that Stripe uses - but downloading gigabytes of images for the sole purpose of "wasting their bandwidth"? Why??]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>justusthane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cosmotic in "PySkyWiFi: Free stupid wi-fi on long-haul flights"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916092</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916092"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I presume the only people you're hurting by downloading gigabytes of docs are the people on the plain that paid for the service. Maybe the company providing the service because those people experiencing the slow connection might never buy again. You're probably a also costing stripe for their upload bandwidth.
And here I am, avoiding downloading things on cell service because it might negatively impact other people around me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cosmotic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jmkb in "PySkyWiFi: Free stupid wi-fi on long-haul flights"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916024</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40916024"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decades ago, my partner used Google Voice for texting -- really handy, texts just showed up in the gmail inbox, and could be replied to from there. She didn't like cellphones, but usually carried one of the old "Kindle Keyboard" models with unlimited 3G data. The Kindle had simple web browser that could load the low-spec gmail interface, so in essence she had a fully functional SMS device, with no monthly charges.
Notification of incoming texts was the only problem. I jailbroke the thing and started trying to schedule network requests, thinking I'd add some kind of new message counter on the home screen. This proved hard. But it occurred to me that the best place for the counter would be right next to the Kindle's device name, at the top of the screen. And the device name could be updated from her Amazon account.
So I automated a web browser on the home server to log into Amazon and update the device name to "My Kindle (x)" where x was the number of unread Google Voice texts. The Kindle would update the name on the home screen in less than a minute. This worked for years!
(Eventually that Kindle was stolen. I wanted to update its name to something foul but the device disappeared from her account too quickly.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jmkb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoS threat report for 2024 Q2]]></title>
        <id>668d0d554f58a9000ada4e20</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2024-q2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 18th edition of the Cloudflare DDoS Threat Report. Released quarterly, these reports provide an in-depth analysis of the DDoS threat landscape as observed across the Cloudflare network. This edition focuses on the second quarter of 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Yoachimik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADIUS/UDP vulnerable to improved MD5 collision attack]]></title>
        <id>6687c6e3a4598c000bd7103d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/radius-udp-vulnerable-md5-attack"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RADIUS protocol is commonly used to control administrative access to networking gear. Despite its importance, RADIUS hasn’t changed much in decades. We discuss an attack on RADIUS as a case study for why it’s important for legacy protocols to keep up with advancements in cryptography]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sharon Goldberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critiquing Biden’s Worldview, Democratic Party Tactics and America’s Destiny]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327578</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/critiquing-bidens-worldview-democratic-party-tactics-and-americas-destiny/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T06:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears that even Biden is reluctant to claim credit in national settings for US support of Israel and Ukraine, and prefers to speak in generalities about the greatness of America as a country whose future is bright except to the extent dimmed by the threat advent of Trump and Trumpism. This tendency to ignore the world should be more troubling to American voters than even Biden’s refusal to leave the presidential stage in light of his thinly deniable disabilities of age and mental health that have put his 2024 candidacy in peril. More
The post Critiquing Biden’s Worldview, Democratic Party Tactics and America’s Destiny appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Falk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racism in the Life of Farage: From Enoch Powell to Reform UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327465</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/racism-in-the-life-of-farage-from-enoch-powell-to-reform-uk/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T06:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nigel Farage has always been a bigoted posh boy with the gift of the gab. Raised in the rolling hills of Downe on the outskirts of London -- a village most famous for its association with Charles Darwin -- Farage attended Eden Park Preparatory School in the 1970s. His wealthy parents then paid for his attendance at one of South London’s most prestigious old boys’ clubs, Dulwich College. Farage’s germinal racism was public even at this early age, and in 1981, his fascist mannerisms were played down as ordinary “naughtiness” by his college’s “Master” when he chose to make him a prefect More
The post Racism in the Life of Farage: From Enoch Powell to Reform UK appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Barker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Twentieth-Century Family Planning Strategy Fueled the Climate Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327647</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/how-a-twentieth-century-family-planning-strategy-fueled-the-climate-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1948, the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (UDHR) was signed, marking a milestone in human rights history. It established the fundamental rights to be universally protected, with Article 1 proclaiming: “All human beings are born free and equal in dignity and rights.” In the following decades, however, specific events and policies revealed a critical oversight  More
The post How a Twentieth-Century Family Planning Strategy Fueled the Climate Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Scher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dreaming of a Great World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/dreaming-of-a-great-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was a warm, humid summer night, just the kind of night I remember my parents taking us kids to see the Lincoln Memorial.  I wanted Erika to have as her first memory of this place that same stunning vista of Lincoln looking at the brightly lit obelisk of the Washington Monument and illuminated dome  More
The post Dreaming of a Great World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dictatorial Trump Court Has Put Our Democracy’s Rule of Law on Quicksand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327676</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/the-dictatorial-trump-court-has-put-our-democracys-rule-of-law-on-quicksand/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The six “corporate state” U.S. Supreme Court Justices, occupying unaccountable lifetime unelected positions, handed over dictatorial power for presidents and corporations that disassembled our Founders’ Constitution and the centerpiece of the American Revolution. In one week! Led by the notorious Trump v. United States case these interwoven and dictatorial commands will live in infamy unless  More
The post The Dictatorial Trump Court Has Put Our Democracy’s Rule of Law on Quicksand appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who “Runs The Country?” We Do!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327646</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/who-runs-the-country-we-do/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Who runs the country?” I’ve been hearing variants of that question a lot over the last  few weeks, mainly in forms like “given Joe Biden’s age and apparent mental decline, can we trust him to run the country for another four years?” For the last eight or nine years, I’ve also heard it a lot,  More
The post Who “Runs The Country?” We Do! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Australia’s Luck Running Out?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327441</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/is-australias-luck-running-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Describing Australia as “the lucky country” has long been a metaphor for how “well” Australia has been doing economically. Unfortunately, for many Australians, things haven’t been going “well” for quite some time. Australia’s past prosperity had precious little to do with luck. Years ago, many analysts saw Australia’s luck as a product of its abundant  More
The post Is Australia’s Luck Running Out? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rory Ellison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Economic Boycotts of the Civil Rights Era Still Offer Lessons on How to Achieve a Just Society]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=327500</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/09/black-economic-boycotts-of-the-civil-rights-era-still-offer-lessons-on-how-to-achieve-a-just-society/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signed into law 60 years ago, the Civil Rights Act of 1964 outlawed discrimination in the U.S. based on “race, color, sex, religion, or national origin.” Yet, as a historian who studies social movements and political change, I think the law’s most important lesson for today’s movements is not its content but rather how it  More
The post Black Economic Boycotts of the Civil Rights Era Still Offer Lessons on How to Achieve a Just Society appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin A. Young</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by deamanto in "Reverse engineering Ticketmaster's rotating barcodes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40911245</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40911245"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T00:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd also like to highlight another bad practice by Ticketmaster.
When you purchase a ticket from them and resell it on their marketplace, once someone purchases it, they(Ticketmaster) hold your funds and only give you the money ~7-14 business days after the event is over. They say this is to verify the validity of the ticket.
On the buyer side, you purchase the ticket from the marketplace and it gets added to your account immediately. (I think) You get the barcode some time ~1 week before the actual event begins.
The confusion for me? Ticketmaster owned the ticket and all logic relating to the validity of it. The logic to validate this shouldn't be complex at all. They OWN the ticket. They KNOW it's legitimate because it never left their database. Yet they double dip and hold both buyer and seller funds. Events can be close to a year in the future but the seller won't see that until after that event ends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deamanto</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is climate change increasing the strength of Australian red wine?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7973</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/climate-change-increasing-strength-australian-red-wine/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T21:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apparently red wines made in Australia — and quite possibly elsewhere, I imagine — have been increasing in alcoholic strength over recent decades. This seems like a mystery of the times, because the go-to culprit, global warming, may not be responsible. Rather, the way grapes are grown, and changes in fermenting methods — which apparently […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yjftsjthsd-h in "No more boot loader: Please use the kernel instead"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40909611</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40909611"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T20:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I'm understanding correctly, it might help to point out that in spite of the title they are proposing a bootloader, which can still let you modify the cmdline, boot to other OSs, etc. It's just that the bootloader is itself using the Linux kernel so it can do things like read all Linux filesystems for "free" without having to rewrite filesystem drivers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yjftsjthsd-h</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lqet in "How I turned seemingly 'failed' experiments into a successful PhD"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40909068</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40909068"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T20:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You really shouldn't start a PhD without doing the PhD simulator first [0]. Sadly, people who haven't yet been through the PhD experience think that this game is exaggerating for comic effect. It really isn't.
[0] https://research.wmz.ninja/projects/phd/index.html]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lqet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alerighi in "No more boot loader: Please use the kernel instead"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40908918</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40908918"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T19:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's something you can do since a lot of years. I used to do so 10 years ago, when I've got the first motherboard with UEFI. But is it useful? It saves a minimal time in the boot sequence, but at what cost?
The bootloader (being it grub, or something more simple as systemd-boot) is useful to me for a couple of reasons:
- it allows to dual-boot with Windows easily: motherboard boot menu is often not easy to access, you need to perform some key combination in a short window, also modern bootloader save the last boot option such that if Windows reboots for an update Linux does not start
- it allows to edit the cmdline of the kernel to recover a system that does not boot, e.g. start in single user mode. That can really save your day if you don't have on hand an USB stick and another PC to flash it
- it allows you to choose between multiple kernels and initrd images easily, again for recovery purposes
- it has a voice for entering the UEFI setup menu: in most modern systems again entering the UEFI with a keyboard combination is unnecessarily difficult and has a too short timeout
- it allows you to boot any other EFI application, such as memtest, or efi shell. Most UEFI firmwares doesn't have a menu to do so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alerighi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by artninja1988 in "Z-Library admins "escape house arrest" after judge approves U.S. extradition"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40908837</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40908837"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T19:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If operating z library is their only "crime" I wish the couple luck and thank them for their service. Hard to say what the money laundering charges are about though]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>artninja1988</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Janeway’s Mesoeconomics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45465</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/08/on-janeways-mesoeconomics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T17:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford “Economics has become irrelevant.” PART ONE Oh my.  Apparently Brad DeLong and I have the same problem.  He, of course, is part of the elite club.  I am decidedly not.  So it is quite a shock to share something. What? He set out to write an 800 word review of Dan Davies’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End Austerity: A Global Report on Budget Cuts and Harmful Social Reforms in 2022-25]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/End-Austerity-A-Global-Report-on-Budget-Cuts-and-Harmful-Social-Reforms-in-2022</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/End-Austerity-A-Global-Report-on-Budget-Cuts-and-Harmful-Social-Reforms-in-2022"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T17:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This report exposes the dangers of a post-pandemic austerity shock, far more premature and severe than the one that followed the global financial crisis. It finds that 85 percent of the world's population is living in the grip of austerity, more than 6.3 billion people. Governments must urgently identify alternative financing options to support their populations that are coping with multiple and compounding crises - from health, energy, finance and climate shocks to unaffordable living (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isabel Ortiz, Matthew Cummins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by RScholar in "Reverse engineering Ticketmaster's rotating barcodes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40907022</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40907022"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T16:50:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Software developers are the wizards and shamans of the modern age. We ought to use our powers with the austerity and integrity such power implies.
This is one of the most powerful truths underlying the world we currently inhabit. The sooner we can agree to behave accordingly, the better our prospects for ripping the reigns of society from the hands of those whose only animating principles are avarice and exploitation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>RScholar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon S3 Access Grants, AWS Lambda, European Sovereign Cloud Region, and more (July 8, 2024).]]></title>
        <id>33de3473228bf0a8001c1a2fab34dcc5d6379d50</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-s3-access-grants-aws-lambda-european-sovereign-cloud-region-and-more-july-8-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T16:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I counted only 21 AWS news since last Monday, most of them being Regional expansions of existing services and capabilities. I hope you enjoyed a relatively quiet week, because this one will be busier. This week, we’re welcoming our customers and partners at the Jacob Javits Convention Center for the AWS Summit New York on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ikesau in "Reverse engineering Ticketmaster's rotating barcodes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40906688</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40906688"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Really good post! I also found this quote which distilled their position in the 404media coverage of the situation.
> “What I can say for sure is that TicketMaster and AXS have had every opportunity to support scam-free third party ticket resale and delivery platforms if they wished: By documenting their ticket QR code cryptography, and by exposing apps and APIs which would allow verification and rotation of ticket secrets,” Conduition told me in an email. “But they intentionally choose not to do so, and then they act all surprised-pikachu when 3rd party resale scams proliferate. They're opting to play legal whack-a-mole with scammers instead of fixing the problem directly with better technology, because they make more money as a resale monopoly than as an open and secure ecosystem.”
from https://www.404media.co/scalpers-are-working-with-hackers-to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ikesau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French elections: political cyber attacks and Internet traffic shifts]]></title>
        <id>668c06d24f58a9000ada4845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/2024-french-elections-political-cyber-attacks-and-internet-traffic-shifts"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check the dynamics of the 2024 French legislative elections, the surprising election results’ impact on Internet traffic changes, and the cyber attacks targeting political parties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Edit My Photos]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/how-i-edit-my-photos/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/how-i-edit-my-photos/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During National Camera Day , I wrote about my non-exhaustive list of cameras I’ve owned. A lot of great discussions came out of this, both via Mastodon and email. One of those things is in regard to my post-processing workflow.

As you can see in my respose to Lou, I currently do very little when it comes to post-processing photos. It wasn’t always like this, but I think that’s a story for another post. This one will focus specifically on what I do now (which isn’t much).
Both of my primary cameras (Fujifilm X100V and Ricoh GRIIIx) have some sort of film simulation that I can set up in-camera and I rely on that to do a majority of my edits.
In my Fujifilm X100V, I primarily use the Reggie’s Portra film sim
Classic Chrome
Dynamic Range: DR-Auto
Highlight: -1
Shadow: -1
Color: +2
Noise Reduc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sascha Engel - Primitive anarchy and the anti-alphabet]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sascha-engel-primitive-anarchy-and-the-anti-alphabet?v=1720450402</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sascha-engel-primitive-anarchy-and-the-anti-alphabet?v=1720450402"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T14:53:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sascha Engel
Title: Primitive anarchy and the anti-alphabet
Date: Summer 2024
Source: Plastic in Utero issue #3

 The way I see it, primitive anarchy is a total challenge to the pacified social field. This means that it is multi-faceted and at once constructive and destructive. Sabotaging the horrors of deep sea mining or “artificial intelligence” requires a different approach than the rewilding of everyday life. Inasmuch as the anti-alphabet is a part of primitive anarchy, it belongs with efforts to rewild everyday life. From this perspective, I think what it does can be summarized in three theses, on which I’ll expand below: 
 1) The terms of the pacified social field – the nouns, verbs, and adjectives of everyday language – are not actually words. Language abolition is only a se…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by deeth_starr_v in "Boeing to plead guilty to criminal fraud charge stemming from 737 MAX crashes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40905437</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40905437"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the article: Paul Cassell, a lawyer for victims’ family members, said he plans to ask the federal judge on the case to reject the deal and “simply set the matter for a public trial, so that all the facts surrounding the case will be aired in a fair and open forum before a jury.”
Hard to disagree]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deeth_starr_v</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bearblog in a nutshell]]></title>
        <id>https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/bearblog-in-a-nutshell/</id>
        <link href="https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/bearblog-in-a-nutshell/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T08:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would hurl words into this darkness, wait for an echo, and if an echo sounded, no matter how faintly, I would send other words to march, to fight, to create a sense of the hunger for life that gnaws in us all, to keep alive in our hearts a sense of the inexpressibly human. -- Richard Wright]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by supernova87a in "Boeing to plead guilty to criminal fraud charge stemming from 737 MAX crashes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40903239</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40903239"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T07:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our governmental methods of punishment for corporations strike me as lacking.  This seems similar to Wells Fargo, where ok, the company was fined, sued, made to pay restitution (somewhat) to victims.  But underlying it all, the culture and incentives at the company that produced the situation didn't get fundamentally changed.   Which often perpetuates across specific leaders, boards, and is a part of what a company is -- and doesn't just get replaced by removing one or two people.
What does it take?   You have to dismantle a company before it changes these kinds of deep-rooted issues?    Or can a government penalty call for that?  That is hard to achieve.  Who's going to change the evaluation procedures that HR has in place to measure what rating or bonus you get this year?  That seems to me as important as who is CEO.
None of the penalties courts mete out (short of dissolution/fined into bankruptcy) seem to be able to achieve this level of change needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>supernova87a</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The physics of running and keeping fit on the Moon]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7967</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/physics-running-keeping-fit-moon/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rhett Allain, writing for Wired, looks at the physics of this important question. If humanity is ever to establish bases on the Moon, ways of keeping occupants fit in the low lunar gravity need to be worked out. A wall of death sort of gizmo, that’s a little like a stationary hamster-wheel, but turned on […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[slapping watermelons]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/slapping-watermelons/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/slapping-watermelons/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite childhood memories is eating watermelons in the summer. Not just the carnal joy of eating them — crunching the sweetness between my teeth and feeling the wetness run down my chin — but the rest of the process too. Watching my dad slap and thump the melons in the supermarket to pick a good one while my brother and I clowned around and mimicked him. Crowding around the cutting board to seeing if we split open a good one. And of course, the best part: spooning the first bite of dark red flesh from the center and watching the juice pour into the crater left behind.
A crate of watermelons greeted me at the supermarket last week and I decided I wanted to buy one for the first time, just to try it. After slapping a few cluelessly (are they supposed to talk back to you or something?) I pushed my cart to a corner and looked up how to pick a good watermelon. I ended up coming across this helpful graphic:

I don't know what my dad was listening for when he tapped and slapped all those watermelons. Like with most things, I'm sure I asked him about it and promptly forgot his answer. In hindsight, I don't think he was that good at choosing them, despite growing up on a farm, because he took home a number of watermelons that were pale and watery inside. And I've been thinking about that as I sprinkle tajín on my watermelon slices and drip pink juice on the counter, how he was probably winging it too, along with the rest of adult- and parenthood, the same way I was slapping watermelons at the market last week and feeling like a fool waiting to be found out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by __turbobrew__ in "A reawakening of systems programming meetups"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40898727</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40898727"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T16:45:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was on the board of directors for a local Linux Users Group and can echo the difficulties in finding a venue. In a city full of empty office spaces on a weekday night it was virtually impossible to find a stable meeting location. Without a stable meeting location you are much less likely to establish a core group since people do not like to have to learn how to get to different venues.
Mozilla hosted us at one point but the political tides changed there and we got kicked out. I think having strong buy in from someone in the C-suite of a company is the only real way to do it. Otherwise you are beholden to the changing winds of the company.
In the end we are now in a stable location in the local library, but only because we had someone on the inside. Previously when we approached the library we were stone walled without someone to grease the wheels.
I do believe that it should be a mandate for the municipality to provide meeting space for local non-profit and special interest groups. In many locations you can no longer pool some money with your buddies to buy a piece of land to build your clubhouse on. In my city there are many such clubs which were formed 50 years ago — the sailing club, the badminton club, the lawn bowling club, etc — but land is too scarce in many places now and we need the municipalities to pick up the slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>__turbobrew__</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by charrondev in "YouTube embeds are heavy and it’s fixable"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40897715</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40897715"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T13:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work on a community forum platform and we detect YouTube embeds and replace them proxied thumbnails that don’t load until clicked.
Just because one person in a thread shares a YouTube video doesn’t mean everyone else loading that page should have to download 1MB+ of YouTube’s JavaScript bloat and have their IPs tracked by google.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>charrondev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jitl in "Show HN: Execute JavaScript in a WebAssembly QuickJS sandbox"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40897658</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40897658"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T13:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I’m the author of the underlying quickjs-emscripten runtime library. I like your ergonomic kind of “standard library” for quickjs-emscripten :)
Did you try running in the browser or with a bundler? I think accepting the variant name as a string you pass to import(variantName) dynamically may not play well with Webpack et al.
EDIT: SECURITY WARNING: this library exposes the ability for the guest (untrusted) code to `fetch` with the same cookies as the host `fetch` function. You must not run untrusted code if enabling `fetch`. Library should come with a big blinking warning about what is safe and unsafe to enable when running untrusted code. It’s not a “sandbox” if the sandboxed code can call arbitrary HTTP APIs authenticated as the host context!
The reason quickjs-emscripten  is low-level and avoids magic is so I can confidently claim that the APIs it does provide are secure. I generally reject feature requests for magical serialization or easy network/filesystem access because that kind of code is a rich area for security mistakes. When you run untrusted code, you should carefully audit the sandbox itself, but also audit all the code you write to expose APIs to the sandbox.
In this case a comment from an other HN user asking about Fetch cookies tipped me off to the potential security issue.
More reading:
Figma blog posts on plugin sandbox security:
- https://www.figma.com/blog/how-we-built-the-figma-plugin-sys...
- https://www.figma.com/blog/an-update-on-plugin-security/
Quickjs-emscripten README: https://github.com/justjake/quickjs-emscripten]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jitl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your trash might be someone else’s treasure]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/trash-treasure/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/trash-treasure/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had dinner with a close friend yesterday.
Afterward, I sent a photo I took of her. She wrote back that she thought it looked awful. I replied that I thought it was beautiful, which I honestly did. I wrote that maybe it's like hearing your voice; it always feels a little strange and "ugly."
The thought lingered while I sat on the subway home…
Perhaps it's the same phenomenon that happens when we're dissatisfied with our writing. The observer and the observed are too close to each other to make a fair judgment. It's like looking at a painting up close and thinking it looks terrible. It's like a trial where the judge and the defendant are the same person.
We are in a constant state of bias when it comes to judging our work.
Anyone who's been blogging for a while has experienced this: You post something you almost threw away because you thought it was garbage, and it turns out to be one of your most popular posts.
Bias.
Next time you find yourself with your index finger resting on the delete button, move it to publish. Your trash might be someone else’s treasure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Swift]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52856</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/07/sunday-photoblogging-swift-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T07:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent many hours trying to take pictures of these over the past three years and have a large collection of indistinct blurs as a result. But I went back to basics, studied the camera setting, watched a bunch of “how to” videos on YouTube and actually managed this one:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by curl-up in "Why Italy Fell Out of Love with Cilantro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40895904</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40895904"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T07:44:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> In 1544, physician and botanist Pietro Andrea Mattioli described the leaves as smelling like bed bugs or stink bugs...
Incredible that neither this, nor the other linked article, even mention the fact that this stink-bug/soap taste is genetically predetermined for some people [1], so above quote can by no means be taken as an argument that cilantro "became unfashionable" so authors started describing it negatively.
Instead, the real story is probably much more interesting, as the changes in cilantro popularity could probably be connected to waves of migrations and general genetic pool changes in a particular place.
[1] https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OR6A2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>curl-up</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by LeFantome in "Advantages of incompetent management"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40894595</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40894595"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T01:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Edit: apologies for the wall of text. A lot of pent up emotion around Creo.]
Best place I ever worked.
This was “the Creo Philosophy”:
Our priority is to provide unique and sustainable value to our customers.
1. All decisions must be based on sound economics.
2. Key decisions are made in consensus, with full team agreement to accept and implement the decision.
3. We believe that people are most effective when self-managed.
4. Compensation is based on contribution, gauged largely by an annual peer review.
5. All employees share the wealth created by their hard work and innovation.
Creo was extremely proud of how “flat” the organization was but my primary take-away from there as an ex-employee is actually how important management is.
First and foremost, management created a shared vision of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LeFantome</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by netcoyote in "Starcraft (A History in Two Acts)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40894363</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40894363"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T00:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a data point, the Blizzard sales team’s projections were that we would sell 4,000 copies of StarCraft in a year in South Korea, so there was no reason to in localize the game.
First year sales were on the order of 100x that amount, quite the surprise for everyone at Blizzard!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>netcoyote</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tonyarkles in "The magic of small engineering teams"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40892151</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40892151"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T18:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most interesting discussions I've had around this was at a small company who mass-hired a bunch of people from a big company. We went round and round in circles for a while because of issues similar to what you're describing. I ran a small 4-6 person hardware team (softly blurry on the edges) and the new people wanted significant amounts of design and documentation review as well as financial oversight. We needed $40 worth of solder and connectors and had to wait a week for PO approval as well as demonstrate that we had gotten multiple quotes... even though there was just a store down the block that sold exactly what we needed.
Anyway, after a month or two of this I started catching significant flak because my team was nowhere near as productive as it used to be. Complaining about slow POs was met with "maybe you should plan better". Complaining about design reviews for one-off boards that would go from idea-to-problem solved was met with "you're engineers, you need to document your work". It was painful and I came very close to resigning.
What ultimately worked, though, was figuring out a catch phrase that spoke the language of the new people: "accountability without authority". This ruffled some feathers but once I repeated "you are trying to hold me accountable for delivering a $500,000 project on time but are not giving me authority to buy $40 worth of stuff to execute on that" enough times it finally got through and the system started to change. But man did it suck for a while.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tonyarkles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You've Got Mail]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/youve-got-mail/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T17:44:04.350Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading Veronique's post this afternoon, Just A Small Town Girl, and smiled at her lovely doodles. But there was one that caught my eye and then, brought a lump to my throat. It featured a stamp and the words, Post Air Mail. And it hit me. I hadn't had any real mail from anyone (not including birthday or Christmas cards) not since my mum passed back in 1999.
It sent a shiver down my spine not just because that was over 20 years ago, but because, the last handwritten letter I ever got, was from a dead woman: my mother.
Where ever I was in the world, travelling and or working, my mother almost religiously took time out of her day to write an aerogramme to me. Do you remember those? You buy them at any post office, singularly or in packs. I think my mother had a draw full of them—after …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thrtythreeforty in "Amazon is bricking $2,350 Astro robots 10 months after release"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40891415</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40891415"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T16:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They are refunding for them. But in my opinion, you only get a couple of these un-launches before you get a reputation like Google has.
Amazon has cancelled lots of consumer stuff in the past (the Alexa buttons or whatever they were) but cancelling business-facing things is new. Businesses are much more cancellation averse than forgetful consumers have proven to be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thrtythreeforty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by supermatt in "Apple okays Epic Games marketplace app in Europe"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40888774</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40888774"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T07:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That third party app stores are subject to review by apple is a problem in itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>supermatt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Barnay: &ldquo;Gaucho-Lepénisme?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gaucho-lepenism"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T18:02:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On France’s far-right vote.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Seymour: &ldquo;Majority Without a Mandate&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/majority-without-a-mandate"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T16:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK election day 2024: traffic trends and attacks on political parties]]></title>
        <id>6687ef98a4598c000bd710d0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/uk-election-day-2024-traffic-trends-and-attacks-on-political-parties"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here, we explore the dynamics of Internet traffic and cybersecurity during the UK’s 2024 general election, highlighting late-day traffic changes and a post-vote attack on a political party]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Familiar Faces&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/familiar-faces"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The photography of Johny Pitts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bye bye, Tories, hello what?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52851</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/05/bye-bye-tories-hello-what/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T09:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the UK, we’re all waking up to the prospect of a new government. The election was an oddity: Labour has converted a modest 35% vote share into a whopping Parliamentary majority; the Tories did somewhat better than suggested, on around 24%, but have lost more than two-thirds of their MPs. (The final figures were […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>