<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-07-31T12:45:09.324Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-07-31T12:45:09.324Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Terraform development with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>300d4fcca3cc4ddfaa28c69451423124ef91adaa</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-your-terraform-development-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post demonstrates how Amazon Q Developer, a generative AI-powered assistant for software development, helps create Terraform templates. Terraform is an infrastructure as code (IaC) tool that provisions and manages infrastructure on AWS safely and predictably. When used in an integrated development environment (IDE), Amazon Q Developer assists with software development, including code generation, explanation, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Rahul Sharad Gaikwad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/31/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275947</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-31-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Change:  Can One Specific Example Counter the Denialists?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275942</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/climate-change-can-one-specific-example-counter-the-denialists.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at climate change impacts, recent and prospective, in coastal Georgia. Can evidence like this change some stubborn minds?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike Lessons: Liability Shields Fuel Risky Practices, Expert Warns]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275959</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-lessons-liability-shields-fuel-risky-practices-expert-warns.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:53:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of the regulatory and behavioral issues that helped produce the Crowdstrike 404.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Balance deployment speed and stability with DORA metrics]]></title>
        <id>8a8dea22000e821c0a8e952928cc68ca33f60778</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/balance-deployment-speed-and-stability-with-dora-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:49:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Development teams adopt DevOps practices to increase the speed and quality of their software delivery. The DevOps Research and Assessment (DORA) metrics provide a popular method to measure progress towards that outcome. Using four key metrics, senior leaders can assess the current state of team maturity and address areas of optimization. This blog post shows […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rostislav Markov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unified Grid: How We Re-Architected Slack for Our Largest Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16924</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/unified-grid-how-we-re-architected-slack-for-our-largest-customers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All software is built atop a core set of assumptions. As new code is added and new use-cases emerge, software can become unmoored from those assumptions. When this happens, a fundamental tension arises between revisiting those foundational assumptions—which usually entails a lot of work—or trying to support new behavior atop the existing architecture. The latter […]
The post Unified Grid: How We Re-Architected Slack for Our Largest Customers appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Hoffman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Nomad - On Why Dr John Drury Is A Collaborationist Asshole]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tom-nomad-on-why-dr-john-drury-is-a-collaborationist-asshole?v=1722415859</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/tom-nomad-on-why-dr-john-drury-is-a-collaborationist-asshole?v=1722415859"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Tom Nomad
Title: On Why Dr John Drury Is A Collaborationist Asshole
Subtitle: A Review of Cop-Out: The Significance of Aufhebengate
Date: 2013, May
Source: Retrieved on July 29, 2021 from <theanvilreview.org/print/aufhebengate>

 On many levels it seems almost pointless to write yet another text on Aufhebengate, especially a review about a book on the scandal and the controversies and collaboration-sympathizing that occurred in the vain, and inexplicable, attempt to defend John Drury from his own actions. Usually interpersonal issues point more to the poverty of the militancy and viability of certain circles of so-called “radical scenes” than anything of consequence. In these cases I would usually not waste my time writing a critique of a second-rate academic who writes for a gener…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Liao - A Catalyst for Fascist Reaction]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction?v=1722415497</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/liao-a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction?v=1722415497"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:44:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Liao
Title: A Catalyst for Fascist Reaction
Date: 7/20/2024
Source: https://www.thecommoner.org.uk/a-catalyst-for-fascist-reaction/

 The fallout from the attempted assassination on United States presidential candidate, Donald J. Trump, will bring an increase in fascist propaganda and reactionary attitudes, while also having serious societal repercussions for marginalized groups and political dissidents. While anarchists typically, and rightfully, disparage engagement in electoral politics, the occurrence of this event will likely have effects far beyond just the 2024 United States election. The main focus of this article is to engage with the likely fallout and effects of such an assassination attempt, rather than discuss the actuality of the attempt in a substantive manner. 
 Lik…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Troubled by Google Maps Reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52892</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/31/troubled-by-google-maps-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just got home from a wonderful trip to Prague, Budapest, and Krakow. All three cities have a rich history of Jewish communities, and one can visit synagogues, musea, and Jewish cemeteries. We visited a number of them, including the very impressive Dohány Street Synagogue in Budapest, which was once the largest synagogue in the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Venezuelan People Stay With the Bolivarian Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329557</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/the-venezuelan-people-stay-with-the-bolivarian-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States has been trying to find a solution to a problem of its own making. Having placed severe sanctions against both Iran and Russia, the United States now cannot easily find a source of energy for its European partners. Liquified natural gas from the United States is expensive and not sufficient. What the U.S. would like is to have a reliable source of oil that is easy to process and in sufficient quantities. Venezuelan oil fits the requirements, but given the U.S. sanctions on Venezuela, this oil cannot be found in the European market. The United States has created a trap from which it finds few solutions. More
The post The Venezuelan People Stay With the Bolivarian Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starvation in Sudan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329567</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/starvation-in-sudan/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For months, we’ve all been able to stay reasonably informed about the wars in Gaza and Ukraine. But there’s another horrific war that’s gotten so little coverage you could be excused for not knowing anything about it. What we have in mind is the seemingly never-ending, utterly devastating war in Sudan. Think of it as the  More
The post Starvation in Sudan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Priti Gulati Cox – Stan Cox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Closes Its Mind and Opens Yours]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329573</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/openai-closes-its-mind-and-opens-yours/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last time I caught up with Edward Snowden online was at his Substack site, Continuing Ed. That was back on September 22, 2022, when he wrote his first piece there in almost a year. He came back briefly to remind us: America’s Open Wound: The CIA is not your friend. Essentially, the piece details the  More
The post OpenAI Closes Its Mind and Opens Yours appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is Cancel Culture, and Is It a Good Thing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329581</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/what-is-cancel-culture-and-is-it-a-good-thing/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing debate about “cancel culture” provides a glimpse into the scope of political polarization in the United States. Opposing sides can’t agree about what it is, who’s doing it to whom, or even whether it exists. Let’s start with a simple summary: The right rejects any attempt to hold people accountable for ugly or  More
The post What Is Cancel Culture, and Is It a Good Thing? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Jensen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Research Stations in Peru and Elsewhere Prepare for Biowarfare]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329576</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/us-research-stations-in-peru-and-elsewhere-prepare-for-biowarfare/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government began preparing for biological warfare during World War II. Biological weapons were employed during the Korean War against North Korea and China. President Nixon in 1969 ended the U.S. use of biological weapons for offensive purposes. The United States joined other nations in approving the Biological Weapons Convention (BWC), which took effect in 1975.  More
The post US Research Stations in Peru and Elsewhere Prepare for Biowarfare appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unspoken]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329533</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/the-unspoken/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How can Annie Jacobsen’s enthralling “Nuclear War: A Scenario” be a NY Times bestseller while there continues to be zero candidate conversation around fundamentally nutty U.S. policies like “launch on warning”? Why don’t we hear anything on the subject from the politicians? The silence is deafening. Jacobsen’s book proves the utter insanity of genocidal nuclear  More
The post The Unspoken appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Winslow Myers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: One World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329483</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/letter-from-london-one-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many know, it was the hottest day ever recorded on earth last week. London was warm yet breezy with flags flapping gently from lofty white flagpoles and one or two tourists fanning themselves with theatre tickets. I was actually attending an outside meeting in Shepherds Market with people working in the green sector. An  More
The post Letter from London: One World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Josh Shapiro Would be a Dangerous Choice as Harris’s Running Mate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329477</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/why-josh-shapiro-would-be-a-dangerous-choice-as-harriss-running-mate/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris has gained strong support as the presumptive Democratic presidential candidate. Putting Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro on the ticket would likely fracture that support. The most divisive issue among Democrats is the U.S.-enabled Israeli war against the civilian population of Gaza. To unify the party and defeat Trump’s MAGA forces, Harris needs to distance  More
The post Why Josh Shapiro Would be a Dangerous Choice as Harris’s Running Mate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Cohen - Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ADA Isn’t Enough: During A Mass Disabling Event, Workers Need Unions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329479</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/the-ada-isnt-enough-during-a-mass-disabling-event-workers-need-unions/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year marks the 34th anniversary of the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), the landmark civil rights legislation that sought to prohibit discrimination against disabled people in employment and public services. It is also the fifth year of a pandemic that experts have deemed a mass-disabling event. Many of those infected with SARS-CoV-2, the virus  More
The post The ADA Isn’t Enough: During A Mass Disabling Event, Workers Need Unions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hayley Brown</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starvation in Sudan: As in Gaza, the Deprivation Is Deliberate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275923</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/starvation-in-sudan-as-in-gaza-the-deprivation-is-deliberate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How a brutal, five year old civil war in Sudan has been producing Gaza-level starvation and war crimes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give Them the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329558</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/give-them-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T05:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was a little girl, I was nourished with healthy food, clean drinking water, safe housing, access to education, adequate medical care, and the loving support of family and friends. As a result, I became an idealist, a perpetual optimist, a lover of people, and a dreamer. It seemed that the world was a  More
The post Give Them the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Fox</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Republicans Probing-attacks on Kamala Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329478</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/31/329478/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T04:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican party faces a new, perplexing challenge in making Donald J. Trump president again. Now, they confront a surge in enthusiasm for a Democratic candidate Biden could not generate. Let’s see how the Republicans found themselves in this predicament. Vice President Kamala Harris bolted out of the gate. A Trump campaign operative told The Bulwark at  More
The post Republicans Probing-attacks on Kamala Harris appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[floating in desire]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/floating-in-desire/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/floating-in-desire/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T23:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had the best small-town weekend again with K.
Country drives, flea market barn jaunts, dinner with his mom, double dog walks + cuddled-up binging our favorite show.

out-the-car-window farm gem
He took me to see his parent's house, where he grew up and has called home his entire life.
It's strange to witness someone have such an intimate connection to land and environment. The ease and pride as he recounts the tapestry of stories that make up his town. I envy his deep roots.
I've moved so many times that I've lost count of how many addresses I've held.
He said he wanted to share his roots with me. Might have been the most romantic thing anyone has ever said to me.

red rubber ball, Courtice, ON
On Sunday, he took me to the Courtice Flea Market, where I found two records that I immediately bought:

Tony Molina, Confront The Truth, 2016. Think: Weezer, The Beatles, with a dash of punk.

Cat Power, Moon Pix, 1998. What a breathtaking cover.
 ✧ you're my internet crush✧
•only two links today bc i've been frolicking in the wildflowers•



Garden of Love Tarot. This gorgeous deck is a burlesque take on the original Tarot de Marseilles. Yes pls.
Cassidy Williams's post about how hard it is to be paid for creative work filled me with over-brimming madness, frustration, and sadness. How do we change our perceptions of money?
heart eyes:
peach cobbler blizzard
Your dad's car by The Rills + Split lip by Delores Forever: playback infinity loop.
Heart spoons for stirring coffee
true-blue laughing with your head back
sensual hand massages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The three main processes used to produce decaffeinated coffee]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8120</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/three-processes-produce-decaffeinated-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tangentially related to the previous post. Do you drink decaffeinated coffee? Did you know there are three common methods used by decaf coffee producers to extract caffeine: the carbon dioxide method, Swiss water process, and finally, solvent-based methods. Not all methods are one-hundred percent effective though, as minute quantities of caffeine remain in the finished […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending July 28, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240730</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240730"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee happy hour, discount prices for early bird customers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8113</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/coffee-happy-hour-discount-prices-early-bird-customers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee happy hours at cafes? This is the first I’ve heard of the idea, but I like it. A growing number of Australian cafes are offering coffees priced at about three dollars a cup, for a couple of hours daily. This compared to the current average cost of about five dollars. Cafe owners concede happy-hour […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.0: Europe is moving to the Right and far Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Version-2-0-Europe-is-moving-to-the-Right-and-far-Right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Version-2-0-Europe-is-moving-to-the-Right-and-far-Right"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In light of the new distribution of seats among the legislative groups in the European Parliament, we are publishing version 2.0 of an article first published in June 2024. This new version has been greatly augmented and updated due to the many events that have taken place in the EU during July. 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 7/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275925</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/200pm-water-cooler-7-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T18:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: politics, syndemics; Democrat idpol, Amazon now responsible for product recalls, Covid at the Olympics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day Log 001 - working out, naming plants, and green tea lattes]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/day-log-001-working-out-naming-plants-and-green-tea-lattes/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/day-log-001-working-out-naming-plants-and-green-tea-lattes/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven't been feeling like myself lately. It’s a similar story to feeling like every day is the same, so I’m not going to go into that again. I’m trying my best to remediate and course correct before it’s too late, but I’m not sure if I’m doing that great of a job.
When I get into this head space, one of the things that helps is working out and running. Runners high and all that. I attempted to wake up 2 hours before my meeting to give myself time to get a workout in but I failed… epically. It’s no surprise because I really am NOT a morning person, so 5am wake up calls are next to impossible.
So maybe I should’ve set a more attainable goal for myself.
It’s still a few hours before noon and I’m already exhausted. The goal is to get a workout in after work instead, or sometime in the evenin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Win ‘Medicare for All,’ First Reclaim Medicare From Profiteers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275920</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/to-win-medicare-for-all-first-reclaim-medicare-from-profiteers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T14:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on the promise of Medicare means taking on the private-sector enriching,  skimpy  “Medicare Advantage” program]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/30/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275847</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/links-7-30-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our miraculous daily links: kiwi hangouts, CA Covid surge, Japan back to nukes? China EVs, EU weak economy, UK bennie cuts, Israel-Hezbollah worries, NewsGuard targets critic Turley, 2024 gender war, Biden pretends not to be a lame duck, AI, McDonald falters, CBDCs v. freedom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groundhog Day in Venezuela]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275835</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/groundhog-day-in-venezuela.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nicolas Maduro "wins" presidential elections but the opposition, the US and US-aligned governments in the region refuse to accept results. Eyes are now on Brazil, Mexico and Colombia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Abolish the Colonial IMF on Its 80th Birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275895</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/lets-abolish-the-colonial-imf-on-its-80th-birthday.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:21:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing country protesters want the IMF to stop exploiting countries in debt crisis. But is BRICS prepared to fill the gap?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Censorship to Defend Democracy”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=275898</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/07/censorship-to-defend-democracy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZOMG, VoxEU starts with the premise that censorship is of course warranted, but finds current implementations have not worked well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Mixed Legacy and a Chance for Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329444</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/bidens-mixed-legacy-and-a-chance-for-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When President Joseph R. Biden finally removed himself from the race for a second presidential term on July 21, there followed a cascade of high praise, not only for his “brave decision” to step down but also for his “remarkable achievements” over a lifetime of public service. Both long-time colleagues and the major media applauded  More
The post Biden’s Mixed Legacy and a Chance for Change appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025: A New Pax Romana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329507</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/project-2025-a-new-pax-romana/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roman poet Juvenal coined the phrase “bread and circuses” nearly 2,000 years ago for the extravagant entertainment the Roman Empire used to distract attention from imperial policies that caused widespread discontent. Imagine the lavish banquets, gladiatorial bouts, use and abuse of young men and women for the pleasure of the rich, and so much more that characterized the later years of that empire. And none of it seems that far off from the situation we, in these increasingly dis-United States, find ourselves in today. More
The post Project 2025: A New Pax Romana appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LIZ THEOHARIS - SHAILLY GUPTA BARNES</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Watering Down’ Genocide: No More Moral Compromises on Palestine, Please]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329492</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/watering-down-genocide-no-more-moral-compromises-on-palestine-please/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:58:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why are many amongst us still tiptoeing around language when it comes to the horrific Israeli genocide in Gaza? Layers of censorship imposed on Palestinian and pro-Palestinian voices in corporate and social media seem to have blurred the judgment of some. They continue to speak of a ‘conflict’, calling on ‘both sides’ to use ‘restraint’  More
The post ‘Watering Down’ Genocide: No More Moral Compromises on Palestine, Please   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Venezuelan Opposition Cries Fraud; People Reelect President Maduro]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329526</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/venezuelan-opposition-cries-fraud-people-reelect-president-maduro/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly before midnight, the president of the National Electoral Council (CNE), Elvis Amoroso, announced the re-election of Venezuela’s President Nicolas Maduro. Like the proverbial boy who cried wolf, the US-backed and funded far-right opposition cried fraud. Maduro won with 51.2% of the vote. His nearest rival, the far-right US-backed candidate Edmundo Gonzalez trailed by 7 percentage points. More
The post Venezuelan Opposition Cries Fraud; People Reelect President Maduro appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From the UK, a New Reminder Why Inequality Must Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329436</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/from-the-uk-a-new-reminder-why-inequality-must-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inequality, note Wilkinson and Pickett, heightens hierarchy and reinforces the notion that some people — rich people — have more intrinsic value than people of more modest means. Within this unequal social reality, “people worry more about how they’re seen and judged.” Status rules supreme, leaving some among us “overcome with a sense of inadequacy and depression” while a fortunate few view life through an exceptionally narcissistic lens. More
The post From the UK, a New Reminder Why Inequality Must Go appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Sum Game With a Fatal Option]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329445</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/zero-sum-game-with-a-fatal-option/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most Israelis perceive their national life as a zero sum game. This may well be a lasting heritage of the Holocaust. Accurately perceived or not, survival is always in question in their minds. You win or you lose. Only short term tactical compromises are allowed. Negotiations with enemies are often fraudulent delaying tactics. All of  More
The post Zero Sum Game With a Fatal Option appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foregone Conclusions: Paul Kagame Retains Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329509</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/foregone-conclusions-paul-kagame-retains-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rwanda has become a curiosity as an African state.  The mere mention of its name tugs the memory: colonial tragedy, ethnic violence, genocide.  Then comes stable rule, for the most part.  It is assured, iron fisted, and corporate.  Since being elected in April 2000, the country has known one leader. Paul Kagame has kept matters running as smoothly much  More
The post Foregone Conclusions: Paul Kagame Retains Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America, Israel-Palestine, and The Goals of Empire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329511</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/america-israel-palestine-and-the-goals-of-empire/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli-Hamas “war” has dramatically changed the trajectory geopolitical affairs in the Middle East, with talk of a Palestinian state not this prevalent since the days of the failed Oslo Accords in the 90s. Hamas’ attack, and the subsequent response from Israeli forces in their destruction of Gaza, has served to create a window of political  More
The post America, Israel-Palestine, and The Goals of Empire appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Inskeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The High Cost of Protectionism: AI Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329458</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/the-high-cost-of-protectionism-ai-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Economists go on endless diatribes against tariffs and quotas as costly policies that raise prices to consumers and slow economic growth. There is considerable truth to this story, even if economists and politicians often exaggerate their case to push favored policies. While virtually all economists will go to their graves touting the evils of protectionism  More
The post The High Cost of Protectionism: AI Edition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Wars with No Way Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329494</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/two-wars-with-no-way-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People involved in conflict resolution often say that every war must end. Most wars do end in some fashion, but plenty of wars—and the wars in Ukraine and Israel appear to be among them—drag on indefinitely, with no prospect for a cease-fire much less a peace settlement. These intractable conflicts most often are civil wars  More
The post Two Wars with No Way Out appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teamsters Über Alles?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329496</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/30/teamsters-uber-alles/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teamster General President Sean O’Brien’s speech before the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee was a public relation’s fiasco. His fawning praise for former President Donald Trump (“one tough S.O.B”) to his shout outs to Josh Hawley and JD Vance, two U.S. Senators closely aligned with European Fascism and anti-union politics, along with the enthusiastic applause from fascist-friendly commentator Tucker Carlson,  More
The post Teamsters Über Alles? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I used AI to generate a robots.txt that blocks AI]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/ai-scrapers-post/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/ai-scrapers-post/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T03:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so fucking lazy. I've never really messed with robots.txt. I'm kinda new to personal blogging; back in the 2000s I had a tech blog but I wanted everything to index my site. I even submitted my link to a bunch of off brand search engines to get my name out there.
But now there's AI bots scraping websites like iFixit literally a million times a day.
I don't hate AI. I'm not an AI doomer. But that's fucking silly.
Maybe it's just me or maybe Google is terrible these days, but all I could find were blog posts six months old or more that just listed individual scrapers that are probably outdated anyway. So I asked Claude 3.5 to generate me a robots.txt file to block all known AI scrapers and I think it did alright! Here's what I got:
(edit: updated on 7/30/2024 for clarity)

# Block AI Crawlers
User-agent: GPTBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: ChatGPT-User
Disallow: /

User-agent: CCBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: Google-Extended
Disallow: /

User-agent: anthropic-ai
Disallow: /

User-agent: Claude-Web
Disallow: /

User-agent: ClaudeBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: cohere-ai
Disallow: /

User-agent: PerplexityBot
Disallow: /

User-agent: FacebookBot
Disallow: /

# Allow Search Engine Crawlers
User-agent: Googlebot
Allow: /

User-agent: Bingbot
Allow: /

User-agent: Slurp
Allow: /

User-agent: DuckDuckBot
Allow: /

User-agent: Applebot
Allow: /

User-agent: Baiduspider
Allow: /

User-agent: Yandexbot
Allow: /

# Default rule
User-agent: *
Allow: /]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS and Multicloud: Existing capabilities & continued enhancements]]></title>
        <id>3ad3398ec7978d558ff6e7bf3304bd20c3a758d9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-and-multicloud-existing-capabilities-continued-enhancements/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T23:28:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS extends existing operational/management capabilities to simplify multicloud oversight. Learn about their approach, recent hybrid/multicloud service launches (18 in 2023), and helpful resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital and growth]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45503</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/29/capital-and-growth/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T21:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We’ve lots of evidence from different times and places that the elasticity of output with respect to capital is indeed small. In his famous paper which kickstarted this approach to thinking about economic growth, Robert Solow estimated (pdf) that only one-eighth of the increase in US GDP per worker between 1900 and 1949 was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only some search engines can access and index Reddit content]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8109</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/only-some-search-engines-access-index-reddit-content/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T21:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google, and Brave Search, are apparently the only search engines permitted to crawl Reddit, and index content published there. Other search engines, including Bing and Duck Duck Go, are presently being prevented from accessing the “front page of the internet” forum and discussion website. Reddit appears to be concerned that search engines other than Google […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java 21 Virtual Threads - Dude, Where’s My Lock?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3052540e231d</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/java-21-virtual-threads-dude-wheres-my-lock-3052540e231d?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting real with virtual threads]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Llama 3.1, Mistral Large 2, AWS Step Functions, AWS Certifications update, and more (July 29, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>e41b9826185fe73ffc313cb5af4abba941bb013f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-llama-3-1-mistral-large-2-aws-step-functions-aws-certifications-update-and-more-july-29-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T18:02:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m always amazed by the talent and passion of our Amazon Web Services (AWS) community members, especially in their efforts to increase diversity, equity, and inclusion in the tech community. Last week, I had the honor of speaking at the AWS User Group Women Bay Area meetup, led by Natalie. This group is dedicated to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saul Nelson: &ldquo;Volume and Shape&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/volume-and-shape</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/volume-and-shape"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tropical Modernism at the V&A.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing your applications with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>135275189c4d14e80cdccdb60c74a99c2f0e35ea</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/testing-your-applications-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing code is a fundamental step in the field of software development. It ensures that applications are reliable, meet quality standards, and work as intended. Automated software tests help to detect issues and defects early, reducing impact to end-user experience and business. In addition, tests provide documentation and prevent regression as code changes over time. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Svenja Raether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OpenID Connect with AWS Toolkit for Azure DevOps to perform AWS CodeDeploy deployments]]></title>
        <id>03a6fcf4bb262fc14a5703bc5eb893441a48c0e8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-openid-connect-with-aws-toolkit-for-azure-devops-to-perform-aws-codedeploy-deployments/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Many organizations with workloads hosted on AWS leverage the advantage of AWS services like AWS CloudFormation, AWS CodeDeploy, and other AWS developer tools while integrating with their existing development workflows. These customers seek to maintain their preferred version control systems, such as GitHub, and continue using their established continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rakesh Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth CADTM-Africa University, in coordination with the World March of Women (WMW) and the National Forum on Economic and Social Strategies (FNSES),]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-fourth-CADTM-Africa-University-in-coordination-with-the-World-March-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-fourth-CADTM-Africa-University-in-coordination-with-the-World-March-of"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the slogan “Avoiding the Scenario of ‘Lost' Economic Decades: A Feminist Perspective on the Debt Crisis in Africa, the Necessary Reform of the International Financial Architecture, and the Global Tax System”. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Africa]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM Afrique</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding downtime: modern alternatives to outdated certificate pinning practices]]></title>
        <id>669eb83f58eb3b000a368e32</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/why-certificate-pinning-is-outdated"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of outages caused by certificate pinning is increasing. We’ll explore why certificate pinning hasn’t kept up with modern standards and recommend alternatives to improve security while reducing management overhead]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unione Sindacale Italiana - Italian syndicalists speak out]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unione-sindacale-italiana-italian-syndicalists-speak-out?v=1722255434</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unione-sindacale-italiana-italian-syndicalists-speak-out?v=1722255434"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T12:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Unione Sindacale Italiana
Title: Italian syndicalists speak out
Subtitle: The USI-AIT denounces what happened at the latest “IWA Congress” in Warsaw
Date: December 29, 2016
Source: Retrieved on 29th July 2024 from lifelongwobbly.com

 The Unione Sindacale Italiana was one of the founding members of the International Workers Association in 1922. Refounded in 1977 after Italy’s “Hot Autumn,” they have been the second-largest and most workplace-focused IWA section for a long time after the Spanish CNT. They have a reputation for avoiding sectarianism, prioritizing solidarity, and maintaining cool heads. Together with the CNT and the German FAU they organized the recent Bilbao Conference of revolutionary unions, and were expelled from the IWA shortly after. [This and all other footnote…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tensors from Scratch #2: Elementwise operations and Broadcasting]]></title>
        <id>https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-2/</id>
        <link href="https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a series of blog posts that will hopefully let you understand what exactly are Tensors, and how you can too implement them from scratch in C. I will be going from basic definitions, illustrations, and explanations to the actual code implementation in this series.
Don't worry, I'm here to help :)
In the part 1 of "Tensors from Scratch" we discussed about what tensors actually are how the shape of a tensor can give us important information about the tensor itself. As a recap:
tensor is an umbrella term for "mathematical objects" or "containers" that have a rank/dimensionality associated with them.
Scalars are rank-0 tensors, vectors are rank-1 tensors, matrices are rank-2 tensors and so on.
One important property of a tensor is its shape. Shape is defined as: the number of elements p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amor y Rabia - Beyond the IWA]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/amor-y-rabia-beyond-the-iwa?v=1722240371</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/amor-y-rabia-beyond-the-iwa?v=1722240371"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T08:06:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Amor y Rabia
Title: Beyond the IWA
Subtitle: An Interview with the CNT’s International Secretary
Date: January 4, 2017
Notes: This interview was originally published in Spanish, in two parts. English translation by Lifelong Wobbly.
Source: Retrieved on 29th July 2024 from libcom.org

 Discretely, almost silently, something is happening which will have serious consequences for the future of the international Anarchist movement: the reorganization of anarcho-syndicalism on a global scope, at the initiative of the CNT. Following the agreements of its XI Congress in 2015, the CNT – together with the German FAU and the Italian USI – has organized an international conference of anarcho-syndicalist and revolutionary unions (November 26–27, Bilbao). To understand the goals of this conferen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europop]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52897</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/29/europop/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One reaction I heard to the Olympic opening ceremony was that continental Europe has been rubbish at popular music for the past century. Given that Céline Dion had just nailed Edith Piaf’s Hymne d’amour the timing of this opinion wasn’t great, but still, I found myself semi-agreeing on first reaction. Admittedly, the so-called anglosphere has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Personal Discussion of Russian National Security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329431</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/a-personal-discussion-of-russian-national-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T06:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I correctly anticipated significant criticism of my last piece for CounterPunch, which argued that President Vladimir Putin’s was not “unproved,” that NATO expansion was a significant factor in the Russian use of force, and that our policymakers and so-called experts failed to understand the central national security aspects of Soviet/Russian policy.  Among the critics of my CounterPunch article were Walter Slocomb who served in Clinton’s national security council and lobbied for NATO expansion, and a former colleague of mine at the National War College, Marvin Ott, who supported expansion and is anticipating a Russian victory in Ukraine to be followed by Putin’s aggression elsewhere. More
The post A Personal Discussion of Russian National Security appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Civil Wars Start]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329430</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/how-civil-wars-start/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a growing division in the U.S. between what seem to be almost irreconcilable opposites.  It is hard to see how that division will be resolved short of some kind of conflict. One can hope it will not be bloody, though the violent history of this country does not inspire confidence. In any event, whoever is elected this November, a vast segment of the U.S. population will be deeply unhappy, in fact feel existentially threatened. That is the recipe for divisive clashes. More
The post How Civil Wars Start appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Mazza</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brother is Already at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329463</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/big-brother-is-already-at-work/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A highlight of the Olympic flame’s peregrinations through France was its meeting with a “102-year-old former Resistance fighter”, which was celebrated by the country’s media, who were quick to see it as an apotheosis of the flame’s… humanist and pacifist virtues. All the more so as this otherwise very sympathetic old lady declared that she  More
The post Big Brother is Already at Work appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aleida March Kisses and Tells All in New Memoir about Che Guevara, Herself and the Cuban Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329461</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/aleida-march-kisses-and-tells-all-in-new-memoir-about-che-guevara-herself-and-the-cuban-revolution/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In one of her best-known songs, Tina Turner, the “Queen of Rock ‘n’ Roll,” asks, “What’s love got to do with it?” For Che “it” was everything. His second wife, Aleida March, provides much the same idea in her story of romance and revolution, perhaps the most romantic of reveries. Now 87 and older than  More
The post Aleida March Kisses and Tells All in New Memoir about Che Guevara, Herself and the Cuban Revolution appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Olympic Games: Perennially Costly and Always Over Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329465</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/the-olympic-games-perennially-costly-and-always-over-budget/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another entertainingly corrupt sporting event has just started in Paris, opening with a barge packed ceremony on the Seine.  Thousands of simpering commentators, paid-up media gawkers and bored influencers have been ready with their computers, phones and confected dreams.  As always, the Olympics throws up the question about how far the host city has managed to come  More
The post The Olympic Games: Perennially Costly and Always Over Budget appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Violence Has No Place in American Life.’ Except, Like, Everywhere You Look]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329442</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/violence-has-no-place-in-american-life-except-like-everywhere-you-look/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. political system runs on the fuel of euphemism—the ability to conceal nefarious aspirations beneath the facade of idealistic slogans. Consider the U.S. Department of Corporate Violence (USDOCV) which, oddly, we have renamed the U.S. Department of Defense (USDOD). I use the word, renamed rather loosely, for The Department of Corporate Violence always required  More
The post ‘Violence Has No Place in American Life.’ Except, Like, Everywhere You Look appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Humanity Has Two Choices: Unification or Mass Suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329440</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/humanity-has-two-choices-unification-or-mass-suicide/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The intensifying cascade of global crises including intractable wars, massive human rights atrocities, nuclear proliferation, climate change and environmental degradation, the growing inequality between the rich and the poor, recurring bouts of global financial instability, and the increasing risks of pandemics to name but a few, call to mind the warning sounded by Arnold Toynbee,  More
The post Humanity Has Two Choices: Unification or Mass Suicide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sovaida Maani Ewing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[War, Genocide and Coups]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329360</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/07/29/war-genocide-and-coups/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Imperialist chickens have come home to roost One of the defining characteristics of the current crisis is the speed at which contradictory social, political and ideological dynamics can change with contradictions shifting from primary to secondary, antagonistic to non-antagonist and conflicts of interests, as well as struggles among the capitalist oligarchy producing new intra-bourgeois  More
The post War, Genocide and Coups appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajamu Baraka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics?v=1722231189</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics?v=1722231189"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics
Date: 07/26/2024
Source: https://unravel.noblogs.org/from-a-matter-of-principle-to-a-matter-of-tactics/

From a Matter of Principle to a Matter of Tactics
 Anarchists who want to take action, when confronted with the choice of tactics, often default to large mass actions, like black bloc. Imagination is ceded to tactical hegemony; autonomy diminishes; creativity recedes; resistance is franchised with stale, processed, prepackaged ideologies and tactics; questionable organizational methods like spokes-councils and democratic decision making give a participatory veneer to a sealed deal–just like in any liberal democracy; most participants spectate rather than act, learning by passive imitation of the leaders rather th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchistische Büchermesse Berlin-Kreuzberg, The Friends of the Class War - When the exhaustion of concepts intensifies]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchistische-buchermesse-berlin-kreuzberg-the-friends-of-the-class-war-when-the-exhaustion-of?v=1722229498</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchistische-buchermesse-berlin-kreuzberg-the-friends-of-the-class-war-when-the-exhaustion-of?v=1722229498"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T05:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchistische Büchermesse Berlin-Kreuzberg, The Friends of the Class War
Title: When the exhaustion of concepts intensifies
Date: 2024
Notes: Source in German: https://anarchistischebuechermesse.noblogs.org/?p=231 English translation: The Friends of the Class War
Source: https://www.autistici.org/tridnivalka/abmb-when-the-exhaustion-of-concepts-intensifies/

 As we are unfortunately repeatedly confronted with groups that support the Ukrainian side in the war between Russia and the Ukraine from an allegedly “anarchist” position, and as an article appeared in April (When ideology gets in the way of solidarity) in which ABC-Belarus was surprised that we described them as supporters of the war and therefore we did not invite them to the bookfair, here are a few words from us. More tha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[dreaming of a low country boil]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/low-country-boil/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/low-country-boil/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T23:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I learned that in Portugal someone flirting is said to be fazendo olhinhos, or literally “making little eyes”. I can’t express how much I love that.
I spent yesterday morning accompanying a close friend from college while he shopped for a 6 monthversary gift. I've met his girlfriend a few times and we get along well, which comes as a small surprise to me because while I am on good terms with the rest of my friends' partners, I can't think of any that I would be friends with in other contexts. (Sorry — I just find it difficult to imagine.)
I like the way her presence brings out a different side of my friend, even though I would be hard pressed to describe the change in words. I hesitate to call it a better side, but I do appreciate her steering our conversations and interactions (unco…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warm tones in San Francisco]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/warm-tones-in-san-francisco/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/warm-tones-in-san-francisco/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A mini collection of photos taken on 07-05-24 along Spear Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudden Stratospheric Warming is bringing weird weather to parts of Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8103</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/sudden-stratospheric-warming-weird-weather-parts-australia/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T21:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[El Niño and La Niña are global metrological events most people are probably familiar with. In Australia, the influence of one or other seems more pronounced over the summer months. El Niño marks periods when ocean temperatures in parts of the Pacific Ocean rise by a certain amount, while La Niña events refer to occasions […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[showing that you care on the tiny internet]]></title>
        <id>https://oak.bearblog.dev/showing-that-you-care-on-the-tiny-internet/</id>
        <link href="https://oak.bearblog.dev/showing-that-you-care-on-the-tiny-internet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T18:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past week, I have enjoyed reading various Bear Blog blogs. It's really interesting to see different viewpoints, and thoughts that are less filtered, and more raw. It reminds me of a simpler era of the internet before social media took over.
A recurring theme that has caught my attention - is mental health, various dealings, thoughts, struggles, and victories. All in all these blogs are written by different people at different points in their lives. Yet, they are connected by this platform on this corner of the internet.
Usually, there are not many interactions with the blog author. It’s just a thought written into the void. Nonetheless, I feel sometimes it’s important to show that somebody hears them. blogline by Robert actually inspired me to write this post.
Maybe an email or a simple upvote is all needed to show that you care?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[let's get weird with it]]></title>
        <id>https://goofpunk.com/lets-get-weird-with-it/</id>
        <link href="https://goofpunk.com/lets-get-weird-with-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T18:29:51.207Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been feeling weird about my blog recently. It's a thoughtful place for me, but it's also felt like a sort of put-on place, like I'm playing a specific version of myself, or like my site has developed a brand or style, which I've already mentioned not liking. So going into the next month of blogging, I have a new mantra: Let's get weird with it. More mini-posts that are just for me, more experimental posts like this one, and a less bland CSS theme (I'll be switching to Bear's "Plain HTML" theme while I work on the new theme, sorry! It makes developing it easier). Idk what my goal is here, but I'm not gonna let myself be bored with my own blog, so here we go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get bored with me: The BearBored Challenge]]></title>
        <id>https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/get-bored-with-me-the-bearbored-challenge/</id>
        <link href="https://corneliuswastaken.bearblog.dev/get-bored-with-me-the-bearbored-challenge/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was inspired by Sit.
What is this?
I am bored. I want to get bored a bit more. Get bored with me. Come join.
The goal?
The goal of the challenge is to waste time. To be as unproductive. To "bear the boredness". (I swear I could think of a better name)
You will need...
A timer (I use the iPhone built-in Clock app. Feel free to choose your own.)
A notebook / sheets of paper
A pen
How to get started:
Step 1: Decide on how long you want to get bored.
15-60 minutes. 5-12 sessions with each session 3-5 minutes long.
Step 2: Write down on your notebook a list of numbers from 1 to X. (X = the number of sessions you chose). 
1.54:59 
Step 3: Start the timer, do nothing and get bored.
Step 4: When each session ends, think of one word that captures the theme of that session. It can be a noun, a verb, an adjective; an emotion, an action, some random vocabulary. Your choice! Write that word down next to the numbered list. 
1.54:59 Distraction 
That is all!
Note:
These are rules I follow when I am doing the challenge. Feel free not to.
No usage of pen and paper besides writing down the keyword. By all means think but let your thoughts slip. Do not write them down. The goal is to be unproductive.
Try not to doze off during the challenge.
Try not to engage in any other activities besides sitting or pacing. Pause the timer if you need to drink water or adjust your posture.
I have been trying this for a couple of days. Turns out getting bored for an hour is way harder than, say, focusing on a textbook and study for an hour. I want to post this to see if anyone is interested in such a format. Write me emails about what more I can do to get the most out of this challenge. Feel free to join me on this journey as well. Let me know if you do!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We have a blogline]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blogline/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blogline/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eriq's entry in my guestbook led me to his recent post, Going from spark to a steady fire. He describes how passions often ignite intensely before rapidly fading away.
I completely resonate with this, just as he did after reading my post I wish I was more dedicated:
It's ridiculous how well that echoes into what I've written above.
Several others have reached out about the same post. One email started with "Dude, that's my life too." The sender described being incredibly invested in a project one week and wanting to abandon it entirely the next.
I've been on the brink of shutting down this blog multiple times, as recently as yesterday. It's hanging by a thread. I’m fighting to keep it going, but the outcome is far from certain.
It's living on borrowed time, like a patient on a ventilator. I'm constantly considering pulling the plug. It's like a dragonfly that's been granted several extra lives, but now feels like its luck is running out. It's sneaking around like a cat aware that its nine lives are nearly spent.
It might sound bleak, but it's my reality. I doubt it will ever change. Yet, there's beauty in it too:
I'm not alone.
It becomes so clear when we share our doubts and shortcomings. When others comment on our posts or send messages.
We're not alone.
Blogging is a fantastic outlet for venting while also fostering a sense of community. Keeping a private diary doesn't have the same impact for me.
Blogging is both liberating and inclusive.
I'm not alone. You're not alone.
We have a blogline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaugust: A Festival of Blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/blaugust-a-festival-of-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/blaugust-a-festival-of-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I stumbled across the Blaugust blogging challenge and thought it would be a good idea to participate. So I decided to join in for the first time.
"Blaugust is a month-long event that takes place each August which focuses on blogging primarily and has started to include other forms of serialized content over the last several years. The goal is to stoke the fires of creativity and allow bloggers and other content creators to mingle in a shared community while pushing each other to post more regularly. Above all the goal of Blaugust has always been to prove to folks that they can in fact sit down every day and create something fresh and then share it with the world. Posting regularly builds a community and in this era of AI-slop content, our voices are needed even more than we ever have been at any point in the past."
– Belghast, Blaugust 2024 is Coming
I hope that Blaugust will help me avoid thinking too much about writing...
Wish me luck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Liverpool]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52889</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/28/sunday-photoblogging-liverpool-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T07:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flow]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52883</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/27/flow/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T22:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you all experience flow? Or rather, as I think everyone does at times, do you experience it often? Obviously I have written plenty of words in my life, but this is not generally something you experience when writing blog posts unless you are maybe excoriating someone in an unnecessarily profane way that is–fundamentally–unfair. Like, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tensors from Scratch #1: Tensors and their Shapes]]></title>
        <id>https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-1/</id>
        <link href="https://maharshi.bearblog.dev/tensors-from-scratch-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a series of blog posts that will let you understand what exactly are Tensors, and how you can too implement them from scratch in C. I will be going from basic definitions, illustrations, and explanations to the actual code implementation in this series.
Don't worry, I'm here to help :)
Before jumping into the implementation of tensors, we first need to understand what are tensors and how can we define them.
Tensors
What the hell do I mean when I say the word tensor? Let's start from the beginning.
Imagine a number say,
$$
x = 33
$$
This number $x$ is just a value and it is "dimensionless" i.e. we cannot attach any arrows to this number in the sense that tells us what this number is made up of. We call numbers like this Scalars. The dimensionality of a scalar is $0$.
Note: in order …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax justice in Pakistan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Tax-justice-in-Pakistan</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Tax-justice-in-Pakistan"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Press statement Abolish taxation from electricity bills Reduce the price of electricity to 10 Rupees a unit Impose a super tax on the rich 
English

/ 
Pakistan, 
Tax Justice, 
Inflation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pakistan Kissan Rabita Committee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[tonight]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/tonight/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/tonight/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sitting on the balcony, listening to America by Simon & Garfunkel, and drinking a glass of rosé. Almost Famous comes to mind. Great film.

It's all happening...
Thinking about lost friendships. How one minute you're saying i love you, and the next, they're gone, and you're left wondering what they're doing with their time, and wishing you could to talk to them like it was the old days.
july songs so far:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Gorrion - We Want to Be Great Like Our Crime]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alex-gorrion-we-want-to-be-great-like-our-crime?v=1722015984</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alex-gorrion-we-want-to-be-great-like-our-crime?v=1722015984"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T17:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alex Gorrion
Title: We Want to Be Great Like Our Crime
Subtitle: The Criminal Ego and the Struggle in Society
Date: June 20, 2010
Source: The Anvil Review

 On Isabelle Eberhardt's “Criminal” and Renzo Novatore's “Toward the Creative Nothing” 
 Quotes refer to the Eberhardt Press edition and the Venomous Butterfly Publications edition, respectively. 
Crime
 In “Criminal,” Isabelle Eberhardt's memoir of land colonization in Algeria written around the turn of the last century, the farmer Mohammed Achouri cuts an interesting figure. A “tall thin old man with the face of an ascetic, his hard features set in an expression of constant preoccupation”, a quiet character who stands “a bit apart from the others”, he is not a likely hero. Though he stands out, and in fact his inability to fit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louis Rogers: &ldquo;Those Days&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/those-days</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/those-days"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The work of Helen Garner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bear Blog is Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://martinschuhmann.com/bear-blog-is-fun/</id>
        <link href="https://martinschuhmann.com/bear-blog-is-fun/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven't written much on my blog in the last few weeks...
I've started some blog posts here and there but haven't finished them. Or I simply didn't publish them for various reasons.
Instead, I created a few slash pages, experimented with my site design, jotted down a few new ideas, read plenty of blog posts from the discovery feed and emailed with some wonderful Bear bloggers.
And I had a lot of fun doing these things...
At first, it felt weird not to finish and publish any blog posts. It also caused me some anxiety. But blogging should be fun...
For me, Bear Blog is fun.
So instead of thinking too much about writing…
I enjoyed experimenting, reading and socializing on Bear Blog.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Old Ass, a film by Megan Park, with Maisy Stella, Aubrey Plaza]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8079</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/my-old-ass-film-megan-park-maisy-stella-aubrey-plaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canadian actor and director Megan Park’s latest feature, My Old Ass, trailer, would be a sure bet to win movie title of the year, should such an award exist. Otherwise, My Old Ass is on my want-to-see movie list because of the time-travel-like, older-self goes back in time to see their younger-self, and dispense some […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elizabeth Schmidt: &ldquo;Evil Empires?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/evil-empires</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/evil-empires"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T19:23:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Africa and the New Cold War.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bullet Journalling — One notebook to replace them all!]]></title>
        <id>https://alexandrawolfe.ca/bullet-journalling-one-notebook-to-replace-them-all/</id>
        <link href="https://alexandrawolfe.ca/bullet-journalling-one-notebook-to-replace-them-all/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T19:15:42.715Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["In the journal I do not just express myself more openly than I could do to any person; I create myself." — Susan Sontag
To keep myself organised and, because I love paper and all things stationery, I've been a journalist all my life. From writing in little spiral-bound notebooks and school exercise books as a child, right on through to a fancy leather-bound Midori (an expensive Japanese notebook) that was a birthday gift. I've been an avid note-maker since I was able to hold a pencil and write.
I've used all sorts of notebooks to scribble in, and even tried the made for journaling journal by Baron Fig—yes, what a great name! Never mind the journal that everyone seems to hold as sacred, the Leuchtturm1917. But amongst them all, big, small, ruled, dotted or blank, fancy, plain, expensive or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to migrate your AWS CodeCommit repository to another Git provider]]></title>
        <id>7b4f30aa5139d59db24b0c92c6d45ed59b18e7f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-to-migrate-your-aws-codecommit-repository-to-another-git-provider/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After careful consideration, we have made the decision to close new customer access to AWS CodeCommit, effective July 25, 2024. AWS CodeCommit existing customers can continue to use the service as normal. AWS continues to invest in security, availability, and performance improvements for AWS CodeCommit, but we do not plan to introduce new features. Customers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodney Bozo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to migrate from AWS Cloud9 to AWS IDE Toolkits or AWS Cloudshell]]></title>
        <id>bba8f9032da39f3ffdf7150385f778f13e2a1674</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-to-migrate-from-aws-cloud9-to-aws-ide-toolkits-or-aws-cloudshell/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After careful consideration, we have made the decision to close new customer access to AWS Cloud9, effective July 25, 2024. AWS Cloud9 existing customers can continue to use the service as normal. AWS continues to invest in security, availability, and performance improvements for AWS Cloud9, but we do not plan to introduce new features. Building […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodney Bozo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do domestic food prices keep going up when global prices fall?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45495</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/07/25/why-do-domestic-food-prices-keep-going-up-when-global-prices-fall/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from C. P. Chandrasekhar and Jayati Ghosh In the past three years, global food prices have been on a roller coaster, rising rapidly especially in the first half of 2022 due to a speculative bubble and then falling from July 2022 onwards (Figure 1). The phase of rising food prices led to increasing food prices […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making WAF ML models go brrr: saving decades of processing time]]></title>
        <id>66a0edd358eb3b000a36905a</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/making-waf-ai-models-go-brr"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we discuss the performance optimizations we've implemented for our WAF ML product. We'll guide you through specific code examples and benchmark numbers, and we'll share the impressive latency reduction numbers observed after the rollout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[STOP the IMF and the World Bank!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/STOP-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/STOP-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T11:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This July 22, about a hundred popular movements, networks and social organizations from around the world launch a Call to join forces to put an end to the criminal actions of the International Monetary Fund (IMF), the World Bank (WB) and the illegitimate debt they create. Together with the open invitation to join in coordinating actions, the call to strengthen mobilization and resistance to prevent these institutions, and the development model they promote from continuing to violate the (...)
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
IMF, 
World Bank]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective, CADTM International</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shane Boyle: &ldquo;Brecht&#8217;s Scissors&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/brechts-scissors</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/brechts-scissors"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T10:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Raven Row.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brother is already at work! Urgent resistance before it's too late...]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Big-Brother-is-already-at-work-Urgent-resistance-before-it-s-too-late</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Big-Brother-is-already-at-work-Urgent-resistance-before-it-s-too-late"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T09:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A highlight of the Olympic flame's peregrinations through France was its meeting with a “102-year-old former Resistance fighter”, which was celebrated by the country's media, who were quick to see it as an apotheosis of the flame's... humanist and pacifist virtues. All the more so as this otherwise very sympathetic old lady declared that she wanted to carry the Olympic flame “in the name of the values of friendship between peoples that she defended during the Resistance”. Obviously, the old (...)
English

/ 
France, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The era of privatisation is nearly over. But cleaning up the mess left behind will take years]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52876</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/07/25/the-era-of-privatisation-is-nearly-over-but-cleaning-up-the-mess-left-behind-will-take-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T04:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From The Guardian Among many other challenges in dealing with the failure of urban policy in Australia, the Minns (NSW state) government is faced with the task of renegotiating, or repudiating, the disastrous set of contracts for toll roads in New South Wales made by its predecessors (Labor and Liberal) with the Transurban group. As […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[birdwatching saved my life]]></title>
        <id>https://froggy.bearblog.dev/birdwatching-saved-my-life/</id>
        <link href="https://froggy.bearblog.dev/birdwatching-saved-my-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T03:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many people, my view of birdwatching ("birding") and its practitioners were neutral at best, holding their stereotypical focal gear, donning vests and hats.
I learned that my friend casually did it on his walks and stuff, and was able to identify birds. That was cool, and made the hobby a bit more approachable for me.
It wasn't until COVID when I saw a pair of cute yellow birds in the tree. Because the leaves haven't grown in yet, I was able to watch them fly around the tree, landing in different spots, and ultimately move on to other spots. I was so mesmerized, I thought I had just seen a legendary pokemon. I immediately went to google, and found that it was an American Goldfinch.
It wasn't really easy to find though. Google took me down an old-web looking site with the title "Birds …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>