<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-21T06:32:03.050Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-21T06:32:03.050Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secret Histories]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331201</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/secret-histories/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T06:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More often than not, the dead do not return to rejoin the living but rather to lead them into some dreadful snare, entrapping them with disastrous consequences [… What] haunts are not the dead, but the gaps left within us by the secrets of others. – Nicolas Abraham I was about six when I learned  More
The post Secret Histories appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous Pro-Palestine Protestors Arrested Outside Consulate of Israel Chicago]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331410</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/numerous-pro-palestine-protestors-arrested-outside-consulate-of-israel-chicago/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As former President Barack Obama prepared to speak at the Democratic National Convention in Chicago on the evening of August 20, pro-Palestine protestors outside the Consulate General of Israel were arrested. Over sixty-six arrests were reported, including press members—photos by Steel Brooks.  
The post Numerous Pro-Palestine Protestors Arrested Outside Consulate of Israel Chicago appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch News Service</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bari Weiss, Zionist Crusaders, and The Era of The Toxic Troll]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331366</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/bari-weiss-zionist-crusaders-and-the-era-of-the-toxic-troll/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent article in the New York Times titled “Bari Weiss Knows Exactly What She’s Doing,” Matt Flegenheimer writes: As the founder, public face and heat-seeking curator of The Free Press, a new media company with ambitions to overtake the old media, Ms. Weiss, 40, has identified a mélange of reliable foils: the illiberal left; diversity, equity and  More
The post Bari Weiss, Zionist Crusaders, and The Era of The Toxic Troll appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mirage of Ceasefire in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331359</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/the-mirage-of-ceasefire-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel escaped a certain military retaliation last week when Joe Biden hastily called to start a new round of ceasefire negotiations —a ploy likely succeeded in delaying a planned reprisals against Israel for its aggression in Tehran, Yemen, and Beirut. Previously, the Palestinians have agreed to multiple revised American ceasefire proposals. Each time, however, Benjamin  More
The post The Mirage of Ceasefire in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wellness as Tyranny: The Cult of Toxic Happiness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331389</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/wellness-as-tyranny-the-cult-of-toxic-happiness/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Be happy.  Think of your wellness.  Across organisations, private and public entities, government bodies and social clubs, the cult of contrived happiness abounds with ritualistic, clotting repetition.  In such cases, the forced grin, the pressured smile, the affected giggle, have become part of a project of puppeteering, manipulation and manufacture.  Critics of such approaches are ostracised, treated as leprous  More
The post Wellness as Tyranny: The Cult of Toxic Happiness appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Refuge: Empowering Rohingya to Lead Their Own Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331361</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/beyond-refuge-empowering-rohingya-to-lead-their-own-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The vast majority of my people are in refugee camps or in apartheid villages, struggling every day just to make a living… They deserve to have a biography, not someone like me, living in Canada with a decent job in the government,” said Raïss Tinmaung. Tinmaung is Rohingya and when we met last month in  More
The post Beyond Refuge: Empowering Rohingya to Lead Their Own Future appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nagasaki, the Gaza Strip, and the Denial of Truth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331260</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/nagasaki-the-gaza-strip-and-the-denial-of-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On 6 August 1945, President Harry Truman announced to the world that one U.S. airplane, named the Enola Gay, had “dropped one bomb on Hiroshima.” The bomb had the equivalent “power of 200,000 tons of T.N.T.” That single bomb killed 140,000 people in a matter of minutes. Truman went on to say that “We are  More
The post Nagasaki, the Gaza Strip, and the Denial of Truth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: Hoof and Feint]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331199</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/letter-from-london-hoof-and-feint/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commentator: ‘The Premier League season, with all its daft cash and crazy splendour, with all its nifty footwork and gifted stars, has commenced. Let us not forget, ladies and gentlemen, the most goals EVER were scored last season. Football, soccer, is upon us once more…’ I have friends whose eyes glaze over if I enthuse  More
The post Letter from London: Hoof and Feint appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep Corporate America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331364</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/deep-corporate-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing our government doesn’t like doing is challenging the greed of health insurance companies. I can speak with some authority about holes in the ever-fraying safety net of our healthcare system, including Tricare, the military health insurance plan used by most troops, veterans, and their families, other employer-sponsored health insurance, state-sponsored care like Medicare  More
The post Deep Corporate America appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrea Mazzarino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post’s Conservative Columnists Just Make it Up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331346</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/the-washington-posts-conservative-columnists-just-make-it-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one expects serious economic analysis from the Washington Post’s conservative columnists and Mark Theissen doesn’t let us down. Theissen starts off by reminding of one of Larry Summers’ most embarrassing moments: “Nonetheless, as president of the Senate, Harris cast the deciding vote to pass the catastrophically misnamed ‘American Rescue Plan’ with only Democratic votes  More
The post The Washington Post’s Conservative Columnists Just Make it Up appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Right’s War on Cultivated-Meat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331263</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/21/the-rights-war-on-cultivated-meat/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was excited to see Upside Foods and the Institute of Justice had filed a lawsuit in federal court seeking to overturn Florida’s ban on cultivated-meat sales. For those who don’t know, cultivated meat is grown from livestock cells, without slaughter. It offers a number of potential animal welfare, public health and environmental benefits. Finally,  More
The post The Right’s War on Cultivated-Meat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fuzzfactor in "US judge throws out FTC's ban on non-compete agreements"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41306187</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41306187"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T02:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a different article:
>"A sweeping prohibition of noncompete agreements by the FTC was an unlawful extension of power that would have put American workers, businesses, and our economy at a competitive disadvantage," U.S. Chamber of Commerce President and CEO Suzanne Clark said in a statement.
If you ever wondered what kind of moron would get this completely backwards and think that non-compete agreements give Americans a competitive advantage, now you know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fuzzfactor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Autoconfiguration For Node Cgroup Driver (beta)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/21/cri-cgroup-driver-lookup-now-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/21/cri-cgroup-driver-lookup-now-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Historically, configuring the correct cgroup driver has been a pain point for users running new
Kubernetes clusters. On Linux systems, there are two different cgroup drivers:
cgroupfs and systemd. In the past, both the kubelet
and CRI implementation (like CRI-O or containerd) needed to be configured to use
the same cgroup driver, or else the kubelet would exit with an error. This was a
source of headaches for many cluster admins. However, there is light at the end of the tunnel!
Automated cgroup driver detection
In v1.28.0, the SIG Node community introduced the feature gate
KubeletCgroupDriverFromCRI, which instructs the kubelet to ask the CRI
implementation which cgroup driver to use. A few minor releases of Kubernetes
happened whilst we waited for support to land in the major two CRI implementations
(containerd and CRI-O), but as of v1.31.0, this feature is now beta!
In addition to setting the feature gate, a cluster admin needs to ensure their
CRI implementation is new enough:
containerd: Support was added in v2.0.0
CRI-O: Support was added in v1.28.0
Then, they should ensure their CRI implementation is configured to the
cgroup_driver they would like to use.
Future work
Eventually, support for the kubelet's cgroupDriver configuration field will be
dropped, and the kubelet will fail to start if the CRI implementation isn't new
enough to have support for this feature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wanting to read more novels, versus trying to do everything else]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8334</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/wanting-read-more-novels-versus-everything-else/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T21:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About six years ago I decided I wasn’t reading enough novels. Books sat on the side table untouched, gathering dust, and inducing a pang of guilt whenever I took notice of them. I wondered what I could do to get more into reading. One thing I am good at is meeting deadlines, and doing things […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The crisis of knowledge and enlightenment’s imitations]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45560</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/20/the-crisis-of-knowledge-and-enlightenments-imitations/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T20:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and current issue of RWER Our current environmental predicament is fundamentally a crisis of knowledge, rooted in the Enlightenment’s narrow conceptualization of epistemology. This shift fostered an illusion of objectivity that has since permeated our understanding of the world, particularly in the context of societal dynamics. The Enlightenment’s emphasis on objective knowledge […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by MarkusQ in "MIT leaders describe the experience of not renewing Elsevier contract"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41303747</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41303747"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T20:29:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aaron Swartz would have liked some of those principles.  This is a small, "better late than never" step for most of us, but for Aaron...it's more like "too little, too late."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MarkusQ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "Data Exfiltration from Slack AI via indirect prompt injection"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41302961</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41302961"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T19:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The key thing to understand here is the exfiltration vector.
Slack can render Markdown links, where the URL is hidden behind the text of that link.
In this case the attacker tricks Slack AI into showing a user a link that says something like "click here to reauthenticate" - the URL attached to that link goes to the attacker's server, with a query string that includes private information that was visible to Slack AI as part of the context it has access to.
If the user falls for the trick and clicks the link, the data will be exfiltrated to the attacker's server logs.
Here's my attempt at explaining this attack: https://simonwillison.net/2024/Aug/20/data-exfiltration-from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277067</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T18:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Democrat National Convention vignettes; Highest Covid wave in two years; Stupid money and blood money ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aparna Ramani discusses the future of AI infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21559</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/20/data-infrastructure/aparna-ramani-future-of-ai-infrastructure-meta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering new AI technologies at scale also means rethinking every layer of our infrastructure – from silicon and software systems and even our data center designs. For the second year in a row, Meta’s engineering and infrastructure teams returned for the AI Infra @ Scale conference, where they discussed the challenges of scaling up an [...]
Read More...
The post Aparna Ramani discusses the future of AI infrastructure appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JohnMakin in "The anatomy of a 2AM mental breakdown"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41300777</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41300777"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T15:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working as a SRE for a year in a large global company broke me out of this "panic" mode described in this post. To a business, every problem seems like a world-ending event. It's very easy to give in to panic in those situations. However, in reality, it's rarely that bad, and even if it is, you'll probably survive without harm. The key in these situations, and what I try to do (totally relate to breaking out in a sweat, that still happens to me, just happened yesterday) is to take 5-10 minutes before doing any action to try to fix it and sketch it out, think about it as clearly as you can. Fear interferes with your ability to reason rationally. Mashing buttons in a panic can make your problems spiral even worse (seen that happen). Disrupting that fear circuit any way you can is important. Splashing my face and hands with extremely cold water is my trick.
Then after you go through a few of these, you'll realize it really isn't too bad and you've dealt with bad situations before and you'll gain the confidence to know you can deal with it, even when there's no one you can reach out to for help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JohnMakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's No Secret]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/no-secret/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/no-secret/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["What's the secret?"
I asked this question to one of my clients today. He was 85 years old, looked 60, and was as fit and agile as a 50-year-old.
He replied: "There's no secret. I enjoy walking. That’s all."
No secrets. No tricks. Completely natural.
But that's often how it is, isn’t it; we think there's a code to crack, a secret recipe to follow to achieve success. When in reality, the answer lies in the most natural thing in the world.
If we want to increase our chances of being in good shape, then we need to make sure we move around a bit. If we want to become a better writer, then we need to make sure we write a lot.
There's no secret.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run WebAssembly on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>0f5f0175f3302ce8a81549c5099bc61006d4ac3f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/16532-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T14:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WebAssembly (Wasm) is a revolutionary technology that promises to bring near-native performance to web applications. However, its potential extends far beyond the browser, enabling developers to run Wasm workloads in various environments, such as cloud-native platforms like Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). In this post, you can explore how AWS empowers users to harness […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Koenig</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BOAK - Our Сomrade, Anarchist-Internationalist from Russia, Vladislav Iurchenko (“Pirate”), Became a Martyr Defending the Peoples of Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boak-our-somrade-anarchist-internationalist-from-russia-vladislav-iurchenko-pirate-became-a-mar?v=1724165397</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boak-our-somrade-anarchist-internationalist-from-russia-vladislav-iurchenko-pirate-became-a-mar?v=1724165397"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T14:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: BOAK
Title: Our Сomrade, Anarchist-Internationalist from Russia, Vladislav Iurchenko (“Pirate”), Became a Martyr Defending the Peoples of Ukraine
Date: August 19, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 20th August 2024 from telegra.ph and t.me

 Another fighter became a martyr. On August 9, our comrade and anarchist-internationalist from Russia, Vladislav Iurchenko (nom de guerre “Pirate”), was killed in battle. He was 22 years old. Vladislav was part of the “Siberian Battalion” of the International Legion, and he was martyred in a fight during a landing operation on the Kinburn Spit. 
 Before coming to Ukraine, Vladislav participated in actions of solidarity with anarchist and other anti-government prisoners. He fought against Russian fascism and imperialism. Knowing that anarchists in Ukraine…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Should You Do to Prepare for the Climate Change Storm?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277058</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/what-should-you-do-to-prepare-for-the-climate-change-storm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T13:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you stand your ground or seek out a climate haven? Some resources to help you decide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The anatomy of a 2AM mental breakdown]]></title>
        <id>https://zarar.dev/anatomy-of-a-mental-breakdown/</id>
        <link href="https://zarar.dev/anatomy-of-a-mental-breakdown/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: this made it on HN somehow.
Around 2AM this morning I had a realization that this was the most stressed I have ever been. On verge of a complete breakdown.
Why? Because I noticed around 10PM that jumpcomedy.com was entirely broken with all HTTP POST calls made by RTK Query failing. Nothing worked and though I had deployed recent changes, none of them would cause this. I was at a complete loss as to where to look, especially as this is working locally. Posting on the usual Discords (NextJS, Vercel) is leading to dead silence. I'm alone and have to fix this issue which I didn't cause.
This isn't the first production defect I've introduced in my 25 years of working, but this is the first one where I had absolutely nobody to turn to in a time of crisis while customer complaints are pilin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST’s first post-quantum standards]]></title>
        <id>66c3a5d84a25d6000ae1d9b0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/nists-first-post-quantum-standards"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T13:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIST has published the first cryptographic standards for protecting against attacks from quantum computers. Learn what this means for you and your organization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Valenta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What went wrong with the Silicon Valley right]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53029</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/20/what-went-wrong-with-the-silicon-valley-right/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T12:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“To promote open inquiry and free, market-based technological progress, you need an open society, not one founded on the enemy principle. The understandable desire to escape criticism, misunderstanding, and the frustrations of ordinary politics does not entail the radical remaking of the global geoeconomic order to confound the New York Times and its allies. The cult of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "Toasts are bad UX"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41299495</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41299495"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T12:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not convinced. Most of the argument seems to be that redundant UX is bad UX:
> But by archiving the email, the email disappears from the list, which already implies the action was successful.
> In this example, the button already includes a confirmation so the toast is entirely unnecessary.
I vehemently disagree with the idea that just because you're already communicating something one way it's bad UX to include another way of communicating the same thing at the same time. Redundancy in communication is a feature, not a bug, and it's present in all human languages. It ensures that even in less than ideal conditions the message still gets through.
In the case of toasts, having a single, standardized way of communicating the status of all actions (and if possible providing the undo) allows a user to quickly pick up on the pattern. Extra indicators closer to the action can be valuable too, but it's when they're paired with the toast that their meaning becomes entirely clear.  To remove the toast in favor of a bunch of specific indicators is to force your user to learn several different ways of saying "it's done now" entirely from context (many of which will be small and subtle as in the examples given). This might work fine for you and me but isn't great for, say, the elderly or the vision impaired or children.
Unless they're actually getting in the way, toasts aren't bad UX, they're redundant UX, and a UX designer shouldn't be striving to optimize away redundancy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Day]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/what-a-day/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/what-a-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today was the first day of classes at the university where I work in IT support. That means campus was full of people who needed help in a variety of ways. The second anyone ventured outside of their office, they's be accosted by an innocent freshman or newly hired professor who needed directions to some other building. In the technology world, there dozens of people who a) forgot their password b) did not want to click the self-service link for forgotten passwords. Later on in the year, I'll make them use the self-service link but today there was no time to convince these neo-adults to take the responsible route out of their self-created problems. I just reset their password for them and moved along to the next person. Some people would listen to the directions on what to do next and say …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Disparate Outcomes of Bank‑ and Nonbank‑Financed Private Credit Expansions]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31442</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/the-disparate-outcomes-of-bank-and-nonbank-financed-private-credit-expansions/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long-run trends in increased access to credit are thought to improve real activity. However, “rapid” credit expansions do not always end well and have been shown in the academic literature to predict adverse real outcomes such as lower GDP growth and an increased likelihood of crises. Given these financial stability considerations associated with rapid credit expansions, being able to distinguish in real time “good booms” from “bad booms” is of crucial interest for policymakers. While the recent literature has focused on understanding how the composition of borrowers helps distinguish good and bad booms, in this post we investigate how the composition of lending during a credit expansion matters for subsequent real outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Boyarchenko and Leonardo Elias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/20/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276926</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-20-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our peregrinating daily links: looks and smart? moar mpox, Long Covid, carbon scheme doubts, China boat busting, Die Welt after secret Hitlers, Netanyahu retrades peace deal, Putin nixes negotiations, cars go full Stasi? Trump v. EV subsidies, Dem convention, Phil Donahue RIP, election AI fakes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In His Last 40 Days in Office, Mexico’s President Lopéz Obrador Pushes Ahead With Plans to Ban Open Pit Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276906</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/in-final-month-in-office-mexicos-outgoing-president-amlo-prepares-to-ban-open-pit-mining-and-fracking-in-new-constitutional-ammendments.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For over three decades, Mexico has been a veritable paradise for global mining conglomerates, serving up some of the laxest regulations in Latin America. That is now changing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robots and Wage Polarisation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277047</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/robots-and-wage-polarisation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle surprise! Introducing robots into workplaces slows wage growth, particularly among factory labor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Status of Europe’s Autonomous Movements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277043</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/the-status-of-europes-autonomous-movements.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU leads in managing autonomous and separatist movements in its states, but non-EU countries can be more vulnerable to outside interference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Against the Sleep=Boring Analogy]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52980</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/20/against-the-sleepboring-analogy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T08:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a midsummer short and light hearted post, but I find that Summer is often the time when I am most reminded of my bodily existence, and of how naïve us philosophers are in forgetting (de facto, if not in principle) how much our thoughts and beliefs are embedded in our bodily experience. Indeed,often […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Ronzoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“And Now They Want Our Votes”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331306</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/and-now-they-want-our-votes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T06:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eman Abdelhadi’s speech from the “Bodies Outside of Unjust Laws” demonstration on Aug. 18 in Chicago. Chicago, we all know why we are here. We are drowning, and our hearts are broken. We are drowning in debt. In medical bills. In rising rents. In inflation. We are under attack in this country. The Right has declared war on people  More
The post “And Now They Want Our Votes” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eman Abdelhadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Convention Speech Made Absurd Claims About His Gaza Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331344</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/bidens-convention-speech-made-absurd-claims-about-his-gaza-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An observation from George Orwell -- “those who control the present, control the past and those who control the past control the future” -- is acutely relevant to how President Biden talked about Gaza during his speech at the Democratic convention Monday night. His words fit into a messaging template now in its eleventh month, depicting the U.S. government as tirelessly seeking peace, while supplying the weapons and bombs that have enabled Israel’s continual slaughter of civilians. More
The post Biden’s Convention Speech Made Absurd Claims About His Gaza Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s Young Mega-Millionaires Just Want to Have Fun]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331179</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/todays-young-mega-millionaires-just-want-to-have-fun/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enormously rich people tend to get bored easily, especially those on the younger side. Stocks and bonds, such a yawn. Wealthy Baby Boomers certainly do still get a kick out of watching their financial portfolios fatten. But their Millennial and Generation Z counterparts have an added expectation. The fortunes they’re investing, they’re expecting, will be filling their lives up with fun. More
The post Today’s Young Mega-Millionaires Just Want to Have Fun appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Distasteful Nonsense of Olympism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331307</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/the-distasteful-nonsense-of-olympism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ekecheiria, also known as the “Olympic Truce,” is a quaint notion dating to Ancient Greece, when three kings prone to warring against each other – Iphitos of Elis, Cleosthenes of Pisa and Lycurgus of Sparta – concluded a treaty permitting the safe passage of all athletes and spectators from the relevant city-states for the duration  More
The post The Distasteful Nonsense of Olympism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Water, Water, Everywhere, But Not for You, Palestinian]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331313</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/water-water-everywhere-but-not-for-you-palestinian/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a very intense relationship with water.  As a result of a long-term health condition, I am often feeling very thirsty and drained. I cannot go more than perhaps 15 minutes without having a sup of water until I start to feel uncomfortable. On average people in the UK use 149 litres of water per-day,  More
The post Water, Water, Everywhere, But Not for You, Palestinian appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Woodrow Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Status of Europe’s Autonomous Movements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331291</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/the-status-of-europes-autonomous-movements/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish officials reassuringly heralded a “new era” for the country after May 2024 elections. Catalonian pro-independence parties had lost the parliamentary majority that had enabled them to govern their region since 2015, and for the first time in decades, had failed to secure a majority of seats in regional parliament. Spain’s ruling Socialists meanwhile managed to emerge as Catalonia’s largest party. More
The post The Status of Europe’s Autonomous Movements appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Are They? The CA Legislative Jewish Caucus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331315</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/who-are-they-the-ca-legislative-jewish-caucus/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While University of California students chanted “Divest!” and erected “Free Palestine” encampments, a little-known pro-Israel faction of the California legislature introduced legislation to indoctrinate six million California public school children and stem the rising tide of college resistance to Israel’s genocide in Gaza. What’s in a name? They call themselves the California Legislative Jewish Caucus and they  More
The post Who Are They? The CA Legislative Jewish Caucus appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcy Winograd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Economics Behind the Fall of Autocracy in Bangladesh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331299</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/the-economics-behind-the-fall-of-autocracy-in-bangladesh/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Naheed Islam was not yet born in 1996, when prime minister Sheikh Hasina of Bangladesh began her first term in office. In 2009, when she was elected to her second term, Islam had just turned 11. On August 5, he brought an abrupt end to Hasina’s 15-year long autocracy. The 26-year-old Islam, a sociology major  More
The post The Economics Behind the Fall of Autocracy in Bangladesh appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarique Niazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speculative Algorithms are the New Invisible Cage for Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331182</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/speculative-algorithms-are-the-new-invisible-cage-for-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was barely a decade ago that many of us became enamored by the “gig” economy. Booking a room, ride, or restaurant took seconds and could be done at virtually any time or place. A major factor enabling the gig economy to grow was organizations using algorithms to create these services. Organizations, such as Airbnb,  More
The post Speculative Algorithms are the New Invisible Cage for Workers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hatim Rahman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tipping Is Racist and Harms Us All, It’s Past Time to Eliminate It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331180</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/tipping-is-racist-and-harms-us-all-its-past-time-to-eliminate-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In most of the country, workers in restaurants, bars, nail salons, barber shops, and other service jobs are paid differently than workers in virtually all other occupations. For these workers, a large portion of their take-home pay comes from gratuity or “tips” provided directly from the customer. While employers of workers in other occupations must  More
The post Tipping Is Racist and Harms Us All, It’s Past Time to Eliminate It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Mast</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just Because We Can Innovate In Healthcare, Doesn’t Mean We Should]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331319</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/20/just-because-we-can-innovate-in-healthcare-doesnt-mean-we-should/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. consumes an incredible amount of healthcare resources, spending more on healthcare than any other high-income country. Much of this spending occurs within the biotechnology sector towards the development of new healthcare technologies. As a result, the U.S. serves as the engine of innovation for the rest of world with many of our most  More
The post Just Because We Can Innovate In Healthcare, Doesn’t Mean We Should appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naveen Reddy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tedchs in "'Rare species' not seen in the area for 50 years spotted on Arizona trail camera"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41296184</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41296184"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T02:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They say this is the first time an ocelot has been spotted in 50 years, but I beg to differ.  An ocelot is /always/ spotted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tedchs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Streaming Transitions from SPDY to WebSockets]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/20/websockets-transition/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/20/websockets-transition/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Kubernetes 1.31, by default kubectl now uses the WebSocket protocol
instead of SPDY for streaming.
This post describes what these changes mean for you and why these streaming APIs
matter.
Streaming APIs in Kubernetes
In Kubernetes, specific endpoints that are exposed as an HTTP or RESTful
interface are upgraded to streaming connections, which require a streaming
protocol. Unlike HTTP, which is a request-response protocol, a streaming
protocol provides a persistent connection that's bi-directional, low-latency,
and lets you interact in real-time. Streaming protocols support reading and
writing data between your client and the server, in both directions, over the
same connection. This type of connection is useful, for example, when you create
a shell in a running container from your local…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Henry James Opposes Wildly Unlikeable Guys]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53018</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/19/henry-james-opposes-wildly-unlikeable-guys/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T22:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henry James: girl, you are so cool and smart, and well-dressed, and beautiful. And I mean this in the least-sexual, but not sassy-gay-best-friend way, exactly, but more like just, your good friend who is also gay? And do you know, that guy is the worst. The worst. I feel like someone should leave you a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Belle Waring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add macOS to your continuous integration pipelines with AWS CodeBuild]]></title>
        <id>7c92c240b5751fb505e0a2c423b6891c4fe90c69</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/add-macos-to-your-continuous-integration-pipelines-with-aws-codebuild/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T21:14:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeBuild now supports macOS, simplifying CI/CD pipelines for Apple apps, using managed M2 machines with pre-installed tools like Xcode. Auto scale capacity seamlessly while CodeBuild manages the fleet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Prime Minister’s Literary Awards 2024 shortlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8320</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-prime-ministers-literary-awards-2024-shortlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do Australian Prime Ministers have time to read books? They may not, but they do have a literary award for Australian publications, created in 2008, of which the 2024 shortlist was announced last week. Five titles, across the six award categories of fiction, non-fiction, Australian history, poetry, children’s, and young adult, were included. Among books […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mpox (“Monkeypox”) Round-Up: History, Wastewater, R0, and Is It Airborne? (Yes)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276972</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/mpox-monkeypox-round-up-history-wastewater-r0-and-is-it-airborne-yes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T20:25:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great news on wastewater, less great news on R0 and airborne transmission.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: G6e instances, Karpenter, Amazon Prime Day metrics, AWS Certifications update and more (August 19, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>204a9127d101972ff3aeb38af0a2c2198f16f9ba</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-g6e-instances-karpenter-amazon-prime-day-metrics-aws-certifications-update-and-more-august-19-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T20:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know what I find more exciting than the Amazon Prime Day sale? Finding out how Amazon Web Services (AWS) makes it all happen. Every year, I wait eagerly for Jeff Barr’s annual post to read the chart-topping metrics. The scale never ceases to amaze me. This year, Channy Yun and Jeff Barr bring us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Work on Gender and Development: Soledad Artiz Prillaman’s The Patriarchal Political Order]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53014</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/19/new-work-on-gender-and-development-soledad-artiz-prillamans-the-patriarchal-political-order/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T20:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The value of individualism often comes up in attempts to make sense of the elusiveness of women’s empowerment. “Investing in women” has not uniformly yielded either the quick reduction in women’s poverty or the decrease in women’s adherence to sexist norms or deference to men policymakers had hoped it would. Of course, this is partly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serene Khader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276974</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T18:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics: Updated Covid data: First sighting of XDV.1 variant from China; a campaign scenario and the Democrat National Convention; Israel accepts US ceasefire deal, but not Hamas. Nice timing! ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by delroth in "The gigantic and unregulated power plants in the cloud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41292982</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41292982"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> In the Netherlands alone, these solar panels generate a power output equivalent to at least 25 medium sized nuclear power plants.
Since this didn't pass the smell test: the author is looking at nameplate capacity, which is a completely useless metric for variable electricity production sources (a solar panel in my sunless basement has the same nameplate capacity as the same panel installed in the Sahara desert).
Looking at actual yearly energy generation data, this is more like 1.5 times the generation of an average nuclear power plant (NL solar production in 2023: 21TWh, US nuclear production in 2021: 778TWh by 54 plants).
Which maybe puts more into perspective the actual risks involved here. I'm not saying there shouldn't be more regulations and significantly better security practices, but otoh you could likely drive a big truck into the right power poles and cause a similar sized outage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>delroth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anarchists - The Hooligans, the Stingies, the Starved People and the Bad Asses]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchists-the-hooligans-the-stingies-the-starved-people-and-the-bad-asses?v=1724088997</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchists-the-hooligans-the-stingies-the-starved-people-and-the-bad-asses?v=1724088997"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T17:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anarchists
Title: The Hooligans, the Stingies, the Starved People and the Bad Asses
Date: 1985
Notes: This is a translation of a leaflet written in 1985 by anarchists frequenting the Chrysallida social space in Limassol, Cyprus.
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:leaflets:xrisalllida:kakakakathkia

 The football league is over; the mass rallies of July have also passed. The Cuéllar initiative froze, as usual, and everything indicated that Cypriot society would remain for about a month without mass spectacles to organize its boredom. 
 And suddenly “chaos” erupts in Germasogeia. A new “fruit” for the “Cypriot reality”; and the hysteria of the occasion is analogous. The newspapers are shouting about hooligans, they are searching for the “brains” (in this place it see…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“New Keynesian” DSGE models]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45554</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/19/new-keynesian-dsge-models-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll To be fair to academia, it has realized that the pure DSGE model is incapable of explaining observable phenomena so they have introduced numerous amendments, known, oddly, as “imperfections” in the model. Long-term nominal contracts, other labour market frictions, imperfection in credit markets, all these and more are prayed in aid and, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just because it’s all in your head doesn’t mean it’s not real]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/just-because-its-all-in-your-head-doesnt-mean-its-not-real/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/just-because-its-all-in-your-head-doesnt-mean-its-not-real/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're anything like me, then you're frequently told by those around you something along the lines of "Oh, don't worry about it, it's all in your head" or perhaps the more common "You're imagining things." These people usually mean well when they give such advise; they're trying to help in their own way. My parents did this all the time while I was growing up, so much so that I ended up believing it. And sometimes, it's true. It could be that "that person" is not being mean to me because they don't like me, but rather because they're having a bad day in general. I get that, and I agree that sometimes (most of the time), we make up our own problems out of confusion, miscommunication, or ignorance.
But what about deeper, more pervasive scenarios?
What about depression, for instance? Peopl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Update on the Reservation Wages in the SCE Labor Market Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31414</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/an-update-on-the-reservation-wages-in-the-sce-labor-market-survey/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve Bank of New York’s July 2024 SCE Labor Market Survey shows a year-over-year increase in the average reservation wage—the lowest wage respondents would be willing to accept for a new job—to $81,147, but a decline from a series’ high of $81,822 in March 2024. In this post, we investigate how the recent dynamics of reservation wages differed across individuals and how reservation wages are related to individuals’ expectations about their future labor market movements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gizem Kosar, Davide Melcangi, and Sasha Thomas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GNOMES in "Roblox is the biggest game in the world, but is unprofitable"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41291192</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41291192"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T14:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My kiddo has easily spent 500+ on Roblox across birthday/Xmas gift cards/chores.
I can't stand that almost all of the games seem to have a pay to win aspect, or are heavily advertising every chance they get.
As a gamer dad, I try to show my kid better games to play, but because they aren't free, his friends can't play. Just drives him to keep playing and wanting more Robux. It's compounded when his favorite Youtubers play...
Seriously don't understand how Roblox isn't being investigated for predatory practices. I imagine they can hide behind the fact users are making most of the mini games, and they are just providing a platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GNOMES</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summer 2024 weather report: Cloudflare with a chance of Intern-ets]]></title>
        <id>66c2ca3c4a25d6000ae1d73e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/2024-interns"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T13:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer, Cloudflare welcomed approximately 60 interns from all around the globe, on a mission to #HelpBuildABetterInternet. Join us as we dive into what we were able to accomplish and our experiences!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Snell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/19/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276910</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-19-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post Report on Russia-Ukraine Negotiation to End Energy System Attacks: An Admission of Russian Long-Term Weakness or More Complex Calcuation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276947</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/washington-post-report-on-russia-ukraine-negotiation-to-end-energy-system-attacks-an-admission-of-russian-long-term-weakness-or-more-complex-calcuation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trying to make sense of a Washington Post story depicting Russia as willing give up its best weapon, its electrical war, for very little.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peasants and Politics in Neoliberal India: The 2020-21 Peasant Movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Peasants-and-Politics-in-Neoliberal-India-The-2020-21-Peasant-Movement</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Peasants-and-Politics-in-Neoliberal-India-The-2020-21-Peasant-Movement"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The persistence of peasantry in the Global South and imperialism's necessity to integrate it into its accumulation network has given birth to a new agrarian question. This question centers around policies and efforts employed by imperialist countries to pressurize countries of the Global South, through international institutions (WTO, World Bank, and IMF), to integrate their peasantry into globalized capital. A peculiar feature of recent developments in this process is the exceptional (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
India, 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paramjit Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Donahue Changed My Life and Millions of Others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/phil-donahue-changed-my-life-and-millions-of-others/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T06:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phil Donahue passed away Sunday night, after a long illness. He was beloved by those who knew him and by many who didn’t. He started as a local reporter in Ohio, was a trailblazer in bringing social issues to a national audience as a daytime broadcast TV host, and then he was pretty much banished  More
The post Phil Donahue Changed My Life and Millions of Others appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Cohen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Starving of Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331133</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/the-starving-of-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T06:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daily reports of Palestinians killed in Gaza focus on deaths from Israeli bombs and missiles, now exceeding 40,000.  Yet the famine stalking the Strip today threatens  the lives of many times that number. Already children in North Gaza are dying of malnutrition. Like canaries in coal mines, they signal mass starvation to come. Sadly, the major media has largely ignored the accelerating famine conditions in Gaza. More
The post The Starving of Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>L. Michael Hager</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Western Solidarity Becomes an Exercise in Gaslighting]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331209</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/western-solidarity-as-an-exercise-in-gaslighting/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Where is the Ummah,” Myriam François, an outspoken journalist, wrote in another absurd X post in Arabic. Does the Palestinian cause concern Muslims alone?
Not only are the specificities of the Arab context made irrelevant, it seems that solidarity in an increasingly Right-leaning West has become an exercise in gaslighting. More
The post When Western Solidarity Becomes an Exercise in Gaslighting appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nabil Salih</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To California’s Energy Policy-Makers:  Control the CAISO and Give Us Electric Rate Relief]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331184</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/to-californias-energy-policy-makers-control-the-caiso-and-give-us-electric-rate-relief/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:58:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose it is really hot.  You go into a store to buy a bottle of water that usually costs you a dollar.  To your shock and dismay the store charges you twenty dollars.  You feel ripped off and you want to complain.  The California Attorney General tells you to complain to him because this type of commercial behavior is an illegal unfair practice, price gouging, and profiteering.  This is so outrageous that it almost never happens. More
The post To California’s Energy Policy-Makers:  Control the CAISO and Give Us Electric Rate Relief appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Julian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partners in Genocide: Israel is Slaughtering Palestinians with Western Arms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/partners-in-genocide-israel-is-slaughtering-palestinians-with-western-arms/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many are earnestly pointing at the devastation of war, the rampant human rights violations and the deliberate relegation of international and humanitarian law, there are those who see war from an entirely different perspective: profits. For the merchants of war, the collective pain and misery of whole nations is dwarfed by the lucrative deals  More
The post Partners in Genocide: Israel is Slaughtering Palestinians with Western Arms  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Feeding Frenzy of Consumerism and Environmental Destruction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331185</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/the-feeding-frenzy-of-consumerism-and-environmental-destruction/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Luther King, Jr. believed that consumerism was one of the major shortcomings of US society. The other issues were militarism and racism. Those were the three major themes King raised in his famous “Beyond Vietnam” speech delivered in April 1967 at Riverside Church in New York City. King spoke against the ongoing debacle of  More
The post The Feeding Frenzy of Consumerism and Environmental Destruction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Attacks on Women, and the Truth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331207</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/donald-trumps-attacks-on-women-and-the-truth/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former President Donald Trump’s attacks against Vice-President Kamala Harris continue unabated and, if anything, have increased in virulence and desperation. As her prestige increases, his goes down. He has become a joke for many late-night comedians, but this hasn’t stopped Trump from becoming even more disrespectful to his opponent, to the point of distorting and  More
The post Donald Trump’s Attacks on Women, and the Truth appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Praise of the Weird]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=331178</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/19/in-praise-of-the-weird/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three witches in ‘Macbeth’ – also known as the ‘weird,’ or ‘wyrd,’ sisters – are prophetesses who often do the opposite of what’s expected of them. Royal Shakespeare Company Collection Republicans, as you’ve probably heard, are being called “weird.” In a quip that launched a million memes, Minnesota governor-turned-VP candidate Tim Walz referred to  More
The post In Praise of the Weird appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Andrew Weinstock</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fishtoaster in "Markov chains are funnier than LLMs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287805</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287805"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T04:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I came to this same conclusion some years ago while working on a side project.
Before anything LLM existed, I built a site[0] to generate fake "AWS Blog Posts."  I trained a markov chain generator on all AWS announcement posts up to that point, copied the html + css of aws's standard blog posts, then glued them all together with some python + JS.  It turned out, IMO, pretty funny!  People familiar with AWS's blog posts would often get several sentences in before they realized they were looking at word-soup.
When GPT was new, I looked into using that to "upgrade" it.  I spent a weekend messing around with Minimaxir's gpt-2-simple generating blog posts based on AWS content.  What I found was, ultimately, it was way less fun.  The posts were far too realistic to be interesting.  They read like totally-real blog posts that just happened to not be true.
I realized then that the humor of those early markov generations was the ridiculousness.  The point where, a few words or sentences in, you realized it was all nonsense.  LLM's these days are too good for that - the text they generate is sometimes wrong, but rarely nonsense in a humorous way.
Markov chain content was wrong in a "kid's say the darndest things" way, while modern LLMs are wrong in a "My uncle doesn't know basic geography" way.
[0] https://totes-not-amazon.com/ - click any link to get a new one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fishtoaster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by andyferris in "Roblox is the biggest game in the world, but is unprofitable"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287768</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287768"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T04:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Unlike other social platforms, Roblox’s revenue is nearly all via user spending rather than advertising. As such, Roblox pays 25% of its revenue to Apple and Google (30% of transactions on those platforms) whereas Facebook, Snap, et al pay effectively 0. Note that Facebook, which has structurally lower costs to service users than Roblox and is far more mature, has an operating margin of roughly 40% — if the company had to pay out 25-30% first, it would never have “tech company” profit margins, let alone profit dollars.
Wow. I've never though about this before, but this is an awful second-order consequence of the high app store fees set by Apple and Google. It essentially incentivizes App makers to treat users as products not customers!
(Not too surprising for Google, but certainly goes against Apple's public stance).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andyferris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wavemode in "Roblox is the biggest game in the world, but is unprofitable"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287638</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41287638"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T03:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Though Roblox isn’t profitable, there are some significant caveats to the situation. Over the last twelve months, operating cash flow—a far more important measure than accounting-defined profits—were $650MM, about 20% of revenue. Roblox has been cash-positive for at least twenty-four quarters.
This feels like an example of the phenomenon highlighted in another recent post: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41263855
Namely, that as long as Roblox's cash flow is increasing year-over-year, they probably don't care about profit. (And if cash flow ever does stop increasing, they can always get back to sustainability by pumping the brakes on reinvestment spending.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wavemode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by burnte in "Google took three months to remove scam app that stole over $5M"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41286672</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41286672"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T00:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That's amazing, it took them 3 months to kill a scam app, but they proactively shutdown smaller apps that break no rules constantly. I swear someone in Google's exec team is going out of their way to make Google products suck. They've all been getting worse for the past several years. Search gives bad results, search qualifiers only work in "verbatim" mode, GMail sucks at spam filtering now, Android is becoming a PITA, Chrome is shoving in new bad features while killing old good features, etc. There was even a big thing about Google Voice having some massive change where lots of features were going away, so I pulled GV out of my life expecting it to go away, and literally nothing changed.
It's almost like Google is suicidal and these are calls for help.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>burnte</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Pod Failure Policy for Jobs Goes GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/19/kubernetes-1-31-pod-failure-policy-for-jobs-goes-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/19/kubernetes-1-31-pod-failure-policy-for-jobs-goes-ga/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post describes Pod failure policy, which graduates to stable in Kubernetes
1.31, and how to use it in your Jobs.
About Pod failure policy
When you run workloads on Kubernetes, Pods might fail for a variety of reasons.
Ideally, workloads like Jobs should be able to ignore transient, retriable
failures and continue running to completion.
To allow for these transient failures, Kubernetes Jobs include the backoffLimit
field, which lets you specify a number of Pod failures that you're willing to tolerate
during Job execution. However, if you set a large value for the backoffLimit field
and rely solely on this field, you might notice unnecessary increases in operating
costs as Pods restart excessively until the backoffLimit is met.
This becomes particularly problematic when running large-sc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by __MatrixMan__ in "Police cannot seize property indefinitely after an arrest, federal court rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41286072</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41286072"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:30:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They took my camera and then when I tried to get it back they claimed that nothing like that was in evidence.  So I filed a police report because the police stole my camera, but I never heard back about it.
Glad you eventually got your money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>__MatrixMan__</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zone of Interest, a film by Jonathan Glazer, with Christian Friedel, Sandra Huller]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8315</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-the-zone-of-interest-jonathan-glazer-christian-friedel-sandra-huller/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Zone of Interest, trailer, the 2023 film by British director Jonathan Glazer (Sexy Beast, Under the Skin), explores a slightly different aspect of the World War II Holocaust, which resulted in the deaths of six million European Jews at the hands of the Nazis. Rudolf Höss (Christian Friedel), the commandant of Auschwitz, a Nazi […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Threads micro-blogging features, badge number Easter egg]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8327</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/new-threads-micro-blogging-features-badge-number-easter-egg/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T20:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coming soon to Threads on the website: the facility to save post drafts, and schedule posts. Post insights, similar I imagine, to those on Instagram, are also on the way, according to a recent thread by Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg. Scheduling posts and saving drafts — at least if using Threads through the website — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nimbius in "Police cannot seize property indefinitely after an arrest, federal court rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41284917</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41284917"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T19:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I once had the cops seize $800 in cash I had on me to pay for motorcycle service (15% discount with cash) and hold it for 3 months.
Eventually I got a letter saying I had to show up and prove I wasnt going to do drugs with it.  So I showed up with my invoice.
Then I was told I had to submit fingerprints and sign a letter promising I wasnt going to do drugs and I refused.
Finally a month later they sent me a letter saying I had forfeited the money and I showed up again (took a day off work) and they said I had to go to court.  So I went to court, and the judge spent ten minutes telling the cops that didnt show up I had to get my money back.
Next month after that I got a call saying I had property to pick up and that I'd be fined daily if I didnt.  So I got the money back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nimbius</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alberth in "Leaving Neovim for Zed"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41284801</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41284801"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T19:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I initially loved Zed.
But as their focus has shifted to building Collaboration & AI features, and still haven’t yet nailed just being a good/great base editor, its become less useful to me.
I still have a lot of hope for Zed.
But for the time being, I’ve switched back to my old editor & IDE … and I’ll try Zed again at a much later date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alberth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silent Sunday (coffee)]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/silent-sunday-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/silent-sunday-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T18:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I “participated” in Silent Sunday partially due to my social battery being drained. I initially thought that Silent Sunday meant posting a photo that conveys silence, tranquility, and the like. Perhaps in some ways, it still can be. However, I’d be remiss not to acknowledge it’s actual origin1 as described by mocha beanie mummy.
Sometimes I find that words can clutter a photograph. Sometimes I want to look at a photograph, and make up my own mind about it, what I think about it, rather than what others might think it should be about.
The rules guidelines are simple:2
Only one photo.
The photo you post must be taken by you.
Photo must be taken the week you post it.
No other words in the post. Title can be: Silent Sunday or date, nothing else.
Of course, like everything out there, people have done their own Silent Sunday renditions. However, from what I see in the Mastodon hashtag, people are mostly keeping to its original concept.

18/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email
Many thanks to R Scott Jones for pointing me in the right direction.↩


wording taken from the site but paraphrased.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by OutOfHere in "Police cannot seize property indefinitely after an arrest, federal court rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41283829</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41283829"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T17:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a well-intentioned but largely useless ruling because it fails to define the maximum duration for which property can be held. As such, it's up to the police as to what qualifies as indefinite. If the ruling had capped it to 14 or 30 days, that would be a useful ruling.
A hard time cap is essential because one's life too has a cap. The amount of time for which one can go without earning a livelihood also has a cap. Imagine if prison sentences didn't have a time cap.
This illustrates a common problem with our laws. They're very often vaguely defined, needlessly so, in a way that keeps attorneys and judges very rich, and the police abusive, to the detriment of the individual. In a sensible world, the laws would all be rewritten for clarity and consistency, starting with the Constitution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OutOfHere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - A Friend of Mine or a Friend of Ours?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-friend-of-mine-or-a-friend-of-ours?v=1723997702</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-a-friend-of-mine-or-a-friend-of-ours?v=1723997702"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T16:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: A Friend of Mine or a Friend of Ours?
Subtitle: An Essay On Vouching
Date: 2024/08/15
Source: https://unravel.noblogs.org/a-friend-of-mine-or-a-friend-of-ours-an-essay-on-vouching/

 Vouching means different things to different anarchists. For some, to vouch for a person means the vouchee is felt to be trustworthy and competent enough for an action. For others, vouching means that the voucher has concrete evidence of the trustworthiness and competence of the vouchee, and is willing to stake their reputation on that evidence. 
 To agree on whether to vouch for someone or not, we need to be clear about what we mean by vouching. We propose three components of a vouch that might be helpful in discussing that meaning: trustworthiness, competence, and the voucher's reput…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: gull]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53009</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/18/sunday-photoblogging-gull/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quit or Stay?]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/quit-stay/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/quit-stay/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A close friend of mine recently landed a new job and is now considering quitting.
It's impossible to predict whether you'll enjoy a workplace, but it usually becomes apparent soon after starting. If you consistently feel like "this is the wrong place for me," I strongly believe you should quit as soon as possible. I've personally quit jobs within the first week.
Given that work occupies a significant portion of our lives, it's crucial that it feels right. But the very fact that work constitutes a large part of our lives can also mislead us.
Besides work, we have relationships, hobbies, financial responsibilities, and our health to maintain. And, as we all know, life isn't always a constant joyride. Relationships can strain, health can deteriorate, and unexpected financial problems can arise.
Life is often challenging. We feel down and want to feel better.
We seek solutions and try to identify what needs to change. We yearn for a quick fix, and it's easy to blame work. Considering it occupies around a third of our daily lives, it's not surprising that we hold our jobs accountable.
"Yes, of course, it's my workplace. There we have it. I gotta quit!"
But is that really the root of the problem?
It might be partially, or not at all. Regardless, it's never wise to make major decisions based on fleeting, fluctuating, and undefined emotions.
There's usually no rush. It's worth waiting a while. The most important thing is that it's the right decision, whenever and whatever we decide.
You can't eliminate ripples on water with a slap. Wait, and they will eventually subside. Against this still background, the correct answer will emerge.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[169. Curate your love]]></title>
        <id>https://marblethoughts.bearblog.dev/curate-your-love/</id>
        <link href="https://marblethoughts.bearblog.dev/curate-your-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a really nice quote that goes along the lines of “we’re a combination of everything we’ve ever known.” We’re just composed of things that we come across in our lives, and I find that very beautiful.
You are a museum.
~evie\
In essence, love is much like the art of curating a museum. We consider, assess, and most importantly choose the "artifacts" of most significance based on what we (uniquely) enjoy. The things we (uniquely) enjoy are informed by factors as varied and disparate as our blood-sugar levels, among other things. We carefully display our "exhibit of love" in beautiful frames and tags. "This is so me."
Or, to put it differently - imagine an unimaginably vast wall that contains every interest, hobby, passion, and person to ever exist. The concepts of "self" and "taste" le…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by j1elo in "Mpv – A free, open-source, and cross-platform media player"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41278719</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41278719"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T22:57:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow those answers are indeed funny. I agree that as an OSS dev/maintainer, it's easy to fall on the vice of over-generalization and crusade for the perfect solution, and it feels that's exactly what happened there.
> this feature is algorithmically impossible
> You're just looking at one specific video, not the general problem.
> is not generally possible.
As a fellow multimedia dev, man, who cares? Sometimes we forget that software ought to be useful, not hypothetical ideals of truth. Just implement the feature for those codecs that support it and which probably are in the 98% percentile of what users actually use, regardless of the damned "general case".
Or accept and announce shamelessly that you don't have either the knowledge or the development resources to tackle such a complex feature. But excuses about not being possible for absolutely every possible codec in a completely generic way is just denying that the world is just a chaotic and dirty place where things are not ideal nor perfect. Just give your users a real-world solution (or rejection).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>j1elo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lairv in "Mpv – A free, open-source, and cross-platform media player"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41278203</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41278203"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T21:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use it to inspect video frames by frames, particularly being able to go back one frame. VLC doesn't support it, this thread about the feature is hilarious https://forum.videolan.org/viewtopic.php?t=120627]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lairv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by etra0 in "Mpv – A free, open-source, and cross-platform media player"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41277640</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41277640"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fantastic mediaplayer, quite minimalistic and performant; it does what it's supposed to do!
Also has a fantastic commit where the author rants about locales: https://github.com/mpv-player/mpv/commit/1e70e82baa9193f6f02... worth a read for some chuckles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>etra0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Notes 018]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-018/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-018/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T18:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🗓️ // August 10 - August 16, 2024
I am enjoying writing these Week Notes on Saturday mornings as I drink my first cup of coffee. Today’s a late start since I’m still slightly under the weather but feeling a tiny bit better.
Took our friend CS down the coast while she was here this past weekend. Every year she visits from the east coast, we take her to a different part of the Bay (Area). Her first year, we explored the city (San Francisco), the second year we went to Point Reyes, and this year we went a little past Half Moon Bay. Pictures slowly incoming in the photo blog.
A co-worker turned friend recently started a blog. I’ve been talking about my blogging experience the past few months, and since she was looking to start something new, figured she’d try her hand in it. She’s currently t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lotharrr in "Magic Wormhole: get things from one computer to another, safely"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276769</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276769"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T18:32:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(magic-wormhole author here)
Thanks for making a donation!
I run the relay server, but the Debian maintainer agreed to bake an alternate hostname into the packaged versions (a CNAME for the same address that the upstream git code uses), so we could change it easily if the cost ever got to be a burden. It hasn't been a problem so far, it moves 10-15 TB per month, but shares a bandwidth pool with other servers I'm renting anyways, so I've only ever had to pay an overage charge once. And TBH if someone made a donation to me, I'd just send it off to Debian anyways.
Every once in a while, somebody moves half a terabyte through it, and then I think I should either move to a slower-but-flat-rate provider, or implement some better rate-limiting code, or finally implement the protocol extension where clients state up front how much data they're going to transfer, and the server can say no. But so far it's never climbed the priority ranking high enough to take action on.
Thanks for using magic wormhole!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lotharrr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by SoftTalker in "Flaw has Microsoft Authenticator overwriting MFA accounts, locking users out"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276507</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276507"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T17:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["This is a small example of a big problem with usability and cybersecurity. This is what happens when apps are developed by engineers who don’t have a strong knowledge of customers"
This really rings true. Just think of all the nonsense you have to deal with in the name of "security." Mandatory password change intervals. Insane rules for constructing passwords. Completely undocumented password requirements that you just have to figure out by trial and error. Complicated error messages full of security jargon. "Secret Questions" that you can't remember the answers to. And on the other side of the coin, the security of these systems themselves is like a sieve. So many data breaches, information disclosures, they are in the news almost daily. I often wonder how they get away with it all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SoftTalker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon blocks advertising of a novel whose narrator is an economist]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45543</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/17/amazon-blocks-advertising-of-a-novel-whose-narrator-is-an-economist/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T17:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Edward Fullbrook A few years ago, I wrote a novel that was published under a pen name and titled Two American Dreams; Which is yours?  Recently its publisher realized that, although set in the Sixties (mostly in Berkeley) this novel pertains to the coming US presidential election to a remarkable degree.  With that in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edward Fullbrook</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by virgulino in "X says it is closing operations in Brazil due to judge's content orders"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276038</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41276038"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T17:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian here. If anyone wants a great introduction to the context and the bigger picture, there's this great article from the NYT in 2022, written by an excellent reporter who lives in Brazil. I highly recommend this article to anyone who hasn't lived in Brazil for the last 10 years:
"To Defend Democracy, Is Brazil’s Top Court Going Too Far?"
https://www.nytimes.com/2022/09/26/world/americas/bolsonaro-...
https://archive.is/plQFT
It covers the judge at the center of the current issue: "Mr. Moraes has jailed five people without a trial for posts on social media that he said attacked Brazil’s institutions. He has also ordered social networks to remove thousands of posts and videos with little room for appeal. And this year, 10 of the court’s 11 justices sentenced a congressman to nearly nine years in prison for making what they said were threats against them in a livestream."
Rumble has been blocked in Brazil for over a year, and WhatsApp and Telegram have been briefly blocked multiple times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>virgulino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oldprogrammer2 in "Ask HN: Do we need to pay billions in fees to Stripe, Block, PayPal and Visa/MC?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41275901</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41275901"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T16:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stripe, Block, and PayPal each solved a massive pain point.
PayPal provided a way to pay people and vendors without giving away your credit card number.
Square made it easy to accept payment in person on a phone, without an extensive upfront underwriting experience and without expensive fixed monthly fees.
Stripe did the same as Square, but for accepting online payments.
Fraud and Risk come in many forms, and these providers, even with their UX innovations, sit on top of those same rails to reduce fraud.  Without those rails, buyers can’t trust sellers and sellers can’t trust buyers.
In my opinion, you need to find a way to solve that problem before you can eliminate the fees being captured by these providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oldprogrammer2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bear Theme: Bearming]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bearming/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bearming/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T16:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My brother said he thought my blog was broken, so I decided to give it a makeover by creating a new theme. I call it Bearming, because every theme needs a fancy name, right?
Based on the default Bear theme, I aimed to create a clean theme with good readability. The appearance of the list of blog posts is inspired by the beautiful McLuhan theme.
I also wanted to make it easily customizable and expandable. The solution became what I've called 'Add-ons'. These are optional additions for special tweaks. Currently, there are three, with more to come:
Print styles
Highlighted tab
Upvote button
You can simply delete the ones you don't want to use. If you want to use the highlighted tab part, it works best if you only have Home, Blog, and any Page in your navigation. Example code:
<span class="nav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lenerdenator in "China's manufacturers are going broke"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41275258</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41275258"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T15:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, if they want to learn from the US, they should ship their manufacturing capacity and intellectual property off to their geopolitical rival for short-term monetary gain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lenerdenator</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ebbs and flows]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/ebbs-and-flows/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/ebbs-and-flows/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been feeling okay for the most part this month. I've been getting work done, I'm keeping up my habits, and I'm exploring my own creativity through writing. So it feels all the more terrible when I'm suddenly hit with a wave of depression.
For me, these waves come and go at random intervals. I could be having the best day and be hit with the most intense bouts of sadness, anxiety, and hopelessness. It might not be the most healthy thing to do, but I try to distract myself from these feelings by immersing myself in my work, hobbies, or playing video games with friends. This doesn't always help, but it does keep my mind off of it, at least for a short time.
It does get overwhelming sometimes dealing with all this by myself. I don't really have anyone in my life to speak about these things, so I have elected to scream these thoughts into the void that is my blog. I rarely, if at all, feel comfortable enough to talk about my feelings with friends or family because I was raised in a culture where that was not common or tolerated.
This might all sound hopeless, but I know that this will soon pass and that these feelings are temporary. All I have to do is ride out the waves.
17/31]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DarkNova6 in "Just use Postgres"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41273310</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41273310"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T10:20:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> If you see a college student or fresh grad using MongoDB stop them. They need help. They have been led astray.
I like this sentence way more than I should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DarkNova6</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sleepless in "Google removed Organic Maps from the Play Store"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41273180</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41273180"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T09:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And here's the Fediverse post about the incident if you don't want to click on a twitter link https://fosstodon.org/@organicmaps/112976308191001762]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sleepless</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by thor-rodrigues in "X ordered to pay €550k to Irish employee fired after yes-or-resign ultimatum"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41272908</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41272908"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T08:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am glad to hear that workers rights are being enforced in Europe.
As an employee in Germany, it sounds deranged to receive an email saying I have one day to completely change my work contract, or be fired from my job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>thor-rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by CharlieDigital in "Interviewing the Interviewer: Questions to Uncover a Company's True Culture"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41272867</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41272867"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T08:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I ask these indirectly.
    "What types of people tend to succeed and do well with your team?  What types of people tend to struggle in your team?"

    "What are your main objectives in the next 6 to 12 months?  What's your plan to meet those objectives?"

    "How do you see the candidate in this role contributing to that objective?"

    "Tell me about how the team collaborates and coordinates work"

(Am I going to be stuck in 1 hour all-hands daily "stand-ups" every day?)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CharlieDigital</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Margaret Killjoy - Why I Joined the Industrial Workers of the World]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-why-i-joined-the-industrial-workers-of-the-world?v=1723882411</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/margaret-killjoy-why-i-joined-the-industrial-workers-of-the-world?v=1723882411"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T08:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Margaret Killjoy
Title: Why I Joined the Industrial Workers of the World
Date: August 14, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 17th August 2024 from margaretkilljoy.substack.com

 Back in probably 2004, maybe 2005, I was working in Portland, Oregon as a landscaper. It was a small crew, just three of us and our boss. Our boss was, for the most part, pretty cool. He didn’t work us to the bone. He was flexible about time off. He was down to call me Magpie. He paid us under the table. Sometimes he’d cancel work to go surfing. That kind of guy. 
 In fact, after my first week of work, I told him: “hey I’m going to leave for about a month to go block roads in Southern Oregon to stop this old growth timber sale, maybe do some treesitting. When I come back, can I have my job back?” and he said yes, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The worst ever global debt crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-worst-ever-global-debt-crisis</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-worst-ever-global-debt-crisis"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T07:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This policy briefing, based on the new Debt Service Watch database, shows that the citizens of the Global South now face the worst debt crisis since global records began. Debt service is absorbing an average 38% of budget revenue and 30% of spending across the South, rising to 54% of revenue and 40% of spending in Africa. Spread across all continents, 35 countries are paying more than half of revenue, and 54 over one third. (...)
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Illegitimate debt, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective, Development finance international</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zhachev - Anarchy and the Mythic Path]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zhachev-anarchy-and-the-mythic-path?v=1723842478</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/zhachev-anarchy-and-the-mythic-path?v=1723842478"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T21:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Zhachev
Title: Anarchy and the Mythic Path
Date: 08/09/2024
Source: https://zhachev.substack.com/p/anarchy-and-the-mythic-path

 Fluctuations within a continuum can be generated from diverging narratives. Uncertain climes, alternative timelines. Chronoflipping, retroswitching, taleshifting. An alterverse created via timeforge. Terra incognita.
 Narratives serve the function of temporal modulators, unbound by the shackles of progress and linearity. Vectors of radivergence. Distorting, disrupting, and corrupting conventional chronologies, conduits to alternative realities proliferate with every shift in narrative azimuth. Each story is a potential rupture in the continuum of time, a machinic assemblage capable of bearing a plethora of parallel existences. Through an intricate tango b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A wild week in phishing, and what it means for you]]></title>
        <id>66be71ff4a25d6000ae1d4a6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-wild-week-in-phishing-and-what-it-means-for-you"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T17:34:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the U.S. elections and geopolitical conflict to tens of millions in corporate dollars lost, phishing remains the root cause of cyber damages. Learn why a comprehensive solution is the best way to stay protected]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Pang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From the “Committee for the Cancellation of Third World Debt” to the “Committee for the Abolition of Illegitimate Debt”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/From-the-Committee-for-the-Cancellation-of-Third-World-Debt-to-the-Committee</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/From-the-Committee-for-the-Cancellation-of-Third-World-Debt-to-the-Committee"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excerpts from Social Movements and the Politics of Debt: Transnational Resistance against Debt on Three Continents. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Debt campaign, 
Debt crisis, 
CADTM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christoph Sorg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing high-definition portrait video support for Cloudflare Stream]]></title>
        <id>66be142d4a25d6000ae1d42b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-high-definition-portrait-video-support-for-cloudflare-stream"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Stream is an end-to-end solution for video encoding, storage, delivery, and playback, focused on simplifying all aspects of video for developers. Newly uploaded or ingested portrait videos will now automatically be processed in full HD quality]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Huang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify cloud routing and object storage configurations with Cloud Connector]]></title>
        <id>66bcdb694a25d6000ae1d2f8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloud-connector"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Cloud Connector — a new free product to simplify your cloud routing and object storage configurations. Say goodbye to frustrating Host Header workarounds and hello to protecting your assets, accelerating applications, and routing your traffic between multiple cloud providers seamlessly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikita Cano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by idop in "VCs don't care if you're nice, they want founders who take risks"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41265149</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41265149"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T10:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VCs want founders who are willing to play the game and can do it well: lying to (potential) customers, making insane promises, presenting fake demos as if they were real products and using fancy accounting tricks to make the business look profitable, when in fact it is bleeding their money, all so that they can easily find _other_ investors to bail them out. VCs have perfected legal Ponzi schemes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>idop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlín Doherty: &ldquo;Prospects&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/prospects</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/prospects"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T10:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forecasting Starmerism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Ozzie_osman in "Former Google CEO Eric Schmidt's Leaked Stanford Talk"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41263864</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41263864"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T07:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[His explanation for Google losing to OpenAI on GenAI: "Google decided that work life balance and going home early and working from home was more important than winning."
What a tremendous lack of self-awareness. Let's put aside all the leadership issues, all the politics, all the complacency, all the bureaucracy, and blame people for working from home.
(Not saying there aren't folks at Google who are just cruising, etc... but that's a fraction of the problem compared to the leadership issues)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ozzie_osman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecuador: Resistance against the policies imposed by the World Bank, the IMF and other creditors between 2007 and 2011]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-Resistance-against-the-policies-imposed-by-the-World-Bank-the-IMF-and</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-Resistance-against-the-policies-imposed-by-the-World-Bank-the-IMF-and"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
Ecuador, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
BM-FMI-Equateur_EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unsalted Counter Info - Red Flags: Before You Join That Org…]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unsalted-red-flags-before-you-join-that-org?v=1723779932</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/unsalted-red-flags-before-you-join-that-org?v=1723779932"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Unsalted Counter Info
Title: Red Flags: Before You Join That Org…
Subtitle: A Primer on Authoritarian & Vanguard Communist Groups & What You Can Do Instead
Date: June 3, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 10 August 2024 from unsalted.noblogs.org/files/2024/06/RedFlags_Web1.pdf


Intro
 When we pay attention to the amount of injustice in the world, we find ourselves wanting to do something about it. And we don’t want to do just anything. We want to participate in what can most strategically stop those injustices. We need to organize together to confront what is killing us and the planet. 
 If you go looking for others involved in this resistance work, you might stumble across some organizations that seem to have all the answers. They say they know exactly how to bring capitalism to its knees…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Templer - From Mutual Struggle to Mutual Aid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bill-templer-from-mutual-struggle-to-mutual-aid?v=1723779766</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/bill-templer-from-mutual-struggle-to-mutual-aid?v=1723779766"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:42:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Bill Templer
Title: From Mutual Struggle to Mutual Aid
Subtitle: Moving Beyond the Statist Impasse in Israel/Palestine
Date: 2003
Source: Borderlands volume 2 number 3, 2003. Retrieved from https://web.archive.org/web/20180123112424/http://www.borderlands.net.au/vol2no3_2003/templer_impasse.htm

What about a no-state solution? Self determination for everyone, no borders, police, or soldiers. A right-of-return for both Jews and Palestinians. —Pirate Prentice (2002)
The regime that will succeed the nation-state will not be the fruit of preconception or social engineering, but of sociological and political imagination wielded through transformative actions. —Gustavo Esteva (2003)
I Introduction: Reclaiming the Commons
 1. Reinventing politics in Israel and Palestine means laying the g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[David S. D’Amato - Fury of a Rebel Poet]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fury-of-a-rebel-poet?v=1723779574</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fury-of-a-rebel-poet?v=1723779574"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:39:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: David S. D’Amato
Title: Fury of a Rebel Poet
Subtitle: The Anarchism of Joseph Déjacque
Date: August 2, 2024
Source: https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/02/fury-of-a-rebel-poet-the-anarchism-of-joseph-dejacque/

 The French firebrand Joseph Déjacque lived a short life defined by a wild and beautiful struggle against authority, a life of intense passion for freedom and genuine class war. Unlike many of the seminal figures of the anarchist movement, Déjacque was truly of the working class. Born in 1821, he was raised in Paris by a single mother, who had become a widow when he was very young, and he worked full time from the age of 12. His trade was house painting and wallpaper hanging, but as we shall see, he was an able polemicist and poet; his words were a shot of adrenaline to ra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antiauthoritarians-Internationalists - Minimal Contribution for Communicating to the Turkish Cypriot Revolutionary Internationalists the Hypocrisy of The ‘Rapprochement’ Elite of the Greek Cypriot State Intellectuals and Social Patriots]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antiauthoritarians-internationalists-minimal-contribution-for-communicating-to-the-turkish-cypr?v=1723779503</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antiauthoritarians-internationalists-minimal-contribution-for-communicating-to-the-turkish-cypr?v=1723779503"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:38:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antiauthoritarians-Internationalists
Title: Minimal Contribution for Communicating to the Turkish Cypriot Revolutionary Internationalists the Hypocrisy of The ‘Rapprochement’ Elite of the Greek Cypriot State Intellectuals and Social Patriots
Date: 1989
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:leaflets:unclassified:antieksousiastes_epanaprosegisi

 Until today, we knew that the mechanisms of repression of the state and capital were the army, the police, the schools, the psychiatric hospitals. Now we know that along with them have been added the Greek Cypriot ‘rapprochement’ state intellectuals and social-patriots. How else could we explain the fact that these gentlemen invite representatives from all the supposedly re-reunificationist areas to such a meeting — for represe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[nvp - Is there a non-colonial language in Cyprus? And if yes, should we all speak Eteo-Cypriot?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nvp-is-there-a-non-colonial-language-in-cyprus-and-if-yes-should-we-all-speak-eteo-cypriot?v=1723779471</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nvp-is-there-a-non-colonial-language-in-cyprus-and-if-yes-should-we-all-speak-eteo-cypriot?v=1723779471"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: nvp
Title: Is there a non-colonial language in Cyprus? And if yes, should we all speak Eteo-Cypriot?
Date: 2017
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:digital:kontrasousta:kontrasousta_language_nvp

 No one can argue that language is not, at a certain level of analysis, a political tool. People in Cyprus intuitively know this, and that’s why I won’t go into the theory, but instead focus on the practical. 
 Language is political, and we, as individuals and groups, are doing politics. Sometimes consciously, other times less so. This website was also created by a series of political decisions, some of which quite conscious (it is a website which doesn’t limit itself to one part of Cyprus, even though the default option is to segregate). It is, among other things, a spirit…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antifascists - On the expulsion of fascists in Faneromeni]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antifascists-on-the-expulsion-of-fascists-in-faneromeni?v=1723779406</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antifascists-on-the-expulsion-of-fascists-in-faneromeni?v=1723779406"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antifascists
Title: On the expulsion of fascists in Faneromeni
Date: 2013
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:digital:unclassified:faneromeni_fasistes

 The provocative show which took place two weeks ago, by members of ELAM (who also have a 5-year temporary contract working for the Cypriot national army) wearing Golden Dawn t-shirts in a cafe in Faneromeni square in Nicosia, could only get a dynamic antifascist response. By the time they were spotted in the square, a lot of people isolated them and threw them away shouting antifascist songs and showing them efficiently that there is zero tolerance in neo-nazism expressions. Why did all this happen? Why did a group of people attacked people wearing Golden Dawn t-shirts? Isn’t it a democratic right for anyone to wear…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[anonymous - Get a Job!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-get-a-job?v=1723779226</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-get-a-job?v=1723779226"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T03:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: anonymous
Title: Get a Job!
Subtitle: On the Usefulness of Jobs and Small Businessess for Illegalist Anarchists
Date: 08/08/2024
Source: https://unravel.noblogs.org/the-unemployment-problem/

 Anarchists sometimes need money: we need to pay our cell phone bills; buy bus tickets to the hopout; get enough money to buy the squat that we’re about to get evicted from. Some things are just hard to steal, like guns, or are only available online, like decent scanner radios or jamming equipment. 
 Individualist and lifestyle anarchists hold their nose and do legitimate work just long enough to get what they need, aiming for enough money to comfortably hit the road, hit the hay, or hit the target. 
 Socialist anarchists, on the other hand, are willing to engage in legitimate work, seeing it …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: MatchLabelKeys in PodAffinity graduates to beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/matchlabelkeys-podaffinity/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/matchlabelkeys-podaffinity/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.29 introduced new fields MatchLabelKeys and MismatchLabelKeys in PodAffinity and PodAntiAffinity.
In Kubernetes 1.31, this feature moves to beta and the corresponding feature gate (MatchLabelKeysInPodAffinity) gets enabled by default.
MatchLabelKeys - Enhanced scheduling for versatile rolling updates
During a workload's (e.g., Deployment) rolling update, a cluster may have Pods from multiple versions at the same time.
However, the scheduler cannot distinguish between old and new versions based on the LabelSelector specified in PodAffinity or PodAntiAffinity. As a result, it will co-locate or disperse Pods regardless of their versions.
This can lead to sub-optimal scheduling outcome, for example:
New version Pods are co-located with old version Pods (PodAffinity), which will ev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Prevent PersistentVolume Leaks When Deleting out of Order]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/kubernetes-1-31-prevent-persistentvolume-leaks-when-deleting-out-of-order/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/kubernetes-1-31-prevent-persistentvolume-leaks-when-deleting-out-of-order/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PersistentVolume (or PVs for short) are
associated with Reclaim Policy.
The reclaim policy is used to determine the actions that need to be taken by the storage
backend on deletion of the PVC Bound to a PV.
When the reclaim policy is Delete, the expectation is that the storage backend
releases the storage resource allocated for the PV. In essence, the reclaim
policy needs to be honored on PV deletion.
With the recent Kubernetes v1.31 release, a beta feature lets you configure your
cluster to behave that way and honor the configured reclaim policy.
How did reclaim work in previous Kubernetes releases?
PersistentVolumeClaim (or PVC for short) is
a user's request for storage. A PV and PVC are considered Bound
if a newly created PV or a matching PV is found. The PVs themselves are
backed by vo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Read Only Volumes Based On OCI Artifacts (alpha)]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/kubernetes-1-31-image-volume-source/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/16/kubernetes-1-31-image-volume-source/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kubernetes community is moving towards fulfilling more Artificial
Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) use cases in the future. While the
project has been designed to fulfill microservice architectures in the past,
it’s now time to listen to the end users and introduce features which have a
stronger focus on AI/ML.
One of these requirements is to support Open Container Initiative (OCI)
compatible images and artifacts (referred as OCI objects) directly as a native
volume source. This allows users to focus on OCI standards as well as enables
them to store and distribute any content using OCI registries. A feature like
this gives the Kubernetes project a chance to grow into use cases which go
beyond running particular images.
Given that, the Kubernetes community is proud to present…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introverts and extraverts are at war, and introverts are winning. WTF?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8297</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/introverts-extraverts-war-introverts-winning-wtf/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T21:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marie Le Conte, writing for New Humanist, in a provocatively titled article: the introverts are winning, seems to suggest introverts and extraverts are embroiled in some sort of global conflict. A quick explainer. People generally fall into one of two personality traits: extraversion or introversion. It’s a scale. You can be close to either end, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Movements and the Politics of Debt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Social-Movements-and-the-Politics-of-Debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Social-Movements-and-the-Politics-of-Debt"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T20:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social Movements and the Politics of Debt, Transnational Resistance against Debt on Three Continents, Christoph Sorg, Amsterdam University Press, 2022 
English

/ 
Debt campaign, 
Debt crisis, 
Debt in History]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christoph Sorg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh: the ‘Global South' debt crisis intensifies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-the-Global-South-debt-crisis-intensifies</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-the-Global-South-debt-crisis-intensifies"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T20:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The overthrow of the Sheikh Hasina's dictatorial government in Bangladesh by students and the populace last week is a startling outcome of the economic nightmare. The country's average GDP growth over the past decade, according to government statistics, was around 6.6%. As late as April this year, the World Bank reckoned that Bangladesh would grow by 5.6% this year, led by its highly successful garment industry, which relies on cheap labour sweat shops to gain market share globally. It (...)
English

/ 
Bangladesh, 
Debt crisis, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 18 will bring distraction free browsing to parts of the web]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8302</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ios-18-distraction-free-browsing-parts-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T20:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[News sites seem to be the worst, but they’re not alone*. You want to read a news item, but are assailed by a plethora of interfering popups of some sort. But a new feature in the soon to be released iPhone operating system, iOS 18, for Apple’s Safari browser, is a step in the right […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mx. Flow - Buddhist Anarchism: Theory and Practice]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mx-flow-buddhist-anarchism-theory-and-practice?v=1723741802</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mx-flow-buddhist-anarchism-theory-and-practice?v=1723741802"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T17:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mx. Flow
Title: Buddhist Anarchism: Theory and Practice
Subtitle: A Vision for a Buddhist Anarchism
Date: August 12, 2024
Source: Retrieved on August 15th 2024 from dhammaflow.org

 “Is it possible to exercise rulership righteously: without killing and without instigating others to kill, without confiscating and without instigating others to confiscate, without sorrowing and without causing sorrow?” 
 -The Buddha, SN 4.20 [1]
Introduction
 Buddhist Anarchism is a synthesis of Anarchism from Buddhist Religion. Buddhism is a religion over 2,500 years old that teaches people to free themselves from Dukkha (suffering, stress, unsatisfactoriness) through practicing Sila, Samadhi and Panya (Virtue, Concentration and Wisdom) and achieving nibbana (enlightenment, freedom from dukkha). Anar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“New Keynesian” DSGE models]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45540</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/15/new-keynesian-dsge-models-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll To be fair to academia, it has realized that the pure DSGE model is incapable of explaining observable phenomena so they have introduced numerous amendments, known, oddly, as “imperfections” in the model. Long-term nominal contracts, other labour market frictions, imperfection in credit markets, all these and more are prayed in aid and, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on depression & hope]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-depression-hope/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-depression-hope/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I haven’t been feeling well the past few days. I have been feverishly urging myself with tasks throughout the day so I can get my mind off things. Better be productive than dwell with my thoughts, right?
This post isn't a vent, but a candid depiction of the reality of living with depression. (And sometimes I have this strange notion, that perhaps I am helping someone out there also battling depression.)
Recently, I have been forcing myself to leave the house. Depression tries to trick me, to convince me: What will change if you go out? This happens every time I am stuck in the depression loop (as I like to call it). Out of bitterness, I would challenge myself to step out the house for two minutes, then I am free to hide back inside. But the moment I step out, I immediately feel better, and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Millennial Memories]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-millennial-memories/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-millennial-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T14:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been posting Throwback Thursday posts for the past few weeks on my Photoblog where I highlight some of my photos from the archive. It’s been a lot of fun so I wanted to do something similar today on here.
The Millennial generation is huge on nostalgia. Here are some of the highlights I remember from growing up in the 1990s.
Fashion
Butterfly hair clips.
Gel bracelets, the more the better... mostly in black and red.
Tattoo chokers -- although I think these are making a comeback amongst the Gen Zs?
White eyeliner -- I'm not sure why I ever thought this looked good on me, but I tried.
Studded belts worn sideways.
Those milky gel pens that we'd use to draw/write on ourselves. I remember writing I <3 and the initials of that week's crush.
Music
Playing the perfect song on my stereo then re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Jäger: &ldquo;Into the Void&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/into-the-void</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/into-the-void"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T13:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining British pogromism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Community]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/our-community/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/our-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I found out a couple of days ago that one of the people I communicate with regularly on Mastodon, a fellow by the name of Jim Mitchell (@jimmitchell@mastodon.social) was the creator of an app I used to use back in the day called YASU, Yet Another System Utility. I was fairly surprised to have my real life and my IndyWeb life collide like that. Jim and I are about the same age and have had some similar life experiences, facts we know because we've read each other's blogs.(Jim's Blog) It just felt good to have two parts of my life meet each other like that.
Ten years ago I discovered the community of Apple People who were separate from the company. A lot of them were podcasters like David Sparks and the guys from the Accidental Tech Podcast, John Siracusa, Casey Liss and Marco Arment. There …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grandizo Munis - Unions Against Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/grandizo-munis-unions-against-revolution?v=1723704444</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/grandizo-munis-unions-against-revolution?v=1723704444"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Grandizo Munis
Title: Unions Against Revolution
Date: 1960
Notes: Unions Against Revolution is a translation of a work by G. Munis written in 1960 and reprinted in France after the events of May 1968. The English version appearing here is from Internationalism No. 3. Black and Red, Detroit
Source: Retrieved on August 11, 2024 from Black and Red Press PDF

 No contradiction can exist between the economic and the political aspects of a revolutionary conception, even supposing the clearest organic and functional demarcation between them. The same is true for any reactionary conception. Hence the present interpenetration, the agreement and collaboration between unions—economic organs —and political parties—ideological organs—gives us the key to understanding both, from whichever side o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young men aren’t shifting right …]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52985</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/15/young-men-arent-shifting-right/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[… at least in the “Anglosphere” One of the striking features of the racist riots in Britain has been the wide spread of ages among those (nearly all men) convicted so far[1]. This is unusual, since criminal violence of all kinds is most commonly associated with young men. And it’s a counter-example to what has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side discussion]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52983</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/15/side-discussion/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As requested by a couple of commenters, I’ve created a separate thread to discuss the issues raised by commenter “closet conservative” in response to my post on US academia. I’ll moderate, but not participate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification Beta]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/kubernetes-1-31-volume-attributes-class/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/kubernetes-1-31-volume-attributes-class/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Volumes in Kubernetes have been described by two attributes: their storage class, and
their capacity. The storage class is an immutable property of the volume, while the
capacity can be changed dynamically with volume
resize.
This complicates vertical scaling of workloads with volumes. While cloud providers and
storage vendors often offer volumes which allow specifying IO quality of service
(Performance) parameters like IOPS or throughput and tuning them as workloads operate,
Kubernetes has no API which allows changing them.
We are pleased to announce that the VolumeAttributesClass
KEP,
alpha since Kubernetes 1.29, will be beta in 1.31. This provides a generic,
Kubernetes-native API for modifying volume parameters like provisioned IO.
Like all new volume features in Kubernetes, this API is…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.31: Accelerating Cluster Performance with Consistent Reads from Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/consistent-read-from-cache-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/consistent-read-from-cache-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is renowned for its robust orchestration of containerized applications,
but as clusters grow, the demands on the control plane can become a bottleneck.
A key challenge has been ensuring strongly consistent reads from the etcd datastore,
requiring resource-intensive quorum reads.
Today, the Kubernetes community is excited to announce a major improvement:
consistent reads from cache, graduating to Beta in Kubernetes v1.31.
Why consistent reads matter
Consistent reads are essential for ensuring that Kubernetes components have an accurate view of the latest cluster state.
Guaranteeing consistent reads is crucial for maintaining the accuracy and reliability of Kubernetes operations,
enabling components to make informed decisions based on up-to-date information.
In large-scale cluster…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta animates AI-generated images at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21542</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/14/production-engineering/how-meta-animates-ai-generated-images-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched Meta AI with the goal of giving people new ways to be more productive and unlock their creativity with generative AI (GenAI). But GenAI also comes with challenges of scale. As we deploy new GenAI technologies at Meta, we also focus on delivering these services to people as quickly and efficiently as possible. [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta animates AI-generated images at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[writing thrusts me into uncharted territory]]></title>
        <id>https://froggy.bearblog.dev/writing/</id>
        <link href="https://froggy.bearblog.dev/writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[there's lots of discourse on writing in the Bear Den (lol). the purposes of writing, who you should write for, why you should write, etc. All great discussions, and everyone should come to their own conclusions on these things. Once you find something that works, double down! shove!
for me writing is a tool for crystallizing thought. a snapshot of how I would describe a topic in my own words at that point in time. There are 3 ways I see this as useful:
It's powerful like how any picture at any point in time is. Like a picture, you can see progress (taking the delta of the snapshot and some future point). Plus, as you continue to write, you have a body of work to point to that monotonically increases1.
Different from pictures, one of the biggest advantages I leverage is the ability to move …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat of AI, demise of blogging, the world in February 2015]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8288</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/threat-ai-demise-blogging-world-february-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since re-booting disassociated in May 2022, I’ve been slowly (incredibly slowly) restoring selected posts from the previous version of the blog that was online between 2007 and 2017. The restored posts are tagged legacy, and also include a few posts written prior to 2007, going back to 2003. On checking as I typed this, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending August 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240814</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240814"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Karpenter 1.0]]></title>
        <id>3adac2c0ec9122f00dd8e58fe5412f2d5a1d5f9f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-karpenter-1-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T20:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In November 2021, AWS announced the launch of v0.5 of Karpenter, “a new open source Kubernetes cluster auto scaling project.” Originally conceived as a flexible, dynamic, and high-performance alternative to the Kubernetes Cluster Autoscaler, in the nearly three years since then Karpenter has evolved substantially into a fully featured, Kubernetes native node lifecycle manager. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Kestner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving Frugal Architecture using the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>663012dc40f89e066329be90a662febacc172e3c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/achieving-frugal-architecture-using-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T19:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the re:Invent 2023 keynote, Dr. Werner Vogels introduced the Frugal Architect mindset. This mindset emphasizes the importance of continuous learning, curiosity, and regular revision of architectural choices with a focus on cost and sustainability. Cost and sustainability should be treated as critical non-functional requirements, alongside factors like security, compliance, and performance. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley DeLoach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Creaghe - Correspondence]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-correspondence?v=1723661187</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-correspondence?v=1723661187"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T18:46:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Creaghe
Title: Correspondence
Date: November 1891
Notes: Original Title: Creaghe, John, "Correspondence", in Commonweal, Vol. 7, No. 291, (London 1891) pp. 155
Source: Retrieved on 14 August from https://www.marxists.org/history/international/social-democracy/commonweal/1890/index.htm

 Comrades of the 'Weal, 
 I am very glad to see that you had so successful a meeting on the 11th. We had a very good one at Sheffield too though the attendance was small, it was very heartily enthusiastic, and our speakers were well received. 
 It will probably be news for you that I have left Sheffield for Liverpool, where I hope to be able to settle down. The fact is, our paper dragged on but badly, we could never pay more than about the half of the cost, and we determined to stop it at least …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[John Creaghe - Why Creaghe Won’t Pay Poor Rates!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-why-creaghe-won-t-pay-poor-rates?v=1723660629</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/john-creaghe-why-creaghe-won-t-pay-poor-rates?v=1723660629"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T18:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: John Creaghe
Title: Why Creaghe Won’t Pay Poor Rates!
Date: September 1891
Notes: Original Title: Creaghe, John, "Why Creaghe Won’t Pay Poor Rates!", in Commonweal, Vol. 7, No. 281, (London, 1891) pp. 113-4
Source: Retrieved on 14 August from https://www.marxists.org/history/international/social-democracy/commonweal/1890/index.htm

Comrade Creaghe is doing some more practical propaganda, by refusing to pay poor rates. He has taken the opportunity to explain his views on the subject, in the Sheffield Independent. His letter is so good and interesting that we reprint the whole of it:
 To the Editor - I have been summoned to the Town Hall, to show cause why I have not paid and refuse to pay poor rate levied on me. My answer is in the first place that I do not wish to do anything that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>