<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-23T01:55:20.179Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-23T01:55:20.179Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dissecting the Performance Gains in Amazon Q Developer agent for code transformation]]></title>
        <id>2966c911cae5944571341ccd2aaafd2f55b81ae5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/dissecting-the-performance-gains-in-amazon-q-developer-agent-for-code-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T22:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer Agent for code transformation is an AI-powered tool which modernizes code bases from Java 8 and Java 11 to Java 17. Integrated into VS Code and IntelliJ, Amazon Q simplifies the migration process and reduce the time and effort compared to manual process. It proposes and verifies code changes, using AI to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Vogel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new experience for AWS Systems Manager]]></title>
        <id>f940f8f10329048e4784f72ecc08202d5e5d467a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-a-new-experience-for-aws-system-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T22:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain centralized visibility and control over AWS, on-premises, and multicloud compute at scale with the new AWS Systems Manager. Featuring a unified dashboard, one-click agent remediation, Amazon Q Developer integration for natural language queries, and cross-account/Region management - all at no extra cost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/22/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282653</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-22-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T19:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Trump border czar beats chest; Resistance 2.0 funders and NGOs;  Mathematical thinking  ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS named as a leader again in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Distributed Hybrid Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>470d069e3ceffa4e8bc9d6d90aa481c7531d1a9e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-again-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-distributed-hybrid-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T18:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS leads in hybrid infrastructure with top ratings from Gartner for edge computing, AI/ML, and hybrid management; recognized for global support and fully managed offerings like Outposts, expanding consistent cloud experience to on-premises and edge locations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your app authentication workflow with new Amazon Cognito features]]></title>
        <id>df4a34c5aba751c2db72ad9ddf287246b0155c9f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-your-app-authentication-workflow-with-new-amazon-cognito-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T17:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity management revamped: Amazon Cognito unveils customizable login flows, passwordless options, and tiered pricing for tailored authentication experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the Bible Belt]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/living-in-the-bible-belt/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/living-in-the-bible-belt/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a good part of my life, I tried to be religious and failed miserably. During my formative years, church was a social connection as well as a place for religious instruction. During elementary school, my Mom was married to a non-believer, so she didn't attend church, but my siblings and I went with a neighbor to a Southern Baptist church on the outskirts near the prison. My brother and I were active in the boys’ youth group, called RAs for Royal Adventurers. In the summer, we went to VBS (Vacation Bible School).
In high school, I lived with my aunt and uncle. They went to a Presbyterian Church, one of many in the area, reflecting the Scottish heritage in the part of North Carolina where we lived. One of my favorite parts of each week was the Sunday evening Youth Fellowship meetings. It …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by iandanforth in "Show HN: A Marble Madness-inspired WebGL game we built for Netlify"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42214423</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42214423"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice! My favorite challenge was avoiding the glowing white dots along the path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iandanforth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fueling the Flames: How the West’s Military Emissions Undermine Climate Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282649</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/fueling-the-flames-how-the-wests-military-emissions-undermine-climate-action.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T14:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World leaders criticized COP29 host Azerbaijan for its oil-dependent economy while ignoring the massive climate bootprint of their militaries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gavin Rae: &ldquo;Contra Populism?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/contra-populism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/contra-populism"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Tusk’s Poland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading the General Election 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Reading-the-General-Election-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Reading-the-General-Election-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National People's Power (NPP) has made history. With its unprecedented, record-breaking electoral victory at the general election of 2024, the NPP has succeeded in engineering popular dissent towards comprehensive regime change. Its parliamentary super majority has been secured on the back of a near complete rout of the political establishment, while seemingly transcending the ethnic majoritarianism manifested by governments in the past to obtain electoral victories. Most significantly, (...)
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amali Wedagedara, Pasan Jayasinghe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? The Predictability of Bank Failures]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32432</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-the-predictability-of-bank-failures/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can bank failures be predicted before they happen? In a previous post, we established three facts about failing banks that indicated that failing banks experience deteriorating fundamentals many years ahead of their failure and across a broad range of institutional settings. In this post, we document that bank failures are remarkably predictable based on simple accounting metrics from publicly available financial statements that measure a bank’s insolvency risk and funding vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/22/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282627</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-22-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T11:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our kinetic daily links.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FT Confirms What We’ve Been Saying for Three Years: The US Is Losing the “Battle… for Latin America” to China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282588</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/ft-echoes-our-warning-from-three-years-ago-the-us-is-losing-the-battle-for-latin-america-to-china.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T11:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Beijing is now the main trading partner for most nations in the region and has the fastest-growing stock of investments."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump Nominates Corporate Lobbyist and Foreclosure Fraudsters Defender Pam Bondi as Attorney General]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282623</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/trump-nominates-corporate-lobbyist-and-foreclosure-fraudsters-defender-pam-bond-as-attorney-general.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T11:30:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pam Bondi has a terrible record as far as going after corporate misconduct is concerned, which explains Senate enthusiasm for her.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Opportunity to Reset U.S.-Iran Relations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282643</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/trumps-opportunity-to-reset-u-s-iran-relations.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T11:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An in-depth look at Iran's economic and political situation suggests that Trump's "maximum pressure" campaign will not have much impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Threats Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344576</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/the-threats-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T07:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, our Annual Fund Fall Fund Drive isn’t over yet. As you have probably noticed, it is not going as well as we hoped. We still have about $5,000 to go. This isn’t to say the prognosis is all bad, in fact, the good news is that the number of donations we have received thus  More
The post The Threats Ahead appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CounterPunch Staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cities Made Differently: Try Imagining Another Urban Existence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344555</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/cities-made-differently-try-imagining-another-urban-existence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T07:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a city without any strangers, where everything is shared, and everyone looks after each other. There are no shops, no money, and no danger at all. We think of the family as a group that practices “basic communism”: from each according to his ability to each according to his needs. Any family is thought to be protected by bonds of kinship from the cruel laws of the outside world. Unlike businesses, rarely will a family throw out a sick child or an elderly parent because they are no longer “revenue-generating assets.” More
The post Cities Made Differently: Try Imagining Another Urban Existence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Graeber – Nika Dubrovsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NYT’s Friedman’s Two-State Solution: Delusion, Illusion and Confusion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344609</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/nyts-friedmans-two-state-solution-delusion-illusion-and-confusion/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T07:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times’ leading columnist, Thomas Friedman, has devised an answer to “How Trump Could Earn an Unexpected Place in History.”  Friedman believes there is an opportunity for Donald Trump to exert pressure on Israelis and Palestinians, which would help the president “find a place in the history books that you did not expect.”  This is part delusion, part illusion, and part confusion, all hallmarks of Friedman’s writings on the Israeli genocidal campaign in Gaza over the past year. More
The post  NYT’s Friedman’s Two-State Solution: Delusion, Illusion and Confusion appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Just Proportion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344537</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/in-just-proportion/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T07:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any successful peace initiative will have to accept that the Ukraine conflict has no single bad guy. We do not recognize Putin’s view of NATO as a beast with encircling claws. At the same time, Russians can be forgiven for thinking that the Western narrative is not quite as defensive as it seems. “The spread of our values makes us safer” declared Tony Blair in Chicago in 1999, justifying NATO’s bombing of Yugoslavia. This sets out the ground for forcible regime change when the opportunity offers. The underlying message is that democracy is the peaceful, dictatorship the warlike form of the state, so a war for democracy is necessarily a war for peace. Many Western analysts view the war in Ukraine as a war for regime change in Russia, which is why they cannot contemplate anything less than a Ukrainian victory. More
The post In Just Proportion  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Skidelsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: The Final Daze]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344517</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/roaming-charges-the-final-daze/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hysteria over Trump’s election must be tempered by just how awful Biden has been after the entirely predictable, if sinister, decision of the American electorate to return Trump to power. The liberal abreaction to Trump has revealed how thoroughly blind many have been to the vileness of Biden and his obedient circle of advisors and enforcers. If there was a secret Biden waiting until after the election to emerge, it was only a more malicious and baleful version of the Biden we’ve witnessed for the last four years.  More
The post Roaming Charges: The Final Daze appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[West Papua: Where Transmigration Means Genocide, Ecocide and, in the End, Suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344289</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/west-papua-where-transmigration-means-genocide-ecocide-and-in-the-end-suicide/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past six decades, Indonesia has been an occupying colonial power in West Papua. The United Nations is responsible for this and its atrocious consequences, as John Saltford meticulously details in his account of the 1969 UN-orchestrated handover of West Papua to Indonesia in a so-called Act of Free Choice, which was nothing more than “a ridiculous and overtly manipulated denial of West Papuan rights”. Ever since, overt manipulation of the reality of the West Papuan people has been the order of the day in the international arena. The murderous farce is officially blessed as Indonesia has been a member of the UN Human Rights Council since 2006. More
The post West Papua: Where Transmigration Means Genocide, Ecocide and, in the End, Suicide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s On Deck for Climate Change?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344496</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/whats-on-deck-for-climate-change/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Peter Carter, an Expert Reviewer of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC), has new information about the status of climate change that meets the IPCC 6th Assessment worst-case scenario. Carter makes the case that the climate system is several years ahead of expectations, and in fact, knocking on the door of the IPCC’s  More
The post What’s On Deck for Climate Change? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Nation in Denial: Why Israel’s Defeat is Imminent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344494</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/a-nation-in-denial-why-israels-defeat-is-imminent/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradoxical phrase, ‘running away forward’ is one of the most apt descriptions that illustrates the state of Israeli affairs now. It seems that everything that Israel has done in the past year or so is a mere attempt to deny, distract from or escape imminent future scenarios – all of which are bleak. Indeed,  More
The post A Nation in Denial: Why Israel’s Defeat is Imminent  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Gaza to COP29: The 9 Types of Violence Wealthy Countries are Inflicting on the Global South]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344309</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/from-gaza-to-cop29-the-9-types-of-violence-wealthy-countries-are-inflicting-on-the-global-south/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The wealthy, imperialist countries of the Global North are committing a long list of crimes against people in Latin America, Africa, the Middle East and Asia. From bombing, to environmental destruction, through to media erasure, the powerful economic and political entities of the Global North are intentionally generating and maintaining catastrophe, then normalizing it. But  More
The post From Gaza to COP29: The 9 Types of Violence Wealthy Countries are Inflicting on the Global South appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamara Pearson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Retreat from Reason:  Palestine in the Time of Monsters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344551</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/retreat-from-reason-palestine-in-the-time-of-monsters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our times are fraught.  This is especially glaring in the Middle East as the United States wrestles to maintain its control over this rich and complicated region.     Today’s ethos of convulsion is aptly reflected in the words of 20th century Italian philosopher, Antonio Gramsci, “The old world is dying, and the new world struggles to  More
The post Retreat from Reason:  Palestine in the Time of Monsters appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Last Thing, America!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344572</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/one-last-thing-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My inbox is full of lament (and encouragement). My Instagram feed is full of anger and “the arc of the moral universe bends slow but…” My Facebook brims with exhortations to focus on the positive, on what we can control, on the next fight. I live in a poor Democratic stronghold in southeastern Connecticut. Kamala Harris won  More
The post One Last Thing, America! appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frida Berrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Limits of Liberal Criticism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344135</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/donald-trump-and-the-limits-of-liberal-criticism/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One silver lining of Trump’s return is that it has undermined the central claim of a now ubiquitous school of thought professing that the fundamental problem with US politics is the conservatism, or countermajoritarianism, of the Constitution. Writers including Levitsky and Ziblatt, Ari Berman, Erwin Chemerinksy, and others have been reintroducing the claim that the  More
The post Donald Trump and the Limits of Liberal Criticism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Sperber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Went So Very Bad: Is There a Way Out?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344544</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/it-went-so-very-bad-is-there-a-way-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s election in 2016 was seen as the ultimate slap in the face to the leftists among my generation of baby boomers. The ultimate truth is, however, that we had had so many real and symbolic slaps in the face since the youth movement and baby boomer cohort of the Vietnam era that one  More
The post It Went So Very Bad: Is There a Way Out? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump and Consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344383</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/trump-and-consequences/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beginning of President-elect Donald Trump 2.0 has started with a chaos that is more sinister than President Trump 1.0. This time around he seems better prepared; this time there are fewer guardrails. Moreover, while there are evident reasons to follow his machinations domestically, there are also international implications to his victory and control of  More
The post Trump and Consequences appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Great Trump Escape: Night Trains to Armenia]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344486</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/a-great-trump-escape-night-trains-to-armenia/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tired of all things Trump—the endless lying and criminality, the perverts in his inner circle, the stealing and the golf course monarchy, and the existence of people who could actually vote for him—I decided to pack my papers, books, computer, and some clothes into two small bicycle saddle bags and head out on a series  More
The post A Great Trump Escape: Night Trains to Armenia appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time and Time Again, Mass Deportations Have Failed–Trump’s Plans Will Be No Different]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344208</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/time-and-time-again-mass-deportations-have-failed-trumps-plans-will-be-no-different/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a student in the 2000s, I was actively involved in immigrant raid response efforts that churches, labor unions, and community groups organized to mitigate the effects of then-President Bush’s nationwide enforcement actions. We took resources like clothes, food, and money to affected families in the states of Minnesota and Iowa, and conducted ‘Know Your  More
The post Time and Time Again, Mass Deportations Have Failed–Trump’s Plans Will Be No Different appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anthony Pahnke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Song Remains the Same: Detuning the Democratic Defeat]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344647</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/the-song-remains-the-same-detuning-the-democratic-defeat/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released only the day before the election, will.i.am’s sonic squib, “Yes She Can,” was the final political misfire of the musical campaign, the cannon’s weak report barely heard as evening fell on Kamala Harris’s presidential campaign and the routed troops fled her standard. But there is another mournful melody that continues to waft across early  More
The post The Song Remains the Same: Detuning the Democratic Defeat appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Glaring Hypocrisy of Establishment US International Education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344137</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/the-glaring-hypocrisy-of-establishment-us-international-education/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after the US presidential election, Fanta Aw, executive director and CEO of NAFSA, posted the following on her LinkedIn page: “Waking up to a new day, and America has spoken. The work of international education has never been more important. It is the bridge that unites us, ensuring a future where we are  More
The post The Glaring Hypocrisy of Establishment US International Education appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Ashwill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada Reinvents the Xenophobic Wheel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344564</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/canada-reinvents-the-xenophobic-wheel/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bikram Singh is running out of time on his post-study work visa in Canada. Singh is one of about 70,000 migrants who were sold on the Canadian dream of eventually making the country their home but now face an uncertain future with their work permits set to expire by December 2024. They came from places like India,  More
The post Canada Reinvents the Xenophobic Wheel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saurav Sarkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should We Have Wolves or Livestock on Public Lands?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344569</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/should-we-have-wolves-or-livestock-on-public-lands/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the American West, the vast majority of public lands are leased to ranchers to graze their livestock. The ranchers can’t seem to get along with any of the wild inhabitants. Coyotes, ravens, eagles, mountain lions, prairie dogs, grizzly bears, beavers are all targeted for elimination by the livestock industry, for its sole convenience. Ranchers  More
The post Should We Have Wolves or Livestock on Public Lands? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Molvar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On and Off in Life and Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344552</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/on-and-off-in-life-and-death/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less than a year after the American philosopher Daniel C. Dennett put out his latest collection of quality ruminations on his life, titled I Was Thinking (2023), he died of interstitial lung disease in a bed at Maine Medical Center in Portland on April 19, 2024. He surely had an intimation of his nearing demise, as he  More
The post On and Off in Life and Death appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life With and After Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344556</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/life-with-and-after-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How does one take seriously having a vaccine denier in charge of public health? How about having the world’s richest corporate owner in charge of cutting regulatory agencies?  Or having the other foxes in the henhouse, much less Oval office-ing the degenerate ringmaster himself? I would guess all who read this article feel outrage and  More
The post Life With and After Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Albert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Maryhouse Stage: Power Politics and War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344293</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/on-the-maryhouse-stage-power-politics-and-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-November, New York’s Catholic Worker community, located in lower Manhattan, opened their sizable auditorium to host “Reap What You Sow: Don’t Lose Heart!” a two act play with two actors which debuted, for two nights, on the Maryhouse stage. Prior to the performance, preparations included selecting the sturdiest wooden chairs for audience seating, carefully  More
The post On the Maryhouse Stage: Power Politics and War appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surviving the New Trump Era]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344554</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/surviving-the-new-trump-era/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s victory in the U.S. presidential election was surprising in a number of ways. He won every swing state as well as the popular vote, which a Republican candidate hadn’t done in two decades. He led his party to a congressional sweep, with the Republicans maintaining control of the House of Representatives and seizing  More
The post Surviving the New Trump Era appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canada and Ukraine: The Careful Suppression of a Shameful History]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344546</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/canada-and-ukraine-the-careful-suppression-of-a-shameful-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few days before Remembrance Day, November 11, 2024, the Government of Canada announced that it will not release the portion of a report produced by the Commission of Inquiry into War Criminals in Canada (Deschênes Commission) that names 900 Canadians accused of war crimes committed on behalf of the Nazis. Canada admitted these people  More
The post Canada and Ukraine: The Careful Suppression of a Shameful History  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Philpot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitulation: The Weimar Dems on Bended Knee]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344582</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/capitulation-the-weimar-dems-on-bended-knee/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Behold the craven post-election capitulation of the dismal Weimar Democrats to the Hitler-channeling fascist Donald “Poisoning Our Blood” Trump. The imperialist butcher “Genocide Joe” Biden said this after Trump won two weeks ago: “For over 200 years, America has carried on the greatest experiment in self-government in the history of the world — the people  More
The post Capitulation: The Weimar Dems on Bended Knee appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Pick for EPA is a Zealot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344492</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/trumps-pick-for-epa-is-a-zealot/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Unqualified,” declared Ben Jealous, executive director of the Sierra Club, about Lee Zeldin being nominated by President-elect Trump to head the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. The nomination, Jealous said, “lays bare Donald Trump’s intentions to, once again, sell our health, our communities, our jobs and future out to corporate polluters. Our lives, our livelihoods, and  More
The post Trump’s Pick for EPA is a Zealot appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Grossman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Photographer Consuelo Kanaga in Black and White: a Role Model for the Age of Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344146</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/photographer-consuelo-kanaga-in-black-and-white-a-role-model-for-the-age-of-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re like many of my friends and neighbors in liberal Democratic San Francisco, you may be shaking your head in disbelief and muttering that you don’t understand the results of the election. If that description fits you, you might chill or gaze at the photographs of Consuelo Kanaga which are now in an exhibit  More
The post Photographer Consuelo Kanaga in Black and White: a Role Model for the Age of Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tipping Point after Trump Victory: Why No One Can Stop the Global Energy Transition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344308</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/tipping-point-after-trump-victory-why-no-one-can-stop-the-global-energy-transition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s victory as next president of the United States is depressing news for climate protection. He already made clear that under his presidency the US will drop out of the Paris agreement which binds countries to the 1.5 to 2 degrees Celsius limit. Trumps announcement comes as no surprise of course, since he already  More
The post Tipping Point after Trump Victory: Why No One Can Stop the Global Energy Transition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Goeßmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An 83-Year-Old Short Story by Borges Portends a Bleak Future for the Internet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344139</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/22/an-83-year-old-short-story-by-borges-portends-a-bleak-future-for-the-internet/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T06:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How will the internet evolve in the coming decades? Fiction writers have explored some possibilities. In his 2019 novel “Fall,” science fiction author Neal Stephenson imagined a near future in which the internet still exists. But it has become so polluted with misinformation, disinformation and advertising that it is largely unusable. Characters in Stephenson’s  More
The post An 83-Year-Old Short Story by Borges Portends a Bleak Future for the Internet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger J. Kreuz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Don’t Just Do Nothing to Counter Fascism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-don-t-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism?v=1732247504</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-don-t-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism?v=1732247504"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T03:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Don’t Just Do Nothing to Counter Fascism
Subtitle: 20 Things You Can Do to Counter Fascism — Yes, You! Yes, Now
Date: November 2024
Source: Retrieved on 22 November 2024 from <mafwdistro.noblogs.org/dont-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism>

Note
 This zine is a communal effort, with advice gleaned from the following Jewish anarchists: alice, asher, cat, chanaleh, cindy, cindy barukh, hannah, jhaavo, lilli, mazel, scarab, simcha, and vicky. 
 “Don’t Just Do Nothing: 20 Things You Can Do to Counter Fascism — Yes, You! Yes, Now” is intended as inspiration for everyone who is striving toward a world without fascism — whether or not they’re Jewish or an anarchist. Please share this zine freely and widely. November 2024 
 
 
 You are not obligated to complete the w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Stirner - Review of Bruno Bauer's Trumpet of the Last Judgment]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/max-stirner-review-of-bruno-bauers-trumpet-of-the-last-judgment?v=1732234735</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/max-stirner-review-of-bruno-bauers-trumpet-of-the-last-judgment?v=1732234735"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T00:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Max Stirner
Title: Review of Bruno Bauer's Trumpet of the Last Judgment
Date: January 1842
Notes: German Source: Telegraph für Deutschland. Red. von Karl Gutzkow. No. 6-8. Julius Campe, Hamburg, Januar 1842, pp. 22-24, 25-28, 30-31; Kleinere Schriften hrs. John Henry Mackay (Berlin: Bernhard Zack, 1914), pp.11-25.
Source: Stepelevich, Lawrence S. “Addenda: II C.” Translated Essay. In Max Stirner On the Path of Doubt, 188–197. Lanham, Maryland: Lexington Books, 2020. See English original for translator's preface. All footnotes Stepelevich's.

 What should not be tolerated, equalized, and reconciled with everything else? We have endured this accommodation, this easy acceptance which, as it can be imagined, has brought us to a state of exhaustion, which has divided our inner hearts, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize compute resources on Amazon ECS with Predictive Scaling]]></title>
        <id>7447588fd8c9011cc2ed6d3b1feb380497e5d2cd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/optimize-compute-resources-on-amazon-ecs-with-predictive-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Jooyoung Kim, Senior Containers Specialist Solutions Architect, Abhishek Nautiyal, Senior Product Manager, Amazon ECS and Ankur Sethi, Senior Product Manager, Amazon EC2. Introduction Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) is an opinionated, easy-to-use container orchestration service with deep AWS integrations that streamlines the deployment and management of containerized applications at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing new capabilities to AWS CloudTrail Lake to enhance your cloud visibility and investigations]]></title>
        <id>9af3e66a3a525e854568fac1b32c692141587e31</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-new-capabilities-to-aws-cloudtrail-lake-to-enhance-your-cloud-visibility-and-investigations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T21:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudTrail Lake updates simplify auditing with AI-powered queries, summarization, and enhanced dashboards for deeper AWS activity insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Track performance of serverless applications built using AWS Lambda with Application Signals]]></title>
        <id>e29ad690a671ba7f9c62224e5a01a357f568efd8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/track-performance-of-serverless-applications-built-using-aws-lambda-with-application-signals/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain deep visibility into AWS Lambda performance with CloudWatch Application Signals, eliminating manual monitoring complexities and improving serverless app health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlotte Wood did not win the Booker Prize, still gets Booker bump]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8874</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/charlotte-wood-did-not-win-booker-prize-wins-booker-bump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of Australian author Charlotte Wood’s latest novel Stone Yard Devotional have enjoyed a boost, as a result of being both long and short listed for this year’s Booker Prize. The phenomena is sometimes called the Booker bump: Her publisher says that since winning the Stella Prize in 2016 for The Natural Way of Things, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Love for Books That Lasts]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/building-a-love-for-books-that-lasts/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/building-a-love-for-books-that-lasts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T19:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to building habits to enjoy reading, I’ve experimented with quite a few ideas. Some worked while others didn’t. The four strategies that follow have proven themselves, making and keeping reading enjoyable.
Here’s hoping they work just as well for you.
Quit Annoying Books (but not immediately)
Are you reading a book and still finding it just average after a hundred pages? Quit it. Put it away and move on. There are too many incredible books waiting to be read to waste time on ones you don’t enjoy. If there’s one thing that can destroy your joy of reading, it’s forcing yourself to read through books you don't like. Think back to the books you were forced to read in school. For most of us, those didn’t exactly ignited our love for reading, did they?
Read 3 Books at a Time
Choose…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/21/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282591</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-20-2024-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Gaetz: Exit, stage right; Ortberg: "The beatings will continue until morale improves"; How the Democrats abandoned the working class ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Bluesky Block Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/some-bluesky-block-lists/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/some-bluesky-block-lists/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instructions:
Select the list
Tap "Subscribe" button on the top
Select "Block" or "Mute" the entire list.
Right wing propaganda and their followers — Bluesky
ANTI NFT/AI/CRYPTO SHILL LIST — Bluesky
Content Scrapers — Bluesky
Spambots and scammers — Bluesky
Nazis — Bluesky
MAGA — Bluesky

Enjoyed it? Please upvote 👇



if (document.querySelector("body").classList.contains("post")) {
  function setContent(child) {
    switch (child["wm-property"]) {
      case "in-reply-to":
        return child.content?.text;
      case "like-of":
        return "liked this";
      case "repost-of":
        return "reposted this";
      default:
        return "interacted with this post in an unknown way";
    }
  }

  async function fetchInteractions(headerTitle) {
    const response = await fetch("https://webmention.io/api/mentions.jf2?target=" + document.URL);
    const data = await response.json();
    if (data && data.children.length > 0) {

      const interactions = document.createElement("div");
      interactions.innerHTML = `
${headerTitle ?? "Interactions"}
`;

      for (const child of data.children) {
        const interaction = document.createElement("div");

        interaction.innerHTML = `
              
${child.author.name}
                   - ${new Date(child["wm-received"]).toLocaleString("en-US", {
          month: "short",
          day: "numeric",
          year: "numeric",
        })}
              
${setContent(child)}
          `;

        interactions.appendChild(interaction);
      }

      const upvoteForm = document.getElementById("upvote-form");
      upvoteForm.parentNode.insertBefore(interactions, upvoteForm.nextSibling);
    }
  }

  fetchInteractions(document.currentScript.getAttribute("data-interactions"));
}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[are you surveilling yourself yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/selfsurveillance/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/selfsurveillance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grades.
IQ points.
Income.
BMI, height, weight.
Calorie intake.
Calorie expenditure.
Step count.
Temperature.
Frequent heart rate monitoring.
Mood tracking.
Habit tracking.
Streaks.
Sleep score.
Countdown to the IF eating window.
Numbered step morning or evening routine.
Followers.
Likes.
Your life in numbers and rows. It’s all laid out like a spreadsheet, everything has to be accounted for. If only you can optimize further and buy the products to track and hit the optimal range, everything will be fine, right? Everything will change once you tackle this one thing.
Your boss is bullying you, you can’t afford rent and you have to take care of your parents, but it will all be better when you hit the 10k steps and read 4 books a month. The university stress is killing you, but getting that pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your DevOps and Developer Productivity guide to 2024 re:Invent]]></title>
        <id>2a0311c795664a031bc2ebab9909d8908478ab66</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/your-devops-and-developer-productivity-guide-to-2024-reinvent/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s that time of the year again. The annual AWS re:Invent conference is just around the corner. Still need to save your spot? You can register here. This year’s DevOps and Developer Productivity (DOP) track features an impressive lineup, including 11 breakout sessions, 14 chalk talks, 2 code talks, 8 workshops, 3 builder sessions, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS CloudFormation Hooks invoked via AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI)]]></title>
        <id>06438beb8b5a369c8d7df0ccec85c17549c361b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-aws-cloudformation-hooks-invoked-via-aws-cloud-control-api-ccapi/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the integration of AWS CloudFormation Hooks with AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI). This integration enables the use of hooks to validate the configuration of resources being provisioned through CCAPI. In this blog post, we will explore the integration between CloudFormation Hooks and CCAPI by configuring an existing hook to work with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin DeJong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacific aid falls due to Ukraine focus + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aid to the Pacific falls 18% as focus shifts to Ukraine; Russia launches its first ICBM in the conflict; ICC issues arrest warrants for Netanyahu and Hamas leaders; Oropouche virus cases in Brazil surge amid new strain investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Dukes: &ldquo;Proliferations&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Kevin Killian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[International Criminal Court Issues Arrest Warrants for Israel Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and Former Minister of Defense, Yoav Gallant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282580</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/international-criminal-court-issues-arrest-warrants-for-israel-prime-minister-benjamin-netanyahu-and-former-minister-of-defense-yoav-gallant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a long delay, the International Criminal Court issued arrest warrants against the open genociders Benjamin Netanyahu and Yoav Gallant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a visual update to the AWS Management Console (preview)]]></title>
        <id>3c48f4b90c1afccc51d832e1bd239d9a4d036796</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-a-visual-update-to-the-aws-management-console-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new intuitive AWS console design enhances readability, reduces complexity for improved task focus and efficiency while maintaining familiarity across AWS experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nabla9 in "ICC issues warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant, and Hamas officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42203754</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42203754"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T12:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(before you jump into discussion, remember that this only about these two individuals)
ICC and the prosecutor are on very solid ground here.
The prosecutor asked opinions from a impartial panel of experts in international law. The panel included people like Theodor Meron (former Legal adviser for the Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs),  Helene Kennedy, Adrian Fulford.
Netanyahu and Yoav Gallant provided plenty of evidence of the intent. Did they really think that when they talk Hebrew to their audience, rest of the world does not hear them. Case like this would be harder to prosecute without evidence of intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nabla9</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? Three Facts About Failing Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32456</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-three-facts-about-failing-banks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do banks fail? In a new working paper, we study more than 5,000 bank failures in the U.S. from 1865 to the present to understand whether failures are primarily caused by bank runs or by deteriorating solvency. In this first of three posts, we document that failing banks are characterized by rising asset losses, deteriorating solvency, and an increasing reliance on expensive noncore funding. Further, we find that problems in failing banks are often the consequence of rapid asset growth in the preceding decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/21/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282570</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-21-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T11:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our overly dynamic daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFK, Jr. Plans Attack on AMA’s Big Meal Ticket, Licensing Fees for Medical Billing Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282563</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/rfk-jr-plans-attack-on-amas-big-meal-ticket-licensing-fees-for-medical-billing-codes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T11:46:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RFK, Jr.'s plan, if confirmed as HHS chair, to end Medicare use of AMA licensed-billing codes somehow will increase, not lower, costs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions & answers on China as a major creditor power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T08:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has been demonized by several commentators: it is said to be the main creditor of many countries of the South and to get the most of them through ruthless exploitation whereas the World Bank, the IMF, the Paris Club, that bring together traditional creditor powers, are supposed to do their best to help those countries burdened by too much debt. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
China, 
BRICS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HP achieved 40% improvement in Kubernetes node utilization on Amazon EKS using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>1cfef501e204d4782ada7fcdd095f8ae11aca063</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-hp-achieved-40-improvement-in-kubernetes-node-utilization-utilization-on-amazon-eks-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post was co-authored by Jon Lewis (SW R&D Director in HP), Gajanan Chandgadkar (Principal Cloud Operations Architect, HP), Rutvij Dave (Sr. Solutions Architect at AWS), Ratnopam Chakrabarti (Sr. Solutions Architect, Containers and Open-Source technologies at AWS), Apeksha Chauhan(Senior Technical Account Manager at AWS) and Chance Lee (Sr. Container Specialist Solutions Architect at AWS) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vannevar Labs cut ML inference costs by 45% using Ray on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>881522d823c2683572eded22898d1b5c5549f643</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-vannevar-labs-cut-ml-inference-costs-by-45-using-ray-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is authored by Colin Putney (ML Engineer at Vannevar Labs), Shivam Dubey (Specialist SA Containers at AWS), Apoorva Kulkarni (Sr.Specialist SA, Containers at AWS), and Rama Ponnuswami (Principal Container Specialist at AWS). Vannevar Labs is a defense tech startup, successfully cut machine learning (ML) inference costs by 45% using Ray and Karpenter on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon CloudFront VPC origins: Enhanced security and streamlined operations for your applications]]></title>
        <id>e9cf7abc977d40ac1bb9255061c1a08c6959b403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-cloudfront-vpc-origins-enhanced-security-and-streamlined-operations-for-your-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securely deliver high-performance web apps with CloudFront VPC origins; serve content directly from private subnets, eliminating undifferentiated work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront now accepts your applications’ gRPC calls]]></title>
        <id>5d526139e265f2b1f97ea808cbe69afe4337f6ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudfront-now-accepts-your-applications-grpc-calls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock high-performance APIs with gRPC on Amazon CloudFront. Reduce latency via a global CDN, secure traffic at the edge, and benefit from DDoS protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger and badder: how DDoS attack sizes have evolved over the last decade]]></title>
        <id>5JhHzAWP0tvrl8ZolsnvyE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/bigger-and-badder-how-ddos-attack-sizes-have-evolved-over-the-last-decade"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we plot the metrics associated with large DDoS attacks observed in the last 10 years, does it show a straight, steady increase in an exponential curve that keeps becoming steeper, or is it closer to a linear growth? Our analysis found the growth is not linear but rather is exponential, with the slope varying depending on the metric (rps, pps or bps).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>José Salvador</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 17, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241120</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241120"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAIRU — a harmful fairy tale]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45841</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/20/nairu-a-harmful-fairy-tale-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The NAIRU story has always had a very clear policy implication — attempts to promote full employment are doomed to fail since governments and central banks can’t push unemployment below the critical NAIRU threshold without causing harmful runaway inflation. Although a lot of mainstream economists and politicians have a touching faith in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient Internet connectivity in Europe mitigates impact from multiple cable cuts]]></title>
        <id>5DP2F9GATeUBYyfl6pQMej</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/resilient-internet-connectivity-baltic-cable-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two recent cable cuts that occurred in the Baltic Sea resulted in little-to-no observable impact to the affected countries, in large part because of the significant redundancy and resilience of Internet infrastructure in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the grass greener on the Bluesky side of the fence?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8870</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/grass-greener-bluesky-side-fence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T20:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter-like microblogging social network Bluesky is having its moment in the sun. We’ve all seen the multiple headlines of late heralding the arrival of another several million new members, most of whom have migrated from Twitter. The buzz is similar to that surrounding Mastodon about two years ago. Even if Mastodon’s decentralised structure confused many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactively validate your AWS CloudFormation templates with AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>6e59f7aea8061022674286f8882daa78a3e476a1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/proactively-validate-your-aws-cloudformation-templates-with-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CloudFormation is a service that allows you to define, manage, and provision your AWS cloud infrastructure using code. To enhance this process and ensure your infrastructure meets your organization’s standards, AWS offers CloudFormation Hooks. These Hooks are extension points that allow you to invoke custom logic at specific points during CloudFormation stack operations, enabling […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a managed hook for Guard]]></title>
        <id>544d1304f85c9b526be6493d28a5fdfad360e121</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-a-managed-hook-for-guard/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T17:17:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s cloud-driven world, maintaining compliance and enforcing organizational policies across your infrastructure is more critical than ever. AWS CloudFormation, a service that enables you to model, provision, and manage AWS and third-party resources through Infrastructure as Code (IaC), has been a cornerstone for automating cloud deployments. While CloudFormation simplifies resource management, ensuring compliance with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Terry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by OutOfHere in "FireDucks: Pandas but Faster"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42195321</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42195321"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T16:12:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't use it:
> By providing the beta version of FireDucks free of charge and enabling data scientists to actually use it, NEC will work to improve its functionality while verifying its effectiveness, with the aim of commercializing it within FY2024.
In other words, it's free only to trap you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OutOfHere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Initial thoughts on The Power of Now by Eckhart Tolle]]></title>
        <id>https://meadow.cafe/initial-thoughts-on-the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/</id>
        <link href="https://meadow.cafe/initial-thoughts-on-the-power-of-now-by-eckhart-tolle/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I finally started reading The Power of Now by Eckhart Tolle. I've tried to start this book many times before, but I always stopped in the first chapter or so because I felt that the author was being unnecessarily airy and, more importantly, he directly claimed that he ended up in this semi enlightened state but doesn't rightly know how he got there. This point was the point where I always stopped, but this time I decided to power through it, and in doing so I discovered I've been missing an important part: after not knowing what had happened, and just living in a state of present bliss, Eckhart discovered that what had happened to him is what many religions aim as their ultimate goal, so he went on to discover more about that and how a normal person might get to his state, but told from hi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetary developments in the Euro Area, september 2024. Quiet.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45832</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/20/monetary-developments-in-the-euro-area-september-2024-quiet/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T15:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like John Stuart Mill, I´m more interested in credit than in money. Developments in the amount of credit provided are much more instructive to the economist than data on money. Look at the graph below (no. 2 in the ECB press release) , a highly Post-Keynesian graph that originated from the pre-Euro Bundesbank and is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Company lawyers reduce server load by 93% by adding cookie consent banner]]></title>
        <id>https://www.theolognion.com/p/company-lawyers-reduce-server-load</id>
        <link href="https://www.theolognion.com/p/company-lawyers-reduce-server-load"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T14:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German e-commerce startup has been battling repeated server downtimes due to increased popularity of their services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Solenya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM stands in solidarity with the Palestinian resistance in the face of apartheid, crimes against humanity and colonisation practised by the extreme right-wing government in Israel.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-stands-in-solidarity-with-the-Palestinian-resistance-in-the-face-of</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-CADTM-stands-in-solidarity-with-the-Palestinian-resistance-in-the-face-of"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We express our solidarity with the people of Palestine and oppose the aerial bombardments and indiscriminate and terrorist military actions carried out by the Israeli authorities. We call for the dismantling of the colonialist apartheid state of Israel and for respect for the rights of peoples to exercise their sovereignty. 
English

/ 
Palestine]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yanis Varoufakis: &ldquo;Quantity to Quality&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/quantity-to-quality</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/quantity-to-quality"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T12:02:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An interview with Yanis Varoufakis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for Abolishing and Replacing the IMF and the World Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-Abolishing-and-Replacing-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Case-for-Abolishing-and-Replacing-the-IMF-and-the-World-Bank"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T10:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mrtksn in "Let's Encrypt is 10 years old now"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42191644</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42191644"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T07:49:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hands down one of the greatest services out there, stopped a racket and made the internet secure.
I remember a time when having an HTTPS connection was for "serious" projects only because the cost of the certificate was much higher than the domain. You go commando and if it sticks then you purchase a certificate for a 100 bucks or something.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mrtksn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominal for Storing, Structural for Manipulating]]></title>
        <id>https://welltypedwitch.bearblog.dev/nominal-for-storing-structural-for-manipulating/</id>
        <link href="https://welltypedwitch.bearblog.dev/nominal-for-storing-structural-for-manipulating/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T02:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Something that comes up sometimes in programming languages is the difference between nominal and structural type systems.
nearly every programming language gets wrong.
But let's start from the top
What's In a Name
If you're coming from a language like Java, Kotlin, Haskell, OCaml or Rust (or most other languages really), nominal types are what you would probably just think of as "types".
In a language like this, a type needs to be defined in a type declaration where it is given a name that acts as its sole source of identity, without any regard for its implementation. Even if two separate types happen to share the same implementation, they are deemed unequal because they have different names.
For example, if I were to define two java classes
class A {
    int x;
}
class B {
    int x;
}

o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C + Raylib: snake game]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/c-raylib-snake-game/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/c-raylib-snake-game/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T01:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Continuation of the snake game series. This one is using C + Raylib and there will be another version with Zig + Raylib. You might wonder why did I wrote multiple versions of this snake games? My gamedev session is usually done in Godot 4, but I have always been curious how it differs when doing gamedev in Raylib.
What's Raylib?

Taken from the website: a programming library to enjoy videogames programming; no fancy interface, no visual helpers, no gui tools or editors... just coding in pure spartan-programmers way.
Key point: "pure spartan-programmers way".
Yes compared to using Godot 4, I do feel like a Spartan warrior when using Raylib! Gamedev in Godot is a walk in the park comparatively.
NOTE: you'll see a super similar code compared to the ASCII snake code.
#1 Libraries
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by redleggedfrog in "When did estimates turn into deadlines?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42188611</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42188611"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've gone through times when management would treat estimates as deadlines, and were deaf to any sort of reason about why it could be otherwise, like the usual thing of them changing the specification repeatedly.
So when those times have occurred I've (we've more accurately) adopted what I refer to the "deer in the headlights" response to just about anything non-trivial.  "Hoo boy, that could be doozy.  I think someone on the team needs to take an hour or so and figure out what this is really going to take."  Then you'll get asked to "ballpark it" because that's what managers do, and they get a number that makes them rise up in their chair, and yes, that is the number they remember.  And then you do your hour of due diligence, and try your best not to actually give any other number than the ballpark at any time, and then you get it done "ahead of time" and look good.
Now, I've had good managers who totally didn't need this strategy, and I loved 'em to death.  But for the other numbnuts who can't be bothered to learn their career skills, they get the whites of my eyes.
Also, just made meetings a lot more fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>redleggedfrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded resource awareness in Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>a0a4939548a04cba5f81d0300776c90f4ad22036</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/expanded-resource-awareness-in-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, Amazon Q Developer announced expanded support for account resource awareness with Amazon Q in the AWS Management Console  and the AWS Mobile Application. This is coupled with the general availability of Amazon Q Developer in AWS Chatbot, enabling you to ask questions from Microsoft Teams or Slack. Additionally, Amazon Q will now provide context-aware assistance for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DO it again: how we used Durable Objects to add WebSockets support and authentication to AI Gateway]]></title>
        <id>2b8uznXSknoVGwTIcxxmKp</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/do-it-again"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Cloudflare’s Developer Platform and Durable Objects to build authentication and a WebSockets API that developers can use to call AI Gateway, enabling continuous communication over a single, persistent connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catarina Pires Mota</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fbartos in "Fair coins tend to land on the side they started (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42187911</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42187911"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I'm the first author of the manuscript, so I thought I could answer some of the questions and clarify some issues (all details are in the manuscript, but who has the time to read it ;)
Low RPM tosses: Most of the recordings are on crapy webcams with ~ 30FPS. The coin spin usually much faster than the sensor can record which results in often non-spinning-looking flips. Why did we take the videos in the first place? To check that everyone collected the data and to audit the results.
Building a flipping matching: The study is concerned with human coin flips. Diaconis, Holmes, and Montgomery's (DHM, 2007) paper theorize that the imperfection of human flips causes the same-side bias. Building a machine completely defeats the purpose of the experiment.
Many authors and wasted public funding:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fbartos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The W3C launches the Sustainable Web Interest Group]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8861</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/w3c-launches-sustainable-web-interest-group/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T20:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Wide Consortium (W3C) has the emissions created by the internet in its sights… who knew just high web caused emissions were? The mission of the Sustainable Web Interest Group is to improve digital sustainability so that the Web works better for all people and the planet. The digital industry is responsible for 2-5% […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Katie Cunningham: write badly to write well]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8858</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/katie-cunningham-write-badly-write-well/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian author and journalist Katie Cunningham: My high school English teacher told me that good writing is the tenth draft of bad writing. I saw this in The Booklist, a weekly newsletter by the Sydney Morning Herald, the other day. Sometimes I feel as if I rewrite everything I post here ten times before publishing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unification, a short Star Trek film, in memory of Leonard Nimoy]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8863</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/unification-short-star-trek-film-memory-leonard-nimoy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T19:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To mark the thirtieth anniversary of the 1994 release of Star Trek Generations, comes Unification, which kind of picks ups after the conclusion of Generations. But it’s also a whirlwind jaunt through The Original Series (TOS) universe. There’s a cameo by Gary Lockwood, of 2001: A Space Odyssey, who featured in Where No Man Has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China boosts support for Global South + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-boosts-support-for-global-south-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-boosts-support-for-global-south-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T17:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese President Xi Jinping announces eight development measures for the Global South; President Biden visits the Amazon rainforest to boost climate efforts; Biden pledges record $4 billion to World Bank fund for poorest nations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequence learning: A paradigm shift for personalized ads recommendations]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21954</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/11/19/data-infrastructure/sequence-learning-personalized-ads-recommendations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T17:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI plays a fundamental role in creating valuable connections between people and advertisers within Meta’s family of apps. Meta’s ad recommendation engine, powered by deep learning recommendation models (DLRMs), has been instrumental in delivering personalized ads to people. Key to this success was incorporating thousands of human-engineered signals or features in the DLRM-based recommendation system. [...]
Read More...
The post Sequence learning: A paradigm shift for personalized ads recommendations appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Stranger I Know]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/the-stranger-i-know/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/the-stranger-i-know/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMA - What's one of the hardest things you have ever done?
My Dad woke up this morning and didn't know what day it was. Panicked, he sent a text message to almost everyone in the family asking for help. At this point, that means my siblings and his. We are a close family and several of us sprang into action. His brother-in-law lives a couple of miles away and was the first to arrive. My aunt, a nurse with more than 40 years experience was there within the hour. They got him to the doctor and then the hospital where the doctors are running tests to rule out a stroke. His thinking seems to have cleared up since he sent the original text but he still couldn't figure out how to set an alarm on his phone. That kind of thing is starting to happen with more frequency.
Dad is the sole care-giver f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring and automating recovery from AZ impairments in Amazon EKS with Istio and ARC Zonal Shift]]></title>
        <id>db09bb00bec3054fc452195e8064aa26f8c5eec4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/monitoring-and-automating-recovery-from-az-impairments-in-amazon-eks-with-istio-and-arc-zonal-shift/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Running microservice-style architectures in the cloud can quickly become a complex operation. Teams must account for a growing number of moving pieces, such as multiple instances of independent workloads, along with their infrastructure dependencies. These components can then be distributed across different topology domains, such as multiple Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (Amazon EC2) instances, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lukonde Mwila</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How China Could Re-Dollarize The World]]></title>
        <id>673c3f761a75f60001d16cb4</id>
        <link href="https://indi.ca/how-china-starts-printing-usd/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China just issued a USD bond in Saudi Arabia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>indi.ca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[are we repeating the cycle?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/repeating-the-cycle/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/repeating-the-cycle/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These past days, I was very busy with playing Magic the Gathering and Pokemon TCG. Oops.
But when I wasn't busy with that, I was reading about Bluesky.
It's everywhere right now - Bearblog, the news, other online spaces talking about the great eXodus. It ranged from singing praises to it just being the new thing or "at least it's not X". I have to say, some things about it are really enticing and cool; aside from it being a new shiny thing to try out, I love the idea of the starter packs, the import tools, the custom domains (and those also serving as a kind of verification system), algorithmic feeds, thread and feed preferences, labeling and more.
But what keeps me critical is wondering if we aren't just repeating the cycle?
People have spoken about the fact that it feels like old Twitter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["abzug" theme for bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/abzug-theme-for-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/abzug-theme-for-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.marquee-container{width:100%;overflow:hidden;padding:10px 0}.marquee{white-space:nowrap;font-family:monospace;font-size:1rem;color:color-mix(in srgb,var(--text-color) 20%,transparent)}.scroll-right{animation:scrollRight 20s linear infinite}.scroll-left{animation:scrollLeft 20s linear infinite}@keyframes scrollRight{0%{transform:translateX(-50%)}100%{transform:translateX(0%)}}@keyframes scrollLeft{0%{transform:translateX(0%)}100%{transform:translateX(-50%)}}.marquee-top{position:fixed;top:0;left:0}@media (max-width:0){.marquee-container{display:none}}




            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 
            TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • TRANS EUROPE EXPRESS • 

-->


Abzug is a simple typography-focused theme that emphasizes readability. Born from a moment of inspiration in a cafe, accompanied by the sounds of Kraftwerk.
Preview: Visit bear.css.observer and select the Abzug preset. 
https://static.mgx.me/bear/themes/abzug.css.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rkharsan64 in "DOJ will push Google to sell off Chrome"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181921</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181921"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T10:27:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People here seem to be underestimating the advantages that Google gets just because of Chrome:
- When you sign in to Google, you sign in browser-wide. Google now gets all of your browsing data, perfect for advertising. (If you ever doubt it, go check out Google Takeout. You'll be shocked at the amount of data you see there.)
- They have special APIs and features that they get to use, and nobody else. Only because they own Chrome. [1]
- They get to move forward with enabling and pushing features that allow for more advertising: see Manifest v3, FLoC.
- Google specifically serves a worse version of Search on Firefox for Mobile. You have to get an extension to get the full experience.
This isn't an isolated attempt. You can see more of the same thing with Android.
- AOSP (the open source counterpart of Android) is now unusable. It doesn't ship with most essential apps, including a Phone app. In previous versions of Android, all of these were a part of AOSP.
- Most third party launchers/stores struggle to implement features because they are only available for Google themselves.
- The signing in with Google thing from above continues here too: you sign in to Google system-wide.
[1]: https://x.com/lcasdev/status/1810696257137959018]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rkharsan64</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wesselbindt in "DOJ will push Google to sell off Chrome"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181001</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42181001"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T08:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm very surprised by the number of people in this thread who don't seem to understand that monopolies are _very_ bad for consumers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wesselbindt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I love blogging]]></title>
        <id>https://jakobusbrahms.com/i-love-blogging/</id>
        <link href="https://jakobusbrahms.com/i-love-blogging/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T01:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is going to be sort of a meta post, but I just felt such an  sense of joy after publishing my last post that I felt I had to write more.
I’ve long wanted to have a blog. Practically ever since I learned HTML programming with my dad when I was 10, I’ve wanted to have a web presence of some sort. And so I coded various websites to try to fulfill that desire. I found out about free hosting on GitHub Pages, and set up a static site generator to publish to it. But I never had anything to say, and so never used my shiny new website. Then I learned about Wordpress and paid for hosting so I could set up a pretty slick website with a hip theme. But again, I didn’t know what to say.
I think whenever I set up a new site I always got caught in the trap of feeling like I needed to write in a niche…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s dictatorship is a fait accompli]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53405</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/19/trumps-dictatorship-is-a-fait-accompli/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-19T00:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I drew up a flowchart to estimate the probability that Trump would establish a dictatorship in the US, which looked, at the time, like an even money bet. We don’t need to speculate any more. Trump has announced the dictatorship, and there is no sign of effective resistance. The key elements […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Know before you go – AWS re:Invent 2024 cloud resilience]]></title>
        <id>21322524039287ae311396c3c1ba05aedce35ee8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/know-before-you-go-aws-reinvent-2024-cloud-resilience/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T23:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re attending AWS re:Invent 2024 with the goal of improving your organization’s cloud resilience operations, we will be offering valuable insights, best practices, and fun activities to improve your cloud resilience expertise. This year, we’re offering more than 100 resilience breakout sessions, workshops, chalk talks, builders’ sessions, and code talks. Find the complete list in the re:Invent 2024 session catalog and filter by “Resilience” in the area of interest field. In this post, we highlight must-see sessions for those building resilient applications and architectures on AWS. Reserved seating is now open, so act quickly to claim your seat. Be sure to also check out the vertical-specific re:Invent guides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shllomi Ezra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS enhances Kubernetes control plane observability]]></title>
        <id>28bc1106056a70a93b5b24d9119e9e7a806241bd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-enhances-kubernetes-control-plane-observability/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T23:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) is a managed Kubernetes service to run Kubernetes in the AWS cloud and on-premises data centers. In the cloud, Amazon EKS automatically manages the availability and scalability of the Kubernetes control plane nodes responsible for scheduling containers, managing application availability, storing cluster data, and other key tasks. However, maintaining […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashok Srirama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astra Dynamic Chunks: How We Saved by Redesigning a Key Part of Astra]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17285</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/astra-dynamic-chunks-how-we-saved-by-redesigning-a-key-part-of-astra/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T22:06:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Slack handles a lot of log data. In fact, we consume over 6 million log messages per second. That equates to over 10 GB of data per second! And it’s all stored using Astra, our in-house, open-source log search engine. To make this data searchable, Astra groups it by time and splits the data…
The post Astra Dynamic Chunks: How We Saved by Redesigning a Key Part of Astra appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Luong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline container application networking with built-in Amazon ECS support in Amazon VPC Lattice]]></title>
        <id>67d7d0b2d520590609cc528db5a2d3e6af8285e0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/streamline-container-application-networking-with-native-amazon-ecs-support-in-amazon-vpc-lattice/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify networking for containerized apps with native VPC Lattice-ECS integration, boosting productivity and flexibility across services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda SnapStart for Python and .NET functions is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>1efe6355721882348179128f93749c102250b8f4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-snapstart-for-python-and-net-functions-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T21:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda SnapStart boosts Python and .NET functions' startup times to sub-second levels, often with minimal code changes, enabling highly responsive and scalable serverless apps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by teruakohatu in "20 years of Google Scholar"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42176959</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42176959"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T20:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best thing, by a long way, that Google Scholar has achieved is denying Elsevier & co a monopoly on academic search.
In most universities here in New Zealand, articles have to be published in a journal indexed by Elsevier's Scopus. Not in a Scopus-indexed journal, it does not count anymore than a reddit comment. This gives Elsevier tremendous power. But in CS/ML/AI most academics and students turn to Google Scholar first when doing searches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>teruakohatu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dumbing down Notepad by giving it artificial intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8853</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dumbing-down-notepad-artificial-intelligence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T20:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having barely touched their simple text editor, Notepad, in years, Microsoft has been laying on the modifications in recent times. A few months ago, they fitted out Notepad with an autocorrect and spell-checker feature. That’s fine for people wishing to use Notepad as a word processor (in preference to paying out for a subscription to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Merchant Ivory, a James Ivory, Ismail Merchant documentary, by Stephen Soucy]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8849</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-merchant-ivory-james-ivory-ismail-merchant-documentary-stephen-soucy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T19:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filmmakers James Ivory, the late Ismail Merchant, and Ruth Prawer Jhabvala, who collaborated as Merchant Ivory, made over forty features between 1963 and 2009. I think you’d be hard pressed to find any well-known actor of recent decades who did not work with them. My favourite is A Room with a View, which I’ve written […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and modify apps using natural language with AWS App Studio, now generally available]]></title>
        <id>ca7af76d4e0c5efc867c78848fb0cbd33937942b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-and-modify-apps-using-natural-language-with-aws-app-studio-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unleash your inner developer with AWS App Studio, the generative AI-powered application builder. Turn your idea into fully-fledged, intelligent, custom, secure, and scalable software in minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda turns ten – looking back and looking ahead]]></title>
        <id>1392cf1e2098d7939ad92ac27e8c9ceb3c6e131b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-lambda-turns-ten-the-first-decade-of-serverless-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T18:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the journey of AWS Lambda, the pioneering serverless computing service, from its 2013 inception to powering over two million users and tens of trillions of function invocations monthly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS BuilderCards at re:Invent 2024, AWS Community Day, Amazon Bedrock, vector databases, and more (Nov 18, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>2bf6f8f4243881c44ffaa2a8d0dc0785ceb1bc65</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-buildercards-at-reinvent-2024-aws-community-day-amazon-bedrock-vector-databases-and-more-nov-18-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T17:38:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, we wrapped up the final 2024 Latin America Amazon Web Services (AWS) Community Days of the year in Brazil, with multiple parallel events taking place. In Goiânia, we had Marcelo Palladino, senior developer advocate, and Marcelo Paiva, AWS Community Builder, as keynote speakers. Florianópolis feature Ana Cunha, senior developer advocate, and in Santiago […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jp57 in "Air traffic failure caused by two locations 3600nm apart sharing 3-letter code"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42174194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42174194"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T16:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FYI: nm = nautical miles, not nanometers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jp57</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superinflation in Milei´s Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45821</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/18/superinflation-in-mileis-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T13:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hyperinflation is defined as over 50% inflation per month. Let´s define ´normal´ inflation as anything between 0 and 1% per month and anything between 1 and 50% per month as superinflation (1% a month is still a lot, yearly!). Before President Milei, Argentina already knew superinflation. After Milei, inflation accelerated, and the country almost entered […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a Little Friction to My Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-18T03:20:03.086Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like the peak internet for me was some time around 2004. The internet felt balanced, and I was happy with my relationship with it. Sure, I probably spent more time than I should have on the internet, but at least I wasn't carrying it around with me. I wasn't surfing the web on my bathroom breaks or while standing in line at the grocery store. The internet was a tool, not a conqueror of my attention.
For years, I've talked about wanting to set up a desktop or a designated computer space. Some place where I have go and sit down in order to log on. A place where I'll keep my computer off and give myself a few seconds to decide whether looking up an actress in some random sitcom episode is truly worth the effort. I want to add a little friction to my computing and just see how my mental health responds. Will I feel better? Will my attention improve? These are the questions I'm curious about.
Being that I have a little free time on my hands, I thought now is as good of a time as ever to give this a shot. So, starting tonight at midnight, I'm disconnecting. For the next week, my MacBook will live on my dining room table. I'm uninstalling most of the apps that I use on my phone to make it as bare-bones as possible. My iPad will remain on, but with the Wi-Fi turned off. I have a lot of magazines downloaded courtesy of Archive.org and some books I plan to read with my free time.
I wonder how my browsing habits will change if I don't have a piece of technology at my fingertips. Will I feel compelled to keep up with as much, or will I just find other mindless activities to fill my time? Heck, I even wonder if I'll make it the whole week. But these are the questions I will hopefully have an answer to around this time next week. With that being said, if anyone needs to contact me e-mail is going to be your best bet, because I'm sure I'll check that, but I'm probably going to miss a lot elsewhere.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blitz, a movie by Steve McQueen, with Saoirse Ronan]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8840</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/film-blitz-steve-mcqueen-saoirse-ronan/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T20:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve ended up seeing a stack of movies featuring Irish-American actor Saoirse Ronan, over the years. Tracking all the way back to Atonement in 2007, I think. Maybe I’m not so much of a Ronan fan, as I am the movies she’s in. But it’s an impressive list of titles. The Lovely Bones, The Way […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My blog theme and my mini, theme-editing dev environment]]></title>
        <id>https://noat.blog/my-blog-theme-and-my-mini-theme-editing-dev-environment/</id>
        <link href="https://noat.blog/my-blog-theme-and-my-mini-theme-editing-dev-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So I've gotten really nice comments about the theme I've put together for this blog! It's actually really nice to hear 'cause it's a bit more involved than simple CSS, so I'm glad it sticks out well!
Digging the look of your page, and this guestbook! Just dropping by to say hello 👋
whoa, i love your blog theme. super cute, sleek, while still very functional... i love it! definitely adding your blog to my rss feeds, i've liked your posts so far!
love the look of the blog.
I wanted to make it reminiscent to some elements from my art archive, but keep it pretty simple, both because Bear is pretty minimal by nature & I didn't want to let my perfectionist side take over. But! There are a few things that I think would be fun to point out since they were neat to implement, as well as the tool I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by leetrout in "Good Software Development Habits"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42165704</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42165704"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T18:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> It's better to have some wonky parameterization than it is to have multiple implementations of nearly the same thing. Improving the parameters will be easier than to consolidate four different implementations if this situation comes up again.
Hard disagree. If you cant decompose to avoid "wonky parameters" then keep them separate. Big smell is boolean flags (avoid altogether when you can) and more than one enum parameter.
IME "heavy" function signatures are always making things harder to maintain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>leetrout</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election: Take Four]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45807</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/17/election-take-four/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T17:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Take four. I continue to listen in on the conversation. The election reverberates loudly around leftish circles. Recriminations mount. Criticisms fly. Finger pointing and over-analysis have become all too common. And this is after just a week. Imagine what a month can produce. So far the central narrative seems to be that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Forest Lawn Memorial Park, Glendale]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53402</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/17/sunday-photoblogging-forest-lawn-memorial-park-glendale/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T17:48:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kitchy and quasi-totalitarian ghastliness, USA (from 2008)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by null0pointer in "The Bluesky firehose viewed in the style of a Windows XP screensaver"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42163194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42163194"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T10:05:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of commenters here are having their minds blown by this. And while I also love this I get the sense that many others here are maybe too young to remember that this kind of open access to data used to exist for lots websites. It inspired companion sites and loads of creativity. I find it tragic really, what the internet has become. I hope federated, and even more-so p2p, protocols take significant foothold on the internet and help revive this spirit of the web. The corpo-web is so fucking boring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null0pointer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by langsoul-com in "CSS gets a new logo and it uses the color `rebeccapurple`"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42162264</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42162264"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T05:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The color was originally going to be called beccapurple, but Meyer asked that it instead be named rebeccapurple, as his daughter had wanted to be called Rebecca once she had turned six. She had said that Becca was a "baby name," and that once she had turned six, she wanted to be called Rebecca. As Eric Meyer put it, "She made it to six. For almost twelve hours, she was six. So Rebecca it is and must be."
Wasn't expecting tears over a colour]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>langsoul-com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Tired, Boss]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/i-m-tired-boss/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/i-m-tired-boss/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }

In the 1999 movie adaption of Steven King's The Green Mile, the guards go into the condemned man's cell to ask about the arrangements for his execution. They want to know his last meal request and if he wants a preacher to be with him. Ultimately, they even ask if he wants a chance to escape. The prisoner, named John Coffey, tells them he's ready to go, starting his speech with a resigned "I'm tired boss." Brother, I can relate.
Most of my working life hasn't been spent in a physically demanding job. Occasionally in educational tech we have …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASCII snake in C]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/ascii-snake-in-c/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/ascii-snake-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T04:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
I've got some small/tiny gamedev projects on my pocket that I haven't documented here in my Bearblog account. The first one is an ASCII Snake game only using the curses library. There will be another similar post on making Snake game using Raylib.
#1 Libraries
#include <curses.h>
#include <stdbool.h>
#include <stdlib.h>
#include <time.h>
#include <unistd.h>
#include <string.h>

#2 Consts, structs and global vars
#define MAX_SCORE 256
#define FRAME_TIME 180000

typedef struct {
    int x;
    int y;
} Vec2;

int score = 0;
char score_message[32];

bool skip = false;
bool is_running = true;

int screen_width = 25;
int screen_height = 20;

// initialize screen
WINDOW *win;

// snake
Vec2 head = {0, 0};
Vec2 segments[MAX_SCORE + 1];
Vec2 dir = {1, 0};

// berry
Vec2 berry;

#3 Fun…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by LakesAndTrees in "Show HN: I built a(nother) house optimized for LAN parties"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160767</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160767"/>
        <updated>2024-11-17T00:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think the thing that I’m most amazed by - and this setup is truly amazing - is the fact that you’ve got a group of friends to enjoy this with. Good for you; this looks like a blast, and I can only imagine how fun that’d be, compared to years of purely solo gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LakesAndTrees</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shermantanktop in "Netflix buffering issues: Boxing fans complain about Jake Paul vs. Mike Tyson"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160502</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42160502"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T23:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time a big company screws up, there are two highly informed sets of people who are guaranteed to be lurking, but rarely post, in a thread like this:
1) those directly involved with the incident, or employees of the same company.  They have too much to lose by circumventing the PR machine.
2) people at similar companies who operate similar systems with similar scale and risks.  Those people know how hard this is and aren’t likely to publicly flog someone doing their same job based on uninformed speculation. They know their own systems are Byzantine and don’t look like what random onlookers think it would look like.
So that leaves the rest, who offer insights based on how stuff works at a small scale, or better yet, pronouncements rooted in “first principles.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shermantanktop</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by softwaredoug in "Netflix buffering issues: Boxing fans complain about Jake Paul vs. Mike Tyson"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42157774</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42157774"/>
        <updated>2024-11-16T17:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way to deal with this is to constantly do live events, and actually build organizational muscle. Not these massive one off events in an area the tech team has no experience in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>softwaredoug</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>