<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-04T02:18:32.045Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-04T02:18:32.045Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – Ukraine War Report]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293232</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-ukraine-war-report.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T18:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have followed the war in Ukraine closely since 2022, and now that the war seems to be heading toward a conclusion, I would like to offer some observations. The War Was Planned and Guided by Western Governments  Recent revelations have ended the pretense that Ukraine has been directing its war against Russia independently with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brussels’s media machine: EU media funding and the shaping of public discourse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/brusselss-media-machine-eu-media"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T15:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New report exposes a vast, previously under-scrutinised system through which the European Union annually disburses €80 million a year to media projects across Europe and beyond]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Another Aid Massacre’: Israeli Military Kills Dozens More Near Privatized Gaza Food Site]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293320</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/another-aid-massacre-israeli-military-kills-dozens-more-near-privatized-gaza-food-site.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Israel genocide strategy: killing Gazans at aid distribution sites.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building an AI Agent that puts humans in the loop with Knock and Cloudflare’s Agents SDK]]></title>
        <id>3YwK1RRHXn4kGrNazu4AKd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-agents-at-knock-agents-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Knock shipped an AI Agent with human-in-the-loop capabilities with Cloudflare’s Agents SDK and Cloudflare Workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bell (Guest author)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/3/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293191</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-3-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our scandalous daily links: excess disability, moar US-China tariff row, Baerbock as new UN chief, Uk crisis coming? IDF targeting aid recipients, Iran deal impasse, Russia in Sumy, FEMA chief ignorant of hurricane season, AI destroying math skills, private credit worries, moar at home eating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larry Wilkerson: “We’re Looking at Nuclear War”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293275</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/larry-wilkerson-were-looking-at-nuclear-war.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Larry Wilkerson: The  deep US involvement in the Ukraine drone attacks on Russia means we are on a path to nuclear war.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iron Rivers Everywhere: How US Arms Smuggling Is Fuelling Violence in Mexico, Central America and the Caribbean]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293203</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/iron-rivers-everywhere-how-the-us-is-arming-criminal-gangs-and-narco-terrorists-throughout-mexico-central-america-and-the-caribbean.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T10:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even US-aligned governments in the region are beginning to ask, somewhat naively, which side the US is on in the war on guns, begging the question: which war?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariff Turmoil and the Money Markets: Yet Another Rescue Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293259</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/tariff-turmoil-and-the-money-markets-yet-another-rescue-coming.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T09:01:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Treasury markets, there are no libertarians, only grateful recipients of single-payer insurance for ailing financiers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models what they don’t know]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/themis-ai-teaches-ai-models-what-they-dont-know-0603"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of MIT researchers founded Themis AI to quantify AI model uncertainty and address knowledge gaps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Winn | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Short Summary Of Why China Is Winning &amp; The West Fading]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDj3LbK-0QR9TAvgYX1QWNu"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T03:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s about living in reality:
The main difference between American and Chinese society today is less that one has more dumb people and one has more smart people and more that within public life being stupid is relentlessly shamed as stupid in one and being smart is relentlessly shamed as stupid in the other.
These days American society assigns intelligence credentials based not on who can demonstrate a meticulous well developed understanding of how anything works but who can give the most smart sounding post hoc rationalization for half baked ideas people desperately want to be true.
If you do the former and it yields answers people don’t like they’ll reach deep into their bag of fantasyland narratives to try to invalidate your credibility. If you provide the latter you’re celebrated not o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI stirs up the recipe for concrete in MIT study]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/ai-stirs-recipe-for-concrete-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T19:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With demand for cement alternatives rising, an MIT team uses machine learning to hunt for new ingredients across the scientific literature.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Paul Laurent | MIT Concrete Sustainability Hub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teaching AI models the broad strokes to sketch more like humans do]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/teaching-ai-models-to-sketch-more-like-humans-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SketchAgent, a drawing system developed by MIT CSAIL researchers, sketches up concepts stroke-by-stroke, teaching language models to visually express concepts on their own and collaborate with humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Shipps | MIT CSAIL</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyze media content using AWS AI services]]></title>
        <id>df70aecbbf09cdd2b5cd5b057a82fffb9d66bac9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/analyze-media-content-using-aws-ai-services/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations managing large audio and video archives face significant challenges in extracting value from their media content. Consider a radio network with thousands of broadcast hours across multiple stations and the challenges they face to efficiently verify ad placements, identify interview segments, and analyze programming patterns. In this post, we demonstrate how you can automatically transform unstructured media files into searchable, analyzable content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Bradham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora DSQL, MCP Servers, Amazon FSx, AI on EKS, and more (June 2, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>75057629af595e8c8b702253ca50ca0709ea6ed9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-aurora-dsql-mcp-servers-amazon-fsx-ai-on-eks-and-more-june-2-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s AWS Summit Season! AWS Summits are free in-person events that take place across the globe in major cities, bringing cloud expertise to local communities. Each AWS Summit features keynote presentations highlighting the latest innovations, technical sessions, live demos, and interactive workshops led by Amazon Web Services (AWS) experts. Last week, events took place at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Questions: How to help students recognize potential bias in their AI datasets]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/3-questions-recognizing-potential-bias-in-ai-datasets-0602"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Courses on developing AI models for health care need to focus more on identifying and addressing bias, says Leo Anthony Celi.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne Trafton | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Germany Steps Up to Replace ‘Unreliable’ US as Guarantor of European Security”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293209</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/germany-steps-up-to-replace-unreliable-us-as-guarantor-of-european-security.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T13:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More evidence that  European pols and pundits, or at least the mainstream sort, are losing their minds as Russia gains ground in Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/2/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293169</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-2-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T10:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our savory daily links, including 'Operation Spiderweb' fallout, Lindsey Graham threatens Gaza aid flotilla, and more 'crackheads in high places.']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Freedom Cities’ and Our Tech Overlords’ Visions for the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293159</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/freedom-cities-and-our-tech-overlords-visions-for-the-future.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T10:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Examining the techno-monarchists’ plans for a United American Emirates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk’s Government Legacy Was Enacting Project 2025. His Ties Go Back Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=293198</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/elon-musks-government-legacy-was-enacting-project-2025-his-ties-go-back-years.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T09:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle surprise! Elon Musk was long a Project 2025-type-program enthusiast and became its lead promoter and implementer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 1, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBW-ZLGE0f5RIDMAeAtUXbw</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBW-ZLGE0f5RIDMAeAtUXbw"/>
        <updated>2025-06-01T18:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 1, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
Strategic Political Economy
Why Are They Trying to Kill Us?
Conor Gallagher, May 28, 2025 [Naked Capitalism]
For all the talk of how incompetent our elites are, there’s one area where they show remarkable skill and determination: relentlessly creating conditions to shorten the lifespans of the disabled, poor, and working class.
Let’s look at just a few of the many examples before examining potential reasons it’s becoming so much more brazen.
In the US, policies to hurt the working poor and disabled are nothing new, but they’ve exploded in scope in recent years. Elites have collectively memory-holed an ongoing pandemic that has thus far officially killed more than 1.2 million (although that number is likely much higher), dis…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 30, 2025 (#563)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22772</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/30/daily-reading-list-may-30-2025-563/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T21:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's pre-vacation links look at building engineering ladders, why you should aim for greatness, and how to negotiate like an expert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New and improved Amazon Q Developer experience in the AWS Management Console and chat applications]]></title>
        <id>cb688afe847e83387e4b36587700c5f9ca49d600</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/new-and-improved-amazon-q-developer-experience-in-the-aws-management-console/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T19:43:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer just launched a new agentic experience within the AWS Management Console, that enables builders to get deeper insights about their AWS resources and improve their operational troubleshooting efficiency. This expands the agentic capabilities of Amazon Q Developer from both the integrated development environment (IDE) and command line interface (CLI) to the AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendan Jenkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Launchpad from Pega enables secure SaaS extensibility with AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>e9e104062df7c68c8a1a66d7e7c0c4390f1845b6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-launchpad-from-pega-enables-secure-saas-extensibility-with-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we share how Pegasystems (Pega) built Launchpad, its new SaaS development platform, to solve a core challenge in multi-tenant environments: enabling secure customer customization. By running tenant code in isolated environments with AWS Lambda, Launchpad offers its customers a secure, scalable foundation, eliminating the need for bespoke code customizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Aleksandrov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare named a Strong Performer in Email Security by Forrester]]></title>
        <id>1V8L0Y4ySPeme0LzUNSodX</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-named-a-strong-performer-in-email-security-by-forrester/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Forrester has recognized Cloudflare Email Security as a Strong Performer in the ‘current offering’ category in “The Forrester Wave™: Email, Messaging, And Collaboration Security Solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayush Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full ban on Russian energy? EU continues to commit economic suicide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/full-ban-on-russian-energy-eu-continues</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/full-ban-on-russian-energy-eu-continues"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T09:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is not about “stopping Putin’s war machine” but about pre-empting any normalisation of EU-Russia relations — at the cost of deepening dependence on the US and accelerating deindustrialisation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Us vs. Them / Our Government vs. The Government]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIh2yitVlwOmr3y_F8EWBC</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIh2yitVlwOmr3y_F8EWBC"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T05:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think it’s clear that democracy and capitalism don’t work together. Capitalists always wind up buying the government, and the only solution is a Great Depression sized catastrophe to reset the wealth of capitalists. But then, over time, they will capture the government again.
This isn’t to say much good may not be done at various times. Usually after things get bad enough, a generation winds up in power who is determined to make government work “for the people” because they’ve seen what happens when it doesn’t. War, revolution, poverty, depression and so on. The second generation staggers on. They don’t really understand in their bones that government must be made to work for the people, and they compromise, but they keep it more or less going. Then the third generation says “hey, if we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 29, 2025 (#562)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22755</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/29/daily-reading-list-may-29-2025-562/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T23:27:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at a programmer's playbook for prompt engineering, how to understand the cost and value of software development, and the state of AI in the enterprise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Lustre launches new storage class with the lowest-cost and only fully elastic Lustre ﬁle storage]]></title>
        <id>8f6a9d5a1f40a5c5a4984dab8dc2807deb9edd7d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-fsx-for-lustre-adds-new-storage-class-with-the-lowest-cost-and-only-fully-elastic-lustre-file-storage/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T20:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon FSx for Lustre Intelligent-Tiering storage class provides cost-effective, virtually unlimited elastic file storage for ML and HPC workloads that automatically optimizes costs by tiering data based on access frequency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance AI-assisted development with Amazon ECS, Amazon EKS and AWS Serverless MCP server]]></title>
        <id>ebe910aa78b4c2c3438417dd26af4f9ed9fe2145</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/enhance-ai-assisted-development-with-amazon-ecs-amazon-eks-and-aws-serverless-mcp-server/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T19:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS introduces specialized Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers for Amazon ECS, EKS, Finch and AWS Serverless, providing real-time contextual responses and service-specific guidance to guide AI assisted application development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why EU elites fear Trump’s tariffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/why-eu-elites-fear-trumps-tariffs</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/why-eu-elites-fear-trumps-tariffs"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T16:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's upending of the global free regime threatens the foundation of their power]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving platform resilience at Cash App]]></title>
        <id>0b26fcc48f0a1bf17466963984bbb1fe157309ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/improving-platform-resilience-at-cash-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T15:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cash App, a leading peer-to-peer payments and digital wallet service from Block, Inc., has implemented resilience improvements across the entire technology stack. In this post, we discuss how Cash App improved the resilience of its compute platform built on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) by implementing a dual-cluster topology to reduce single points of failure. We also discuss how Cash App used AWS Fault Injection Service (AWS FIS) to conduct an Availability Zone power interruption scenario in non-production environments, preparing the platform team for real-world failures and ongoing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Ellis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Hazeldine: &ldquo;Unconfined&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/unconfined</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/unconfined"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T14:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hugh Roberts (1950-2025).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s DO this: detecting Workers Builds errors across 1 million Durable Objects]]></title>
        <id>2dJV7VMudIGAhdS2pL32lv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/detecting-workers-builds-errors-across-1-million-durable-durable-objects/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers Builds, our CI/CD product for deploying Workers, monitors build issues by analyzing build failure metadata spread across over one million Durable Objects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Hands</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Shenzhen Futures&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/shenzhen-futures</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/shenzhen-futures"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T08:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Fisher in China.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – May 28, 2025 (#561)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22740</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/05/28/daily-reading-list-may-28-2025-561/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T23:07:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at a key part of landing your AI impact within a company, why product managers need to act more like product creators, and a new open framework for model evals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rationale engineering generates a compact new tool for gene therapy]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/rationale-engineering-generates-compact-new-tool-gene-therapy-0528</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/rationale-engineering-generates-compact-new-tool-gene-therapy-0528"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers redesign a compact RNA-guided enzyme from bacteria, making it an efficient editor of human DNA.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Michalowski | McGovern Institute for Brain Research</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An anomaly detection framework anyone can use]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/anomaly-detection-framework-anyone-can-use-sarah-alnegheimish-0528</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/anomaly-detection-framework-anyone-can-use-sarah-alnegheimish-0528"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PhD student Sarah Alnegheimish wants to make machine learning systems accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Barbra Gilley Williams | Center for Complex Engineering Systems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing fleet operations using Amazon SageMaker AI and Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>33b0026a29bd3f07988e98b83b25f6c31b8ca00f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/optimizing-fleet-operations-using-amazon-sagemaker-ai-and-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T18:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we'll explore how to maximize the value of dashcam footage through best practices for implementing and managing Computer Vision systems in commercial fleet operations. We'll demonstrate how to build and deploy edge-based machine learning models that provide real-time alerts for distracted driving behaviors, while effectively collecting, processing, and analyzing footage to train these AI models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manny Sidhu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>