<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-09-13T18:33:15.286Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-09-13T18:33:15.286Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278559</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T18:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; new polling averages (it's a tie) and new Covid tables (some encouragement); Taibbi roasts mainstream debate coverage; Boeing strikes, could lead to ratings downgrade ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambrit: Zeitgeist Report from the Heartland]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278395</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/ambrit-zeitgeist-report-from-the-heartland.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Naked Capitalism helps you rise above  the sterile wastelands of the mainstream media.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[an introduction, and some thoughts on the cohost shutdown]]></title>
        <id>https://jkap.io/an-introduction/</id>
        <link href="https://jkap.io/an-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T15:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hello! it's blogging time.
now that cohost is shutting down, i'm setting up a new home for whatever long-form (or even medium-form) writing i do. i've found over time that the microblogging formats of most social media don't really work for me, and i like having ownership / control of my writing. so here we are.
i'm spending some time migrating some of my favorite posts over from cohost to here; you can view them in the #cohost tag if you so wish.
i'm planning to write more about my overall Feelings around the cohost shutdown soon; there's a lot of things i'd do differently if we were to do it again, but i'm proud of what we accomplished regardless.
one thing that i've been contending with in the wake of the shutdown announcement is the outpouring of love for cohost that i've gotten from s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Year of Georgia’s Medicaid Work Requirement Is Mired in Red Tape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278544</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/the-first-year-of-georgias-medicaid-work-requirement-is-mired-in-red-tape.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Georgia's Medicaid work rules are operating as planned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Last Bottle of Bourbon]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/power-underneath-despair/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September is Suicide Prevention Month, and the IndyWeb Carnival theme is "Power Underneath Despair." We are asked to share stories about times in our lives when we managed to come back from low points. This is contribution.
As someone who has dealt with chronic depression since the 1980s, I could share about that. But the more powerful story is how I felt almost 16 years ago during the last few weeks of active alcoholism, before I had the moment of clarity that led to my recovery.
Active alcoholism was a series of contradictions for me. I would start almost every day determined not to drink, even though it had been literally years since I'd been alcohol-free for an entire 24 hours. I was never the kind of person to keep beer in the fridge for later or to maintain a bar so that I could make…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 9/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278473</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/links-9-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T10:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our audacious daily links: baby hippo, pointless earlobes? Covid warning, climate change and migrants, China's Africa strategy, Germany payment system fail, UK killing pensioners, Foreign Affairs Israel handwave, long distance missile strikes on Russia? Trump gets court breaks, Harris debate debunking, US corp tax increase?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Country for Old Men (or Women): Pensioners in Argentina Bear Brunt of Milei’s Hardcore Austerity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278489</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/no-country-for-old-men-or-women-pensioners-bear-brunt-of-hardcore-austerity-in-mileis-argentina.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T10:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloaked in a flimsy veil of libertarianism, neoliberalism is not just alive and well in Argentina; it's more virulent than ever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can We Afford the Welfare State?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278524</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/can-we-afford-the-welfare-state.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T08:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking why the obstacle to preserving the welfare state is not national income or demographics but rentiers increasing their take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rajiv Sethi: On Models, Markets, and Disagreement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278516</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/rajiv-sethi-on-models-markets-and-disagreement.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T08:42:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at prediction market reactions to the Harris-Trump debate, and why they need to be taken with at least a bit of salt.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Week of Action for Climate Finance and a Fossil-Free Future!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Global-Week-of-Action-for-Climate-Finance-and-a-Fossil-Free-Future"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head towards COP 29, the issues of climate finance and a fossil fuel phaseout towards a just energy transition are ever more critical for climate action. The upcoming UN General Assembly, the UN Summit of the Future and the Global Renewables Summit all taking place one after the other in September provide an important opportunity to reiterate our demands and escalate public pressure to compel governments, international institutions and corporations to listen and take action. 
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by loupol in "Entire staff of game publisher Annapurna Interactive has reportedly resigned"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528724</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528724"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Article is missing some context imo :
* Annapurna Pictures (the parent company of Interactive) had some financial issues previously at least (see [0] from 2019) while Annapurna Interactive was doing well for itself.
* Annapurna Pictures wanted to integrate the gaming division in-house (possibly to prop up the rest of the company)
* Staff and exec at Annapurna Interactive wanted to be spin off (see [1])
* Negotiations fell through, so most exec and staff at Interactive left
[0] https://variety.com/2019/film/news/annapurna-resolves-more-t...
[1] https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-12/annapurna...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>loupol</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by williamdclt in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528536</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528536"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Treat it as a naive but intelligent intern
That’s the problem: it’s a _terrible_ intern. A good intern will ask clarifying questions, tell me “I don’t know” or “I’m not sure I did it right”. LLMs do none of that, they will take whatever you ask and give a reasonable-sounding output that might be anything between brilliant and nonsense.
With an intern, I don’t need to measure how good my prompting is, we’ll usually interact to arrive to a common understanding. With a LLM, I need to put a huge amount of thought into the prompt and have no idea whether the LLM understood what I’m asking and if it’s able to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>williamdclt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism International is Working Both Sides of the Atlantic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333306</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/zionism-international-is-working-both-sides-of-the-atlantic/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AIPAC is funded by corporations that are happy to support the defeat of progressive members of Congress who tend to stand up for both Palestinian rights and worker rights in America. Almost 60% of AIPAC’s money comes from corporate CEOs and other top executives from Fortune 500 companies. The largest single donor to the United Democracy Project is Jan Koum, the multibillionaire former CEO of WhatsApp and a regular Republican funder. The biggest institutional contributors to UDP come from FIRE, finance/insurance and real estate sectors. More
The post Zionism International is Working Both Sides of the Atlantic appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gerald Sussman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murder in Beita: the IDF’s Killing of Ayşenur Eygi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333492</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/murder-in-beita-the-idfs-killing-of-aysenur-eygi/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Israeli version of the shooting, which the Biden administration swiftly adopted, was quickly shown by witnesses, cellphone videos and a detailed investigation by the Washington Post to be not only implausible but absolute bunk. The murder of Ayşenur Eygi took place at least 20 minutes after the last confrontation between Palestinian villagers and IDF troops. Ayşenur never threw any stones and was never within 200 yards of anyone who did. The rooftop sniper had a clear view of where Ayşenur was standing, talking to her friend Helen, and she couldn’t be confused for a Palestinian “instigator.” For whatever reason, Ayşenur was targeted; the sights of the rifle focused on her head and shot. The bullet that killed her didn’t ricochet off of a tree or a rock or a dumpster. The sniper had a clear shot and took it. As Rachel Corrie’s father, Craig, said this week: “Israel does not do investigations; they do cover-ups.” More
The post Murder in Beita: the IDF’s Killing of Ayşenur Eygi appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Legacy: the Decline of Arms Control and Disarmament]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333325</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/bidens-legacy-the-decline-of-arms-control-and-disarmament-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T06:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden’s neglect of arms control and disarmament means that the next president will inherit a nuclear landscape that is more threatening and volatile than any other since the Cuban missile crisis more than 60 years ago.  The Cuban missile crisis, however, was a wake up call for both President John F. Kennedy and General Secretary Nikita Khrushchev, leading to a series of arms control and disarmament treaties beginning with the Partial Test Ban Treaty of 1963.   More
The post Biden’s Legacy: the Decline of Arms Control and Disarmament appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Debate: Catch Trump If You Can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333427</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/the-debate-catch-trump-if-you-can/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The day after the debate, I woke up to the resounding evidence that Harris had floated like a butterfly over the proceedings and occasionally had stung the hapless Trump like a bee. He, I was assured, had done no better on tariffs, Gaza, Ukraine, abortion, climate change, or January 6 than he had with his eloquence over the Springfield protein diet. Then I re-watched the C-Span feed, including the dismal soundbites from the spin rooms, and came to the conclusion that presidential debates are just a variation on Narcissus’s pond in which we only see our own reflections and hear our own words, which explains why debates rarely move the voting dials. More
The post The Debate: Catch Trump If You Can appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nice Health Ya Got There, Mister. Be a Shame if Someone Took it for Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333393</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/nice-health-ya-got-there-mister-be-a-shame-if-someone-took-it-for-cash/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The very notion that it is acceptable to tie one's health in a civilized nation to having ample cash is clearly anathema to most of the world, but it's the way things are in the United States. Countless individuals toil at jobs that do not provide even cursory health coverage. Many individuals who do have some coverage generally try to avoid tapping into many needed health resources due to the sheer cost-inhibitory manner of it all. Co-pays, deductibles, coinsurance, and mandatory first-born deposits will cost you even if you have insurance. We are at a time when even those who have fairly “decent” insurance ration it, many times avoiding care in the early stages of a condition, which often manifests itself later in more expensive and less treatable conditions. The setup of care in the United States is anything but sensible or cost-efficient.  More
The post Nice Health Ya Got There, Mister. Be a Shame if Someone Took it for Cash appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Catastrophe Smashes Heat Records, as Plutocrats, Politicians Twiddle Their Thumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333343</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/climate-catastrophe-smashes-heat-records-as-plutocrats-politicians-twiddle-their-thumbs/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, 2023, was the hottest year on record. But 2024 isn’t over, and July 2024 was the warmest recorded July. So you can expect this year to beat 2023 in the abnormal heat sweepstakes, because that fits the pattern of the last decade, the warmest one ever…Gee whiz, whatever could be causing all this  More
The post Climate Catastrophe Smashes Heat Records, as Plutocrats, Politicians Twiddle Their Thumbs appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are Police Entitled to Lie and Slander?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333389</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/why-are-police-entitled-to-lie-and-slander/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a presidential race in which both major party candidates are kowtowing to law enforcement, don’t expect any candor about the perils that politicians have unleashed. To serve and protect, police are allowed to slander and destroy. Cops in many states and localities have acquired the right to lie about their shootings, searches, and practically  More
The post Why are Police Entitled to Lie and Slander? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atavism in the American Mass Psyche]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333448</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/atavism-in-the-american-mass-psyche/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s victory in 2016 was a surprise, I conjecture, to Trump himself. I think he was surprised earlier in the Primaries how easy it was to mock and upstage his challengers. He could break all the protocols of proper Primary behavior without check. Perhaps that was the first time he realized there was no  More
The post Atavism in the American Mass Psyche appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Bloody Negotiations Strategy in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333407</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/israels-bloody-negotiations-strategy-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fifty-two years ago, almost to the day, on September 8, 1972, I survived the first of many Israeli air and sea raids on my refugee camp in northern Lebanon. I was less than two hundred yards from the area across the river where a group of us young kids met every day, between 4 and  More
The post Israel’s Bloody Negotiations Strategy in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election 2024: Finally Weird Enough?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333451</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/election-2024-finally-weird-enough/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It never got weird enough for me,” says Hunter S. Thompson — or, rather, Bill Murray as Hunter S. Thompson in 1980s kinda sorta Thompson biopic, Where the Buffalo Roam.  “I moved to the country when the boat got too crowded. Then I learned that President Nixon had been eaten by white cannibals on an  More
The post Election 2024: Finally Weird Enough? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cartography of Genocide: Why Netanyahu Erased Palestine from the Map]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333401</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/cartography-of-genocide-why-netanyahu-erased-palestine-from-the-map/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When asked why his latest map has erased the whole of the West Bank, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu retorted with the most detestable answer. “I didn’t include the Dead Sea. It’s not shown on the map. I didn’t show the Jordan River. It’s not on this map. I didn’t show the Sea of Galilee,”  More
The post Cartography of Genocide: Why Netanyahu Erased Palestine from the Map  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Ambivalent Anniversary of “The One Set of Rules We All Agree On”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333287</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/an-ambivalent-anniversary-of-the-one-set-of-rules-we-all-agree-on/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[August 2024 marked the 75th anniversary of the four Geneva Conventions which form the basis of international humanitarian law (IHL). The dream of five Swiss men (Henri Dunant, Louis Appia, General Guillaume Henri Dufour, Gustave Moynier, Theodore Maunoir) was realized and codified in the hope of “civilizing” the way wars were fought. Separating civilians from  More
The post An Ambivalent Anniversary of “The One Set of Rules We All Agree On” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antarctica’s Deep Vulnerability Exposed at 11th Scientific Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333413</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/antarcticas-deep-vulnerability-exposed-at-11th-scientific-conference/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 11th Scientific Committee on Antarctic Research conference was held in Pucón, Chile August 19-23, 2024. Fifteen-hundred academics, researchers, and scientists specializing in Antarctica met to share cutting-edge research. Reports at the conference exposed new dimensions of the Antarctic risk profile that should move the world’s leadership posthaste to mitigate society’s self-destructive dependence on fossil  More
The post Antarctica’s Deep Vulnerability Exposed at 11th Scientific Conference appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking 9/11: Fascism, Memory, and the Crisis of Democracy in the 21st Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333470</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/rethinking-9-11-fascism-memory-and-the-crisis-of-democracy-in-the-21st-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At this moment in history, we find ourselves in a society defined by relentless speed, overwhelming amounts of information, the proliferation of misinformation, and widening inequality.[1] Fascist politics are increasingly legitimized, long-term commitments are devalued, and the far-right’s vision of society constantly shifts, maintaining control through chaos and confusion. In such an environment, memory becomes  More
The post Rethinking 9/11: Fascism, Memory, and the Crisis of Democracy in the 21st Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peril and Possibility: Post-Election Scenarios]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333480</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/peril-and-possibility-post-election-scenarios/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Walz is telling people to “leave it all on the field” of the election. Americans better not follow his advice. The 2024 election day will kick off a much bigger game full of peril but not without some opportunity on the path to the emancipation of humanity. Poisoning Our Blood Let’s start with some  More
The post Peril and Possibility: Post-Election Scenarios appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Personal Meditation on Growing Old]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333411</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/a-personal-meditation-on-growing-old/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Washington Post headline reads: “A big problem for young workers: 70- and 80-year-olds who won’t retire.” For the first time in history, reports Aden Barton, five generations are competing in the same workforce. His article laments a “demographic traffic jam” at the apexes of various employment pyramids, making it ever harder for young people “to launch their careers and  More
The post A Personal Meditation on Growing Old appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Gordon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Be Bamboozled by Nuclear Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333439</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/dont-be-bamboozled-by-nuclear-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the face of a complex and urgent problem like climate change, it’s tempting to believe in simple solutions. Just as detox teas or diet pills claim to solve health issues that truly require lifestyle changes, nuclear energy has been marketed as a quick fix for the socio-political problem that climate change is. It’s presented  More
The post Don’t Be Bamboozled by Nuclear Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prerna Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nick Kyrgios: The Donald Trump of Tennis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333294</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/nick-kyrgios-the-donald-trump-of-tennis/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-August, a few days before the US Open kicked off, it was revealed that the number one in the men’s world ranking and the eventual winner of the tournament, Jannik Sinner of Italy, had left two positive doping tests earlier this year. During and shortly after a tournament the ATP (Association of Tennis Professionals)  More
The post Nick Kyrgios: The Donald Trump of Tennis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabriel Kuhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Law of Force or the Force of Law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333404</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/the-law-of-force-or-the-force-of-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are the nations of the world doomed to go on fighting the brutal, horrifying wars that have long characterized human history? We might well wonder about that as we watch, aghast, while Israeli armed forces slaughter thousands of Palestinian civilians, Russian military might relentlessly pounds Ukrainian towns and cities into rubble, and new, bloody wars  More
The post The Law of Force or the Force of Law appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Wittner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Do We Need a State for Anyway?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333206</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/what-do-we-need-a-state-for-anyway/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a healthy society of non-human primates, there are no nations, no extended organizations, no supraterritorial forms that might resemble a state. Troops of primates do have a social cohesion about them, creating various temporary leaders or hierarchies according to the function at hand—one for fighting, say, another for vigilance, a third for feeding— and  More
The post What Do We Need a State for Anyway? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirkpatrick Sale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Déjà Vu All Over Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333465</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/deja-vu-all-over-again-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times/Sienna poll (New York Times, September 8, 2024) brought back the same sickening sense of doom that I felt in both 1969 and 1971. George McGovern’s defeat in the 1972 presidential campaign nailed down the lid on the coffin of anything that seemed even close to sanity to me in those years during the  More
The post Déjà Vu All Over Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Myth of Black Capitalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333460</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/the-myth-of-black-capitalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mass protests across the US against Jim Crow drove the rise of the Black Power and Civil Rights movements generations ago. The impacts were far reaching across the lines of class, color and gender. Ruling circles in and out of the federal, state and local governments responded, the backdrop to Earl Ofari Hutchinson’s The Myth  More
The post The Myth of Black Capitalism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Sandronsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recycling the Discarded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333462</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/recycling-the-discarded/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The stigma of a criminal conviction can be a major barrier to community reentry for recently released prisoners. A December 2021 report by the Bureau of Justice Statistics highlighted the employment barrier faced by the more than 50,000 who were incarcerated, with 33 percent of them being unable to find any employment “over four years” after their  More
The post Recycling the Discarded appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Damon Orion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Far Right Lies About Immigrants]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333468</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/why-the-far-right-lies-about-immigrants/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When my dad moved to southwest Ohio in the early 1970s, the Dayton-Springfield area’s second city was home to over 80,000 people. When I was growing up nearby in the 1990s, it was 70,000. Today, it’s less than 60,000. Springfield’s decline looks like an awful lot of Rust Belt cities and towns. And behind those numbers  More
The post Why the Far Right Lies About Immigrants appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Certo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charles Bukowski’s Ordinary Madness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333419</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/charles-bukowskis-ordinary-madness/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I received a review of Charles Bukowski’s Hollywood for AMASS Magazine (formerly Enclitic) as we were finalizing the current issue. We wanted to include it, but it was riddled with problems. I tried to salvage it, extracting a few of its good points, but it was hopeless. And the author had no interest in being  More
The post Charles Bukowski’s Ordinary Madness appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John O'Kane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025 is a Blue Print for the End of the American Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333469</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/project-2025-is-a-blue-print-for-the-end-of-the-american-dream/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe you’ve heard some of the buzz about “Project 2025.” What is it — and what would it mean for you and your family? Project 2025 is a proposed “transition plan for a new Republican administration” put together by the Heritage Foundation, a right-wing think tank. It’s an in-depth list of what conservative groups will  More
The post Project 2025 is a Blue Print for the End of the American Dream appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen Dolan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young People Will Save the World, Because We’re the Last Generation That Can]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333474</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/young-people-will-save-the-world-because-were-the-last-generation-that-can/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past 20 years have been critical in the fight for bold and sustainable climate solutions. The next five years will be even more vital — and young people like me are fighting hard to make sure our leaders get it right. Research shows we have about five years left to avert global warming beyond 1.5  More
The post Young People Will Save the World, Because We’re the Last Generation That Can appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keara Sosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Official US Poverty Rate Declined in 2023, But More People Faced Economic Hardship]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333330</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/official-us-poverty-rate-declined-in-2023-but-more-people-faced-economic-hardship/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The number of Americans living in poverty, according to the nation’s official definition, fell slightly to about 36.8 million in 2023, the Census Bureau announced on Sept. 10, 2024. The data released also indicated that the poverty rate declined a little. However, an alternative way to measure poverty ticked up, as more people in the  More
The post Official US Poverty Rate Declined in 2023, But More People Faced Economic Hardship appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Robert Rank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Chutzpah” in the Presidential Debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333417</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/chutzpah-in-the-presidential-debate/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Yiddish word chutzpah, related to the Hebrew word huspãh has a strong negative connotation. It means “insolence,” “cheek” or “audacity.” It became part of American English vernacular with a broader, less pejorative meaning, but in Hebrew it is used to describe a person who has overstepped the boundaries of respectful behavior. In the The Joys of Yiddish Leo Rosten,  More
The post “Chutzpah” in the Presidential Debate appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Both Trump and Harris Agree, It’s Time to Stop Arresting People for Marijuana]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=333334</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/09/13/both-trump-and-harris-agree-its-time-to-stop-arresting-people-for-marijuana/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a time when voters and politicians are historically divided, there is one issue that Americans largely agree upon: It’s time to legalize marijuana. Months ago, Vice President Kamala Harris tweeted that “Nobody should have to go to jail for weed.” Despite her past oppositionto marijuana legalization, she’s since become the first major presidential nominee  More
The post Both Trump and Harris Agree, It’s Time to Stop Arresting People for Marijuana appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Armentano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by toomuchtodo in "Boeing workers vote to strike"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528096</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528096"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Boeing spent $43B on stock buybacks between 2013 and 2019 while paying their CEO ~$30M/year.
> To support its share price, the company under McNerney poured billions into stock buybacks instead of investing profits into the kind of research and development needed to stay competitive. McNerney decided not to spend billions of dollars building a new plane to replace the 737. Instead, Boeing tweaked and updated the existing model and called it the 737 Max, outfitting it with larger, more efficient engines for increased economy. Compensating for the resulting instability was a secretive automated system called MCAS that would adjust the plane’s pitch without input from the pilot.
> McNerney also fought to deeply cut costs. On his watch, the company opened its first non-unionized aircraft production line and initiated a program called “Partnering for Success” that pushed suppliers to cut their prices by 15 percent or more. Many feared that squeezing suppliers would harm the quality of their components, but McNerney was determined to recoup the cost of the 787’s development; if the subcontractors complained, they could find their work taken away from them, as happened to landing-gear-maker United Technologies Aerospace Systems.
> McNerney retired in 2015, handpicking his successor, president and COO Dennis Muilenburg. Over the next three years, Boeing’s stock price more than doubled as it sold new planes the world over. (As Bloomberg News reported, Muilenberg and McNerney “had personal reasons to emphasize productivity and cost-cutting” because their compensation was tied to share performance. Together they took $209 million in total pay over seven years.)
https://nymag.com/intelligencer/article/boeing-planes-proble...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>toomuchtodo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by MPSimmons in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528061</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41528061"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failure is in how you're using it. I don't mean this as a personal attack, but more to shed light on what's happening.
A lot of people use LLMs as a search engine. It makes sense - it's basically a lossy compressed database of everything its ever read, and it generates output that is statistically likely - varying degrees of likeliness depending on the temperature, as well as how many times the particular weights your prompt ends up activating.
The magic of LLMs, especially one like this that supposedly has advanced reasoning, isn't the existing knowledge in its weights. The magic is that _it knows english_. It knows english at or above a level equal to most fluent speakers, and it also can produce output that is not just a likely output, but is a logical output. It's not _just_ an output engine. It's an engine that outputs.
Asking it about nuanced details in the corpus of data it has read won't give you good output unless it read a bunch of it.
On the other hand, if you were to paste the entire documentation set to a tool it has never seen and ask it to use the tool in a way to accomplish your goals, THEN this model would be likely to produce useful output, despite the fact that it had never encountered the tool or its documentation before.
Don't treat it as a database. Treat it as a naive but intelligent intern. Provide it data, give it a task, and let it surprise you with its output.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>MPSimmons</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And so, we return to 1999.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.aurahack.jp/and-so-we-return-to-1999/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.aurahack.jp/and-so-we-return-to-1999/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T04:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did not think I would ever be spinning a blog again. I think I did in the, like, pre-Google Blogger days? Or something? I was 14. I thought everyone would follow it and I would be internet famous. I wish I could go back in time and kick my own ass.
This will not be a newsletter. I wanted to make one to have a more centralized "here's an important update" kinda thing but that's a) sort of what my Patreon is and b) if you collect enough emails, which I don't think is unrealistic given my reach at this point, you need to start paying hundreds a month for that shit and, like, no. I will not.
So here's a blog. How often will I post here? I don't know! I don't care! It's actually kind of nice! I don't need to give a shit about it. It's a siloed area I can dump thoughts in and you can read them. Cohost taught me that I really don't need to care about having a statement or take on shit, I can just post and have it immediately leave the aether, so this is what this is for. I also want to have a place to, like, make dev logs or something for comic stuff in the future!
Subscribe to the RSS in the navbar above or bookmark this, if you want.
If you'd like important updates, you can follow my Patreon for free and any major updates like shop updates, new merch, new site launches, etc. will be posted there and mailed to everyone like a newsletter.
Thanks for reading and if you're coming from Cohost, thanks for being there while it was active. The community there was something I'll cherish forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by layer8 in "Notes on OpenAI's new o1 chain-of-thought models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41527354</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41527354"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The o1-preview model still hallucinates non-existing libraries and functions for me, and is quickly wrong about facts that aren't well-represented on the web. It's the usual string of "You're absolutely correct, and I apologize for the oversight in my previous response. [Let me make another guess.]"
While the reasoning may have been improved, this doesn't solve the problem of the model having no way to assess if what it conjures up from its weights is factual or not.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>layer8</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[this was going to be about Chappell Roan]]></title>
        <id>https://electricsheep.bearblog.dev/this-was-going-to-be-about-chappell-roan/</id>
        <link href="https://electricsheep.bearblog.dev/this-was-going-to-be-about-chappell-roan/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T01:28:37.745Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 has more than any other year been the year for most Americans of apathetic detachment. Donald Trump got shot in the head last month, kind of, and nobody really talks about it. It feels trite and stupid to write about anything that isn't Gaza, it feels trite and stupid to write about anything while Gaza is burned. You know what's funny is that every time I try to give a shit about writing I can't help but think about Gaza. It feels like I forget about it, or push it back, but it always resurfaces. Always there but never really. It's far off. I can self-flagellate all I want about it but it doesn't matter what I say or think about it. I can't do anything about it. Earlier this year Aaron Bushnell self-immolated and what's crazy is when you google "protestor who set himself on fire" he d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planting A Digital Garden]]></title>
        <id>https://darrenhester.com/planting-a-digital-garden/</id>
        <link href="https://darrenhester.com/planting-a-digital-garden/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T22:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love the idea of a digital garden. I first heard about them in an article by Maggie Appleton where she wrote:
Gardens present information in a richly linked landscape that grows slowly over time. Everything is arranged and connected in ways that allow you to explore.
I’m beginning to cultivate my own digital garden using Bear.  It's a place where I can experiment with creative projects and test new ideas.
Some Examples
This week, I added a Sketchbook and a collection of Wallpapers.

Neither of these fits into the mold of a traditional blog, but they interest me, and I enjoy working on them. I wanted to find a place where they could live on my website.
I also created a Typography page to test markdown syntax and CSS themes. I initially hid this page but decided to make it public in my new digital garden. It’s just the kind of thing I want growing there.
I’ll be adding new pages and updating existing ones often. Anyone curious can always wander around the garden to see what I’m up to.
Over time, I hope to find connections between the different pages. It is a good way to spark more creative ideas.
None of this replaces my blog. It’s in addition to my blog posts. I don’t think it has to be one format or the other. Your blog can also have an area for a digital garden.
What are your thoughts? Do you like this idea?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon RDS for MySQL zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift, now generally available, enables near real-time analytics]]></title>
        <id>f63b64a0773b039fe7590c2f6116b3ee57fc4cda</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-rds-for-mysql-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-redshift-now-generally-available-enables-near-real-time-analytics/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:47:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Near real-time data replication: RDS for MySQL zero-ETL with Redshift streamlines data ingestion with filtering, multiple integrations, and CloudFormation support for customized insights without managing complex pipelines.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gravitational waves may reveal presence of warp drive starships]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8460</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/gravitational-waves-reveal-presence-warp-drive-starships/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gravitational waves have been helping scientists and astronomers answer some of the big questions of the universe. But gravitational waves may be able to do something else: detect the presence of vessels with Star Trek like warp drive engines, as they move through the cosmos. One problem with the warp drive space-time is that it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Must Humans Compete for Electric Power with AI Bullshit Generators Programmed by Ritual Incantations?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278476</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/why-must-humans-compete-for-electric-power-with-bullshit-generators-programmed-by-ritual-incantations.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A takedown of AI so-called "prompt engineering."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee drinkers ditch coffee as price rises continue to bite]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8456</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/coffee-drinkers-ditch-coffee-price-rises-continue/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T20:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian food critic Terry Durack, writing for the Sydney Morning Herald: Coffee’s changing. The cost of beans continues to rise, and everyone is on the lookout for alternatives. Old-fashioned espresso coffee is in danger of being shouldered aside, just as cow’s milk is making way for oat, almond and soy. With coffee prices rising, people […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bartman in "Learning to Reason with LLMs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41524263</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41524263"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T18:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is incredible. In April I used the standard GPT-4 model via ChatGPT to help me reverse engineer the binary bluetooth protocol used by my kitchen fan to integrate it into Home Assistant.
It was helpful in a rubber duck way, but could not determine the pattern used to transmit the remaining runtime of the fan in a certain mode. Initial prompt here [0]
I pasted the same prompt into o1-preview and o1-mini and both correctly understood and decoded the pattern using a slightly different method than I devised in April. Asking the models to determine if my code is equivalent to what they reverse engineered resulted in a nuanced and thorough examination, and eventual conclusion that it is equivalent. [1]
Testing the same prompt with gpt4o leads to the same result as April's GPT-4 (via ChatGPT) model.
Amazing progress.
[0]: https://pastebin.com/XZixQEM6
[1]: https://i.postimg.cc/VN1d2vRb/SCR-20240912-sdko.png (sorry about the screenshot – sharing ChatGPT chats is not easy)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bartman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Romaric Godin: &ldquo;The Gravedigger&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-gravedigger</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-gravedigger"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michel Barnier and Macronism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 9/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=278477</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/200pm-water-cooler-9-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Trump the heel, full of grievances; Counting electoral votes now a National Special Security Event; Boeing strike -- today? ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Albrt: Naked Capitalism – a Home for the Heterodox]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=277290</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/09/albrt-naked-capitalism-a-home-for-the-heterodox.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Naked Capitalism is doing the work virtually no other site does and also provides a refuge for independent thinkers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In solidarity with the people of the southeast of Moroccoand all those affected by the floods after September 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/In-solidarity-with-the-people-of-the-southeast-of-Moroccoand-all-those-affected</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/In-solidarity-with-the-people-of-the-southeast-of-Moroccoand-all-those-affected"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Press Release 
Press releases

/ 
Poverty, 
Morocco, 
Ecology/Climate, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting APIs from abuse using sequence learning and variable order Markov chains]]></title>
        <id>27ZTkLyAI8VPmwUK2U3jU7</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/protecting-apis-from-abuse-using-sequence-learning-and-variable-order-markov"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we protect customer APIs from abuse. This is no easy task, as abusive traffic can take different forms, from giant DDoS attacks to low-and-slow credential stuffing campaigns. We now address this challenge in a new way: by looking outside typical volumetric measures and using statistical machine learning to find important API client request sequences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Foster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 1st International Antifascist Conference will take place in Porto Alegre in May 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-1st-International-Antifascist-Conference-will-take-place-in-Porto-Alegre-in</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-1st-International-Antifascist-Conference-will-take-place-in-Porto-Alegre-in"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its cancellation due to the floods in Porto Alegre in May 2024, the 1st International Antifascist Conference will take place next year in the capital of Rio Grande do Sul. This delay was a result of the climate crisis, with effects on the host city so severe that, even to this day, the Porto Alegre airport remains closed. The impact was tremendous, causing losses of lives, homes, jobs, memories, and belongings. While this tragedy has forced us to postpone the Conference, it makes (...)
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Collective, CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jackson Hole celebrates itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Jackson-Hole-celebrates-itself</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Jackson-Hole-celebrates-itself"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every August the world's top central bankers meet in Jackson Hole, Wyoming, a ski resort in central US for [a ‘symposium' organized by the Kansas City Federal Reserve. ->https://www.kansascityfed.org/research/jackson-hole-economic-symposium/jackson-hole-economic-policy-symposium-reassessing-the-effectiveness-and-transmission-of-monetary-policyThe bankers take this opportunity to discuss monetary policy and its efficacy in ‘managing the economy', in particular, ‘controlling' inflation and (...)
English

/ 
Capitalism, 
Banks, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“No Fist Is Big Enough to Hide the Sky”: 100 Years of Amilcar Cabral]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/No-Fist-Is-Big-Enough-to-Hide-the-Sky-100-Years-of-Amilcar-Cabral</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/No-Fist-Is-Big-Enough-to-Hide-the-Sky-100-Years-of-Amilcar-Cabral"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T09:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Colonialist and anti-imperialist, party organizer and guerilla warfare strategist, diplomat and publicist, revolutionary theorist and internationalist, Amílcar Cabral was among the most original Marxists of the 20th century. 
 Amílcar Lopes da Costa Cabral was born on September 12, 1924 in the town of Bafata in Portuguese Guinea, wedged between what was then French Guinea and the French colony of Senegal, in West Africa. His parents hailed from Cape Verde (Cabo Verde), an archipelago of (...)
English

/ 
Africa, 
Colonialism, 
Imperialism, 
Guinea-Bissau]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by estsauver in "Show HN: Konty – A Balsamiq-alternative lo-fi wireframe tool for modern apps"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41518910</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41518910"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T09:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reason that I've heard used repeatedly is that a shocking percentage of folks who aren't Technology producers can't separate visual quality from "doneness" of a project. If you show some business folks something that looks like it works, they'll mentally update the project to "Nearly done!" and then everything else after that becomes "Unreasonable delays."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>estsauver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/about/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/about/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[whose blog is this
hi! i’m Lena Raine. i’ve written the music you may have heard in indie games such as Celeste & Chicory: A Colorful Tale, and slightly larger games like Minecraft & Guild Wars 2.
i have also written and designed a visual novel called ESC, and am currently working on a brand new game called ANOTHEREAL. i’ll be introducing the game & talking about its development in these little blogs, so stay tuned if you want to find out more!
separately, i’ve also been known to blog about games, music, and other things that interest me. i had an ongoing series of longer posts on the website Cohost, which I’m no longer able to continue due to it shutting down. i hope to use this blog to keep the long-form posting alive. so if you like(d) reading my thoughts on games and other media, those will continue here as well!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[starting once more]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/starting-once-more/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/starting-once-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[well, here we are again. this time in a new space. less eggbug, less (immediate) community… but still a place for me to put words & hopefully have some degree of long-form posting that i’m comfortable with.
i was contemplating setting up a newsletter, and that is well and dandy, but ultimately there’s a lot of baggage that comes from blasting out emails to everyone’s inboxes every time i want to write something on a whim. that’s not necessarily what i’m here for!
i've done my best to port over & fill out the archive with some of my game blogs and other ‘best of’ from cohost, tagging those where appropriate! and then we’ll keep on going… i hope you’ll stick around, subscribe to the rss or atom feed, whatever keeps you updated!
so if you’re new here, have a little dose of introduction:
hi! i’m lena raine. i’ve written the music you may have heard in indie games such as Celeste & Chicory: A Colorful Tale, and slightly larger games like Minecraft & Guild Wars 2.
i have also written and designed a visual novel called ESC, and am currently working on a brand new game called ANOTHEREAL. i’ll be introducing the game & talking about its development in these little blogs, so stay tuned if you want to find out more!
separately, i’ve also been known to blog about games, music, and other things that interest me. i had an ongoing series of longer posts on the website Cohost, which I’m no longer able to continue due to it shutting down. i hope to use this blog to keep the long-form posting alive. so if you like(d) reading my thoughts on games and other media, those will continue here as well!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ad Buster - brandalism in the Netherlands]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brandalism-in-the-netherlands-ad-buster?v=1726099845</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/brandalism-in-the-netherlands-ad-buster?v=1726099845"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T00:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ad Buster
Title: brandalism in the Netherlands
Subtitle: the vandalism of capitalist propaganda
Date: 21-8-2024
Notes: based on local experience


 advertisement shits in your head 
brandalism
 noun 
 /ˈbrændəlɪzəm/ 
 /ˈbrændəlɪzəm/ 
 1. the vandalism of capitalist propaganda 
 2. subvertising; parodies of advertisements 
 3. protest art to hide advertisement. 
 Our main goal is removing advertisement from the public space. 
 As citizens we should have a say in how our public space looks, we do not accept government renting out the space to some companies, that is supposed to be for all of us. 
 We accept bus stop advertisement as a method to support the bus stop. But there is no excuse for stand alone advertisement in the public space, in this zine we will show some tactics to rem…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes - Two years after the victims were found]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/feminist-collective-kores-xapolytes-two-years-after-the-victims-were-found?v=1726096942</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/feminist-collective-kores-xapolytes-two-years-after-the-victims-were-found?v=1726096942"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T23:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes
Title: Two years after the victims were found
Subtitle: Text by feminist group about the handling of the femicide cases by the state and the police
Date: 2021
Notes: This leaflet was written by the Cypriot Feminist Collective Kores Xapolytes in June of 2021 and was distributed at a protest outside the Cypriot Attorney General's office that took place on the 18th of June, in Nicosia.
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:leaflets:kores:femicides

 The police, the army, the law office of the republic, the ministries – we consider all of these to comprise the web of patriarchal structures which govern our female bodies in more ways than one. Two years after the “shocking” revelations about the “first serial killer” in Cyprus, not only …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andrea Teruel - An Anarchist Conjuration]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrea-teruel-an-anarchist-conjuration?v=1726093411</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/andrea-teruel-an-anarchist-conjuration?v=1726093411"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T22:23:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Andrea Teruel
Title: An Anarchist Conjuration
Subtitle: The Benjamin-Bataille Meeting and the Critique of Left-Wing Progressism
Date: 2022
Source: revistas.unc.edu.ar

Abstract
 The article explores the theoretical complicities between the thought of Walter Benjamin and Georges Bataille. Taking as a starting point the anecdote of the Book of Passages, according to which Benjamin would have entrusted this manuscript to the care of Bataille, questions are raised about the possible link between the two thinkers. The relationship that both authors maintained with the leftist political thought of the time and the way in which their revolutionary conceptions distance themselves from orthodox Marxism and dialectical materialism are particularly problematized. In this way, through an analy…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook has been scraping the pages of Australians since 2007]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8453</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/facebook-scraping-pages-australians-2007/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jake Evans, writing for the Australian Broadcasting Corporation: Facebook has admitted that it scrapes the public photos, posts and other data of Australian adult users to train its AI models and provides no opt-out option, even though it allows people in the European Union to refuse consent. For sure, Facebook operates a little differently in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending September 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240911</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240911"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on writing about my mental health on Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-writing-about-my-mental-health-on-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/on-writing-about-my-mental-health-on-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T19:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am aware I've been navigating heavy topics in recent blogposts - childhood trauma, depression, and mental health in general. On Bear, I have regularly shared light, easily digestible reads, like slices of life and productivity takes. But I have also shared the brutal reality of living with mental health struggles.
I created this blog during the peaks of a depressive episode, at a time I desperately sought a healthy outlet for my oppressive emotions and ricocheting thoughts. Actually, it was an attempt to abide by my psychologist's advice, who urged me to live for myself, do things I love. I promised myself to write about what matters to me, what I always wanted to share - life updates, opinions, introspections, and most importantly, my mental health journey.
I won't lie to you, though, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[what i'm grasping for is not a place, but a feeling]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-09-home/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-09-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to go home, I want to go home, but what I mean, what I'm grasping for, is not a place, it's a feeling. I want to go back. But back where?1
It's ten in the morning. I'm sitting on a wooden chair in my room. A
breeze brings a hint of fragrant morning dew through the open window. The robins are screaming their good mornings and the first maple leaves are starting to burn mauve and brown and let go of their branches. I slept wonderfully last night — a deep, dreamless slumber — and while that is likely the result of accumulated sleep debt, there is something about this place that puts me at ease. I love the chorus of cicadas and crickets, the verdant air, the quiet rush of cars passing by, the caress of my velvet bedspread, the pale yellow walls surrounding me, even the intermittent buzz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging is Hard]]></title>
        <id>https://seadave.org/blogging-hard/</id>
        <link href="https://seadave.org/blogging-hard/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I slowly got into a blog when I retired and decided to give Micro.blog a whirl. I was intrigued by the notion of a community, as I had long been receiving weekly emails with samples of the “Discovery Feed”. I mostly did true “micro posts” for quite a while, then I tried my hand at few long form posts. I got into photo posting, and eventually did a 30 day photo challenge. I also got into the bookshelf feature and posted more than two years of my reading to my blog site.
There came a time when I felt like I had disclosed too much personal information. I realized, for example, that I had always hated that there were digital records of what I read at the library and records of anything I bought at Amazon. This gets at a fundamental issue we all have with all electronic records and communication. I decided last December to “nuke” that blog in its entirety.
I continued to micro post there for a while, and to do several entries that I thought were innocuous. I then looked around at my options, including weblog.lol and bearblog.dev (this blog). The community features at Micro-blog simply didn’t amount to much, after all. Good, but it felt like it could be great. So, I came over here to bearblog.dev and started afresh.
While I still ponder what is too much disclosure, or too little for that matter, I feel like even being factual about some of my past might be a turn off to many potential readers. Lord knows, there aren’t many actual readers. It feels like people want to hear a certain kind of experience, but not hear about others. I am not sure I have the “voice” to be appealing, so I could just file my little essays away privately. I do still seek community, but I find the interaction is on Mastodon (social.lol for me) and that is good.
I’ll poke away at this for a while. None too sure of its longevity.
Reply via email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A left that does not take the lead in the fight against climate catastrophe has no reason to exist!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-left-that-does-not-take-the-lead-in-the-fight-against-climate-catastrophe-has</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-left-that-does-not-take-the-lead-in-the-fight-against-climate-catastrophe-has"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T17:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What follows is not addressed to the right and its supporters (economic, social and other) who - unfortunately - are doing their job very well. What follows is addressed above all to the left, which - unfortunately - is not doing its job at all well... 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Capitalism, 
Ecology/Climate, 
Greece]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dsr_ in "Ask HN: Why is Pave legal?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41513186</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41513186"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T16:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You make an excellent argument here for tight regulation of the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dsr_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dghlsakjg in "David Chang on the long, hard, stupid way"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512972</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512972"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T16:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Chang is a salesman and a businessman first. I get the point being made, but keep in mind that he is a brand, and part of that is the stories he tells.
He has slapped his name on so many subpar food goods that were a total disappointment that I actually have started avoiding things marketed under his brand name.
He might do things the hard way in his restaurants, but they certainly aren't ensuring tasty or high quality goods under his brand. I would rather he do things in a way that makes sense and provides the best tasting food.
More broadly, the point is that you should take advice only from people whose successes you want to emulate. The actual advice I get out of this article is:
Tell stories that paint the picture you want your customers to have about your product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dghlsakjg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Harris-Trump US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>4NI7PBab9zePZzucqLYhPh</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-harris-trump-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Kamala Harris and Donald Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns compared to the Biden-Trump debate. We also review email trends and observed attack activity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wing-_-nuts in "Ask HN: Why is Pave legal?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512326</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512326"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T15:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I downloaded a personal report from the work number website and found to my horror that my employer was reporting every. single. paystub. gross and net, to equifax.
That felt like a huge breach of privacy.  Given that equifax had already proven incompetent at keeping my data secure, I immediately sent HR a request to stop sending my supposedly 'confidential' pay info.  They politely told me to kick rocks, so I went on TWN's website and froze that report so no one would be able to request it, and it will be a cold day in hell before I thaw it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wing-_-nuts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atrettel in "Ask HN: Why is Pave legal?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512162</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41512162"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T15:16:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have never heard of Pave before, but this just sounds like yet another copy of Equifax's "The Work Number" [1].  Basically, HR at many companies gives your salary and employment history data to Equifax, who then sells access to the information to certain parties with supposed need to access it, including potential and current employers and creditors.  This report is likely one of the most invasive consumer files out there for many people.
I cannot comment on the legality of this kind of data sharing, but as I and others have pointed out, it has existed for a while.  I do agree that it is concerning.  You can freeze your Equifax The Work Number report at least, just like other credit reports.
[1] https://theworknumber.com/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atrettel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by post-it in "We spent $20 to achieve RCE and accidentally became the admins of .mobi"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41511941</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41511941"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T14:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obviously there are a lot of errors by a lot of people that led to this, but here's one that would've prevented this specific exploit:
> As part of our research, we discovered that a few years ago the WHOIS server for the .MOBI TLD migrated from whois.dotmobiregistry.net to whois.nic.mobi – and the dotmobiregistry.net domain had been left to expire seemingly in December 2023.
Never ever ever ever let a domain expire. If you're a business and you're looking to pick up a new domain because it's only $10/year, consider that you're going to be paying $10/year forever, because once you associate that domain with your business, you can never get rid of that association.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>post-it</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customers get increased integration with Cloudflare Email Security and Zero Trust through expanded partnership with CrowdStrike]]></title>
        <id>2oxT0UhMM8loVoSuUom7W8</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/customers-get-increased-integration-with-cloudflare-email-security-and-zero-trust"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post explains how our integrations with CrowdStrike Falcon® Next-Gen SIEM allow customers to identify and investigate risky user behavior and analyze data combined with other log sources to uncover hidden threats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Corey Mahan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank did not Foresee the Arab Spring Popular Uprisings and still Promotes the very same Policies that triggered them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-did-not-Foresee-the-Arab-Spring-Popular-Uprisings-and-still</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-did-not-Foresee-the-Arab-Spring-Popular-Uprisings-and-still"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
Africa, 
World Bank, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Ghost World&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghost-world</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghost-world"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T10:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Oleksiy Radynski.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mikhail Bakunin - On the Question of the Right of Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikhail-bakunin-on-the-question-of-the-right-of-inheritance?v=1726015496</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/mikhail-bakunin-on-the-question-of-the-right-of-inheritance?v=1726015496"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:44:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Mikhail Bakunin
Title: On the Question of the Right of Inheritance
Subtitle: in Speeches to the Basle Congress
Date: 1871
Notes: Translation by Robert M. Cutler. ISBN 13: 978-0-87975-745-8 ISBN 10: 0-87975-745-0
Source: The Basic Bakunin: Writings, 1869-1871

 There is but a simple difference between the standpoint of those collectivists who believe that it is useless to vote to abolish the right of inheritance after having voted "for collective property, and that of those collectivists who think, as do we, that it is useful and even necessary to do so. 
 They place themselves entirely in the future and, taking collective property as their point of departure, discover that there is no longer any good reason to be concerned with the right of inheritance. 
 We on the contrary take ou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My impressions of Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://daviramos.com/my-impressions-of-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://daviramos.com/my-impressions-of-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post will be very plain. That is because Bear Blog is excellent in a way that is obvious and requires little explaining.  Bear Blog is a minimalistic blogging service that will store your posts and serve them without fluff and at great speed. As Tildes blogging brother, Bear Blog has nothing in excess. At the same time, it allows you complete access to the CSS style, as well as other elements, to the point that it is entirely possible to achieve a layout that resembles a traditional page rather than a blog. Not that I would want that myself, but that looks entirely achievable to me.
It pleases me that Bear Blog doesn't have built-in comments, nor does it have any essential element that goes against its simply stated core goals. In fact, if you look at its roadmap, you will notice that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous Action - Anti-war statement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/autonomous-action-anti-war-statement?v=1726013751</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/autonomous-action-anti-war-statement?v=1726013751"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T00:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Autonomous Action
Title: Anti-war statement
Date: 29 August 2024
Source: Retrieved on 2nd September 2024 from avtonom.org

 We have stated from the very start that the beginning of a full-scale war in Ukraine on February 24, 2022 is an imperialist aggression of the Russian state. That is still true. 
Our position on the war in Ukraine
“Autonomous Action” is not on the side of the Ukrainian state — and not on the side of any other state. However, in the current circumstances, the victory of Russia is not beneficial to the peoples of neither Ukraine, nor Russia, nor Belarus. Fighting against Russian aggression is now beneficial to everyone except the Kremlin. It is easy to see why it is beneficial to the Ukrainian authorities. But why is it also beneficial to people (and, accordingly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IDIOTEQ, Warzone Distro, Flower Bomb - BURNING DOWN THE WORLD]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/idioteq-burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro?v=1726009440</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/idioteq-burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro?v=1726009440"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T23:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: IDIOTEQ, Warzone Distro, Flower Bomb
Title: BURNING DOWN THE WORLD
Subtitle: IDIOTEQ interviews Warzone Distro
Date: SEPTEMBER 2, 2024
Source: https://idioteq.com/burning-down-the-world-anarchy-veganism-and-total-liberation-with-warzone-distro/

 Born in 2013, WARZONE DISTRO free zine project, stands at the intersection of nihilist, anti-civilization anarchy, and total liberation, bridging gaps between veganism, straight edge, and insurrectionary thought. WARZONE DISTRO is dedicated to challenging the very foundations of oppression, wherever it festers, and in whatever form. 
 In our interview below, we delve into the radical philosophy driving WARZONE DISTRO, exploring how they blend anarchist and vegan ideals to craft a vision of true total liberation. We talk about the unique ch…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wulfinna - Bias]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-bias?v=1726007334</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wulfinna-bias?v=1726007334"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wulfinna
Title: Bias
Date: 09-09-2024
Source: https://ignitedindark.wordpress.com/2024/09/09/bias/

 Along the horridly neglected path out of being commanded and subjected, from the stinking bowels of the societies of oiled gears, permanent emissions, bright screens, information haze and ceaseless masturbation to worn-out sensibility, there arises a shrill hissing of such stupid nature, of such whining entitlement, that the lone rebel catches herself snickering — then nearly dying laughing . . . 
 "You have a left-wing bias!" 
 "You have a right-wing bias!" 
 "You have a centrist bias!" 
 "You have an extremist bias!" 
 Ha! Ahahaha! Ah, the acrid hell of human hubris knows no end! The sheer closeness in conceptual capacity to being god — yet holding oneself back at the last second …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A.X. - Blackness and Democratic Modernity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/a-x-blackness-and-democratic-modernity?v=1726007099</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/a-x-blackness-and-democratic-modernity?v=1726007099"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:24:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: A.X.
Title: Blackness and Democratic Modernity
Date: January 10, 2023
Source: https://harbinger-journal.com/issue-2/blackness-and-democratic-modernity/

 “Modernity as a concept means time, the present. There are different moderns, depending on the age. From Sumerian modernity to Roman modernity, and even before and after them, there have been…many examples of modernity.” 
 Abdullah Öcalan, The Sociology of Freedom
 “The Negro’s revolutionary history is rich, inspiring, and unknown. Negroes revolted against the slave raiders in Africa; they revolted against the slave traders on the Atlantic passage. They revolted on the plantations. The docile Negro is a myth… The only place where Negroes did not revolt is in the pages of capitalist historians.” 
 C.L.R. James, “Revolution and the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antonis Pastellopoulos - Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1726006831</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antonis-pastellopoulos-cypriot-anarchist-ideology-in-the-post-partitioned-republic-of-cyprus-19?v=1726006831"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antonis Pastellopoulos
Title: Cypriot Anarchist Ideology in the Post-Partitioned Republic of Cyprus (1985 to 1994)
Subtitle: “Cyprus Belongs to its Mouflons”
Date: 2017
Notes: This is an undergraduate dissertation submitted at the Department of Sociology of the University of Glasgow in 2017.
Source: Retrieved on 24rd August 2024 from archive.org

Abstract
 This dissertation examines the structure of Cypriot anarchist ideology and the way it challenges Greek Cypriot ethnic nationalism, as it developed in the first decade following the partition of the island of Cyprus. It aims to contribute to the understanding of grass root political activity in Cyprus, by examining the early expressions of anarchism in the island. Ideology has been argued to function around the use of key discursi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by renhanxue in "Why Not Comments"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41506182</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41506182"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T22:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I saw someone quip (on twitter, I think) many years ago something like:
"A junior engineer writes comments that explain what the code does. A mid-level engineer writes comments that explain why the code does what it does. A senior engineer writes comments that explain why the code isn't written in another way."
(except punchier, of course. I'm not doing the quip justice here)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>renhanxue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does a court ruling mean no more Internet Archive, Way Back Machine?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8444</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/court-ruling-ends-internet-archive-way-back-machine/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Archive (IA) has been fighting a number of legal proceedings recently, after making digitised copies of numerous books and novels freely available, through their website. At no point did the IA seek permission from any of the authors involved, nor did they offer them any sort of payment, for copying and distributing their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by edm0nd in "Another police raid in Germany"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41505379</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41505379"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T20:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the reason I sadly stopped running any exit nodes was law enforcement harassment.
I ran a few exits for about about ~5 years. In those 5 years, my hosting provider (DigitalOcean) received 3 subpoenas for my account information.
The first two were random. The 1st one was someone sent a bomb threat email to a university. The 2nd one was someone sending a phishing email.
The last and final subpoena was the most serious one. Some nation-state hackers from Qatar had ended up using my exit IP to break into some email accounts belonging to people they were interested in and spied upon them and stole some info.
Thankfully both the Tor Project and the EFF were able to help me pro-bono. The EFF lawyer that was assigned to me helped me fight this subpoena but ultimately we had to turn over my account information to the DOJ + I had to give an affidavit stating that I was simply just an operator and nothing on the server in question would be useful to their investigation (by design).
The stress of having to deal with law enforcement, lawyers, and having to entertain the possibility of having my home raided over something so silly ultimately led to me finally shutting down my exits.
Even though I had all of my exits using a reduced exit policy and I would blacklist known malicious IPs and c2/malware infra from being able to use it, I was still a target.
I feel law enforcement realizes this is a big weakness they can target since a lot of Tor exit operators are individuals with not a lot of resources to fight them. They can use the legal system to scare operators into shutting down.
I one day hope to resume running exits as I find it rewarding to be able to help people from around the world in a small way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edm0nd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pushy to the Limit: Evolving Netflix’s WebSocket proxy for the future]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b468bc0ff658</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/pushy-to-the-limit-evolving-netflixs-websocket-proxy-for-the-future-b468bc0ff658?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T19:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pushy is Netflix’s WebSocket server that maintains persistent WebSocket connections with devices running the Netflix application. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Back to Bear]]></title>
        <id>https://goofpunk.com/back-to-bear/</id>
        <link href="https://goofpunk.com/back-to-bear/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:56:37.861Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of July, I moved my domain away from Bear Blog, and back to a site hosted on NearlyFreeSpeech.NET, thinking I would get to do whatever creative things I wanted to on my own site where I control everything. The site then sat there and did nothing, but that was fine, because I didn't need to have an actual blog, I had cohost1 for any kind of longer-than-a-tweet writing I wanted to do.
Then two things happened.
First, I got nervous about social media. I feel weird about the way it works and the kind of interaction it encourages, and especially the way endless feeds hijack my ADHD brain. I decided to put all my accounts essentially on hold, including my cohost, and not post for a while, figuring I'd come back eventually. In the mean time, maybe I'd start blogging again? The time I s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Noisy Neighbor Detection with eBPF]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/64b1f4b3bbdd</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/noisy-neighbor-detection-with-ebpf-64b1f4b3bbdd?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T18:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Jose Fernandez, Sebastien Dabdoub, Jason Koch, Artem Tkachuk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker HyperPod introduces Amazon EKS support]]></title>
        <id>b6be07b1f469321af78fecbb25121071d42162ad</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-introduces-amazon-eks-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:53:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker HyperPod's integration with Amazon EKS brings resilience, observability, and flexibility to large model training, reducing downtime by up to 40%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simulator-based reinforcement learning for data center cooling optimization]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21675</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/09/10/data-center-engineering/simulator-based-reinforcement-learning-for-data-center-cooling-optimization/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T16:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing more about the role that reinforcement learning plays in helping us optimize our data centers’ environmental controls. Our reinforcement learning-based approach has helped us reduce energy consumption and water usage across various weather conditions in our data centers.   Meta is revamping its new data center design to optimize for artificial intelligence and the [...]
Read More...
The post Simulator-based reinforcement learning for data center cooling optimization appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Running (away from Peloton classes)]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-running-away-from-peloton-classes/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/on-running-away-from-peloton-classes/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I needed to clear my head, so I went for a run (yesterday).
And then since I was doing cardio anyways, I figured I might as well turn it into a full workout session by adding some strength training. Instead of sticking to my usual Peloton run / strength classes, I decided to go off-script.
Ever since getting our Peloton bike in 2021, my workouts have been some sort of Peloton class: bike, strength, stretch, and now run. I was obsessed with my Peloton streak (that is non-existent now since I took a break), and so no matter what I did, it was a Peloton class.
Yesterday, I just wanted to enjoy my workout without the pressure of having to follow the instructor cues, adhering to the class length, or having to listen to someone else’s music playlist. I wanted the freedom to move at my own pace; run as fast or slow as I wanted, or rest longer/shorter in between reps.
Although I took a break from a consistent workout routine due to other life things, the pressure to complete some streak or decide which class fits my current mood, made me not want to work out.
It was nice to just be able to do my own thing, at my own pace. I know that people typically don’t take classes during their workouts but if you’re used to structured classes, and feel overwhelmed by the routine, switch things up. Sometimes the best way to restart a routine that becomes not-so-fun anymore is to let go of the rules and simply just enjoy the process.
And if you must know, my workout playlist consisted of a lot of Eminem.
55/100
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A good day to trie-hard: saving compute 1% at a time]]></title>
        <id>2CqKLNS1jaf5H2j99sDONe</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/pingora-saving-compute-1-percent-at-a-time"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pingora handles 35M+ requests per second, so saving a few microseconds per request can translate to thousands of dollars saved on computing costs. In this post, we share how we freed up over 500 CPU cores by optimizing one function and announce trie-hard, the open source crate that we created to do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Guthrie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Strauss and Mother Night]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53179</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/10/leo-strauss-and-mother-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T12:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will be brief. Straussianism is a set of interpretative practices along the following lines, as best as I understand it. The great philosophers and thinkers may have a specific private belief – let’s call it x. But they may not be able to say exactly what they want to say, especially when times are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by anonymousDan in "Apple must pay 13B euros in back taxes, EU's top court rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41499960</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41499960"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T12:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For non-EU readers, note that taxation is explicitly not a competency of the EU (i.e. Ireland can set its tax levels to whatever it wants). The only thing in question here is whether it was applying the same taxation rules to all companies, as granting special exceptions to certain companies could be viewed as state aid (which is not allowed). Ireland claimed it wasn't, the current (over-)ruling says otherwise. This case is also specific to tax rules from many years back. AFAIK the rules have subsequently been tightened and the exemption no longer exists.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anonymousDan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogs Are More Important Than Ever Now]]></title>
        <id>https://popcar.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-more-important-than-ever-now/</id>
        <link href="https://popcar.bearblog.dev/blogs-are-more-important-than-ever-now/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year is 2024. Social media is melting down and locking down their content behind increasingly expensive APIs. Websites are increasing ads to a ridiculous degree because they aren't as profitable as they used to be. The first 5 articles on top of Google are garbage created using AI specifically tuned to maximize search engine optimization. 90% of comments on that one review you read are astroturfing accounts trying to sell you something. Youtube still cannot stop the "pu$$y In BIO!!" spam comments.
The bad news everyone figured out is that the internet is getting more chaotic and buckling under the stress of spam and bot accounts running around everywhere. The worse news is that nobody knows what to do about it.
That's why I think blogging has become so important. You get to read though…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iwona Janicka - Are These Bubbles Anarchist?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/iwona-janicka-are-these-bubbles-anarchist?v=1725927914</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/iwona-janicka-are-these-bubbles-anarchist?v=1725927914"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Iwona Janicka
Title: Are These Bubbles Anarchist?
Subtitle: Peter Sloterdijk’s Spherology and the Question of Anarchism
Date: 2016
Notes: Janicka, Iwona. (2016) Are These Bubbles Anarchist? Peter Sloterdijk’s Spherology and the Question of Anarchism. Anarchist Studies, 24 (1).
Source: wrap.warwick.ac.uk

Abstract
 The question of solidarity is an important one for anarchism. However, so far solidarity as a concept has not been given the philosophical attention it deserves. In this paper I wish to fill in this gap in the anarchist literature and discuss solidarity from the perspective of Peter Sloterdijk’s work. I will examine the key features of Sloterdijk’s theory of spheres and claim that his spherology can be useful for thinking about solidarity in the context of anarchism. Slot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Friends of Russell Maroon Shoatz - Anarchists Against Counter-Revolution]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/friends-of-russell-maroon-shoatz-anarchists-against-counter-revolution?v=1725927009</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/friends-of-russell-maroon-shoatz-anarchists-against-counter-revolution?v=1725927009"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Friends of Russell Maroon Shoatz
Title: Anarchists Against Counter-Revolution
Date: 9/7/2024
Source: Retrieved on 9/7/2024 from https://abolitionmedia.noblogs.org/post/2024/09/07/anarchists-against-counter-revolution/

 There has been a disturbing trend within anarchism in the last few years. It could be called the right wing of anarchism, liberal anarchism, anarchism in name only, or reformism. Whatever it is called, people who believe that they are anarchists have taken positions that side with colonizers, nation-states, and western hegemony. 
 The most glaring of these positions are: 1) the Resistance in Palestine should not be supported or should only be partially supported because Hamas is not sufficiently 'anarchist.' 2) Money and solidarity should be sent to 'anarchist' batt…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryandrake in "FTC Pushed to Crack Down on Companies That Ruin Hardware via Software Updates"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41495475</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41495475"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T23:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[They need to crack down on companies that ruin hardware (or will one day ruin hardware) when they shut off their last cloud server.
There's no excuse for an appliance to brick itself or lose functionality just because of the manufacturer's remote action. When I buy a device, I don't want a perpetual, tethered relationship with the manufacturer in order to work the device. I don't want it to ask the manufacturer for permission to run every day. I don't want it to be dependent on the manufacturer to keep it alive. I don't want to create an account. I don't want to log in to the manufacturer's servers. I don't want them to know my IP address or my home address. Leave me alone, I'm just not that into you!
A hardware device should work on day 10,000 just as it worked on day 1. If you as a company can't do that, you should not be able to sell the device (EDIT: OR at least you should be required to prominently mark the devices as "dependent on the manufacturer's servers")]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryandrake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cypriot Anarchist Kernel - RESISTANCE AGAINST THE PLANS OF THE DOMINATORS]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cypriot-anarchist-kernel-resistance-against-the-plans-of-the-dominators?v=1725924321</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cypriot-anarchist-kernel-resistance-against-the-plans-of-the-dominators?v=1725924321"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T23:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cypriot Anarchist Kernel
Title: RESISTANCE AGAINST THE PLANS OF THE DOMINATORS
Date: 2003
Source: https://movementsarchive.org/doku.php?id=en:leaflets:anarxikospirinas:anarxikospirinas_antistasi

 Note: The present passage was written on 11-16 December 2002 (period of the Cyprus entry into the European Union) by anarchist prisoner Giorgos Garakasian in the jails of free Cypriot democracy. 
 Through the general secretary of United Criminals Kofi Annan the Americans and British have been attempting for some time now to impose a ‘fair and viable solution’ upon the inhabitants of Cyprus. 
 The period that we are living in is characterized by the reorganization of global dominion, which has completed its first phase of ‘anti-terrorist’ hysteria with the devastating intervention in Afgha…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mithr in "iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41494090</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41494090"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know that I completely agree. To some degree, sure — most folks probably don't notice the year-to-year updates in e.g. computing power.
But my 70yo mother, who is pretty far from being technologically savvy, uses continuity every day to copy one-time-use codes from her phone to her computer, even though she'd have no idea what the term "continuity" means in this context. She notices that it's easier to snap better pictures in more conditions than it was a few years back (and that pictures she receives are better looking on average, too). She uses 1Password with FaceID, which I set up for her, because it's so easy to just look at your phone to unlock that there's very little in the way of enabling and using that, and she doesn't need to write down passwords anymore.
I think some of the magic of the Apple ecosystem is that you don't have to know about these things in order to use them. Someone shows you how to do something (Apple could certainly improve on the organic discoverability of many of these features! Some are impossible to find without looking), and then it often just works. And these things do keep getting closer to that ideal over time, with each generation. When I first started using continuity — long before my mother did — it definitely did not work all the time, and I persisted because I'm a techie early adopter. Eventually, though, it reached a state where once folks learn about it, they can just use it.
I'm also not sure about the 3-4 year number, at least from personal experience, fwiw. We pass down phones in my family, and it easily takes 5-6 generations for them to reach the end of that chain and be in use for a year or two before they're switched out for the next model. Battery has never been the reason someone in that chain switched phones.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mithr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by arcticbull in "iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493803</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493803"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> If the iPhone would have true user-swappable batteries, their business would collapse.
Battery replacement costs at Apple are $69-99 and offered all the way back to the iPhone SE 1st Generation. That's the all-in cost where you bring it in, they open it up, swap it out, and give your phone back to you.
An OEM battery for an Android phone is like $50.
Budgeting $69-99 once every 3-4 years hardly seems like it's going to nuke their business from orbit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>arcticbull</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Milk & Serial, a found footage horror film by Curry Barker]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8435</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/milk-serial-found-footage-horror-film-curry-barker/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m no fan of horror movies, though I’ve sat through a few. The Birds, Psycho, The Changeling, Ghost Story, Triangle, Autopsy, to name a few most of them. I might make another exception though for Milk & Serial, a one hour long “found footage” horror film, directed by Curry Barker — who also wrote the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More NPM packages on Cloudflare Workers: Combining polyfills and native code to support Node.js APIs]]></title>
        <id>3zICVbgdxrLByG4g2Dsddy</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/more-npm-packages-on-cloudflare-workers-combining-polyfills-and-native-code"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Workers now supports more NPM packages and Node.js APIs using an overhauled hybrid compatibility layer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James M Snell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by iteratethis in "iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493693</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493693"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T20:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm conflicted.
It's absolutely stunning what smartphones can do these days and Apple makes an excellent product. It feels ungrateful and cynical to keep calling new models "boring".
The reality though is that normie needs were accomplished several generations ago. I'll use my girlfriend as a sample of such user.
She can't tell the difference between LCD and OLED nor would she notice Pro-motion.
You can add a million features to the camera app but she opens it and presses the shutter. Her only awareness of features is when she accidentally enables one and doesn't know how to get back.
You could set her back 8 iOS versions and she probably wouldn't notice. Because she uses none of the hundreds of features released since. Not because she dislikes them, she doesn't know they even exist.
All the spectacular advances in computing power are lost on her as this makes zero difference for the Facebook cat video group and Pinterest.
You might assume my girlfriend is perhaps lowly educated or just not tech savvy. Wrong, she's highly educated, even works in IT, although not in an engineering role. It's not that she's unable to understand the advances, she simply doesn't care.
It's becoming ever harder to justify new models for normies. Pretty much they buy the new one when the battery of their current one runs bad, typically every 3-4 years.
I think this is also why Apple put many Pro features into the regular model. Most people don't buy the pro and they're desperate for selling points in the regular model.
If the iPhone would have true user-swappable batteries, their business would collapse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iteratethis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Brian_K_White in "Why GitHub won"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493527</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493527"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T20:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You sound like you're proud of this work and this plan and this sequence of events.
code.google going away, without the excuse that google itself was going away, after I had started to rely on it and link to it in docs and scripts all over the place, is what taught me to never depend on google for anything.
If google had said "The purpose of this service is an academic goal of Googles, not to serve users needs. This service will be shut off as soon as Googles academic purpose is met." I would not have used it.
But Google did not say that. Google presented the service as a service whos purpose was to be useful to users. And only because of that, we used it.
Do you see the essential problem here? Effectively, Google harnessed users for it's own purposes without their consent by means of deception. The free-ness of the service  that the users received doesn't even count as a fair trade in a transaction because the transaction was based on one party misinforming the other.
So thanks for all your work making the world a better place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian_K_White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by swyx in "iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493023</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41493023"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T20:08:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i clipped the 5 mins on apple intelligence here for those interested https://x.com/swyx/status/1833231875537850659
notes:
- photos/album search now includes video understanding, which imo seems very good from the first 2 examples they showed. includes scroll to exact time of the moment you describe.
- Mail and Notifications will show summaries instead of str[:x]
- Siri now knows iPhone, becomes the ultimate manual on how to use the increasingly complicated iOS 18. and can read your texts (!) to suggest actions with Personal Context Understanding (also it will try to advertise apple tv shows to you... i'm SURE it will be totally objective and aligned to your preferences amirite)
- new iphone 16 camera control button is PRIME real estate - notice how OpenAI/ChatGPT is now next to Google search, and both are secondary clicks to Apple's visual search, which comes first
- camera adds events to calendar!
- "all done on device" and on cloud (though craig doesnt say that haha)
overall i think insanely good ideas on ai + phone integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>swyx</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41492320</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41492320"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T19:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smaller notch? Touch ID? Better battery life? Faster charging? Larger default storage? Nope, let's skip all that and spend most of the event talking about video recording.
Is anyone here actually excited about the features they just announced? Or are people simply upgrading because they get the latest iPhone every year or two by default?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Synthetic diamonds are now purer, more beautiful, and cheaper than mined"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41492001</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41492001"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T18:47:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That's a good article. The whole history is there.
The commercial side has made huge progress, too. Look up "diamond making machine" on Alibaba. You can buy a high-pressure, high temperature six sided press for about US$200,000. A chemical vapor deposition machine is about the same price.
De Beers, the diamond cartel, has an R&D operation, Element Six. They sell synthetic diamonds for lasers and other exotic applications. The technology is good enough to achieve flaw levels in the parts per billion range, and to make diamond windows for lasers 10cm across.[1]
This is way above jewelry grade.
Over on the natural diamond side, there's been a breakthrough. The industry used to break up some large diamonds during rock crushing. Now there's a industrial X-ray system which is used to examine rocks before crushing to find diamonds. It's working quite well. A 2500 carat diamond was found recently.[1][2] TOMRA, which makes high-volume sorters for everything from recyclables to rice, has a sorter for this job. This is working so well that there's now something of a glut of giant diamonds too big for jewelry.
The finishing processes of cutting and polishing have been automated. The machinery for that comes mostly from China and India.
Diamonds are now something you can buy by the kilo, in plastic bags.
[1] https://e6-prd-cdn-01.azureedge.net/mediacontainer/medialibr...
[2] https://www.forbes.com/sites/amandakooser/2024/08/23/monster...
[3] https://ikcabstracts.com/index.php/ikc/article/download/4101...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by extr in "Apple Hearing Study shares preliminary insights on tinnitus"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41491395</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41491395"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T17:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have mild tinnitus and the best advice I've ever read on the internet for it is: Stop reading. Don't look up information about tinnitus. Don't think about it. If you happen to notice it, try to distract yourself immediately. There maybe legitimate hearing damage but for the psychological aspect, the more you think about it the worse it becomes. I think I saw a quora answer somewhere where the doctor said "Nobody complains about tinnitus while playing Playstation". And it's very true. Until this post just now, I hadn't thought about it in weeks (months?).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>extr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by defen in "Why GitHub won"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490782</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490782"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T17:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incidentally, this is why I don't use any Google products other than search. It's never clear to me which ones are real products that are trying to win and make money, and which ones are just fun side projects that a multibillion dollar corporation is doing out of the goodness of their hearts, but could get shut down at any time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>defen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AnotherGoodName in "Why GitHub won"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490407</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490407"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T16:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well Sourceforge literally bundled malware for a while. So everyone had to move.
https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=31110206
This articles about the open source distribution side but I will also point out that the number of developers who don’t realise your remote GitHub repo can be located on any machine with an ssh connection and nothing more is surprising. As in people use private GitHub repos thinking that’s THE way you work with git. If GitHub was just for open source hosting I suspect they’d have trouble monetising like sourceforge clearly did which led to scammy attempts to make money. But they always had this huge usage of private GitHub repos supporting the rest. This must have helped a lot imho.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnotherGoodName</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DannyBee in "Why GitHub won"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490357</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41490357"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T16:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Actually, Google Code was never trying to win.
It was simply trying to prevent SF from becoming a shitty monoculture that hurt everyone, which it was when Google Code launched.  Google was 100% consistent on this from the day it launched to the day it folded. It was not trying to make money, or whatever
I was there, working on it, when it was 4 of us :)
So to write all these funny things about taste or what not, is totally besides the point.
We folded it up because we achieved the goal we sought at the time, and didn't see a reason to continue.
People could get a good experience with the competition that now existed, and we would have just ended up cannibalizing the market.
So we chose to exit, and worked with Github/bitbucket/others to provide migration tools.
All of this would have been easy to find out simply by asking, but it appears nobody bothers to actually ask other people things anymore, and I guess that doesn't make as good a story as "we totally destroyed them because they had no taste, so they up and folded".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DannyBee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon DynamoDB, AWS AppSync, Storage Browser for Amazon S3, and more (September 9, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>0b51c17d0042fb5a57a9c69c341e9765d332a961</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-dynamodb-aws-appsync-storage-browser-for-amazon-s3-and-more-september-9-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T16:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the latest AWS Heroes arrived! AWS Heroes are amazing technical experts who generously share their insights, best practices, and innovative solutions to help others. The AWS GenAI Lofts are in full swing with San Francisco and São Paulo open now, and London, Paris, and Seoul coming in the next couple of months. Here’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radhika Desai: &ldquo;Soft Landing?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/soft-landing</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/soft-landing"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T14:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve’s dilemma.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tomorrow’s Canvas | Writing Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/968ae3a68f1d</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/tomorrows-canvas-writing-competition-968ae3a68f1d?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T10:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Alibaba Cloud Blog team are inviting you to share your insights into how AI will transform our futures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by renhanxue in "Bitten by Unicode"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41486455</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41486455"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T08:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three Minus Signs for the Mathematicians under the pi,
  2212 MINUS SIGN
  2796 HEAVY MINUS SIGN
  02D7 MODIFIER LETTER MINUS SIGN

  2012 FIGURE DASH
  2013 EN DASH
  2014 EM DASH
  2015 QUOTATION DASH
  2E3A TWO-EM DASH
  2E3B THREE-EM DASH
  FE58 SMALL EM DASH

  00AD SOFT HYPHEN
  058A ARMENIAN HYPHEN
  1400 CANADIAN SYLLABICS HYPHEN
  1806 MONGOLIAN TODO SOFT HYPHEN
  2010 HYPHEN
  2011 NON-BREAKING HYPHEN
  2E17 DOUBLE OBLIQUE HYPHEN
  2E40 DOUBLE HYPHEN
  30A0 KATAKANA-HIRAGANA DOUBLE HYPHEN

In the land of ASCII where Basic Latin lie.
One String to rule them all, One String to find them,
One String to bring them all and in the plain-text, bind them
In the land of ASCII where Basic Latin lie.
  002D HYPHEN-MINUS

- @FakeUnicode on Twitter, with apologies to J. R. R. Tolkien]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>renhanxue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by raggi in "QUIC is not quick enough over fast internet"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41485526</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41485526"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T04:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of concrete problems:
- syscall interfaces are a mess, the primitive APIs are too slow for regular sized packets (~1500 bytes), the overhead is too high. GSO helps but it’s a horrible API, and it’s been buggy even lately due to complexity and poor code standards.
- the syscall costs got even higher with spectre mitigation - and this story likely isn’t over. We need a replacement for the BSD sockets / POSIX APIs they’re terrible this decade. Yes, uring is fancy, but there’s a tutorial level API middle ground possible that should be safe and 10x less overhead without resorting to uring level complexity.
- system udp buffers are far too small by default - they’re much much smaller than their tcp siblings, essentially no one but experts have been using them, and experts just retune stuff.
- udp stack optimizations are possible (such as possible route lookup reuse without connect(2)), gso demonstrates this, though as noted above gso is highly fallible, quite expensive itself, and the design is wholly unnecessarily intricate for what we need, particularly as we want to do this safely from unprivileged userspace.
- several optimizations currently available only work at low/mid-scale, such as connect binding to (potentially) avoid route lookups / GSO only being applicable on a socket without high peer-competition (competing peers result in short offload chains due to single-peer constraints, eroding the overhead wins).
Despite all this, you can implement GSO and get substantial performance improvements, we (tailscale) have on Linux. There will be a need at some point for platforms to increase platform side buffer sizes for lower end systems, high load/concurrency, bdp and so on, but buffers and congestion control are a high complex and sometimes quite sensitive topic - nonetheless, when you have many applications doing this (presumed future state), there will be a need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>raggi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ksajadi in "Reclaim the Stack"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41485081</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41485081"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T02:56:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been building and deploying thousands of stacks on first Docker, then Mesos, then Swarm and now k8s. If I have learned one thing from it, it’s this: it’s all about the second day.
There are so many tools that make it easy to build and deploy apps to your servers (with or without containers) and all of them showcase how easy it is to go from a cloud account to a fully deploy app.
While their claims are true, what they don’t talk about is how to maintain the stack, after “reclaiming” it. Version changes, breaking changes, dependency changes and missing dependencies, disaster recovery plans, backups and restores, major shifts in requirements all add up to a large portion of your time.
If you have that kind of team, budget or problem that deserves those, then more power to you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ksajadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - The Cell Phone and Its Double]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-the-cell-phone-and-its-double?v=1725841614</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-the-cell-phone-and-its-double?v=1725841614"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: The Cell Phone and Its Double
Date: 09/02/2024
Source: https://unravel.noblogs.org/the-cell-phone-and-its-double/

 Cellular phones are common targets for digital surveillance, along with all the software and applications they enable. These phones can be purchased anonymously — in person, in cash, with a covid mask and hat, and with a car parked far away — meaning only surveillance footage of the purchase is available once you walk out of the store. Yet, after purchasing these devices, we often bring them to houses, apartments, squats, camps, and hideouts. Cellular phones can be tracked using GPS or triangulation information from the cellular network provider, to determine your identity after purchase. Here we discuss a method to minimize the risk of unintentionall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authors slam NaNoWriMo neither for nor against AI stance]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8423</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/authors-slam-nanowrimo-neutral-ai-stance/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-08T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Novel Writing Month, AKA NaNoWriMo, the popular, twenty-five year old, write a fifty-thousand word novel in thirty-days challenge, infuriated authors last week, after organisers appeared to support the use of AI tools by participants. While they didn’t specifically endorse apps such as ChatGPT, they did not rule them out either: NaNoWriMo neither explicitly supports […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese threat in critical minerals]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45585</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/09/08/the-chinese-threat-in-critical-minerals/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-08T20:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from C. P. Chandrasekhar and Jayati Ghosh It is more than a year since China, reportedly in retaliation to US-driven restrictions on exports of advanced semiconductors and related manufacturing equipment, imposed export controls on two crucial materials—germanium and gallium—that enter into the production of semiconductors and military and communications equipment (advanced microprocessors, fibre-optic products and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick O’Brian is a great conservative writer]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53174</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/08/patrick-obrian-is-a-great-conservative-writer/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-08T12:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Commercial announcement: My and Abraham Newman’s book, Underground Empire: How America Weaponized the World Economy is still available for $2.99 on Amazon Kindle. Also, it is about to come out in paperback in the UK and US. We now return you to your scheduled programming. Also: this post was first published at Programmable Mutter]. After nuzzling up against […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Farrell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image Gallery for Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/image-gallery-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/image-gallery-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-08T12:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image Gallery for Bear Blog
This gallery add-on for the Bearming theme is the first where I felt a separate page was needed. It's also been the hardest to make – a good example of the joy of limitations.
Actually, the gallery add-on itself isn't very complicated. The challenge has been to make it fairly simple for anyone to use, and making it compatible with Markdown. Here's the result (instructions below):









Instructions
The gallery uses an unordered list, and the list is wrapped around a div (a "section") with the class gallery. Example:
<div class="gallery">

* ![Photo 1](https:/link-to-photo-1.jpg)
* ![Photo 2](https:/link-to-photo-2.jpg)
* ![Photo 3](https:/link-to-photo-3.jpg)

</div>

Since the page becomes quite heavy if you have many images in the gallery, I recommend using smaller versions and linking them to the original image. Example:
<div class="gallery">

* [![Photo 1](https:/link-to-photo-1-thumbnail.jpg)](https:/link-to-photo-1.jpg)
* [![Photo 2](https:/link-to-photo-2-thumbnail.jpg)](https:/link-to-photo-2.jpg)
* [![Photo 3](https:/link-to-photo-3-thumbnail.jpg)](https:/link-to-photo-3.jpg)

</div>

Finally, add the following styles to your theme:
/* Gallery */
.gallery ul  {
  display: grid;
  grid-template-columns: repeat(3, 1fr);
  grid-auto-rows: 150px;
  grid-gap: 12px;
  padding: 20px 0;
  list-style: none;
}
.gallery li {
  position: relative;
  flex-basis: calc(50% - 20px);
}
.gallery img {
  width: 100%;
  height: 100%;
  object-fit: cover;
}


There have been some improvements to the Bear media center in recent days. Hopefully Herman has more in the works. I would love to see thumbnails created automatically and the ability to copy the Markdown code for embedding images, not just the URL.
I hope you find the gallery useful!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: swans at Crosby]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53171</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/09/08/sunday-photoblogging-swans-at-crosby/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-08T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Camp Snap 103 - new and improved]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/campsnap103/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/campsnap103/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T19:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been testing the new Camp Snap 103 version the past few months, and it’s officially available so that means I can tell you all about it now.
For those who are new around here, I’ve written a little bit about my initial Camp Snap Adventure, as well as when the first version of the Camp Snap retro filter came out. Here’s another post I wrote about my favorite screen-free digital camera.
So back to the update…
Key Updates
Changing the date and time (metadata) is super easy straight out of the box. Now it’s much easier to organize your photos by the timestamp.
You will also be able to toggle through the volume (3 levels) of your camera in that same section where you can change the date (bottom of the camera hidden by a panel you have to unscrew).
There is an updated shutter sound. I much prefer this one to the older sound. The shutter sound also triggers as you’re turning off the camera, which can get confusing, but you get used to it.
A battery meter has been added. When you’re charging, it will say FULL when charging has been completed. It will also show the battery meter in percentage as soon as you turn on the camera for a few seconds.
The long awaited camera loops so you can attach a lanyard are now available.
The counter is now an LCD instead of LED, so it will no longer blind you when youre out taking photos at night.
Updated vintage filter - the colors lean more magenta than green (see sample photos).
The response between clicking the shutter button and the camera actually taking the photo is so much faster now. I took quite a few photos from a slow moving car, and they didn’t turn out blurry!
…and of course, much better photo quality that renders the highlights SO. MUCH. BETTER.
Sample photos
Photos taken with the new vintage filter, all straight out of the camera with absolutely no edits.
If you're interested in getting your hands on a Camp Snap, feel free to use CAMP51 at checkout for $5 off your order at campsnapphoto.com. Looks like they're shipping these new cameras now.






affiliate code.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the worst thing about depression is indifference]]></title>
        <id>https://tala.bearblog.dev/the-worst-thing-about-depression-is-indifference/</id>
        <link href="https://tala.bearblog.dev/the-worst-thing-about-depression-is-indifference/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was first diagnosed with depression, I found myself going down the rabbit hole - Reddit posts from ten years ago, outdated mental health forums, and scattered blogposts written by other people with depression. In a sense, I felt like a pariah compared to my peers, and I was curious how depression manifests in others compared to me, because, despite living with this condition for years, I was clueless about what it was.
People tend to think that the most telltale sign of depression is sadness, but I discovered depression manifests overwhelmingly different across individuals: those who experience the crushing sadness, those with the intense mood swings, or those with detachment from their lives. There are depressed people who neglect hygiene for days, people who live in messy rooms ov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>