<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-27T06:37:51.129Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-27T06:37:51.129Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No! We Did Not Survive the First Term]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345219</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/27/no-we-did-not-survive-the-first-term/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T06:35:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a seemingly comforting phrase for those struggling with the results of the recent U.S. presidential election, I’ve heard variants of “It’s okay, we survived the first term.” While this may be a well-intentioned attempt to provide comfort to those in distress, it deserves a more thoughtful examination. A parent might comfort a child by  More
The post No! We Did Not Survive the First Term appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wim Laven</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monetary Policy in Response to Tariff Shocks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282938</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/monetary-policy-in-response-to-tariff-shocks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T06:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the Trump tariff scheme weakens the economy enough, the Fed would do better to ease rather than tighten even if inflation increases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving Holiday Schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282935</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/thanksgiving-holiday-schedule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T05:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have a happy Turkey Day! We will be kicking back a bit over the holiday weekend in light of (hopefully) lower news flow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peaceful Protests Work: Lessons from the UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345136</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/27/peaceful-protests-work-lessons-from-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T05:40:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disruptive climate protests annoy some people, but studies from the UK confirm that they have been effective at shifting public opinion and helping create policy change. Back in July, activists from the UK protest group Just Stop Oil repeated their common tactic of being dramatically disruptive at landmarks and cultural events. Two protesters made news after spraying  More
The post Peaceful Protests Work: Lessons from the UK appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Janene Yazzie: COP29, Leonard Peltier and the Future of Indigenous Resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345221</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/janene-yazzie-cop29-leonard-peltier-and-the-future-of-indigenous-resistance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T03:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this episode of CounterPunch Radio, Janene Yazzie, Director of Policy and Advocacy at the NDN Collective, joins Joshua Frank and Erik Wallenberg to talk global climate policy, the plight of Leonard Peltier, and the push for clemency from President Biden. Janene, who just returned from COP29, also addresses how we move forward under a second Trump term. As a bonus, we've included Janene's scorching plenary speech from Socialism 2024. 
To learn about NDN Collective- www.ndncollective.org
For our actions and campaigns: https://ndncollective.org/take-action/
Palestine Solidarity: https://ndncollective.org/the-right-of-return-is-landback/
For Leonard Peltier work- https://freeleonard-peltier.com/
Or text “FREELEONARDNOW” to 50302 More
The post Janene Yazzie: COP29, Leonard Peltier and the Future of Indigenous Resistance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transforming Istio into an enterprise-ready service mesh for Amazon ECS]]></title>
        <id>de2fd3b7da33ab9ea64af38d12aae1e6afd237fc</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/transforming-istio-into-an-enterprise-ready-service-mesh-for-amazon-ecs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-27T01:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is authored by John Howard(Senior Architect, Solo.io), Petr McAllister(Engineer on the Partner Team, Solo.io), Christian Posta(VP, Global Field CTO, Solo.io) and Jooyoung Kim (Senior Containers Specialist Solutions Architect, AWS). Introduction Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) is a fully managed service that streamlines the deployment, management, and scaling of containerized applications. Although Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jooyoung Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Time-based snapshot copy for Amazon EBS]]></title>
        <id>2780add382124234bd566eba632030da9555e3b9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/time-based-snapshot-copy-for-amazon-ebs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T22:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With time-based copying, critical EBS snapshots and AMIs can now meet crucial RPOs by specifying exact completion durations from 15 minutes to 48 hours for disaster recovery, testing, development, and operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gail Jones wins Creative Australia Award for Lifetime Achievement in Literature]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8886</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/gail-jones-wins-creative-australia-award-lifetime-achievement-literature/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based Western Australian author Gail Jones was last week presented with the Creative Australia Lifetime Achievement in Literature award. Jones’ books have won the ARA Historical Novel Prize, Barbara Ramsden Award, and Western Australian Premier’s Book Awards. They have also been included on the long and short lists of numerous literary awards, including the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/26/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282912</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-28-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; "Joy" at Bluesky; Trump team drags feet on signing ethics and transparency agreements; "Everyone is taking their skim"  (of Democrat campaigns); Boeing 737 DHL plane crashes. In Lithuania. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capital One’s sessions and speakers at AWS re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/098ea5265b56</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/capital-ones-sessions-and-speakers-at-aws-re-invent-2024-098ea5265b56?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T18:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud forward, data powered, AI ascendant. That’s how we stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by phil21 in "California's most neglected group of students: the gifted ones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247816</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247816"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:36:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Killing truly progressive programs for the purpose of virtue signaling is a loss for society
It's not just a loss for society.  It's society-killing.
Taking resources away from those who move society forward and spending them on those who are unlikely to "pay it back" is a way your culture dies.  Conquerers in the past used this strategy to win massive empires for themselves.  It's a ridiculous self-own.
This is perhaps the sole political topic I will die on a hill for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>phil21</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by csa in "California's most neglected group of students: the gifted ones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247695</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42247695"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T17:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not just California, but California may be one of the more egregious state neglecters.
The push at the state level for policies that focus on equality of outcomes over equality of opportunities will not end well for the gifted and talented communities.
Whenever I hear these people talk about their policies, I can’t help but recall Harrison Bergeron.
Focusing on equality of outcomes in a society that structurally does not afford equality of opportunities is a fool’s game that ends with Bergeron-esque levels of absurdity.
Imho, the only viable/main solution is to acknowledge that we all aren’t equal, we don’t all have access to the same opportunities, but as a country we can implement policies that lessen the imbalance.
Head Start is a good example.
Well-run gifted and talented programs in schools are also good examples.
Killing truly progressive programs for the purpose of virtue signaling is a loss for society.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>csa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analyzing your AWS Cost Explorer data with Amazon Q Developer: Now Generally Available]]></title>
        <id>677db6e38f74e929dcdd46ad8d92b84fe21e3332</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/analyzing-your-aws-cost-explorer-data-with-amazon-q-developer-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the general availability of the cost analysis capability in Amazon Q Developer. This powerful feature integrates Q Developer’s natural language processing capabilities with AWS Cost Explorer, revolutionizing how you analyze and understand your AWS costs. Initially launched in preview on April 30, 2024, the Amazon Q cost analysis capability now offers enhanced […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Riya Dani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Benefits with Bottlerocket: A Purpose-Built Container OS]]></title>
        <id>7fd5d2aa425994eb182752ee6f7b22bfd45719d3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/benefiting-from-bottlerocket-an-open-source-container-optimized-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T16:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Post updated on Nov 26, 2024. This post discusses Bottlerocket, a Linux-based open source operating system that is purpose-built for running containers. We will walk through fleet management at scale and how users can benefit from it. We will also share the key pillars that support Bottlerocket’s development plan. The challenges of fleet management with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Charan Teja Gopaluni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How SmugMug Increased Data Modeling Productivity with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>60be41c2505f5225f2f910fd21a76bb690d633ff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/how-smugmug-increased-data-modeling-productivity-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T15:40:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-written with Dr. Geoff Ryder, Manager, at SmugMug. Introduction SmugMug operates two very large online photo platforms: SmugMug and Flickr. These platforms enable more than 100 million customers to safely store, search, share, and sell tens of billions of photos every day. However, the data science and engineering team at SmugMug and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Will Matos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxpayers Spend 22% More Per Patient to Support Medicare Advantage – The Private Alternative to Medicare That Promised to Cost Less]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282904</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/taxpayers-spend-22-more-per-patient-to-support-medicare-advantage-the-private-alternative-to-medicare-that-promised-to-cost-less.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Medicare Advantage, with less coverage than traditional Medicare via gatekeeping and thin networks, is a bad deal for taxpayers too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TikTok in Romania]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53447</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/26/tiktok-in-romania/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T14:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ownership and control of social media platforms is a first-order concern for both domestic politics and international conflict. The most important battleground in the Russia-Ukraine war is elections in NATO member states. And there, Russia is clearly winning. Trump, obviously, but yesterday saw the stunning success of formerly fringe right-wing candidate C?lin Georgescu. In an […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/26/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282736</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-26-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T11:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our razzy daily links: squirting cucumber secrets, wildfire smoke-Alzheimers link, HN51, water looting, euro parity to USD? IDF sport sniping, Lebanon ceasefire, Medvedev warns of nuke transfers, Trump v. CPFB, Texas to relax abortion rules? Kit Dotcom stroke, pro pols lousy at messagaing, Amazon Black Friday strikes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Inflation-Stoking 25% Mexico and Canada Tariff Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282866</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/trumps-inflation-stoking-25-mexico-and-canada-tariff-scheme.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T11:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's latest tariff threat is quickly getting a lot of well-warranted criticism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Trump About to Deal a Mortal Blow to NAFTA 2.0?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282848</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/why-is-canada-threatening-to-push-mexico-out-of-usmca-is-it-really-about-china.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T11:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The USMCA trade agreement, in its fifth year of existence and up for renegotiation in 2026, is already looking frail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COP29 Puts World on Course for More Extreme Weather – and More Deaths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282859</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/cop29-puts-world-on-course-for-more-extreme-weather-and-more-deaths.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T08:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[COP29 summit proves change won’t come until floods and wildfires are killing tens of thousands in rich Global North cities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[最近通勤路上的习惯变化]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/20241126/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/20241126/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[我的公司距离我的家有 17km 距离，所以我每天会花单程 30-40mins 的时间开车通勤。今天简单说说我怎么度过这每天一个多小时的时间。
🎵 听音乐
通勤时间总是无聊的，我最早的时候是听歌。但是我这个人有一个毛病，很难听得进去新歌，但是我的收藏列表我又听烂了。所以现在通勤路上听音乐的频率较少，也会，但不多。
📻 听播客
我个人很喜欢听播客，不光在通勤的时候会听。但是我又很挑，对于信息和内容输出质量很低的播客我极少收听。所以我有一个白名单，一旦白名单的播客更新，我才会考虑听。所以，不会每天有一个小时的可收听量。
📚 听书
这个是我最近半个月养成的新习惯，起因是我在一些播客中听到过一些书籍的分享，但是我又没有很好的建立起读新书的习惯，所以我就瞅准了通勤这段时间。恰好微信读书又有听书模式，如果你是付费会员，可以想听歌一样的听书。这简直是一举多得，解决了我通勤路上恰好收听内容不足的隐患，又拓展了「阅读量」，还能完成微信读书的任务。

▲ 阅读了 13 天的成果
关于微信读书我准备后面找时间专门写一篇有趣的观察和思考，作为产品分析吧。
💬 总结
综上所述，我现在通勤路上依然会听歌和听播客，听歌比较少，听播客比听音乐稍多。这两者的区别在于听歌可以随时开播，听播客我需要提前甄选一下听的内容。如果两者都不想实施，我使用了微信读书的听书来补齐，这样又可以在这个通勤的时间段内拓展出一个内容输入的渠道。可喜可贺。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by stackghost in "Cybertruck's Many Recalls"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42243288</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42243288"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T07:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>I wonder if you exclude "recalls" resolved by software updates, for all cars, where it would rank then?
Why have you put "recalls" in quotes?  It gives the impression you think this makes it somehow lesser.  The cybertruck, for example, was subject to a recall because the rearview camera wouldn't come up, but the mirrors are insufficient to back the vehicle up safely without the camera.
That's a safety issue, irrespective of whether or not the fix was in software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>stackghost</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reformist Program on Immigration (Or What Harris Might Have Said)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345061</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/a-reformist-program-on-immigration-or-what-harris-might-have-said/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T07:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The immigration issue has split and/or weakened both center and left parties and movements across many nations in recent years. Serious economic and social problems afflicting national working classes have been “managed”—at least temporarily—by scapegoating immigrants as if they were responsible for those problems. Leaders on the left fear that many among their supporters are vulnerable to that scapegoating. In contrast, leaders on the right often see that scapegoating as a means to achieve electoral gains. Trump reflected and strengthened the view that such scapegoating can get votes. The widespread perception that Kamala Harris too would be “tough on immigrants” showed that she offered no real alternative program on immigration. Thus, the classically reactionary posing of the issue as “protecting the nation against an immigrant ‘invasion’” widely prevailed. More
The post A Reformist Program on Immigration (Or What Harris Might Have Said) appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Engineered Chaos and Looting in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345104</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/israeli-engineered-chaos-and-looting-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last March, I wrote Gaza: Genocide by Starvation, analyzing Israel's strategy to divert attention from the starvation caused by its blockade by shifting the narrative to food distribution and internal security. In support of this strategy, the Biden administration implemented a flawed plan, squandering more than $320 million of U.S. taxpayers’ money on a failed floating pier, and inefficient airdropping—an illusory remedy aimed at buying Israel more time by diverting attention from the siege, while offering a hollow promise to alleviate starvation in Gaza. More
The post Israeli Engineered Chaos and Looting in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Magic Number Is 2.5 in the UK]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344934</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/the-magic-number-is-2-5-in-the-uk/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Europe it can be 2.0 or 2.5, while in the US it’s somewhere between 4 and 6 Those numbers in the above headline are the percentages of Gross Domestic Product that each country’s government and politicians figure needs to be spent on the military annually in order to be “safe” from potential Russian aggression.  More
The post The Magic Number Is 2.5 in the UK appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US-backed Venezuelan Opposition Never Tried to Win the Presidency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345089</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/us-backed-venezuelan-opposition-never-tried-to-win-the-presidency/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“On the campaign trail, she [María Corina Machado] was received almost as a religious figure, often wearing white, promising to restore democracy and reunite families torn apart by an economic crisis and mass migration. ‘María!’ her followers shouted, before falling into her arms,” the New York Times reverently reported.  Indeed, Machado’s personally chosen surrogate to contend in  More
The post US-backed Venezuelan Opposition Never Tried to Win the Presidency appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zionism: In the Words of the Leading  Zionists and Their Allies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345080</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/zionism-in-the-words-of-the-leading-zionists-and-their-allies/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly all of these quotes are gathered from the chapter epigraphs in the book, M. Shahid Alam, Israeli Exceptionalism: The Destabilizing Logic of Zionism (Springer: 2008). A few of the quotes are from non-Zionists. The sources for most these quotes can be found in this book.  Chosenness “Israel is not another example of the species  More
The post Zionism: In the Words of the Leading  Zionists and Their Allies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shahid Alam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lawsuit Targeting LA Teachers Union Aims to Make CA an Open Shop State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345086</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/lawsuit-targeting-la-teachers-union-aims-to-make-ca-an-open-shop-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Under the guise of fighting alleged “anti-semitism”, the anti-labor Freedom Foundation has filed a lawsuit seeking to undo California’s “exclusive representation” provisions as they apply to the Los Angeles Unified School District. FF’s lawsuit asserts that these provisions are unconstitutional because they compel the litigants–five Jewish LAUSD teachers–to accept the allegedly anti-semitic union, United Teachers Los Angeles,  More
The post Lawsuit Targeting LA Teachers Union Aims to Make CA an Open Shop State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Sacks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fencing the Ocean: Australia’s Social Media Safety Bill]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345078</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/fencing-the-ocean-australias-social-media-safety-bill/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian government is being run ragged in various quarters.  When ragged, such a beast is bound to seek a distraction. And what better than finding a vulnerable group, preferably children, to feel outraged and noble about? The Albanese government, armed such problematic instruments as South Australia’s Children (Social Media Safety) Bill 2024, which will fine  More
The post Fencing the Ocean: Australia’s Social Media Safety Bill appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345108</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/trump-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:50:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If they do these things when the wood is green, what will happen when it is dry?” (Luke 23:31) Before November 5th, millions of us were already struggling with poverty, extreme storms, immigration nightmares, anti-trans bills, criminalized reproductive health, the demolition of homeless encampments, the silencing of freedom of speech on campuses… and, of course,  More
The post Trump 2.0 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LIZ THEOHARIS - SHAILLY GUPTA BARNES</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dogecoin is a Joke, So What Explains Its Rally?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344941</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/dogecoin-is-a-joke-so-what-explains-its-rally/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockets aren’t the only thing Elon Musk is sending into the stratosphere. After a three-year plummet, Dogecoin is blasting off again, jumping 250% since the election of Donald Trump – part of a broader wave of optimism in the industry, due to Trump’s courting of crypto advocates during his campaign. Trump’s informal appointment of Musk  More
The post Dogecoin is a Joke, So What Explains Its Rally? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maximilian Brichta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Times of Crisis We Need More People Power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345106</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/in-times-of-crisis-we-need-more-people-power/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:40:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social movements often face a contradiction: To expand and thrive, they need to bring in ever-greater numbers of new participants. And yet, knowing how to effectively absorb new people and plug them into a movement’s work can be very difficult. This is a problem even during normal times, but it grows even bigger during times  More
The post In Times of Crisis We Need More People Power appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives are Destroying Legacy Media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345111</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/conservatives-are-destroying-legacy-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that conservatives will have full control of the triumvirate – the White House, Congress, and Senate – they appear eager to dominate the legacy media as well and ultimately destroy it. The latest talk of the town is Elon Musk’s potential buyout of MSNBC, a move that would greatly damage the media’s ability to broadcast  More
The post Conservatives are Destroying Legacy Media appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chloe Atkinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Housing Director Threatens to Evict Florida Families]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344969</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/housing-director-threatens-to-evict-florida-families/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 900 families living at the Li’l Abner mobile home park in Sweetwater, Florida, were taken aback on Tuesday November 12 when The Urban Group,a real estate consulting firm, issued a surprise mass eviction notice. After the initial shock passed, residents got organized and started daily protests. The letter warned that residents of the park,  More
The post Housing Director Threatens to Evict Florida Families appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omar Ocampo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mainstream Media’s Big Lie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344965</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/26/the-mainstream-medias-big-lie/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-26T06:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eduardo Porter joined the chorus of people telling us that the inequality of the last four decades was just the result of the free market in his Washington Post column. As Porter puts it: “A paper last year by economists from Princeton and Columbia argues that Democrats started losing the working class back in the  More
The post The Mainstream Media’s Big Lie appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CDC’s Conflicted HICPAC Anti-Airborne Goons Grasp “Baggy Blues” with Cold, Dead Hands, Vote to Infect More Patients with Airborne Diseases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282789</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/cdcs-conflicted-hicpac-anti-airborne-goons-grasp-baggy-blues-with-cold-dead-hands-vote-to-infect-more-patients-with-airborne-diseases.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T21:25:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HICPAC improves its process a little, but with the same lethal outcome]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cold Enough for Snow by Jessica Au being adapted to film]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8884</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/cold-enough-for-snow-jessica-au-film/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian author Jessica Au’s multi-award winning 2022 novel, Cold Enough for Snow, is being made into a film, says publisher Giramondo. No word yet as to who the lead actors will be, but production is scheduled to commence in 2025, and will be the debut feature of Jemima James. Fingers crossed this is a faithful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/25/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282806</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-25-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T19:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluesky Widget]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bluesky-widget/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bluesky-widget/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's been a lot of talk about the social network Bluesky lately. If you have an account there and want to show your latest status update on your blog, here's an easy way to do that.
Vincent Will has put together a script named bsky-embed. All you need to do is enter your username and modify the settings to your liking. I've added it to the footer using this setup:
<div class="bluesky">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bsky-embed/dist/bsky-embed.es.js" async></script>
<bsky-embed
  username="birming.com"
  limit="1"
  load-more="false"
  custom-styles=".border-slate-300 { border: none; }"
>
</bsky-embed>
</div>

The bluesky div class is my own addition, giving the widget a style that matches the Bearming Theme. Here's the CSS styling for that:
/* Bluesky */
.bluesky {
  margin: 30px 0;
  padding: 10px;
  font-family: var(--font-secondary);
  font-size: inherit;
  text-align: left;
  background: var(--accent-color);
  border-radius: 10px;
}

Good luck!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing future-dated Amazon EC2 On-Demand Capacity Reservations]]></title>
        <id>c82766052a1eefeefa0411b4276a70ec3f98023b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-future-dated-amazon-ec2-on-demand-capacity-reservations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS EC2 Capacity Reservations empowers you to secure compute capacity for critical future workloads up to 120 days ahead, ensuring seamless performance during peak demand events like product launches or seasonal sales.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[imza hücresi ve diğerleri]]></title>
        <id>https://vitriolpodcast.blog/imza-hucresi-ve-digerleri/</id>
        <link href="https://vitriolpodcast.blog/imza-hucresi-ve-digerleri/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[geçtiğimiz hafta sonu, sevgili üstadım seda bağcan’ın “imza hücresi şifası birinci seviye eğitimi”nde, artık ben de bir eğitmen olduğum için, asistan olarak bulundum. birçok son derece kuvvetli şifacının el almasına tanık oldum, ben de el verme onuruna eriştim.
detaylara inmeden evvel, bu el verme olayını, diğer isimleriyle inisiyasyon veya erginlenme, biraz kendi cümlelerimle açmak istiyorum.
elbette birçok şekilde anlatılabilir, eski hayata ölmek ve yeni hayata doğmak, ki bu yeni hayat kişinin olması gerektiği kişi olmasına sıçramasıdır, yeni bir bilginin alınması ve içselleştirmeye başlanması süreci, zaten titreşimlerden oluşan atomlardan oluşan insan bedeninin, ki bu bedenler (en az) dört tanedir ve fiziksel beden bunların içinden titreşimi en düşük veya en az süptil olanıdır (diğerler…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sangnoir in "Hey, wait – is employee performance Gaussian distributed?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42238109</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42238109"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:27:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Performance management, as practiced in many large corporations in 2024, is an outdated technology that is in need of an update
Author made a couple of fundamental mistakes: the first is they assume employees are (or should be) paid according to how much they "individually" earned the company. Employers strive to pay employees the minimum they can bear, on employer's terms. Those terms are information asymmetry and a Gaussian distribution. Fairness is the last thing one should expect from employers, but being honest about this is not good for morale, so instead, they rely on keeping employees uninformed, while the employers collude to gather everyone's remuneration history via the Work Number.
The second mistake they made is assume that companies would prioritize being lean and trimming the mediocre & bottom 5%. There are other considerations, combined productivity is more important than having individual superstars working on the shiniest features. How much revenue do you think a janitor or café staffer generates? Close to zero. The same goes for engineering. Someone has to do the unglamorous staff, or you end up with a dysfunctional company, with amazing talent (on paper).
Edit: there's an infamous graph that shows when aggregate worker productivity and average income. The two tracked closely, rising in tandem until the 1970s, where they got decoupled. With income becoming much flatter, and productivity continuing to rise. That's how the world has been for the past 50 years on the macro and the micro]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sangnoir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking down CPU speed: How utilization impacts performance]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The Performance Engineering team at GitHub assessed how CPU performance degrades as utilization increases and how this relates to capacity.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/engineering/architecture-optimization/breaking-down-cpu-speed-how-utilization-impacts-performance/">Breaking down CPU speed: How utilization impacts performance</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The latest from GitHub's engineering team - The GitHub Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: multiple new launches, AI training partnership with Anthropic, and join AWS re:Invent virtually (Nov 25, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>1534a75f44b8d95651046b97d6cd9b1d87d12a92</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-multiple-new-launches-ai-training-partnership-with-anthropic-and-join-aws-reinvent-virtually-nov-25-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T16:28:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I saw an astonishing number of new feature and service launches from AWS. This means we are getting closer to AWS re:Invent 2024! Our News Blog team is also finalizing blog posts for re:Invent to introduce some awesome launches from service teams for your reading pleasure. The most interesting news is that we’re […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chevelle Restoration - Part 4]]></title>
        <id>https://datadiaries.bearblog.dev/chevelle-restoration-part-4/</id>
        <link href="https://datadiaries.bearblog.dev/chevelle-restoration-part-4/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3
Well, for this birthday edition of our restoration project, the 307 engine has completed its full rebuild. While much of the details of how this is all done went way over my head, what I do know is all the shiny bits from the last post now live inside the engine. Not to understate the amount of back-breaking labour my father went through to get it all set up, but the orange boi has all the requisite parts strapped on and is ready to rock and roll!

It was with much excitement and a little trepidation that I approached the milestone of this engine's 55th birthday compared to my measly 34 years of age. Would these shiny bits of expensive metal, meticulously installed into the bowels of this mysterious orange machine, reignite its thumping heartbeat in a flurry of noise and smoke?

Yes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving back to Japan - countryside]]></title>
        <id>https://dostoynikov.com/moving-back-to-japan-countryside/</id>
        <link href="https://dostoynikov.com/moving-back-to-japan-countryside/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:46:14.158Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a two-month writing hiatus, I'm back to share my recent adventure: moving back to Japan.
Two weeks ago, I left my croupier job in Estonia, moved back to Japan and already achieved one of my long-standing dreams – settling into a charming two-story house with a garden. My plan is to transform this outdoor space into a green haven, with lemon trees and herb-filled pots(Yes I love lemon trees a lot and fortunately there are lemon trees everywhere around my neighborhood). The house was completely empty when I moved in, so I'm gradually acquiring basic appliances to make it feel like home.
Transportation here presented an interesting challenge. While a car is essential in the countryside, my current financial situation – thanks to the loans I took for this journey – means I've opted for a bicycle. I purchased a Giant Escape for around 70,000 yen and will be commuting 5km each way, a distance familiar from my university days.
This isn't my first time in Japan, but living in the countryside as a foreigner feels like a unique privilege. The locals are incredibly welcoming. While I'm visibly different – a bearded foreigner in a small Japanese city – I've been pleasantly surprised by the warm interactions. Elders, children, and dog owners are particularly friendly, often greeting me with enthusiastic "konnichiwa"s.
My ability to speak Japanese fluently is making a big difference, of course. In this small city, encountering a Turk who speaks Japanese at an advanced level is not something locals experience everyday. Whenever I need assistance, people go out of their way to help me, which I deeply appreciate.
My professional journey is just beginning. Starting December 2nd, I'll join a new workplace where I've already met most of my colleagues. Contrary to stereotypes about Japanese companies, my new team is quite supportive and genuinely interested in making me feel comfortable. I'm aware that I'm really lucky to have found such an environment, and I'm hopeful about building a long-term community here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka's People Have Kicked Out the Old Political Class]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-People-Have-Kicked-Out-the-Old-Political-Class</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Sri-Lanka-s-People-Have-Kicked-Out-the-Old-Political-Class"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T15:39:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The progressive alliance that backs Sri Lanka's new president, Anura Kumara Dissanayake, won a landslide victory in last week's parliamentary election. The government has a clear mandate for change but now faces many obstacles to its reform agenda. 
English

/ 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Corruption / financial criminality, 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balasingham Skanthakumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the Recipients of the 2024 Spotify FOSS Fund]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7274</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/11/congratulations-to-the-recipients-of-the-2024-spotify-foss-fund/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR The Spotify FOSS Fund is back again! We created the Spotify FOSS Fund in 2022 to help support the [...]
The post Congratulations to the Recipients of the 2024 Spotify FOSS Fund appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alexandrawei</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is everyone here a CS major?]]></title>
        <id>https://wyverian.bearblog.dev/is-everyone-here-a-cs-major/</id>
        <link href="https://wyverian.bearblog.dev/is-everyone-here-a-cs-major/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like whenever I browse bear blog its mostly posts about coding and or being a computer science major? Not that that's a bad thing, I'm just observing a theme on here. Sometimes I can feel out of my depth here with it all, I only know basic html and although I do code, it's in R (woo lets go statistics). Just sometimes I can feel a bit lonely on here browsing etc because none of my hobbies or pursuits have been reflected on here as of yet :0. Any other earth science ppl out there ?Maybe this is a nothing burger post but whatever]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? Bank Runs Versus Solvency]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32467</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-bank-runs-versus-solvency/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence from a 160-year-long panel of U.S. banks suggests that the ultimate cause of bank failures and banking crises is almost always a deterioration of bank fundamentals that leads to insolvency. As described in our previous post, bank failures—including those that involve bank runs—are typically preceded by a slow deterioration of bank fundamentals and are hence remarkably predictable. In this final post of our three-part series, we relate the findings discussed previously to theories of bank failures, and we discuss the policy implications of our findings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The political economy of estimating productivity.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45871</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/25/the-political-economy-of-estimating-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T10:52:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who decides what statistical offices measure and how they measure it? And what are the implicit values embedded in these decisions? Recently, the ILO issued a new manual on measuring productivity. Below, I´ll discuss the questions posed. But for starters, it is essential to realize that economists measure monetary productivity, not physical productivity, which leads […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stare into Gaza: The Horror Was Not What I Expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344823</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/stare-into-gaza-the-horror-was-not-what-i-expected/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T07:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That is Gaza behind me. The fence line is 600m away. The northern part of Gaza, where Israel is carrying out a genocide within a genocide, systematically starving 300,000 Palestinians to death, is about 2km further. The absurdity and the obscenity of being able to be this close to 20,000 murdered children, their bodies “prophetic  More
The post Stare into Gaza: The Horror Was Not What I Expected appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Hoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/daily/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/daily/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[{{ posts|tag:daily }}]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Done, Done, So Done With Duopoly]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344836</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/done-done-so-done-with-duopoly/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T07:03:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the election, some Trump voters told reporters they don’t pay much attention to what Trump says. They pay attention to their bank accounts (if they still have them). And they think groceries were cheaper when Trump was in office, and maybe remember the stimulus payments Trump signed. (Yes, Biden’s administration sent stimulus payments too—but remember the facts. Trump set a $2,000 figure and Biden’s additional payment—a promised $2,000—turned out to be $1,400, added to a $600 payment that Congress signed off during Trump’s term.) More
The post Done, Done, So Done With Duopoly appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the Houthis Gaining the Upper Hand?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344956</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/are-the-houthis-gaining-the-upper-hand/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T07:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 14, 2023, a month into Israel’s genocidal attack on the Palestinians in Gaza, Abdul-Malik al-Houthi, one of the leaders of Ansar Allah and of the government of Yemen, delivered a speech that was broadcast on Al-Masirah television. “Our eyes are open to constant monitoring and searching for any Israeli ship,” he said. “The enemy relies on camouflage in its movement in the Red Sea, especially in Bab al-Mandab, and [does] not dare to raise Israeli flags on its ships.” The Bab al-Mandab, the Gate of Grief, is the 14-nautical-mile wide waterway between Djibouti and Yemen. What is interesting is that, by United Nations treaty, a country claims 12 nautical miles as its territorial limit; this means a large part of the waters are within Yemen’s jurisdiction. More
The post Are the Houthis Gaining the Upper Hand? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maccabi in Amsterdam: Media at the Service of Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344951</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/maccabi-in-amsterdam-media-at-the-service-of-disinformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two weeks after the acts of violence on the sidelines of the game between the Israeli team Maccabi Tel Aviv and Ajax, in Amsterdam, on November 7th, there are those who continue to battle to correct the facts, accusing main media outlets of having distorted the events to get in step with the Israeli narrative.  More
The post Maccabi in Amsterdam: Media at the Service of Disinformation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nelson Pereira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, AUKUS and Australia’s Dim Servitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344999</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/trump-aukus-and-australias-dim-servitors/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something enormously satisfying about seeing those in the war racket worry that their assumptions on conflict have been upended.  There they were, happily funding, planning and preparing to battle against threats imagined or otherwise, and there comes Donald Trump, malice and petulance combined, to pull the rug from under them again. What is fascinating  More
The post Trump, AUKUS and Australia’s Dim Servitors appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Return of a Demagogic Populist President After 200 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344997</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/the-return-of-a-demagogic-populist-president-after-200-years/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year, our nation experienced the mobilization of the lowest economic class against the establishment controlled by the elites for the second time. It’s not a Marxist revolution or a fascist coup; it’s a significant portion of American voters uprising to overthrow the established order. This bare majority may not endure, but a visible eruption  More
The post The Return of a Demagogic Populist President After 200 Years appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICC Arrest Warrants: Moral Equivalence?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344820</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/icc-arrest-warrants-moral-equivalence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing that reasonable people can agree with in the outraged and outrageous Israeli and American reactions to the arrest warrants issued by the International Criminal Court against two Israeli leaders and one (presumably dead) Palestinian leader is that there can be no moral equivalence between the Israeli government and Hamas. Indeed, there can be  More
The post ICC Arrest Warrants: Moral Equivalence? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Whitbeck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Second-Term “Efficiency” Offering: Microwaved Leftovers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344995</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/trumps-second-term-efficiency-offering-microwaved-leftovers/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 12, president-elect Donald Trump announced his second-term plans for a “Department of Government Efficiency” which will, in his words, “dismantle government bureaucracy, slash excess regulations, cut wasteful expenditures and restructure federal agencies.” He’s assigning leadership of the “department” to the world’s most successful corporate welfare queen, Elon Musk, and to Vivek Ramaswamy, whose  More
The post Trump’s Second-Term “Efficiency” Offering: Microwaved Leftovers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Impact of Images]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344668</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/the-impact-of-images/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most people seem to think that the saying “A picture is worth a thousand words” originated with Confucius, Ben Franklin or some other sage. In fact, it is actually attributed to an advertising man named Fred R. Barnard. Apparently, Barnard introduced the phrase in an article in the advertising journal Printers Ink discussing the merits  More
The post The Impact of Images appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transcript, Trump’s First Cabinet Meeting, January 21, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344961</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/344961/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Location: Cabinet Room, West Wing of the White House. The president is seated in the middle of a long, oval table, flanked by Vice President Vance and Attorney General Bondi. Trump to all: “Isn’t this the biggest cabinet meeting ever? Nothing like Biden’s or Obama’s meetings. Susie, what’s first on the agenda? Chief of Staff  More
The post Transcript, Trump’s First Cabinet Meeting, January 21, 2025 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Makes Dan Osborn Run?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344971</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/what-makes-dan-osborn-run/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T06:36:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most consequential races in this past election was for U.S. senate in Nebraska, where Independent Dan Osborn lost to Republican Deb Fischer. The race was “unexpectedly close,” reported the Nebraska Examiner November 5. Maybe that was because 49-year-old Osborn is a union mechanic who led the Omaha Kellogg’s 2021 strike and is  More
The post What Makes Dan Osborn Run? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Follow Up to: Adding a Little Friction to My Computing]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/a-follow-up-to-adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/a-follow-up-to-adding-a-little-friction-to-my-computing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T05:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, I wrote a post about how I wanted to add a friction between myself and getting online. I was curious to see how it would affect my mental health as well the amount of time I spend online. Things didn’t exactly go to plan, but I did come away with some interesting take aways and some ideas on how I want to proceed in the future.
The first two days, I didn’t log on to the internet at all. My laptop remained off, my tablet had the wi-fi turned off, and my phone was restricted to just a few apps. I forgot to turn off my email notifications (the only notifications I have on), so I saw some emails on my phone and that was fine. I didn’t respond to any, because I prefer to type on a real keyboard, but it helped me keep track of some Amazon orders as well as a few other things I had goi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Warm Embrace of Coffee and Quiet Ambition]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/the-warm-embrace-of-coffee-and-quiet-ambition/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/the-warm-embrace-of-coffee-and-quiet-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I strolled through yet another city on a mid-week trip, I came across a cozy-looking coffee shop. Looking through the window, I saw a variety of people sitting inside. Most of them were looking at their laptops: reading, typing, and occasionally writing something down on a physical notepad. Other people were just enjoying today's newspaper.
I had my own laptop with me, tucked away in my backpack, and that made me curious. I knew people were working in places like these, but it never really appealed to me to try the same thing. Probably due to the fact that I've always had a full-time job, working out of an office and without the need or time to work anywhere else. But now that I was here, on a little holiday and with some time on my hands, I felt a force that tried to drag me inside.
An…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges of Bilingual Writer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344954</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/25/challenges-of-bilingual-writer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T05:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing professionally in two languages, Spanish and English in my case, poses stimulating challenges. After more than fifty years of living in the United States, I still find it laborious to write in English. The main reason is that, even after so many years, I frequently think in Spanish when I write in English. One  More
The post Challenges of Bilingual Writer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jeroenhd in "RFC 35140: HTTP Do-Not-Stab (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232991</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232991"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T03:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's important to note that the Do-Not-Stab header has been deprecated because one browser engine switched it on by default and requiring users to opt into stabbing hurt the bottom line of the stabbing industry, so it's no longer respected. Luckily someone came up with General Assault Control, a non-standard alternative, which also only has one value, so you can set Sec-GAC to 1 to request websites not to assault you. By design, this header cannot be extended, so it cannot be used to distinguish brutal stabbings from a comedic pie to the face in the future.
Because of legal requirements, the General Assault Control header may not be enabled by default, as American states like Colorado require explicit opt-out (rather than explicit opt-in). This protects Colorado's thriving stabbing and shooting industry as most users will never want to opt into being stabbed.
Despite the feature being forced to be disabled by default, the organisation behind the spec is pushing hard for customers to download fringe browsers  that implement the feature (though you may need about:config to enable it). Because of the small user base, the request not to be assaulted can be used by websites not willing to follow the standard to make their stabbings and shootings more precise. End users can request a JSON file from the web server containing the supposed support for the GAC header, but requesting this URL may be used to kick the user in the teeth by non compliant servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jeroenhd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by foundry27 in "RFC 35140: HTTP Do-Not-Stab (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232593</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232593"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T02:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s great satire, but it really does mirror a larger societal shift where the burden of safeguarding personal autonomy has shifted from institutions/regulators to individual users. Do-Not-Stab, Do-Not-Track, whatever it might be, any sort of “voluntary compliance” is a non-starter in the face of financial pressures
IMO we need to start normalizing being militant about this stuff again, to aggressively and adversarially defend the freedom to use your computer the way you choose to use it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>foundry27</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by saurik in "The two factions of C++"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232183</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42232183"/>
        <updated>2024-11-25T01:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I compile a lot of C++ code from a lot of places, and the only time I run into code that somehow simply doesn't work on newer versions of C++ and where the developers aren't even sure if they will accept any patches to fix the issue as they claim it "isn't supported" to use a newer version of C++--even for the public headers of a library--is, you guessed it: code from Google.
Meanwhile, most of the C++ code from Google seems to be written in some mishmash of different ideas, always at some halfway point along a migration between something ancient and something passable... but never anything I would ever dare to call "modern", and thereby tends to be riddled with state machines and manual weak pointers that lead to memory corruption.
So... I really am not sure I buy the entire premise of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>saurik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JacobJeppesen in "Denmark will plant 1B trees and convert 10% of farmland into forest"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42231053</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42231053"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T22:07:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've seen a bit of confusion regarding this. First, it's 10% of Denmark's total land area, which is roughly equivalent to 15% of farmland area. Second, the conversion of farmland area into nature and forests is mainly for improving water quality, as excess nitrogen from agriculture has essentially killed the rivers and coastal waters through oxygen depletion from algae.
Regarding global warming and CO2, the area conversion of peatlands will help, but the major change here is the introduction of a carbon tax for the entire agricultural industry. And to end confusion regarding other emissions than CO2, it's actually a CO2-equivalent (CO2e) tax, which includes a range of other gasses. E.g., 1kg of methane is 25kg CO2e.
If you'd like to read more, see the two PDF documents below, which are the main official documents. They're in Danish, but upload them to Claude or ChatGPT, and you'll have a much better source of information if you'd like to know more about the specifics and how the actual implementation is planned.
[1] https://www.regeringen.dk/media/13261/aftale-om-et-groent-da...
[2] https://mgtp.dk/media/iinpdy3w/aftale_om_implementering_af_e...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JacobJeppesen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by pfraze in "This website is hosted on Bluesky"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42230689</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42230689"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T21:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Appreciated Daniel reaching out to the team about this! Hosting blobs is one of those things that will inevitably go through iterations as we understand the abuse vectors more and more, but for now it's really fun to see this kind of usage in action. The PDS is meant to be a database host in the same sense that a webserver is a website host.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>pfraze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are You Thankful for?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/what-are-you-thankful-for/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/what-are-you-thankful-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T21:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["When asked if my cup is half-full or half-empty, my only response is that I am thankful I have a cup."
There’s a lot of not so great things happening in the world right now that we often forget to be thankful for the little things.
Or is that just me?
I used to write one line a day of things that I was grateful for. In every day life, I would find something that I am thankful for. It could be as little as the sun came out today after days of rain to big things like I got the promotion I’ve been waiting for today.
Then I stopped.
It was hard to keep up with. I was struggling to find the silver lining in things. I got tired of people telling me it happened for a reason. You’ll see!
With Thanksgiving in the horizon, I want to bring a little bit of that grateful attitude back. I know, I know,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Substack, no alternative to independent websites and blogs]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8877</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/substack-no-alternative-independent-websites-blogs/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T20:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online publishing platform Substack, founded in 2017, was all anyone could talk about by 2022. Writers were scrambling to jump on the bandwagon, having heard tales of six-figure revenues being earned by some publishers. Even though we’ve heard those sorts of stories before. I even joined up myself, to see what the fuss was about. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Responce to ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot, or the Necessity to Write Our Own Histories’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/responce-to-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-write-our-own-histories?v=1732477766</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/responce-to-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-write-our-own-histories?v=1732477766"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T19:49:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Responce to ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot, or the Necessity to Write Our Own Histories’
Notes: This essay is a response to Yintah film review: Anarchists in the blind spot, or the necessity to write our own histories which was posted to BC Counter Info on Nov 9th, 2024.
Source: Retrieved from https://bccounterinfo.org/2024/11/17/review-of-anarchists-in-the-blind-spot-or-the-necessity-to-get-an-editor/

 ‘Anarchists in the Blind Spot’ has the posture of a disappointed lover who didn’t make it into their songwriter ex’s latest LP. None of the songs are about them, so they leave a scathing review. 
 The anonymous author argues that Yintah should have included the history of anarchist participation in the Wet’suwet’en struggle. I agree that the film is incomplete witho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can businesses flourish in a world with a cap on personal wealth?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53415</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/can-businesses-flourish-in-a-world-with-a-cap-on-personal-wealth/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T18:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[by Rutger Claassen and Ingrid Robeyns Let’s establish an upper limit on the personal wealth any individual can possess. This is the core principle behind ‘limitarianism’. Limitarianism represents one of the more radical proposals in the debate on wealth inequality. Over the past few years, one of us has developed the philosophy of limitarianism (first […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan and Romania join a very special club]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53421</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/taiwan-and-romania-join-a-very-special-club/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T17:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So in the last three years or so — since COVID, basically — Romania and Taiwan have both joined a very special club of countries. There are not a lot of countries in this club. If you’re very generous, you could include perhaps a dozen or so. But to my way of thinking, there are […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by equestria in "A career-ending mistake"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42228934</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42228934"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T17:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's the thing about the average career in big tech: five years after you leave, almost no one will remember you were there. Most of your old team mates will leave for other other jobs. Your code will get refactored or rewritten. Docs will be superseded, then lost in some CMS migration. Before long, it will be as if you have never worked there.
I know it sounds preposterous, but ask anyone over the age of 55 or 60: except for folks who built their own companies or made truly exceptional contributions to their field, most will say that hobbies, friends, and family mattered a lot more.
So, there is this fundamental contradiction in this article: you can engineer a very neat career, but for most techies, the most useful goal is to make money fast in a way that doesn't drain your life energy. And most of the time, this means responding to opportunities, not sticking to your guns. For example, a lifetime IC job may be ultimately worth less than a management job that gets you to VP level in a decade. You don't need to dream about being a manager; you just need to be reasonably good at it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>equestria</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[重新开始记录每一天]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.solazy.me/20241125/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.solazy.me/20241125/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[重新开始公开写日记。
Why
前一段时间发现自己在浑噩过日子，并不是像一具行尸走肉，而是缺少自律的可持续的沉淀过程。熟悉我的朋友可能知道，我运营了一个名叫不求甚解的 Telegram 频道，这是我的得意之作，也是我的心头之痛。为什么这么讲，得意的是因为我在运营这个介质的同时获得了诸多关注和肯定，难过的是我经常缺少更新它的动力。
但是我经常思考。是的，作为一个 INTJ-A，我是非常喜欢思考，人生经历了 30 多年，到达了现在的阶段，我已经养成了时刻思考的能力和习惯，但是我缺少系统化沉淀的动作。
所以，我准备开启我人生的新阶段 ———— 养成自律的思考到沉淀的链路。
How
我准备按照时间周期的维度产出一些内容：
[Daily] 每天在这里写日记，哪怕是流水账；
[Weekly] Telegram 频道一周至少 3 更；
[Monthly] 召集思想同频的小伙伴录制播客。
Specially
需要说明几点，以上产出的内容，都是为了我自己，如果能帮助到此刻正在看的你，我很荣幸，但这不是我的职责以及初心。
最后，除了上面那些看起来很高大上的原因外，另外一个让我开始想要系统化记录自己生活的原因，是因为我看到了我的朋友 61 正在这么做，能够通过他的内容中感受到他对生活的热爱以及快乐，我也同样需要这些。
以上，祝各位都好。]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nations pledge $300 billion for climate aid + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nations-pledge-300-billion-for-climate-aid-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nations-pledge-300-billion-for-climate-aid-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T15:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwan's president plans South Pacific tour for stronger ties; UN talks result in $300 billion climate funding for developing nations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zug_zug in "Dear friend, you have built a Kubernetes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42227960</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42227960"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T14:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For what it's worth, I've worked at multiple places that ran shell scripts just fine for their deploys.
- One had only 2 services [php] and ran over 1 billion requests a day. Deploy was trivial, ssh some new files to the server and run a migration, 0 downtime.
- One was in an industry that didn't need "Webscale" (retirement accounts). Prod deploys were just docker commands run by jenkins. We ran two servers per service from the day I joined the day I left 4 years later (3x growth), and ultimately removed one service and one database during all that growth.
Another outstanding thing about both of these places was that we had all the testing environments you need, on-demand, in minutes.
The place I'm at now is trying to do kubernetes and is failing miserably (ongoing nightmare 4 months in and probably at least 8 to go, when it was allegedly supposed to only take 3 total). It has one shared test environment that it takes 3-hours to see your changes in.
I don't fault kubernetes directly, I fault the overall complexity. But at the end of the day kubernetes feels like complexity trying to abstract over complexity, and often I find that's less successful that removing complexity in the first place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zug_zug</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't buy me a coffee... yet]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/dont-buy-coffee/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/dont-buy-coffee/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A contradictory title from someone who lives in a country that is among the world's largest coffee consumers, and who loves a Swedish fika.
The title, of course, refers to the "Buy Me a Coffee" buttons that you see on every other blog. Today, it's often easier to find a donation button than a link to the RSS feed or a contact page.
I tried it myself when launching the Bearming Theme. It lasted for a day; then I removed it. It simply doesn't feel right—at least not at the moment.
I don’t think I offer anything that justifies a call to donate money. I write some blog posts and let others use my theme. That’s it!
Maybe it's a matter of background and culture. Maybe it has to do with the typically Scandinavian "jantelagen" (Law of Jante). I don't know.
I don't blame anyone who chooses to use these buttons. Some may see it as a way to put some pressure on themselves to deliver. Some may see it as a way for others to show appreciation.
Personally, I blog almost daily anyway, and I think it's nice to know that I don't "have to." And when it comes to appreciation from others, a short email or a guestbook entry feels much more valuable to me.
But hey, if you're ever in Sweden and feel like buying me a real cup of coffee, I'll gladly accept your fika invitation any day of the week. ☕️]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peak babies has been. Young men are not expendable, anymore.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45847</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/24/peak-babies-has-been-young-men-are-not-expendable-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T09:21:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peak Babies was in 2012. At this moment, we´re back to the level of forty years ago (and the most recent data may well be an overestimate). For the first time in centuries, cohorts entering the global labour market will soon be smaller than the cohorts preceding them. Even when there are significant differences in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Handy Mini-Market]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53422</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/24/sunday-photoblogging-handy-mini-market/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T09:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amnesia in Trump Country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344863</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/24/amnesia-in-trump-country/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T06:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump at an “Autoworkers for Trump” rally in Detroit. (Screengrab from a video posted on X.) Twice, when Donald Trump has won the presidency, Democratic politicians, liberal media, and ‘progressive’ academics have rediscovered – momentarily and rhetorically – ‘the working class’, and especially the ‘white working class’. Senator Bernie Sanders recently said that Democrats lost […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Amnesia in Trump Country appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Forrest Hylton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grappling With Genocide at the United Nations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=344067</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/24/grappling-with-genocide-at-the-united-nations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T06:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Davi Mendes. Israel’s genocide of Palestinians and widening war against Lebanon provided a particularly violent and lawless back drop to this year’s five-week session of the UN General Assembly First Committee on Disarmament and International Security. The First Committee, which deliberates about and adopts resolutions on a range of weapon issues from small […]
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Grappling With Genocide at the United Nations appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ray Acheson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[if you give a misu a cookie (or ten)]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lacy-oatmeal-cookies/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/lacy-oatmeal-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-24T02:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[E came over for late lunch today. My family's never been the hosting type, so having friends over at my house is a rare treat. As if that weren't special enough, she also drove a long way to see me and brought carnations, oatmeal cookies, and "Bounder", this little porcelain jackrabbit1 who now lives at the base of my desklamp with the blue penholding crab. A proper menagerie, they are.
E also brought her guitar, so we spent the better part of two hours singing songs we both knew, her strumming the guitar and me playing on my upright. Our shared repertoire is severely limited by my general unculturedness and I'm still kicking myself for not practicing River more enough for us to record something (it is getting to be that time of year), but it was still one of the most fun afternoons I've h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by NAHWheatCracker in "How to give a senior leader feedback without getting fired"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42224244</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42224244"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T21:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree with you that's how it should be, but experience tells me that everyone is insecure and it's hardly correlated with position and job security.
People lower down the chain are insecure because they could legitimately be let go at any time for any reason.
People higher up the chain are insecure because any loss of face is debilitating. Especially having failings pointed out by someone "below" them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NAHWheatCracker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lijok in "How to give a senior leader feedback without getting fired"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223920</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223920"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T21:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astonishing. Completely backwards. This article describes how to give feedback to your subordinates, not to your superiors. If your superiors are unable to process no-fluff information, regardless of whether it's feedback or updates, they have no business lording over anyone and will sink whatever function they have oversight of. If you find yourself working under such people, don't bother giving feedback, start polishing your resume.
The reason you fluff up feedback to your subordinates is because lower down the chain they tend to be insecure and don't yet have the experience to distinguish between actionable impartial feedback, and threats to their job security.
The reason you don't fluff feedback, or any information for that matter to your superiors, is described in basically every handbook on highly effective communication in organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lijok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gary_0 in "The tech utopia fantasy is over"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223132</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42223132"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T19:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In retrospect it was extremely arrogant of us 90's nerds to think that the bullies and autocrats and sleazebags of the world were too stupid to figure out how to use the Internet to their own ends, and overwhelm the incumbent minority. Once you could use a sleek, trendy iPhone instead of a clunky desktop computer to get online, the writing was on the wall.
Technology changes, people don't.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gary_0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nkrisc in "School did nothing wrong when it punished student for using AI, court rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42222533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42222533"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T18:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The parents' case hangs largely on the student handbook's lack of a specific statement about AI, even though that same handbook bans unauthorized use of technology. "They told us our son cheated on a paper, which is not what happened," Jennifer Harris told WCVB last month. "They basically punished him for a rule that doesn't exist."
I'm going out on a limb here, but if this is the viewpoint of the people who raised him, then I'm not surprised he cheated.
If this was my son and the facts were the same, he'd be grounded in addition to whatever consequence the school deems fit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nkrisc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jaysinn_420 in "The 'Return to Office' Lies"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42221849</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42221849"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T16:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I quit my FAANG job yesterday to join a fully remote company. I took a >50% pay cut but I think it is a 100% life saver. I remember spending 3-4 hours/day commuting and I am just not willing to do that any more. I've cut back on expenses and simplified my life, built up some savings so I can make do with less. My retirement savings will slow down dramatically, but if I don't hate my work life then those savings will be less of an all-consuming goal.
Thank you senior leadership for your wisdom, "If you don't like it, find another place to work". The first good advice I've heard from them in 5 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jaysinn_420</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Blog?]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/why-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/why-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T14:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do I blog? Because I like to write.
That's my spontaneous answer.
And it's true—but far from the whole truth. It became obvious when I chose to write without blogging during the week.
I felt creatively stifled. As if everything I created was never really complete. A gallery with paintings lacking frames.
For me, blogging is so much more than publishing texts. I like to tinker with the design and format the texts with a "digital mentality." I like my blogging workflow and everything surrounding it.
I blog because I love blogging.
Community echoes 🔊
Blogging keeps me motivated
Why Do I Blog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[it pulls you back in]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/pulled-back/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/pulled-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T04:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday one of my students asked me, after class was over and she was the last one left in our online classroom, if we would have new classmates next time.
Me: "What do you mean? Like next week?"
Her: "No, like next round, when we do this again."
She'd meant after the end of our ten weeks together, at the start of the new quarter. Ahhhh! I didn't have the heart to tell her there wouldn't be a next round. I said I didn't know, and that I'd have to ask the school.
After I responded, she raised her hand – which was not necessary at this point, but a testament to her behavior in class. When I called on her, she told me unprompted that she'd asked because she loves the class and looks forward to the two days at the end of the week because it's when we meet.
This student is the youngest in my …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by wheybags in "Dear sir, you have built a compiler (2022)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42218947</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42218947"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T03:12:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a sentiment that I've seen expressed in comment sections many times. I've been programming professionally now for 10 years, and it just doesn't resonate with my experience. Problems with build systems for external dependencies, package managers, and underfeatured / overcomplicated / buggy third party dependencies have been by far the worse issue in my career, compared to problems with homebrewed systems.
I'm not saying you're wrong, I don't doubt that many people have the opposite experience. It just makes me feel a bit alien when I read comments like this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>wheybags</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[need to quit social media again]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/need-to-quit-social-media-again/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/need-to-quit-social-media-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T02:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I've been thinking back to that wonderful week I had in the summer when I had no social media on my phone. How fulfilled I felt without my phone gnawing at me every 5 seconds. I really want to do that now, in the hopes that it'll allow me to focus on my work more, and also allow me to enjoy my non-work hobbies more (like this one!).
The issue now though is that most of my new uni friends are mainly contacted through instagram, and while contacting friends through other means wasn't an issue for me last time, this time I'm still in the process of building these bonds with these people (not that the growing ever ends, but I don't want to cut off my only non-in-person access!). At the same time, my stupid monkey brain can't help but go to my phone whenever I'm bored, no matter how much I try to help it.
I've been cutting down on digital inputs in my life in almost every other way. I've taken a habit of pinning my to do lists for assignments right in front of me on my desk, and I carry my notebook and sketchbook (which is more of a junk journal now) with me wherever I go. I just need to cut out that damn reels page!! Screw Instagram for copying TikTok as soon as I deleted it, I had literally no chance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Subscriptions in 2024 - Worth It or Not?]]></title>
        <id>https://brandons-journal.com/my-subscriptions-in-2024-worth-it-or-not/</id>
        <link href="https://brandons-journal.com/my-subscriptions-in-2024-worth-it-or-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-23T00:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11/24/24 - Update: After some feedback, I've added some calculations to this post as well as a forgotten subscription.
Subscriptions are a necessary evil these days. It seems like everyone wants to you to subscribe to whatever they offer and as much as I try to avoid subscriptions, I still have a huge list of them I pay for each month.
I try to take advantage of annual sales around Black Friday and so I thought now would be a good time to recap what I've subscribed to this past year and see whether or not I found value in the subscription. If anyone else makes a list like this, please let me know, I love unbiased opinions on these sorts of things.
I did not include any trial subscriptions or anything that I paid for less than three months.
Streaming Services \
Netflix - $16 per month - 👍�…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dissecting the Performance Gains in Amazon Q Developer agent for code transformation]]></title>
        <id>2966c911cae5944571341ccd2aaafd2f55b81ae5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/dissecting-the-performance-gains-in-amazon-q-developer-agent-for-code-transformation/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T22:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer Agent for code transformation is an AI-powered tool which modernizes code bases from Java 8 and Java 11 to Java 17. Integrated into VS Code and IntelliJ, Amazon Q simplifies the migration process and reduce the time and effort compared to manual process. It proposes and verifies code changes, using AI to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Vogel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing a new experience for AWS Systems Manager]]></title>
        <id>f940f8f10329048e4784f72ecc08202d5e5d467a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-a-new-experience-for-aws-system-manager/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T22:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain centralized visibility and control over AWS, on-premises, and multicloud compute at scale with the new AWS Systems Manager. Featuring a unified dashboard, one-click agent remediation, Amazon Q Developer integration for natural language queries, and cross-account/Region management - all at no extra cost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS named as a leader again in the Gartner Magic Quadrant for Distributed Hybrid Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>470d069e3ceffa4e8bc9d6d90aa481c7531d1a9e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-named-as-a-leader-again-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-distributed-hybrid-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T18:51:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS leads in hybrid infrastructure with top ratings from Gartner for edge computing, AI/ML, and hybrid management; recognized for global support and fully managed offerings like Outposts, expanding consistent cloud experience to on-premises and edge locations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by frankus in "Phased Array Microphone (2023)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42215936</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42215936"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T17:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["As part of the calibration, the speed of sound is also a parameter which is optimized to obtain the best model of the system, which allows this whole procedure to act as a ridiculously overengineered thermometer."
Reminds me of the electronics adage: "all sensors are temperature sensors, some measure other things as well."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>frankus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your app authentication workflow with new Amazon Cognito features]]></title>
        <id>df4a34c5aba751c2db72ad9ddf287246b0155c9f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/improve-your-app-authentication-workflow-with-new-amazon-cognito-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T17:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity management revamped: Amazon Cognito unveils customizable login flows, passwordless options, and tiered pricing for tailored authentication experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by iandanforth in "Show HN: A Marble Madness-inspired WebGL game we built for Netlify"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42214423</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42214423"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T15:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nice! My favorite challenge was avoiding the glowing white dots along the path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>iandanforth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gavin Rae: &ldquo;Contra Populism?&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/contra-populism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/contra-populism"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Tusk’s Poland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sri Lanka: Reading the General Election 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Reading-the-General-Election-2024</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Reading-the-General-Election-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The National People's Power (NPP) has made history. With its unprecedented, record-breaking electoral victory at the general election of 2024, the NPP has succeeded in engineering popular dissent towards comprehensive regime change. Its parliamentary super majority has been secured on the back of a near complete rout of the political establishment, while seemingly transcending the ethnic majoritarianism manifested by governments in the past to obtain electoral victories. Most significantly, (...)
English

/ 
Sri Lanka, 
IMF, 
Debt crisis, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amali Wedagedara, Pasan Jayasinghe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the ‘return to office’ lies]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/rto/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/rto/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edit: Sorry for the people seeing it on HackerNews, didn’t post it there and it wasn’t intended for that audience 🤷🏻‍♀️ yes, it’s an “immature rant”, because it starts with “I have to rant about the home office situation […] specifically at my place of employment”. This is not a professional article, it’s a personal blog; it was written after I was on the phone with the disability rep, talking to each other about these matters. I fear since this isn’t the US private sector I’m talking about, it may not match your experiences.
I have to rant about the home office situation in general, but also specifically at my place of employment and similar places.
I cannot stand the fake positivity and cute-sounding arguments for returning to the office. It falls flat for so many and it’s trying to ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? The Predictability of Bank Failures]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32432</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-the-predictability-of-bank-failures/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can bank failures be predicted before they happen? In a previous post, we established three facts about failing banks that indicated that failing banks experience deteriorating fundamentals many years ahead of their failure and across a broad range of institutional settings. In this post, we document that bank failures are remarkably predictable based on simple accounting metrics from publicly available financial statements that measure a bank’s insolvency risk and funding vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Various Authors - Don’t Just Do Nothing to Counter Fascism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-don-t-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism?v=1732247504</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/various-authors-don-t-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism?v=1732247504"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T03:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Various Authors
Title: Don’t Just Do Nothing to Counter Fascism
Subtitle: 20 Things You Can Do to Counter Fascism — Yes, You! Yes, Now
Date: November 2024
Source: Retrieved on 22 November 2024 from <mafwdistro.noblogs.org/dont-just-do-nothing-to-counter-fascism>

Note
 This zine is a communal effort, with advice gleaned from the following Jewish anarchists: alice, asher, cat, chanaleh, cindy, cindy barukh, hannah, jhaavo, lilli, mazel, scarab, simcha, and vicky. 
 “Don’t Just Do Nothing: 20 Things You Can Do to Counter Fascism — Yes, You! Yes, Now” is intended as inspiration for everyone who is striving toward a world without fascism — whether or not they’re Jewish or an anarchist. Please share this zine freely and widely. November 2024 
 
 
 You are not obligated to complete the w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Max Stirner - Review of Bruno Bauer's Trumpet of the Last Judgment]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/max-stirner-review-of-bruno-bauers-trumpet-of-the-last-judgment?v=1732234735</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/max-stirner-review-of-bruno-bauers-trumpet-of-the-last-judgment?v=1732234735"/>
        <updated>2024-11-22T00:18:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Max Stirner
Title: Review of Bruno Bauer's Trumpet of the Last Judgment
Date: January 1842
Notes: German Source: Telegraph für Deutschland. Red. von Karl Gutzkow. No. 6-8. Julius Campe, Hamburg, Januar 1842, pp. 22-24, 25-28, 30-31; Kleinere Schriften hrs. John Henry Mackay (Berlin: Bernhard Zack, 1914), pp.11-25.
Source: Stepelevich, Lawrence S. “Addenda: II C.” Translated Essay. In Max Stirner On the Path of Doubt, 188–197. Lanham, Maryland: Lexington Books, 2020. See English original for translator's preface. All footnotes Stepelevich's.

 What should not be tolerated, equalized, and reconciled with everything else? We have endured this accommodation, this easy acceptance which, as it can be imagined, has brought us to a state of exhaustion, which has divided our inner hearts, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimize compute resources on Amazon ECS with Predictive Scaling]]></title>
        <id>7447588fd8c9011cc2ed6d3b1feb380497e5d2cd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/optimize-compute-resources-on-amazon-ecs-with-predictive-scaling/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T23:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is co-authored by Jooyoung Kim, Senior Containers Specialist Solutions Architect, Abhishek Nautiyal, Senior Product Manager, Amazon ECS and Ankur Sethi, Senior Product Manager, Amazon EC2. Introduction Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) is an opinionated, easy-to-use container orchestration service with deep AWS integrations that streamlines the deployment and management of containerized applications at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing new capabilities to AWS CloudTrail Lake to enhance your cloud visibility and investigations]]></title>
        <id>9af3e66a3a525e854568fac1b32c692141587e31</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-new-capabilities-to-aws-cloudtrail-lake-to-enhance-your-cloud-visibility-and-investigations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T21:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CloudTrail Lake updates simplify auditing with AI-powered queries, summarization, and enhanced dashboards for deeper AWS activity insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Track performance of serverless applications built using AWS Lambda with Application Signals]]></title>
        <id>e29ad690a671ba7f9c62224e5a01a357f568efd8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/track-performance-of-serverless-applications-built-using-aws-lambda-with-application-signals/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gain deep visibility into AWS Lambda performance with CloudWatch Application Signals, eliminating manual monitoring complexities and improving serverless app health.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Charlotte Wood did not win the Booker Prize, still gets Booker bump]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8874</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/charlotte-wood-did-not-win-booker-prize-wins-booker-bump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T20:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sales of Australian author Charlotte Wood’s latest novel Stone Yard Devotional have enjoyed a boost, as a result of being both long and short listed for this year’s Booker Prize. The phenomena is sometimes called the Booker bump: Her publisher says that since winning the Stella Prize in 2016 for The Natural Way of Things, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[are you surveilling yourself yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.avas.space/selfsurveillance/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.avas.space/selfsurveillance/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grades.
IQ points.
Income.
BMI, height, weight.
Calorie intake.
Calorie expenditure.
Step count.
Temperature.
Frequent heart rate monitoring.
Mood tracking.
Habit tracking.
Streaks.
Sleep score.
Countdown to the IF eating window.
Numbered step morning or evening routine.
Followers.
Likes.
Your life in numbers and rows. It’s all laid out like a spreadsheet, everything has to be accounted for. If only you can optimize further and buy the products to track and hit the optimal range, everything will be fine, right? Everything will change once you tackle this one thing.
Your boss is bullying you, you can’t afford rent and you have to take care of your parents, but it will all be better when you hit the 10k steps and read 4 books a month. The university stress is killing you, but getting that pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your DevOps and Developer Productivity guide to 2024 re:Invent]]></title>
        <id>2a0311c795664a031bc2ebab9909d8908478ab66</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/your-devops-and-developer-productivity-guide-to-2024-reinvent/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T18:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s that time of the year again. The annual AWS re:Invent conference is just around the corner. Still need to save your spot? You can register here. This year’s DevOps and Developer Productivity (DOP) track features an impressive lineup, including 11 breakout sessions, 14 chalk talks, 2 code talks, 8 workshops, 3 builder sessions, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Artur Rodrigues</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AWS CloudFormation Hooks invoked via AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI)]]></title>
        <id>06438beb8b5a369c8d7df0ccec85c17549c361b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/introducing-aws-cloudformation-hooks-invoked-via-aws-cloud-control-api-ccapi/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing the integration of AWS CloudFormation Hooks with AWS Cloud Control API (CCAPI). This integration enables the use of hooks to validate the configuration of resources being provisioned through CCAPI. In this blog post, we will explore the integration between CloudFormation Hooks and CCAPI by configuring an existing hook to work with […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin DeJong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pacific aid falls due to Ukraine focus + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/pacific-aid-falls-due-to-ukraine-focus-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T17:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aid to the Pacific falls 18% as focus shifts to Ukraine; Russia launches its first ICBM in the conflict; ICC issues arrest warrants for Netanyahu and Hamas leaders; Oropouche virus cases in Brazil surge amid new strain investigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by numpad0 in "The meme-ification of the “Demon Core”"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42206210</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42206210"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T16:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oh they still haven't figured this one out at knowyourmeme?
Demon Core meme came from KanColle(2013) communities in Futaba, and permeated to nicovideo.jp as well as to Twitter. That's why it is predominantly image based with few GIFs inbetween, why it is Demon Core and Demon Core only, and why there are few comical non-girl versions created years after inception.
I'd guess overlap between outspoken (ex-)Futaba users AND HN readers(hops_max=3) OR knowyourmeme users is exactly 1.0f, and this won't ever go on record anywhere unless someone say it somewhere, so here you go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>numpad0</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nielsbot in "ICC issues warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant, and Hamas officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205310</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205310"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Also important to note that Khan, who filed the warrant requests, was one of Israel’s preferred appointees to the ICC as chief prosecutor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nielsbot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by shihab in "ICC issues warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant, and Hamas officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205280</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205280"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is common and expected. Even when a serial killer suspected of 20 murder is apprehended, arrest is often made based on one or two confirmed cases, more charges are later added as investigation deepens.
Also, keep in mind foreign journalists are completely banned by Israel from entering Gaza- complicating evidence gathering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>shihab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hunter Dukes: &ldquo;Proliferations&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/proliferations"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Kevin Killian.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by 0xDEAFBEAD in "ICC issues warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant, and Hamas officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205059</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42205059"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T15:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>In his first response to the ICC issuing a warrant for his arrest on allegations of war crimes, Benjamin Netanyahu’s office has described the ruling as “absurd and false lies” and said the decision is “antisemitic.”
https://www.theguardian.com/world/live/2024/nov/21/internati...
If Netanyahu and Gallant really think they are innocent, and the allegations are absurd and false, they should cooperate with the ICC.  Have your day in court and show how absurd the accusations are.  If you're not willing to do that, it seems reasonable for the public to draw a proverbial negative inference.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>0xDEAFBEAD</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing a visual update to the AWS Management Console (preview)]]></title>
        <id>3c48f4b90c1afccc51d832e1bd239d9a4d036796</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-a-visual-update-to-the-aws-management-console-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T14:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new intuitive AWS console design enhances readability, reduces complexity for improved task focus and efficiency while maintaining familiarity across AWS experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nabla9 in "ICC issues warrants for Netanyahu, Gallant, and Hamas officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42203754</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42203754"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T12:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(before you jump into discussion, remember that this only about these two individuals)
ICC and the prosecutor are on very solid ground here.
The prosecutor asked opinions from a impartial panel of experts in international law. The panel included people like Theodor Meron (former Legal adviser for the Israeli Ministry of Foreign Affairs),  Helene Kennedy, Adrian Fulford.
Netanyahu and Yoav Gallant provided plenty of evidence of the intent. Did they really think that when they talk Hebrew to their audience, rest of the world does not hear them. Case like this would be harder to prosecute without evidence of intent.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nabla9</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Do Banks Fail? Three Facts About Failing Banks]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32456</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/why-do-banks-fail-three-facts-about-failing-banks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why do banks fail? In a new working paper, we study more than 5,000 bank failures in the U.S. from 1865 to the present to understand whether failures are primarily caused by bank runs or by deteriorating solvency. In this first of three posts, we document that failing banks are characterized by rising asset losses, deteriorating solvency, and an increasing reliance on expensive noncore funding. Further, we find that problems in failing banks are often the consequence of rapid asset growth in the preceding decade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sergio Correia, Stephan Luck, and Emil Verner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Questions & answers on China as a major creditor power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Questions-answers-on-China-as-a-major-creditor-power"/>
        <updated>2024-11-21T08:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has been demonized by several commentators: it is said to be the main creditor of many countries of the South and to get the most of them through ruthless exploitation whereas the World Bank, the IMF, the Paris Club, that bring together traditional creditor powers, are supposed to do their best to help those countries burdened by too much debt. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
China, 
BRICS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How HP achieved 40% improvement in Kubernetes node utilization on Amazon EKS using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>1cfef501e204d4782ada7fcdd095f8ae11aca063</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-hp-achieved-40-improvement-in-kubernetes-node-utilization-utilization-on-amazon-eks-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post was co-authored by Jon Lewis (SW R&D Director in HP), Gajanan Chandgadkar (Principal Cloud Operations Architect, HP), Rutvij Dave (Sr. Solutions Architect at AWS), Ratnopam Chakrabarti (Sr. Solutions Architect, Containers and Open-Source technologies at AWS), Apeksha Chauhan(Senior Technical Account Manager at AWS) and Chance Lee (Sr. Container Specialist Solutions Architect at AWS) […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vannevar Labs cut ML inference costs by 45% using Ray on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>881522d823c2683572eded22898d1b5c5549f643</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-vannevar-labs-cut-ml-inference-costs-by-45-using-ray-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T23:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is authored by Colin Putney (ML Engineer at Vannevar Labs), Shivam Dubey (Specialist SA Containers at AWS), Apoorva Kulkarni (Sr.Specialist SA, Containers at AWS), and Rama Ponnuswami (Principal Container Specialist at AWS). Vannevar Labs is a defense tech startup, successfully cut machine learning (ML) inference costs by 45% using Ray and Karpenter on Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS). […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sabsawan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Amazon CloudFront VPC origins: Enhanced security and streamlined operations for your applications]]></title>
        <id>e9cf7abc977d40ac1bb9255061c1a08c6959b403</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-cloudfront-vpc-origins-enhanced-security-and-streamlined-operations-for-your-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:12:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securely deliver high-performance web apps with CloudFront VPC origins; serve content directly from private subnets, eliminating undifferentiated work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront now accepts your applications’ gRPC calls]]></title>
        <id>5d526139e265f2b1f97ea808cbe69afe4337f6ae</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudfront-now-accepts-your-applications-grpc-calls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock high-performance APIs with gRPC on Amazon CloudFront. Reduce latency via a global CDN, secure traffic at the edge, and benefit from DDoS protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bigger and badder: how DDoS attack sizes have evolved over the last decade]]></title>
        <id>5JhHzAWP0tvrl8ZolsnvyE</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/bigger-and-badder-how-ddos-attack-sizes-have-evolved-over-the-last-decade"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we plot the metrics associated with large DDoS attacks observed in the last 10 years, does it show a straight, steady increase in an exponential curve that keeps becoming steeper, or is it closer to a linear growth? Our analysis found the growth is not linear but rather is exponential, with the slope varying depending on the metric (rps, pps or bps).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>José Salvador</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 17, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241120</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241120"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NAIRU — a harmful fairy tale]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45841</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/20/nairu-a-harmful-fairy-tale-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll The NAIRU story has always had a very clear policy implication — attempts to promote full employment are doomed to fail since governments and central banks can’t push unemployment below the critical NAIRU threshold without causing harmful runaway inflation. Although a lot of mainstream economists and politicians have a touching faith in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilient Internet connectivity in Europe mitigates impact from multiple cable cuts]]></title>
        <id>5DP2F9GATeUBYyfl6pQMej</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/resilient-internet-connectivity-baltic-cable-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two recent cable cuts that occurred in the Baltic Sea resulted in little-to-no observable impact to the affected countries, in large part because of the significant redundancy and resilience of Internet infrastructure in Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the grass greener on the Bluesky side of the fence?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8870</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/grass-greener-bluesky-side-fence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T20:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter-like microblogging social network Bluesky is having its moment in the sun. We’ve all seen the multiple headlines of late heralding the arrival of another several million new members, most of whom have migrated from Twitter. The buzz is similar to that surrounding Mastodon about two years ago. Even if Mastodon’s decentralised structure confused many […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TheJoeMan in "Undergraduates with family income below $200k will be tuition-free at MIT"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42197249</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42197249"/>
        <updated>2024-11-20T19:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a great step in the right direction. I can't speak directly for MIT, but there are issues with how these programs don't apply to parents with small family businesses. My parents had a small business, with my father taking home a salary of $XX,XXX. Duke University used the business assets to determine the EFC (expected family contribution) of literally 90% of the salary. Essentially saying to sell off the family business for the college fund, which was a non-starter.
Small businesses are allegedly the backbone of America, and I feel these tuition support programs overlook this segment of the middle-class.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TheJoeMan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>