<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-24T18:42:39.238Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-24T18:42:39.238Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – Circular Error Probability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294468</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-circular-error-probability.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Circular error probability (CEP) is the metric weapons designers use to describe the accuracy of munitions. CEP is defined as the radius of a circle, centered on the intended target, within which 50% of projectiles or warheads are expected to land. As guidance technology has advanced, CEPs of modern missiles and drones have grown smaller. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran Screws Up &amp; Gaza Death Toll]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItABXKUkjhWoHl5SL3YbcQ6R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T17:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, Iran has accepted the ceasefire offer. Iran was, as best I can tell, winning. The Iron Dome could not stop their more advanced missiles and was days from running out of interceptor missiles. Two weeks if the US sent its entire stockpile. The US attack on Iran’s nuclear facility was a dud, the enriched uranium has been moved, etc…
I said that Iran had finally gotten over its caution, but feared it would revert, and so it has. It’s clear that the sooner Khameini dies and is replaced the safer Iran will be, also because that will be the end of the non-nuclear fatwa. (It should be noted that 60% enriched is enough to create a dirty bomb which would render Israel uninhabitable, and Iran should inform Israel that it has created a number, read for missile deployment.)
Iran could have kept goi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Downgrading Uncle Sam, Not America]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294509</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/downgrading-uncle-sam-not-america.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T13:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An orthodox economist describes inconsistencies in rating agencies' approach to downgrading US debt and their view of reserve currency status]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The world’s craziest ceasefire]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-worlds-craziest-ceasefire"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The smug idea that Israel can get away with anything without ever paying a price seems to have vanished]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/24/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294459</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-24-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daily links, including kabuki theater in West Asia, but is there a way out? Plus more militarization on the home front and how animals taught us culture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Orders Attack on Iran After Iran Allegedly Violated Ceasefire It Never Agreed To]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294485</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/israel-orders-attack-on-iran-after-iran-allegedly-violated-ceasefire-it-never-agreed-to.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:52:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel is, or is about to be, back into the war-making game. And the US is sure to be in on the action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Javier Milei’s Controversial “Memorandum of Understanding” With Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294427</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/javier-mileis-controversial-memorandum-of-understanding-with-israels-netanyahu-regime.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T10:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Milei's crushing austerity will not apply to Israeli residents of Argentina. Meanwhile, Israel's national water company controls more and more of Argentina's water supply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deluge of Metanarrative Bullshit]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDIfRYkujEuoLRIeszN745R"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T07:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anytime anyone anywhere begins an argument or uses the word “narrative” my bullshit detector goes off. Because it’s a nonsense construct.
My suggestion is to follow French philosopher Jean-François Lyotards definition of “narrative.” He said: “Simplifying to the extreme , I define postmodern as incredulity toward metanarratives.”
So, if you hear someone use the term in a conversation, one of three things can happen: you can choose to remain willfully ignorant (I doubt many in this crowd would pursue this course), two, your bullshit detector can go off, like mine and you can begin an argument or three you can simply sit with a Cheshire cat grin and be skeptical.
But chose one, please.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Accelerating Decline in US Medical Training, and With It, Doctor Competence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294480</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/on-the-accelerating-decline-in-us-medical-training-and-with-it-doctor-competence.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-24T07:08:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A warning to US readers on the further degradation in medical training and resulting crapification of care.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 23, 2025 (#573)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23026</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/23/daily-reading-list-june-23-2025-573/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T23:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at why not all micromanagement is bad, agent-to-agent protocol truly becoming an industry standard, and why software development won't ever be the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture in an AWS landing zone]]></title>
        <id>d99d4df75c23e56992bed599dc075700701c55d6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/amazon-bedrock-baseline-architecture-in-an-aws-landing-zone/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T18:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, we explore the Amazon Bedrock baseline architecture and how you can secure and control network access to your various Amazon Bedrock capabilities within AWS network services and tools. We discuss key design considerations, such as using Amazon VPC Lattice auth policies, Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) endpoints, and AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to restrict and monitor access to your Amazon Bedrock capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdel-Rahman Awad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Nihilists at Google Wrecking Existing Business to Chase AI Growth]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294347</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-nihilists-at-google-wrecking-existing-business-to-chase-ai-growth.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T18:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nihilism on the part of Alphabet's CEO explains Google's willingness to risk its search business and the open web itself to chase OpenAI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Wilson Turner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: re:Inforce re:Cap, Valkey GLIDE 2.0, Avro and Protobuf or MCP Servers on Lambda, and more (June 23, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>939e6ae6e5cce485ea26e1e9c5165b803613c28b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-reinforce-recap-valkey-glide-2-0-avro-and-protobuf-or-mcp-servers-on-lambda-and-more-june-23-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T16:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week’s hallmark event was the security-focused AWS re:Inforce conference. Now a tradition, the blog team wrote a re:Cap post to summarize the announcements and link to some of the top blog posts. To further summarize, several new security innovations were announced, including enhanced IAM Access Analyzer capabilities, MFA enforcement for root users, and threat […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump  Backfire: How the 2018/19 US Tariffs Against China Boosted Exports and Employment in Mexico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294426</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/trump-backfire-how-the-2018-19-us-tariffs-against-china-boosted-exports-and-employment-in-mexico.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T13:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How a Trump 1.0 tarrifs backfire illustrates fundamental flaw in how Trump goes about doing things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gangster empire: what the bombing of Iran reveals about the West]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/gangster-empire-what-the-bombing"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T13:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have now entered a new phase of Western-led global savagery — prefigured by the genocide in Gaza — in which all pretences have been dropped and only the logic of raw, unrestrained violence remains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TACO Trump Bombs Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBDSPK5NTWQ6f-CrxazUqbJ"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T12:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re getting a bit tired of Iran all the time, so am I, and we’ll see if we can slip in an article on something else.
In the meantime, Trump hit Iran’s nuclear enrichment site. As best I can tell, the attack was ineffective and did essentially no damage. Even if it had, Iran’s highly enriched, 60% stockpile, had already been moved. I’ve seen Israeli claims they know where, but there’s a good chance they’re lying and if the Iranians are smart, they’ve split it up and made sure that only a few people know where each package is, and no one knows where all the packages are, which doubles as “if you hit it, you lose your spy.”
Iran’s parliament has passed a motion asking for the Straits of Hormuz to be closed, it’s waiting for Khameini’s approval. Some ships appear to be already turning aw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/23/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294402</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-23-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T10:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our daily links, including analysis, fallout, and maneuvering in the aftermath of US strikes on Iran, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking: Fordow Attacked Again; Trump Talks Up Regime Change, Brays About Iran Nuclear Site Success as Israel Taking Increasing Toll from Attacks, Iran Puts Pieces in Place for Strait of Hormuz Closure; UPDATE: Iran Media Claims Attack on US Base in Syria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294424</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/trump-talks-up-regime-change-brays-about-iran-nuclear-site-success-as-israel-taking-increasing-toll-from-attacks-iran-puts-pieces-in-place-for-strait-of-hormuz-closure.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T10:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran updates, with the big underlying pressure being Israel's decay path and US failure so far to arrest that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLMs factor in unrelated information when recommending medical treatments]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/llms-factor-unrelated-information-when-recommending-medical-treatments-0623"/>
        <updated>2025-06-23T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers find nonclinical information in patient messages — like typos, extra white space, and colorful language — reduces the accuracy of an AI model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAfYXOnyS9MJubfkhDygXIg"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 22, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
War
[TW: This is what the “globalist” elites centered on the City of London and Wall Street have been scheming for ever since Franklin Roosevelt told Winston Churchill at the 1943 Casablanca Conference that there would be no restoration of the British empire.
[Now that Trump has fully thrown in with the pro-war faction, we will learn if those who supported Trump because they believed Trump would be a foil against the “globalist” elites, accept the chastening of a hard lesson learned. More importantly, now that Trump has allowed the globalists to steer us into a war against Iran, will those who supported Trump be vigilant against Trump using the war to exercise his “war powers” and impose authoritarian measures on the USA p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wars Metastize]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItApRYnqW1zknNsYplBO5J-7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-22T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The title says it own. So did Clausewitz.
We committed an act of war against a sovereign state that had every right to peaceful nuclear power.
Tulsi Gabbard told Donald Trump in March that Iran had NO nuclear weapons program.
There is a huge difference between radio medcine and nuclear power, and a nuclear weapons program. Iran has the former by legal right under the NNPT and does not, nor has plans for the latter.
This war will spiral out of control just like the assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand in July 1914.
Prepare yourselves. We will all suffer before this is over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 20, 2025 (#572)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22998</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/20/daily-reading-list-june-20-2025-572/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T23:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how one company uses AI in their software workflow, debating single versus multi-agent systems, and why every service should have a killswitch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDv1jIfsJz98n8W0jyQToUO</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDv1jIfsJz98n8W0jyQToUO"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T21:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts (no Iran/Israel war).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers present bold ideas for AI at MIT Generative AI Impact Consortium kickoff event]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/researchers-present-bold-ideas-ai-mit-generative-ai-impact-consortium-event-0620</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/researchers-present-bold-ideas-ai-mit-generative-ai-impact-consortium-event-0620"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T20:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Presentations targeted high-impact intersections of AI and other areas, such as health care, business, and education.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Diehl | MIT Schwarzman College of Computing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corey Robin: &ldquo;Waiting Game&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/waiting-game"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On ‘late capitalism’.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Did You Hear It or Actually Witness It?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItD8F5LVCUwf_-020_4b1Z_e"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christine Lagarde’s “global euro” is a fantasy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/christine-lagardes-global-euro-is"/>
        <updated>2025-06-20T12:59:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The euro remains plagued by structural and political flaws that make this impossible — and thank God for that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Big One]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDTCA58J4QKUGh_ZQEozGxt"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:49:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several months ago I wrote two essays on Russian grand strategy. (My apologies on never completing the nuclear one, an extremely necessary but far too grim subject for my taste.) In that series of essays I made a few assertions I want to bring to your attention again in a more contemporary context. First, that the result of wars tend to confirm strengths of the coalition arrayed against the main combatants before the war even started. This is, in fact, not an assertion, but an iron law of warfare that still exists in chimpanzee warfare. See Strategy: a history, chapter one, by Freedman if you disagree.
 
Second, that big global dustups tend to run in about 100 year cycles these days.
So, take a look around–got a big hot war in the Ukraine slightly analogous to the Sino-Japanese war of the 1930s. Next, you got weird, unresolved shenanigans in the Middle East that have a weird reverse-appeasement type feal.
We’re quite possible looking at the two opening battles of WWIII, right now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline Operational Troubleshooting with Amazon Q Developer CLI]]></title>
        <id>6ca0238df379c9f06e7af49f9ea247df0b913de3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/streamline-operational-troubleshooting-with-amazon-q-developer-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T22:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer is the most capable generative AI–powered assistant for software development, helping developers perform complex workflows. Amazon Q Developer command-line interface (CLI) combines conversational AI with direct access to AWS services, helping you understand, build, and operate applications more effectively. The Amazon Q Developer CLI executes commands, analyzes outputs, and provides contextual recommendations […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kirankumar Chandrashekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new AWS CDK EKS v2 L2 Constructs]]></title>
        <id>99b0d8b7cbff701292b81232dbf10edca9376525</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/announcing-the-new-aws-cdk-eks-v2-l2-constructs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Today, we’re announcing the release of aws-eks-v2 construct, a new alpha version of AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) L2 construct for Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). This construct represents a significant change in how developers can define and manage their EKS environments using infrastructure as code. While maintaining the powerful capabilities of its predecessor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Luigi Restelli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate development with secure access to Amazon Q Developer using PingIdentity]]></title>
        <id>a2400f3bcbd784c93bb5d83c61721efb7a0b8517</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-development-with-secure-access-to-amazon-q-developer-using-pingidentity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T21:03:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview Customers adopting Amazon Q Developer, a generative AI-powered coding companion, often need authentication through existing identity providers like PingIdentity. By leveraging AWS IAM Identity Center, organizations can enable their developers to access Amazon Q Developer with their existing PingIdentity credentials, streamlining authentication and removing the need for separate login procedures. Amazon Q Developer can […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sid Vantair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No, Iran Didn’t Target A Hospital (+Iran Update)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDHLivp9EXYVTSrnr1-fvTf</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDHLivp9EXYVTSrnr1-fvTf"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T17:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel uses hospitals as human shields for their military targets, which is what they claimed Hamas did.
#Soroka Hospital is located between two major Israeli military sites: the IDF’s main intelligence headquarters and a central command facility, both of which are situated in the Gav-Yam Technology Park. These installations reportedly serve as critical hubs for Israel’s cyber operations, digital command systems, and military intelligence infrastructure (including IDF C4I and C4ISR systems). While the hospital sustained shockwave damage from nearby blasts, it was not directly hit, Iranian reports emphasize. 

Sororka is the primary hospital for military casualties, I understand, but it wasn’t targeted. It got hit in the blast.

Now, of course, Israel complaining about a hospital attack is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about NIST’s new guidance in “SP 1800-35: Implementing a Zero Trust Architecture”]]></title>
        <id>4Py1QO6TikGfaBeGSPBmFv</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/nist-sp-1300-85/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We read NIST’s new guidance on “Implementing a Zero-Trust Architecture” so that you don’t have to.  Read this to get the key points on the newly-released NIST Special Publication 1800-35.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron McAllister</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending the Internet: how Cloudflare blocked a monumental 7.3 Tbps DDoS attack]]></title>
        <id>4BIcJ46lxWU4w1NytPTCsu</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/defending-the-internet-how-cloudflare-blocked-a-monumental-7-3-tbps-ddos/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-May 2025, Cloudflare blocked the largest DDoS attack ever recorded: a staggering 7.3 terabits per second (Tbps).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omer Yoachimik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 18, 2025 (#571)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22976</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/18/daily-reading-list-june-18-2025-571/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T00:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at a new "cloud finder" API, what has a bigger impact than AI coding tools on your team, and writing docs for an AI world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason For French Collapse At The Outset Of WWII]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T17:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I doubt one in ten of you know the importance of the Battle of the Marne? Quite simple, had the French plus a smallish-medium but crucial contigent of soldiers from the UK, not halted the invading Germans at the Marne, the 20th century would have looked very different. Sure, von Moltke the Younger lost his nerve and pulled two corps from his right flank, shipped East to help fend off the Russian hordes. But, the French were glorious at the Marne and each and every one of us owe a debt a gratitude to France for the elan and courage.
As Holger Herwig writes in The Marne, 1914, “At dawn on 6 September, 980,000 French and 100,000 British soldiers with 3,000 guns assaulted the German line of 750,000 men and 3,300 guns [across a front stretching from] Verdun and Paris.” The Miracle of the Marne …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine and Iran: two fronts of a piecemeal world war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T15:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukraine war and the Israel-Iran conflict are not separate crises, but interlinked fronts in a piecemeal world war — one that pits the US against a de facto alliance of of Russia, Iran and China]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Continues To Accelerate Its Decline (+Iran)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T14:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wavered between writing another Iran war update and this article, so I’ll say a few things about the Iranian war. There’s evidence that Israeli intelligence networks in Iran and elsewhere are being compromised fast. It appears that:
In simple terms:
Israel’s attack on Iran exposed a hidden network. For 25 years, India’s RAW and Israel’s Mossad have worked together using Indian tech workers across the Gulf as quiet access points into sensitive infrastructure. This network runs through millions of Indian… https://t.co/zkJRVuSoPx
— Thomas Keith (@iwasnevrhere_) June 17, 2025


 
That India, a Hindu/Brahmin supremacists state which is increasingly treating its minorities the way Israel used to treat Palestinians before it went full genocidal is allied this deeply with Israel is not a surpris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Log Explorer is now GA, providing native observability and forensics]]></title>
        <id>kg7dxMzYcRnJdVFrxQmCw</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/logexplorer-ga/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the General Availability of Cloudflare Log Explorer, a powerful product designed to bring observability and forensics capabilities directly into your Cloudflare dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Sells</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect any React application to an MCP server in three lines of code]]></title>
        <id>4gk3k2ZiTN6DZoHu3e090r</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/connect-any-react-application-to-an-mcp-server-in-three-lines-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're open-sourcing use-mcp, a React library that connects to any MCP server in just 3 lines of code, as well as our AI Playground, a complete chat interface that can connect to remote MCP servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>