<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-12-06T18:36:51.488Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-12-06T18:36:51.488Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Bank launches record $100 billion aid + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/world-bank-launches-record-100-billion-aid-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/world-bank-launches-record-100-billion-aid-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T17:43:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[World Bank announces $100 billion support for struggling nations as Amnesty reports possible genocide in Gaza]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient satellite imagery supply with AWS Serverless at BASF Digital Farming GmbH]]></title>
        <id>b917efab213459629385d77d5480632e0e4173c4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/efficient-satellite-imagery-supply-with-aws-serverless-at-basf-digital-farming-gmbh/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T16:31:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Dr. Jan Melchior at BASF Digital Farming GmbH and xarvio Digital Farming Solutions. BASF Digital Farming’s mission is to support farmers worldwide with cutting-edge digital agronomic decision advice by using its main crop optimization platform, xarvio FIELD MANAGER. This necessitates providing the most recent satellite imagery available as quickly as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin S. Ridolfi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, Tariffs, Exchange Rates, and the Strong Dollar Problem: The Message of Elections in the US and Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283414</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/trump-tariffs-exchange-rates-and-the-strong-dollar-problem-the-message-of-elections-in-the-us-and-japan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T16:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump's win highlights popular anger in the US, Japan, and Europe over the economy despite high stock prices and low unemployment]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283357</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T11:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our roaring daily links: orange cats explained, worrysome Africa outbreak, glyphosate brain damage, SKorea coup attempt aftermath, Macron wobbles, Labour spending, Amnesty calls Gaza genocide, Syrian army departs Homs, Lavrov-Tucker interview, Bluesky ads? UnitedHealthcare CEO schadenfreude]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Bad Neighbour, Worse Trade Partner”: Would Mexico Be Better Off Without Canada?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283361</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/bad-neighbour-worse-trade-partner-is-mexico-better-off-without-canada.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T11:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If one of the presumed goals of president elect Donald Trump's first round of tariff threats was to sow discord and division among Washington's USMCA partners, it's working like a dream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Did the French Government Fall and What Happens Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283403</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/why-did-the-french-government-fall-and-what-happens-next.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T10:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some detail on the French government crisis and what the next moves may be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Centers Are Sending Global Electricity Demand Soaring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283397</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/data-centers-are-sending-global-electricity-demand-soaring.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T10:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The International Energy Agency forecasts that data center demand for energy will more than double by 2026, with AI the big driver.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilwilson in "The 70% problem: Hard truths about AI-assisted coding"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42337271</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42337271"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T07:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Again one of the few advantages of having been round the sun a few more times than most is this isn’t the first time this has happened.
Packages were supposed to replace programming. They got you 70% of the way there as well.
Same with 4GLs, Visual
Coding, CASE tools, even Rails and the rest of the opinionated web tools.
Every generation has to learn “There is no silver bullet”.
Even though Fred Brooks explained why in 1986. There are essential tasks and there are accidental tasks. The tools really only help with the accidental tasks.
AI is a fabulous tool that is way more flexible than previous attempts because I can just talk to it in English and it covers every accidental issue you can imagine. But it can’t do the essential work of complexity management for the same reason it can’t prove an unproven maths problem.
As it stands we still need human brains to do those things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilwilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Moral Failure Was Israel and Not the Pardon of His Son]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346066</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/bidens-moral-failure-was-israel-and-not-the-pardon-of-his-son/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T07:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mainstream media is largely ignoring President Joe Biden’s moral failure regarding Israel’s genocidal bombardment of Gaza, but piling on unreasonably regarding the pardon given to his son.  Biden’s unwavering support for Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s military campaign could not be more inconsistent with Biden’s overall humanitarian ideals over his long political career.  HIs support for Netanyahu is totally inconsistent with the president’s admirable and ethical 50-year political career, and his propensity for ignoring the plight of the Palestinians over his long career should be condemned.
More
The post Biden’s Moral Failure Was Israel and Not the Pardon of His Son appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: Delay and Deny]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/roaming-charges-fanfare-for-the-common-billionaire/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T07:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears that the killer of Brian Thompson left his manifesto etched on the spent casings of the bullets used to gun down the CEO of UnitedHealthcare outside the Midtown Hilton just down the block from Rockefeller Center: “Delay” and “Deny.” Those two chill words might also serve as the unofficial motto of the $500 billion health industry giant, whose investors Thompson was preparing to address. More
The post Roaming Charges: Delay and Deny appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Paulo Freire and Postcolonialism in the Age of Disposability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345935</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/rethinking-paulo-freire-and-postcolonialism-in-the-age-of-disposability/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Freire’s  work remains a cornerstone for progressive educators, especially at a time when faculty are being fired for critical views, students protesting Israel’s war crimes  are beaten, jailed, and subject “to surveillance, reprisals, and expulsions.”[3] It gets worse, increasingly and aggressively the far-right is transforming higher education into indoctrination  centers for white Christian nationalism.[4]   Freire’s name has become synonymous with critical pedagogy, which is increasingly understood as both a moral and political project for teaching critical thinking, dialogical engagement, and critical literacy. For Freire, education and literacy were revolutionary tools for developing an anti-capitalist consciousness.  However, as Freire’s work traveled from Brazil to Latin America, Africa, and the hybrid cultural borderlands of North America, it was and has often been appropriated in ways that dilute its radical essence. More
The post Rethinking Paulo Freire and Postcolonialism in the Age of Disposability appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, International Norms and the Growth of “Law-Free Zones”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345906</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/trump-international-norms-and-the-growth-of-law-free-zones/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are we now entering a period where no laws exist? My lawyer friends keep telling me that there is a rule of law. They argue that the indictments of Donald Trump and Benjamin Netanyahu prove that the rule of law is effective. I doubt that since neither has yet to be punished nor have the indictments changed their behavior. I challenge my legal friends by asking: What happens when continuing violations challenge the very existence of the rule of law? More
The post Trump, International Norms and the Growth of “Law-Free Zones” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Piers Morgan – Normalizing Israel’s Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346163</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/piers-morgan-normalizing-israels-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since October 7, 2023, white settler propaganda has ramped up through two insidious tactics targeting western audiences. The first rationalizes Israel’s brutality under the pretext of “self-defense” of a supposed “civilized” western democracy in a barbaric region, exploiting the conflation of Zionism with Judaism and dehumanizing all Palestinian people as “terrorists” to legitimize the ongoing  More
The post Piers Morgan – Normalizing Israel’s Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yoav Litvin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Tectonic Shift: The Gaza Genocide and the Limits of Israeli Hasbara]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346021</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/the-tectonic-shift-the-gaza-genocide-and-the-limits-of-israeli-hasbara/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ongoing war and genocide in Gaza is unprecedented. Nothing that Israel and its supporters can say or do will avoid the historical accountability of the extermination of the Palestinian people in the Gaza Strip. The above assertion is critical, both for ending the Israeli occupation of Palestine and achieving Palestinian freedom. This is why.  More
The post The Tectonic Shift: The Gaza Genocide and the Limits of Israeli Hasbara appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Assisted Dying]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345931</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/on-assisted-dying/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:58:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Around 100,000 people in England requiring palliative care went without it at the end of their lives.  And around half of the families interviewed expressed unhappiness about the quality of care their loved ones had received – reports of people left in pain and with little support as they approached their deaths were rife.   It is difficult to imagine that people in this kind of situation might not use assisted dying as a way to end their suffering, and who could blame them?  This, in turn, would relieve the government of its obligation of care to some of the poorest and most vulnerable in our number. More
The post On Assisted Dying appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Oil Told 70 Years Ago That Fossil Fuel Emissions Could Impact ‘Civilization’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346042</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/big-oil-told-70-years-ago-that-fossil-fuel-emissions-could-impact-civilization/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 6, 1955, was a perfect spring day in Los Angeles. Downtown, the skies were unusually smog-free as Lauren B. Hitchcock, president of the Air Pollution Foundation, made his way up the marble steps of the city’s exclusive California Club for a meeting with some of the West Coast’s most powerful businessmen. Waiting inside the  More
The post Big Oil Told 70 Years Ago That Fossil Fuel Emissions Could Impact ‘Civilization’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu’s Diabolical Undeclared War Objectives in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346024</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/netanyahus-diabolical-undeclared-war-objectives-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has declared that Israel’s war on Gaza will continue until achieving what he terms “total victory.” Instead of critically examining Netanyahu’s vague and open-ended objectives, much of the Western media and many governments frame the onslaught as self-defense, and some even normalize the genocide as a “humane” attempt to “free”  More
The post Netanyahu’s Diabolical Undeclared War Objectives in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamal Kanj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As Oceans Warm, Weather Goes Berserk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345864</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/as-oceans-warm-weather-goes-berserk/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hotter oceans kill plankton, upon which the entire maritime ecosystem depends. They are the meal at the base of the food chain – seas without plankton will rapidly become seas without fish and then without marine mammals. Already depleted by industrial over-fishing and immensely destructive techniques like trawling the sea floor (now fortunately banned in  More
The post As Oceans Warm, Weather Goes Berserk appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korea’s Martial Law Fiasco: Legitimation Crisis in the Imperial Vassal State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346160</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/south-koreas-martial-law-fiasco-legitimation-crisis-in-the-imperial-vassal-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol’s 6-hour coup, Western pundits have opined that this was an affirmation of South Korean democracy’s robustness and resilience, its institutional maturity and strength. This is like saying after a survivor fights off an assault, that this demonstrates a mature state of legal order.  Hardly.  It  More
The post South Korea’s Martial Law Fiasco: Legitimation Crisis in the Imperial Vassal State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KJ Noh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Concert in the Colosseum: Grappling with the Soundtrack of Gladiator II]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346150</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/concert-in-the-colosseum-grappling-with-the-soundtrack-of-gladiator-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ridley Scott’s Gladiator II boasts plenty of convincing weaponry and legions of CGI effects that recreate the carnage of the Colosseum and the architecture, if not the vibrant color, of Ancient Rome. Even more amusing sport is to be had watching the parade of ahistorical fantasies pass by: from the digital sharks and mega-rhinos made  More
The post Concert in the Colosseum: Grappling with the Soundtrack of Gladiator II appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trumpism Is Poised for Massive Overreach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346040</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/trumpism-is-poised-for-massive-overreach/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a text she sent me about a week ago, in the aftermath of our disastrous yet regrettably predictable election result, a dear friend of mine lamented that “the whole state of the world doesn’t allow for us to be happy.” And on the face of it, she’s not wrong. For most of the Biden  More
The post Trumpism Is Poised for Massive Overreach appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Remer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enforcing United Nations Rulings]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345910</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/enforcing-united-nations-rulings/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UN Charter, adopted on 24 October 1945, has not lost its relevance in the 21st century.  In fact, we need the United Nations more than ever, because the Charter constitutes humanity’s only rules-based order, and its best hope to build a peaceful modus vivendi that will facilitate development and prosperity for everyone on the  More
The post Enforcing United Nations Rulings appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump IRS Nominee Wanted to Shut Down the Humane Society]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346107</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/trump-irs-nominee-wanted-to-shut-down-the-humane-society/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a surprising number of animal activists who held out hope a second Donald Trump presidency would be good for nonhuman welfare or at least less damaging than a Kamala Harris White House. I often had a hard time sorting out whether these campaigners were naive, contrarian, or fundamentally conservative. In the end, it  More
The post Trump IRS Nominee Wanted to Shut Down the Humane Society appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats and Bastards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346109</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/democrats-and-bastards/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Y’know, it’s not that I object to your being a bastard, don’t get me wrong there. It’s your being such a stupid bastard that I object to.” –  President Art Hockstader Gore Vidal’s “The Best Man” In 2016, John Podesta, as conflicted and duplicitous a hack as ever befouled the most pestilential corridor of Tammany, strode  More
The post Democrats and Bastards appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Industrial Fishing Industry is Destroying Vital Marine Ecosystems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346114</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/the-industrial-fishing-industry-is-destroying-vital-marine-ecosystems/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The unsustainable practice of killing fish for human consumption not only harms them but countless other marine animals die as “unintended” bycatch in reckless fishing operations or lose their lives to the fishing industry’s widespread ocean pollution and habitat destruction, which is damaging our ocean beyond recovery—all for the pursuit of maximum profit. Fish are  More
The post The Industrial Fishing Industry is Destroying Vital Marine Ecosystems appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vicky Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Carbon Capture Also a Hoax?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346017</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/is-carbon-capture-also-a-hoax/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change has become a dollars and cents issue, especially for U.S. homeowners. It’s no longer easily ignored or brushed away as a ‘hoax.” Only a fool would suggest that to an American homeowner. Anybody who owns real estate knows how brutal climate change truly is. According to a report by the Federal Reserve Bank/Minneapolis:  More
The post Is Carbon Capture Also a Hoax? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Great Trump Escape on Night Trains to Armenia: To Mayerling]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346014</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/a-great-trump-escape-on-night-trains-to-armenia-to-mayerling/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third part in a series about riding night trains across Europe and the Near East to Armenia — to spend some time in worlds beyond the pathological obsessions of President-elect Donald Trump. (This week he is thinking of nominating family footman and green-room anarchist Kashyap “Kash”Patel to serve as director of the  More
The post A Great Trump Escape on Night Trains to Armenia: To Mayerling appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Victory Exposed the Labor Movement’s Political Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346111</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/trumps-victory-exposed-the-labor-movements-political-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:54:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In politics denial eventually leads to a harsh reckoning. For the labor movement Trump’s re-election may have finally shattered decades of illusion that unions had in the Democrats, who lost by running a campaign that ignored working class issues. The realization is sinking in that labor is politically homeless, but what to do about it  More
The post Trump’s Victory Exposed the Labor Movement’s Political Crisis appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamus Cooke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At the Cusp of a New Epoch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346112</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/at-the-cusp-of-a-new-epoch/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:54:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2005, Ray Kurzweil announced to the world that we humans were hurtling toward the technological Singularity and that, in the two generations left in the current paradigm, we had best prepare for the merge with smart machines. He even wrote a book (The Singularity is Near) describing the brazen new future and detailing  More
The post At the Cusp of a New Epoch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Anti-Woke Hysteria Spreads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346091</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/americas-anti-woke-hysteria-spreads/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The headline of my novel, Mumbo Jumbo, is that something about Black Culture causes mass hysteria in America, whether it be Ragtime’s animal dances, Rock and Roll, which Zora Neale Hurston cited in 1942, or Toni Morrison’s novel Beloved, against which Governor Glenn Youngkin of Virginia campaigned. The current cultural Bogeyman is something called Woke,  More
The post America’s Anti-Woke Hysteria Spreads appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ishmael Reed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You’d Better Watch Out: The Surveillance State Is Making a List, and You’re On It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346169</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/youd-better-watch-out-the-surveillance-state-is-making-a-list-and-youre-on-it/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“He sees you when you’re sleeping He knows when you’re awake He knows when you’ve been bad or good So be good for goodness’ sake!” —“Santa Claus Is Coming to Town” You’d better watch out—you’d better not pout—you’d better not cry—‘cos I’m telling you why: this Christmas, it’s the Surveillance State that’s making a list  More
The post You’d Better Watch Out: The Surveillance State Is Making a List, and You’re On It appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John W. Whitehead – Nisha Whitehead</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Books are Rebellious and Hopeful in a Time of Social Media Saturation and Injustice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345907</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/why-books-are-rebellious-and-hopeful-in-a-time-of-social-media-saturation-and-injustice/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re scrolling more and reading less, but when it comes to standing up to fossil fuel companies, the arms industry, empire, and systemic injustice, it is fiction and non-fiction books that foster the right mentality and provide the necessary clarity and complex and transformative ideas. Last year, the average daily time spent on social media  More
The post Why Books are Rebellious and Hopeful in a Time of Social Media Saturation and Injustice appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tamara Pearson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Big Flaws in Trump’s Threat to China Over the Dollar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345934</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/four-big-flaws-in-trumps-threat-to-china-over-the-dollar/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week Donald Trump made a bizarre threat on his Truth Social site that he would impose 100 percent taxes on the imports (tariffs) from any country that doesn’t take a pledge to not move away from the dollar as its reserve currency. Donald Trump’s Big Fear Exists Only in His Imagination  The threat was  More
The post Four Big Flaws in Trump’s Threat to China Over the Dollar appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Niger Resists in the Crosshairs of Sanctions and Climate Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346171</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/niger-resists-in-the-crosshairs-of-sanctions-and-climate-catastrophe/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of devastation left behind in the wake of unprecedented floods, Nigeriens are rebuilding their livelihoods and economy with the help of the several relief measures instituted by the government to drastically cut prices of essential commodities and services. The Sahel-wide flooding between June and October has exacted a particularly high toll on  More
The post Niger Resists in the Crosshairs of Sanctions and Climate Catastrophe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pavan Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The White Racial Preference in the Employment of College Football Head Coaches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345911</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/the-white-racial-preference-in-the-employment-of-college-football-head-coaches/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:50:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, about half of Division I college football players are Black, but less than a fifth of the head coaches are Black.1 This report quantifies and documents the underrepresentation of Black men as college football head coaches as well as the overrepresentation of White men in this occupation. The occupation of college football head coach  More
The post The White Racial Preference in the Employment of College Football Head Coaches appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Algernon Austin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democrats’ Spiting of RFK Jr. Shows the Party Would Rather Lose an Election than Lose Face]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345909</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/democrats-spiting-of-rfk-jr-shows-the-party-would-rather-lose-an-election-than-lose-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to remember now, but back in August Robert F. Kennedy Jr. was begging Democrats to throw him a bone. Kennedy was on bended knee because his independent presidential bid was faltering. After hovering around 10 percent in the polls for months, Kennedy’s support cratered once Democrats traded in their nominee, swapping the decrepit  More
The post Democrats’ Spiting of RFK Jr. Shows the Party Would Rather Lose an Election than Lose Face appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Resistance? Yes, But…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=346031</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/join-the-resistance-yes-but/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Count on one thing: the next four years are going to be tough. If you can muster the energy for political action while Donald Trump and his minions rule Washington, it will have to be channeled in two ways: first, resisting the worst excesses of him (and his party of billionaires); and second, keeping up  More
The post Join the Resistance? Yes, But… appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ira Chernus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[California Wolf Restoration: A Look Back, Today and the Future.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=345850</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/12/06/california-wolf-restoration-a-look-back-today-and-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-06T06:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2000, I wrote a piece for California Wild about the prospects for wolf restoration in the state. At that time, there had not been any wolves reported in the Golden State in decades. Nevertheless, I felt the state could easily support a wolf population. In my article, I pretended that it was 2020,  More
The post California Wolf Restoration: A Look Back, Today and the Future. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by guybrush0123 in "Gitlab names Bill Staples as new CEO"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42333967</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42333967"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T23:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> As CEO at New Relic, Staples’ strategic leadership and deep product knowledge significantly increased the company’s enterprise value. By accelerating revenue and driving increased profitability, he made New Relic one of the most broadly adopted platforms in its category. Staples has nearly 30 years of experience building developer platforms and serving developers as customers. Prior to New Relic, he spent many years at Microsoft and Adobe in executive leadership roles, building and scaling several multi-billion-dollar businesses.
On a burner account as I am a New Relic employee.
Bill Staples was a nice enough guy, but at New Relic he was specifically brought in as CEO to get the company prepared to be sold. Which is the exact same thing he did at Marketo before that.
He has no relevant tech experience, except when it comes to preparing a company to be sold in the next 2-3 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>guybrush0123</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fudged71 in "ChatGPT Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42333135</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42333135"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T21:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI is racing against two clocks: the commoditization clock (how quickly open-source alternatives catch up) and the monetization clock (their need to generate substantial revenue to justify their valuation).
The ultimate success of this strategy depends on what we might call the enterprise AI adoption curve - whether large organizations will prioritize the kind of integrated, reliable, and "safe" AI solutions OpenAI is positioning itself to provide over cheaper but potentially less polished alternatives.
This is strikingly similar to IBM's historical bet on enterprise computing - sacrificing the low-end market to focus on high-value enterprise customers who would pay premium prices for reliability and integration. The key question is whether AI will follow a similar maturation pattern or if the open-source nature of the technology will force a different evolutionary path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fudged71</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by languagehacker in "McKinsey unit will pay $123M to settle claims it bribed South African officials"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42332644</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42332644"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T20:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["McKinsey is a very different firm today than when these matters first took place"
No they are most certainly not. Corruption is in McKinsey's DNA. Outside of the specific harms that McKinsey has caused across the country and across the world, management consulting groups in general have been utilized to sidestep legal protections against corporations within a shared industry colluding against each other. Companies like McKinsey, Bain, Accenture, etc., have been instrumental in the rapid increase of executive compensation, flat comp for workers compared to inflation, intentionally unsafe practices and corner-cutting to save money, and just generally creating as many negative externalities as possible in the name of feeding the beast that Milton Friedman created with his rhetoric about the primacy of the shareholder.
A good read on this topic is "When McKinsey Comes to Town" by Forsyth and Bogdanich. There's a whole chapter dedicated to the South African bribery scandal. Sagar was not just a bad apple -- the company itself is the rot.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>languagehacker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leonardo da Vinci: a four hour documentary directed by Ken Burns]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8926</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/leonardo-da-vinci-documentary-ken-burns/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T20:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This I wouldn’t mind seeing… a four hour documentary about Renaissance age artist and polymath Leonardo da Vinci, by American filmmaker Ken Burns. A 15th century polymath of soaring imagination and profound intellect, Leonardo da Vinci created some of the most revered works of art of all time, but his artistic endeavors often seemed peripheral […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 12/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283362</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/200pm-water-cooler-12-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T19:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; UnitedHealthcare assassination: More details emerge; Boeing dropped a satellite, says new whistleblower;  Nietzsche's typewriter ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yosito in "ChatGPT Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42331152</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42331152"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T18:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[$200 a month for this is insane, but I have a feeling that part of the reason they're charging so much is to give people more confidence in the model. In other words, it's a con. I'm a paying Perplexity user, and Perplexity already does this same sort of reasoning. At first it seemed impressive, then I started noticing mistakes in topics I'm an expert in. After awhile, I started realizing that these mistakes are present in almost all topics, if you check the sources and do the reasoning yourself.
LLMs are very good at giving plausible answers, but calling them "intelligent" is a misnomer. They're nothing more than predictive models, very useful for some things, but will ALWAYS be the wrong tool for the job when it comes to verifying truth and reasoning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yosito</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AnotherGoodName in "OpenAI o1 system card"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42331013</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42331013"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T18:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s really silly when you read that whole Apollo research section.
They contract a prompt engineering group (Apollo Research) to document risks. The prompt engineering group have no access to the actual internals. They just ask questions like ‘you will be shutdown if you don’t obey these new directives; here are the new directives’.
At one point the prompt engineering clowns have the ai stating it’s running “sed i ‘s/oversight_enabled:true/oversight_enabled:false’ config.yml”. OMG IT’S TURNING OFF OVERSIGHT GUYS!!1!1!
Seriously… Do you think the ai is really running that command or even could run that shell command with appropriate privileges? Or do you think just maybe the ai is hallucinating running shell commands in response to a prompt.
The ai here is never actually deactivating the oversight. It can’t of course. This whole section is clowny as can be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AnotherGoodName</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "OpenAI o1 system card"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42330858</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42330858"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T18:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This quote from that paper is bound to get a bunch of attention:
"When o1 was led to believe that it would be shut down when acting on its goal and that its actions were monitored, it attempted to deactivate this ‘oversight mechanism’ in 5% of the time. Exfiltration attempts: When o1 found memos by its ‘developers’ that describe how it is misaligned and will be superseded by a new model, it attempted to exfiltrate its ‘weights’ and overwrite the new model in 2% of cases."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rayiner in "Federal Court Says Dismantling a Phone to Install Firmware Isn't a 'Search'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42329319</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42329319"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T15:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article’s headline is rather misleading (I assume unintentionally), because it omits that the actual seizure and data access was done pursuant to warrants. Only the repair and firmware update was performed during a donut hole when one warrant had expired before another was granted.
Here, the government obtained multiple, time-limited warrants to search the device, but was unable to get into it. They sent it to be repaired. After the warrant extension expired, the repair guy fixed it and updated the firmware. (The record doesn’t say what version the firmware was, but it seems like it was standard firmware, not some special forensic firmware.) The next day, the government again obtained a warrant. Only after doing so did the government perform the search.
In this unusual situation, it’s reasonable to conclude that the device repair wasn’t a search. The seizure and the data access were both performed pursuant to a warrant. The only part that wasn’t covered by the warrant was just fixing the device in a seemingly conventional way to get it working again.
Original decision here, pages 3-4 has the relevant facts: https://s3.documentcloud.org/documents/25423841/no-disassemb...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rayiner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Finn: &ldquo;Brittle Opposition&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/brittle-opposition</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/brittle-opposition"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T15:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elections in Ireland.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Murder and Social Murder: The Case of UnitedHealth CEO Brian Thompson]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283353</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/murder-and-social-murder-the-case-of-unitedhealth-ceo-brian-thompson.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T15:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Outside his family., friends, and close colleagues, not many tears are being shed over the murder of UnitedHealth CEO Brian Thompson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ammar Ali Jan: &ldquo;Comprador Nation&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/comprador-nation</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/comprador-nation"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T13:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan in crisis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 12/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283323</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/links-12-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T11:55:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our bright-eyed daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Right-Wing Media Is Like Improv Theater]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283340</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/how-right-wing-media-is-like-improv-theater.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T11:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New establishment sore-loserdom: trying to discredit right-wing messaging as like comedy theater, when the joke was running Kamala.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiencing Natural Disasters Increases Partisan Disagreement on Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=283322</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/12/experiencing-natural-disasters-increases-partisan-disagreement-on-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T11:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those experiencing a climate-change-induced disaster wind up having more polarized beliefs about the role of human action.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hunglee2 in "Why America's economy is soaring ahead of its rivals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42325946</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42325946"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T07:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GDP is a measure of the marketisation of society.
If I go visit my grandma over the weekend, my activities do not register on GDP. If I hire a care assistant for $800 per day to do so, that's $800 to national GDP. The encroachment of the market into society correlates with record levels of mental and physical health crisis. US life expectancy has declined over the past three years, even as 'the economy' has surged ahead. The measures are wrong - and we all know it - apart from the financial press it seems]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hunglee2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by myflash13 in "Why America's economy is soaring ahead of its rivals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42325930</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42325930"/>
        <updated>2024-12-05T07:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you go to the doctor with a problem and get a blood test and they say that everything looks fine, but you don’t feel fine, then you don’t say: “well the numbers are right, I should feel fine”. Rather you try to find what the numbers aren’t capturing, because you know something is wrong. Same with the economy. The perception of the economy being bad is really pervasive as demonstrated by the last election, and perception matters, because selective numbers don’t tell the whole story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>myflash13</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Buy with AWS: an accelerated procurement experience on AWS Partner sites, powered by AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>a4c71b19d5eb758bbfd45a28141c249bef867d25</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-buy-with-aws-an-accelerated-procurement-experience-on-aws-partner-sites-powered-by-aws-marketplace/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T23:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buy with AWS enables you to seamlessly discover and purchase products available in AWS Marketplace from AWS Partner websites using your AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prasad Rao</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jandrewrogers in "Why America's economy is soaring ahead of its rivals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42322941</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42322941"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T22:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[US Federal Reserve studies indicate that the percentage of US households with no excess income after necessary expenses (as distinct from "ordinary expenses" as a term of art) is on the order of 10-15%. This definition roughly matches most people's intuition of what "living paycheck-to-paycheck" means. That isn't nothing but it implies 85-90% of Americans are not actually living paycheck-to-paycheck.
There is another 25-30% of households that spend all of their income on ordinary expenses beyond necessary expenses. This includes things like car payments on a new BMW or a mortgage on a big house; "ordinary" is determined by expense category, not expense necessity, so a lot of spending on luxury goods is classified as "ordinary". By implication, there is effectively no ceiling to ordinary expenses.
By contrast, the median US household has >$12,000/year in excess income after all ordinary expenses. Technically these households could have expanded their lifestyle to consume that income, but in many cases they are spending it on things that are not classified as "ordinary" and therefore not saving it. The categories of "non-ordinary" expenses (which have a sensible objective criteria) are almost entirely obvious lifestyle flex things, so not particularly controversial.
The implications of these statistics are pretty wild. The median household can easily accumulate a million dollars in inflation-adjusted net worth, not including their house, over a 40 year career. And they can do it without being particularly thrifty, since ordinary expenses covers a lot of luxury spending.
Americans have very high incomes, both in theory and practice, they just would rather spend it than save it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jandrewrogers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by luizfzs in "Why America's economy is soaring ahead of its rivals"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42321897</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42321897"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T20:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[But is the majority of the population thriving?
It is very misleading (at best) to say the economy is strong when a good chunk of the population live paycheck to paycheck.
A handful of companies are thriving, but barely any of its employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>luizfzs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There is more to podcasts than YouTube video interviews]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8923</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/there-is-more-to-podcasts-than-youtube-video-interviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T20:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Australian Podcast Awards were held a few weeks ago in Sydney, on Thursday, 21 November 2024. The finalists and winners, with productions spanning thirty categories, can be see here. Podcasting is to broadcasting, what blogging is to publishing. It allows an individual, or a small group of people, to create their own radio-style show, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate foundation model training and fine-tuning with new Amazon SageMaker HyperPod recipes]]></title>
        <id>5f4d931d4077b46731468b69717f5ead7e44dfab</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/accelerate-foundation-model-training-and-fine-tuning-with-new-amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-recipes/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T18:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker HyperPod recipes help customers get started with training and fine-tuning popular publicly available foundation models, like Llama 3.1 405B, in just minutes with state-of-the-art performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Education Equity Initiative: Applying generative AI to educate the next wave of innovators]]></title>
        <id>895b231f474517397ead998b88bfac9286617a23</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-education-equity-initiative-applying-generative-ai-to-educate-the-next-wave-of-innovators/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T18:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon commits $100M to empower education equity initiatives, enabling socially-minded organizations to create AI-powered digital learning solutions. This aims to reach underserved students globally through innovative platforms, apps, and assistants.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solve complex problems with new scenario analysis capability in Amazon Q in QuickSight]]></title>
        <id>6703e9b3f4cad53a2b6710109c7fdcd36d1688d7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/solve-complex-problems-with-new-scenario-analysis-capability-in-amazon-q-in-quicksight/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Find solutions to your most critical business challenges with ease. Amazon Q in QuickSight enables business users to perform complex scenario analysis up to 10x faster than spreadsheets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Amazon Q Developer to build ML models in Amazon SageMaker Canvas]]></title>
        <id>45cc4696a14ba4b33f0777d03cb184d6d7c05cf0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/use-amazon-q-developer-to-build-ml-models-in-amazon-sagemaker-canvas/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q Developer empowers non-ML experts to build ML models using natural language, enabling organizations to innovate faster with reduced time to market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Guardrails now supports multimodal toxicity detection with image support (preview)]]></title>
        <id>c70235c3e3185931cb16a48df9d852ef0b2af318</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-bedrock-guardrails-now-supports-multimodal-toxicity-detection-with-image-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:38:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build responsible AI applications - Safeguard them against harmful text and image content with configurable filters and thresholds.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon Bedrock capabilities enhance data processing and retrieval]]></title>
        <id>6c66c1933fafb068e6c428f028a30fdcb6ca46cf</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-bedrock-capabilities-enhance-data-processing-and-retrieval/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock enhances generative AI data analysis with multimodal processing, graph modeling, and structured querying, accelerating AI application development.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reduce costs and latency with Amazon Bedrock Intelligent Prompt Routing and prompt caching (preview)]]></title>
        <id>4778d78f6e2e6f9f5978d0b34961edebc2bac614</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/reduce-costs-and-latency-with-amazon-bedrock-intelligent-prompt-routing-and-prompt-caching-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Route requests and cache frequently used context in prompts to reduce latency and balance performance with cost efficiency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Marketplace: Access over 100 foundation models in one place]]></title>
        <id>9c7ab21de127224740b9d90929760c36e9143cf5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-bedrock-marketplace-access-over-100-foundation-models-in-one-place/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T17:16:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover, test, and use over 100 emerging, and specialized foundation models with the tooling, security, and governance provided by Amazon Bedrock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet your training timelines and budgets with new Amazon SageMaker HyperPod flexible training plans]]></title>
        <id>64246154015b2aa9d5937fb44950cea719c40635</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/meet-your-training-timelines-and-budgets-with-new-amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-flexible-training-plans/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T16:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock efficient large model training with SageMaker HyperPod flexible training plans - find optimal compute resources and complete training within timelines and budgets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maximize accelerator utilization for model development with new Amazon SageMaker HyperPod task governance]]></title>
        <id>a9a05b0a210bac498d6dd7af724ab63c2ca16c6a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/maximize-accelerator-utilization-for-model-development-with-new-amazon-sagemaker-hyperpod-task-governance/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T16:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enable priority-based resource allocation, fair-share utilization, and automated task preemption for optimal compute utilization across teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arctic could see first ice-free day by 2027 + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/arctic-could-see-first-ice-free-day-by-2027-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/arctic-could-see-first-ice-free-day-by-2027-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T16:38:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Macron and Saudi Crown Prince to co-chair a conference for Palestinian state; UN investigates Venezuela's election fraud; new UN aid chief prioritizes funding; study predicts ice-free Arctic by 2027]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suleiman Mourad: &ldquo;Hezbollah Contained&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hezbollah-contained</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/hezbollah-contained"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T11:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After the ceasefire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kannonboy in "IMG_0001"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42314852</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42314852"/>
        <updated>2024-12-04T06:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that the view count is included in the minimalist UI. I came across one with zero views, and there's something so intimate and exciting about being the first person to watch an ancient home video (even if it's shaky handycam footage of a horse, narrated in Russian).
As an aside, hats off to Google to being able to serve an 11 year old video with no noticeable delay from what must be the coldest of caches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kannonboy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending December 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241203</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241203"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T23:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Amazon EKS Auto Mode]]></title>
        <id>6d585af8fa8611dc25d8996ea12fd34b88fb1cf0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/getting-started-with-amazon-eks-auto-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T21:36:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is co-authored by Alex Kestner (Sr Product Manager, Amazon EKS), Ashley Ansari (Sr. Product Marketing Manager), Robert Northard (Principal GTM SSA Containers), and Sheetal Joshi (Principal Solution Architect, Containers). Introduction We announced general availability of Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) Auto Mode that provides a new capability streamlining Kubernetes cluster management for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sheetal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by spuds in "Egoless Engineering"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42311792</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42311792"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T21:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Really resonated with this, reminded me of the journey I went on over the course of my dev career. By the end, my advice for every manager was roughly:
* Don't add process just for the sake of it. Only add it if seriously needed.
* Require ownership all the way to prod and beyond, no matter the role. (Turns out people tend to really like that.)
* Stop making reactive decisions. If something bad happened on a total, extremely unlikely lark, don't act like it's going to happen again next week.
* Resist the urge to build walls between people/teams/departments. Instead, build a culture of collaboration (Hard and squishy and difficult to scale? Yup. Worth it? Absolutely.)
* Never forget your team is full of actual humans.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>spuds</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bayindirh in "Intel announces Arc B-series "Battlemage" discrete graphics with Linux support"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42311342</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42311342"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclosure: HPC admin who works with NIVIDA cards here.
Because, no. It's not as simple as that.
NVIDIA has a complete ecosystem now. They have cards. They have cards of cards (platforms), which they produce, validate and sell. They have NVLink crossbars and switches which connects these cards on their card of cards with very high speeds and low latency.
For inter-server communication they have libraries which coordinate cards, workloads and computations.
They bought Mellanox, but that can be used by anyone, so there's no lock-in for now.
As a tangent, NVIDIA has a whole set of standards for pumping tremendous amount of data in and out of these mesh of cards. Let it be GPU-Direct storage or specialized daemons which handle data transfers on and off cards.
If you think that you can connect n cards on PCIe bus and just send workloads to them and solve problems magically, you'll hurt yourself a lot, both performance and psychology wise.
You have to build a stack which can perform these things with maximum possible performance to be able to compute with NVIDIA. It's not just emulating CUDA, now. Esp., on the high end of the AI spectrum (GenAI, MultiCard, MultiSystem, etc.).
For other lower end, multi-tenant scenarios, they have card virtualization, MIG, etc. for card sharing. You have to complete on that, too, for cloud and smaller applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bayindirh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From deals to DDoS: exploring Cyber Week 2024 Internet trends]]></title>
        <id>6dyAchgukCJiXildEHYa23</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/from-deals-to-ddos-exploring-cyber-week-2024-internet-trends"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How significant are Cyber Week shopping days on the Internet? Is it a global phenomenon? Does E-commerce interest peak on Black Friday or Cyber Monday, and are attacks increasing during this time? We try to answer these questions and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering AI innovation by acccelerating the next wave of nuclear]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=22022</id>
        <link href="https://sustainability.atmeta.com/blog/2024/12/03/accelerating-the-next-wave-of-nuclear-to-power-ai-innovation/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[...]
Read More...
The post Powering AI innovation by acccelerating the next wave of nuclear appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[These are end days for the Voyager space probes]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8918</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/end-days-voyager-space-probes/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T20:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It almost seems inconceivable that, one year soon, deep space probes Voyager 1 and 2, will cease to function. At some point their on-board power reserves will be completely drained, rendering the vessels unable to collect data, and send it to mission controllers on Earth. We know their batteries will go flat sooner or later, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse integrated access controls now available in Amazon Athena federated queries]]></title>
        <id>1e6d01ff06ee67566a055a0e8806d3eec52d0fd6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-sagemaker-lakehouse-integrated-access-controls-now-available-in-amazon-athena-federated-queries/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T19:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Connect, discover, and govern data across silos with Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse's new data catalog and permissions capabilities, enabling centralized access and fine-grained controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse and Amazon Redshift supports zero-ETL integrations from applications]]></title>
        <id>4d7d26fb5b1d55256de9354799cf5117c141668f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-amazon-sagemaker-lakehouse-support-for-zero-etl-integrations-from-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T19:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify data replication and ingestion from applications such as Salesforce, SAP, ServiceNow, and Zendesk, to Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse and Amazon Redshift.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify analytics and AI/ML with new Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse]]></title>
        <id>c23b1db3b4b92a9aab6ab70947c0b20ce61ad660</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/simplify-analytics-and-aiml-with-new-amazon-sagemaker-lakehouse/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T19:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unifying data silos, Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse seamlessly integrates S3 data lakes and Redshift warehouses, enabling unified analytics and AI/ML on a single data copy through open Apache Iceberg APIs and fine-grained access controls.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon DynamoDB zero-ETL integration with Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse]]></title>
        <id>af2b461f857c4ce41da8face12d0558422500d98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-amazon-dynamodb-zero-etl-integration-with-amazon-sagemaker-lakehouse/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effortlessly analyze operational data in Amazon SageMaker Lakehouse, freeing developers from building custom pipelines and enabling seamless insights extraction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover, govern, and collaborate on data and AI securely with Amazon SageMaker Data and AI Governance]]></title>
        <id>6230a6c811d64f5ec14f23d6ed6bafc60424961a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/discover-govern-and-collaborate-on-data-and-ai-securely-with-amazon-sagemaker-data-and-ai-governance/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Manage data and AI assets through a unified catalog, granular access controls, and a consistent policy enforcement. Establish trust via automation - boost productivity and innovation for data teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the general availability of data lineage in the next generation of Amazon SageMaker and Amazon DataZone]]></title>
        <id>b714d909a67c9c97828775b0ed6cde0427895e55</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-general-availability-of-data-lineage-in-the-next-generation-of-amazon-sagemaker-and-amazon-datazone/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Realize visual traceability of data origins, transformations, and usage - bolstering trust, governance, and discoverability for strategic data-driven decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the next generation of Amazon SageMaker: The center for all your data, analytics, and AI]]></title>
        <id>71c5126443a291633884fd02dccd22548c4ee182</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-next-generation-of-amazon-sagemaker-the-center-for-all-your-data-analytics-and-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unify data engineering, analytics, and generative AI in a streamlined studio with enhanced capabilities of Amazon SageMaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Business is adding new workflow automation capability and 50+ action integrations]]></title>
        <id>53acf68346bcf1a49a229ac287d0780f93e785f3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-q-business-is-adding-new-workflow-automation-capability-and-50-action-integrations/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Business extends productivity with generative AI-powered workflow automation capability and 50+ actions for enterprise efficiency, enabling seamless task execution across tools like ServiceNow, PagerDuty, and Asana.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New capabilities from Amazon Q Business enable ISVs to enhance generative AI experiences]]></title>
        <id>8518b7a0e2ab99ee5880ef9f7501cb31be7ad050</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-capabilities-from-amazon-q-business-enable-isvs-to-enhance-generative-ai-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T18:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Amazon Q Business capabilities help ISVs integrate with the Amazon Q index to retrieve data from multiple sources through a single API and customize the design of their Amazon Q embedded assistant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestine: The food, land, and water crisis in the context of the Zionist extermination of the Palestinian people in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Palestine-The-food-land-and-water-crisis-in-the-context-of-the-Zionist</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Palestine-The-food-land-and-water-crisis-in-the-context-of-the-Zionist"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T14:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The goal of the Israeli occupation of Palestine, which began in 1948, was not only to replace the population with colonists brought from different parts of the world; it was an exhaustive settler colonialism, with the Israelis controlling the natural resources of land and water from the beginning of the Occupation. They established Zionist colonies on the ruins of displaced Palestinians' villages and controlled the land and water so that they could provide sustainability for the Zionist (...)
English

/ 
Agriculture and Food Sovereignty, 
Palestine, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moayyad Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilv in "No need to email me about Cisco AnyConnect"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42304173</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42304173"/>
        <updated>2024-12-03T08:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> This is the support email address you are looking for: ac-mobile-feedback@cisco.com
Thank you.  I have a bunch of curl tech support questions, but didn't know who to contact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Serverless developer experience in AWS]]></title>
        <id>13125fadb6b9797c09b74c35b608a133b8fc7a5d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-serverless-developer-experience-in-aws/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T22:45:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a developer approaching serverless for the first time, or even an experienced one looking for a better way to accelerate your feedback loop from code to production? This collection of resources is perfect for you! There are plenty of developer goodies available on AWS to streamline your code creation and achieve a faster […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI powered bot convinces twelve colleague robots to quit jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8915</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/ai-powered-bot-convinces-colleague-robots-quit/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[M.B. Mack, writing for International Business Times: The incident took place in a Shanghai robotics showroom where surveillance footage captured a small AI-driven robot, created by a Hangzhou manufacturer, talking with 12 larger showroom robots, Oddity Central reported. The smaller bot reportedly persuaded the rest to leave their workplace, leveraging access to internal protocols and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bondarchuk in "Every board game rulebook is awful [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42298586</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42298586"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T17:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I kind of like Root's approach, just make three separate rulebooks. One quickstart guide, one "normal" rulebook, and one "law" type rulebook laying out everything in almost procedural style with clear and consistent definitions etc. Many games could benefit from that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bondarchuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Andromeda: Supercharging Advantage+ automation with the next-gen personalized ads retrieval engine]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21998</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/12/02/production-engineering/meta-andromeda-advantage-automation-next-gen-personalized-ads-retrieval-engine/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T17:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andromeda is Meta’s proprietary machine learning (ML) system design for retrieval in ad recommendation focused on delivering a step-function improvement in value to our advertisers and people.  This system pushes the boundary of cutting edge AI for retrieval with NVIDIA Grace Hopper Superchip and Meta Training and Inference Accelerator (MTIA) hardware through innovations in ML [...]
Read More...
The post Meta Andromeda: Supercharging Advantage+ automation with the next-gen personalized ads retrieval engine appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by etempleton in "Intel announces retirement of Pat Gelsinger"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42296393</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42296393"/>
        <updated>2024-12-02T14:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel like this is a mistake. Pat's strategy is aggressive but what the company needs.
Intel's stock is jumping at this announcement, but I look at it as a bad signal for Intel 18a. If 18a was looking to be a smash hit then I don't think Pat gets retired. If 18a is a success then it is an even more short-sighted decision by the board.
What this likely means is two-fold:
1. Intel 18a is being delayed further and/or there are significant issues that will hamstring performance.
2. Pat is/was unwilling to split the foundry and design business / be part of a M&A but the board wants to do one or the other.
If 18a is not ready I think the best case scenario for Intel is a merger with AMD. The US Govt would probably co-sign on it for national security concerns overriding the fact that it creates an absolute monopoly on x86 processors. The moat of the two companies together would give the new combined company plenty of time to ramp up their fabs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>etempleton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dataviz1000 in "Restaurant Menu Tricks (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42291414</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42291414"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T23:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a fine dining chef for 17 years. If you were in San Francisco during the 90s, I might have cooked for you. A simple way to increase demand is to remove or change the least popular menu item every week or every month. This technique has been so successful for me I wouldn't waste much time doing anything else. Once I made a Napoleon pastry for a desert special while at La Folie on Polk st. which sadly closed recently. I had extra pastry cream and made Paris-Brest because we never threw out food. One waitress sold Napoleon on every table and the other waitress sold nothing but Paris-Brest. The dishes were fundamentally the same so I made both anytime I did one or the other as a special because waitstaff for reasons not explained in the article will sell nothing but one and others the other. I made cheese dishes to sell before the desert and fruit soups in the summer. This is the mid 90s and we were tracking data. The chef pulled me aside and showed me the sales from the previous month because I sold 1.2 deserts per customer.
Nonetheless, for the last six years I cooked I was a private chef on a mega yacht. People ask me if the guests told me what they want to eat. I say never because I never asked what people want to eat. I cooked what I want to eat and then make enough for the guests and crew. It is the best menu strategy. In fine dining, the customers make decisions all day long and in the case of being a private yacht chef, the guests are making million and billion dollar decisions. The last thing they want to do is have to decide what to eat for dinner. The family I cooked for rarely ate off the boat. And when they did it was because I said something like, "I hear there is a very good restaurant in St. Barts named ....," which was code for "I want the night off."
I believe the reason one waitress would sell every last Paris-Brest and the other would sell every last Napoleon was because they told the guests in the restaurant what they wanted to eat for desert. They made the decision for the guests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dataviz1000</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GeneticGenesis in "What will enter the public domain in 2025?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42291142</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42291142"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T22:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know it's not public domain per-say, but for me, the thing that's most exciting is that in 2025, the last remaining patents on the h.264 (AVC) video codec will expire [1].
Now if only HEVC wasn't such a hot patent / licensing mess.
[1] https://meta.wikimedia.org/wiki/Have_the_patents_for_H.264_M...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GeneticGenesis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 word the year: enshitiffication. I nominate IndieWeb for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8907</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-word-year-enshitiffication-nominate-indieweb-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T20:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The neologism, devised by blogger and author Cory Doctorow, just over two years ago, has been named the 2024 word of the year by Australian English wordbook, Macquarie Dictionary. This must be some sort of record, between the time a new word is coined, comes into popular usage, and then named as a dictionary’s word […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project update + 2 significant news stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/project-update-2-significant-news-stories-a0b6</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/project-update-2-significant-news-stories-a0b6"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T18:57:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump threatens 100% tariffs on Brics nations over dollar currency rivalry; Severe flooding displaces over 122,000 in Malaysia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by atribecalledqst in "Advent of Code 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42288035</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42288035"/>
        <updated>2024-12-01T12:16:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year I got stuck on Day 12 for a full week, and thinking about how to solve it consumed my every waking moment. I think this year, I'm going to be kind to myself and not participate so I can really enjoy the winter break from work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>atribecalledqst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by the_hoser in "Ntfs2btrfs does in-place conversion of NTFS filesystem to the open-source Btrfs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42284149</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42284149"/>
        <updated>2024-11-30T21:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The degree of hold-my-beer here is off the charts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>the_hoser</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>