<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-06-25T01:36:51.966Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-06-25T01:36:51.966Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by suby in "Windows 11 is now enabling OneDrive folder backup without asking permission"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781691</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40781691"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T22:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This happened to me. I was wondering why my internet speeds were slow when I discovered that Microsoft was in the process of uploading my users directory, they had already uploaded almost two gigs when I realized. They also changed the path to these directories to something like C:\Users\name\OneDrive\Desktop\. Another poster in this thread claimed it's easy to reverse -- I disagree, it's a pain in the ass to track down the setting, and I shouldn't have to do this. When I did, it gave me an error for one of the directories and refuses to revert (documents?).
I don't like leaving negative or hyperbolic comments on HN, but this was enraging and unacceptable to me. It's hard to convey without coming off as unhinged. I only ever boot into Windows nowadays when I need to compile and test a Windows build of software. I understand Microsoft has built up good will through efforts like VS Code, but it's all undone because of things like this. I avoid MS products, they cannot be trusted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>suby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put your Palace Cinema wine glass in the cup-holder carefully]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7882</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/put-palace-cinema-wine-glass-cup-holder-carefully/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T21:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether they are a part of an on-going series of light-hearted clips by Australian cinema group Palace Cinemas, remains to be seen, but the two I’ve caught to date, on their Instagram page, have been pretty witty. The first is in response to the apparent problem of patrons nicking the cinema’s wine glasses. Why would […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025: 920 Pages of Irritable Mental Gestures, or a Blueprint for Fascism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273812</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/project-2025-920-pages-of-irritable-mental-gestures-or-a-blueprint-for-fascism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T20:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Litmus tests to see if Project 2025 is serious, and a close reading of its "Mandate for Leadership"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 6/24/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273822</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/200pm-water-cooler-6-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T18:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics and pandemics; many new Covid charts (New York and New England wastewater down; positivity up; New York hospitaliztation continues its weirdly steady rise);  Trump lawfare status; Supreme Court decisions and Thursday's debate ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping keep customers safe with leaked password notification]]></title>
        <id>6675c883a4598c000bd703c6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/helping-keep-customers-safe-with-leaked-password-notification"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:06:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help protect against account compromise via credential stuffing attacks, Cloudflare will notify dashboard users when we detect that a password was found in an external data breach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Garrett Galow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proactive scaling of Amazon ECS services using Amazon ECS Service Connect Metrics]]></title>
        <id>dddca191d6a2df5df6c28c233a33652b924833c9</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/proactive-scaling-of-amazon-ecs-services-using-amazon-ecs-service-connect-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This post discusses Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) Service Connect, a capability that provides a secure and scalable way to connect different Amazon ECS service deployments. This enables seamless communication between micro-services while reducing the operational overhead. It provides features such as service discovery, load balancing, and network traffic metrics. This post primarily […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Nalpet Ramakrishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging AI for efficient incident response]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21393</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/24/data-infrastructure/leveraging-ai-for-efficient-incident-response/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T16:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re sharing how we streamline system reliability investigations using a new AI-assisted root cause analysis system. The system uses a combination of heuristic-based retrieval and large language model-based ranking to speed up root cause identification during investigations. Our testing has shown this new system achieves 42% accuracy in identifying root causes for investigations at their [...]
Read More...
The post Leveraging AI for efficient incident response appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Claude 3.5 Sonnet in Amazon Bedrock, CodeCatalyst updates, SageMaker with MLflow, and more (June 24, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>7dacc08a7aef106cc0797e9788dead147aa616ac</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-claude-3-5-sonnet-in-amazon-bedrock-codecatalyst-updates-sagemaker-with-mlflow-and-more-june-24-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I had the opportunity to try the new Anthropic Claude 3.5 Sonnet model in Amazon Bedrock just before it launched, and I was really impressed by its speed and accuracy! It was also the week of AWS Summit Japan. JAWS-UG, a Japanese AWS user group, held various sessions with AWS Heroes and Community Builders at […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fanf2 in "Microfeatures I love in blogs and personal websites"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40776533</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40776533"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T14:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of these suggestions are good. (I should make my subheds clickable!) But a couple of them, oh dear…
I really hate progress bars, they are incredibly distracting. One of the worst examples of front end programmers wasting their time reimplementing browser functions badly. I already have scroll bars! I do not need more scroll bars!
Also, link decoration: my browser already has a nice discreet indicator to tell me where a link goes, I don’t need or want mysterious dingbats in the running text. (It reminds me of websites that are so scared of hyperlinks that they send them via interstitial warning pages “YOU ARE LEAVING THE SITE!!!!1!1!”, or in a recent case via a $yber$ecurity box that broke the link completely.) And preview popups? Get in the sea, hostile obnoxious interruption.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fanf2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using machine learning to detect bot attacks that leverage residential proxies]]></title>
        <id>66722bd6a4598c000bd700f0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/residential-proxy-bot-detection-using-machine-learning"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare's Bot Management team has released a new Machine Learning model for bot detection (v8), focusing on bots and abuse from residential proxies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob AminAzad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feedle, A Search Engine For Blogs]]></title>
        <id>https://linkage.lol/feedle-a-search-engine-for-blogs/</id>
        <link href="https://linkage.lol/feedle-a-search-engine-for-blogs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of folks who blog are always on the lookout for other bloggers to follow. BearBlog has a discover feed that lists recent and recent top posts. Many bloggers maintain a blogroll where they suggest the writing of people they like to others. I've found some good stuff there. (Note - Quit putting Daring Fireball in your blogroll. Everyone in the universe who needs to know about that blog already reads it). A few months ago, I found Feedle, a search engine for blogs and podcasts that allows you to add your own blog to its database. It's a good resource to find people who are well versed in the things you are interested in. Check it out.
Feedle, A World of Feeds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deciphering the Disinflation Process]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30281</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/deciphering-the-disinflation-process/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. inflation surged in the early post-COVID period, driven by several economic shocks such as supply chain disruptions and labor supply constraints. Following its peak at 6.6 percent in September 2022, core consumer price index (CPI) inflation has come down rapidly over the last two years, falling to 3.6 percent recently. What explains the rapid shifts in U.S. inflation dynamics? In a recent paper, we show that the interaction between supply chain pressures and labor market tightness amplified the inflation surge in 2021. In this post, we argue that these same forces that drove the nonlinear rise in inflation have worked in reverse since late 2022, accelerating the disinflationary process. The current episode contrasts with periods where the economy was hit by shocks to either imported inputs or to labor alone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Heise and Ayşegül Şahin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/24/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273779</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-24-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Between the Kremlin Cup and the General Staff Lip After Sunday’s Crimea and Dagestan Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273797</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/between-the-kremlin-cup-and-the-general-staff-lip-after-sundays-crimea-and-dagestan-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another tug-of-war between the Russian General Staff plus its hawkish friends and Putin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JumpCrisscross in "US prosecutors recommend Justice Department criminally charge Boeing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774272</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774272"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> This will go nowhere
As will this comment thread. We saw the same rhetoric on Holmes and Bankman-Fried. Once they were charged it was obvious they’d get off. Once convicted that they’d get a light sentence. Once sentenced that they’d have their sentences shortened, et cetera.
It’s a lazy learned helplessness that’s always potentially right because it feeds into a type of cynicism that has always been part of human nature in every culture since the beginning of history.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JumpCrisscross</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by madeofpalk in "Apple found in breach of EU competition rules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774176</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40774176"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can feel however you want about Apple's rules and EU regulation, but I think it's pretty indispuitable how wrong it is that Apple prevents developers from explaining these rules to their users. Apple prevents developers from saying that Apple takes a % cut of the sale. Apple prevents developers from saying its available cheaper elsewhere. If Apple feels these rules are so just and fair and indispuitably correct, why does it go to such measures to hide them from its consumers?
Consistently these anti-steering rules are what gets Apple in trouble all around the world. It's the one part Apple lost in the US Epic case, and it's the EUs first point on their breach. Apple has done this to themselves by being so stubborn and refusing to budge an inch on how they run their platforms. The tiniest concession years ago could have avoided all this regulation on them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>madeofpalk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Compromised Cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16687</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/catching-compromised-cookies/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Slack uses cookies to track session states for users on slack.com and the Slack Desktop app. The ever-present cookie banners have made cookies mainstream, but as a quick refresher, cookies are a little piece of client-side state associated with a website that is sent up to the web server on every request. Websites use this […]
The post Catching Compromised Cookies appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Slama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freeports Are Dangerous]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273785</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/freeports-are-dangerous.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T09:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rishi Sunak is still flogging his failed freeports initiative as a success.  If they were to take off, the winners would be dodgy operators.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DebtDeflation in "US prosecutors recommend Justice Department criminally charge Boeing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773948</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773948"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T09:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem for Boeing is that this wasn't a one time thing.  Two weeks ago it came out that they were using counterfeit titanium, then a few days later the CEO testifies that they had in fact retaliated against whistleblowers, then a few days later it comes out that they actually hid faulty parts from FAA regulators and then lost them.  Every apple that gets pulled from the bushel is rotten and there are a lot of apples left.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DebtDeflation</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Corporations Are Fueling Geopolitical Tensions and Global Conflicts in the 21st Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273761</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/how-corporations-are-fueling-geopolitical-tensions-and-global-conflicts-in-the-21st-century.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T09:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multinational corporations with global reach are increasingly getting entangled in conflicts and geopolitical rivalries by supporting multiple sides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sim7c00 in "I am using AI to drop hats outside my window onto New Yorkers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773600</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40773600"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T08:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This seems to only support windows :(]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sim7c00</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The economic crisis and unfolding disaster in Argentina]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45445</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/24/the-economic-crisis-and-unfolding-disaster-in-argentina/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The population of Argentina is suffering. The purchasing power of people who still have a job is down (a lot), and unemployment must have doubled (it was 5,7% in the last quarter of 2023) if it has not tripled. Less government spending, less consumer spending, and, no doubt, less private investment means that Argentina is […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tuesday’s Jamaal Bowman Primary Hits Close to Home for Me]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326380</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/tuesdays-jamaal-bowman-primary-hits-close-to-home-for-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T06:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The American Israel Public Affairs Committee has been around over 60 years, but it only began intervening in Democratic primaries in a big way last election cycle. AIPAC’s move came on the heels of a string of corporate Democrats losing primary contests to progressive “Squad” members, such as Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez in 2018, and Bowman two years later.  More
The post Tuesday’s Jamaal Bowman Primary Hits Close to Home for Me appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember the Palestinian Doctors Killed by Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326396</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/remember-the-palestinian-doctors-killed-by-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first week of June 2024, the Palestine office of the World Health Organization (WHO) released figures about the atrocious attacks on health care facilities and workers in Gaza since October 7, 2023. Thus far, according to the WHO, the Israelis have attacked 464 health care facilities, killed 727 health care workers, injured 933 health  More
The post Remember the Palestinian Doctors Killed by Israel appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quibbling About Killing: Netanyahu’s Spat with Washington]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326398</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/quibbling-about-killing-netanyahus-spat-with-washington/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Prime Minister, Benjamin Netanyahu, is unhappy.  Not so much with the Palestinians, whom he sees as terroristic, dispensable and a threat to Israeli security.  Not with the Persians, who, he swears, will never acquire a nuclear weapon capacity on his watch.  His recent lack of happiness has been directed against the fatty hand that feeds him and his country’s war making capabilities. More
The post Quibbling About Killing: Netanyahu’s Spat with Washington appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Think Trump’s Bad?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326302</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/you-think-trumps-bad/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poland is supposed to be one of the politically sane places in Europe right now. The far-right Law and Justice Party lost national elections last year to a centrist coalition and exited power after eight long years of democratic repression. Donald Tusk, who’d previously been the president of the European Council, once again became the  More
The post You Think Trump’s Bad? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Feffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Buy The Tariff Lie]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326399</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/dont-buy-the-tariff-lie/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:54:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If he returns to the White House,” Bloomberg reports, “Donald Trump has pledged to enact a 10% across-the-board tariff on imports that he says will raise billions of dollars in revenue to pay for more tax cuts.” He’s even floated the idea, per CNBC, of an “all tariff policy” and elimination of the federal income  More
The post Don’t Buy The Tariff Lie appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rescinding Dr. Segal: Mt. Irony in the Age of Resurrected US McCarthyism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326357</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/rescinding-dr-segal-mt-irony-in-the-age-of-resurrected-us-mccarthyism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The resurrection of McCarthyism in the US has returned in full force since October 7th. Careers have been truncated, protests have been muffled and employment opportunities curtailed. MSNBC cancelled the Mehdi Hasan Show in November. In June, Briahna Joy Gray was canned by The Hill, where she co-hosted the Rising web series. 30% of students  More
The post Rescinding Dr. Segal: Mt. Irony in the Age of Resurrected US McCarthyism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Crowley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gavin Newsom’s $12 Billion Radioactive Diablo Scam Could Soon Be Twisting In The Wind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326311</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/gavin-newsoms-12-billion-radioactive-diablo-scam-could-soon-be-twisting-in-the-wind/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diablo Canyon’s infamous $12 billion nuclear war is raging hot and heavy in Sacramento. Citizen action may soon decide the outcome. In the midst of a massive budget crisis, Governor Gavin Newsom is slashing social programs left and right. But he still wants to subsidize PG&E’s two money-losing atomic reactors near San Luis Obispo. The  More
The post Gavin Newsom’s $12 Billion Radioactive Diablo Scam Could Soon Be Twisting In The Wind appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey Wasserman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the Heedless Dems Giving Trumpty Dumpty a Path to Become America’s FÜHRER?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326242</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/are-the-heedless-dems-giving-trumpty-dumpty-a-path-to-become-americas-fuhrer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last several months, the chips have been falling in Trump’s favor to a level that probably astonishes this convicted felon. Consider the following: 1. Three of the four serious state and federal criminal lawsuits have been delayed by Trump’s lawyers and judges, so it is unlikely there will be trials until after the  More
The post Are the Heedless Dems Giving Trumpty Dumpty a Path to Become America’s FÜHRER? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saying a Final Goodbye to Baseball’s ‘Say Hey Kid’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326298</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/saying-a-final-goodbye-to-baseballs-say-hey-kid/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 1959, when Soviet Premier Nikita Khruschev visited San Francisco and members of the International Longshoreman’s Union greeted him with cheers, newspaperman Frank Coniff quipped: “This is the damndest city. They cheer Khruschev and boo Willie Mays.” It was the height of the Cold War and, for Coniff and many of his readers, there was  More
The post Saying a Final Goodbye to Baseball’s ‘Say Hey Kid’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lincoln Mitchell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Sutherland: Remembering a Peacemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326354</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/24/donald-sutherland-remembering-a-peacemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T04:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world just lost a great actor and a notable peace advocate. Donald Sutherland died on June 20, 2024, aged 88. Known globally for his compelling roles in films like Kelly’s Heroes, MASH, and The Hunger Games, Sutherland was much more than an accomplished actor. He was a relentless advocate for peace and social causes.  More
The post Donald Sutherland: Remembering a Peacemaker appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the trap of good memories]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/the-trap-of-good-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I struggle with this thing, of remembering certain people in such a golden light. Before this seems like a post talking about not-so-good people, it's not. It's about perfectly nice people.
The thing is, the way I tend to remember people is by how they made me feel. Few people in my life have made me feel like a real, raw person when talking to them. But some have. Some of these people are miles away, and have maybe always been miles away, both geographically and otherwise.
It's a really painful thing, because as these memories I hold go further and further back in my memory, I don't know what I want anymore. All I really want is to feel the way they made me feel again. Not so easy though, is it?
We've both grown in separate ways, and I'm grateful for where I am in my life, I think I've done pretty alright for myself so far. No matter what I do though, it does feel like there's a certain hole in my life, somewhere I'm lacking greatly. The remedy is so far though. Maybe it doesn't even exist, not anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Copilot Extensions are all you need]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/06/24/extensions-are-all-you-need"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to extend GitHub Copilot by using the Chat and Language Model APIs in your Visual Studio Code extension. Get inspired by early adopters and their extensions.
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A book about ferns: the truth of the three-hour Gilligan’s Island cruise]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7876</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/book-ferns-truth-three-hour-gilligans-island-cruise/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gilligan’s Island was a slapstick American TV series which ran from 1964 to 1967. Despite its popularity, the show was cancelled shortly before filming of a fourth series commenced. I first saw reruns of Gilligan’s quite some time later. A number of movies, featuring most of the original cast, were made between 1978 and 1982. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We can’t have a new paradigm as long as people think the old one was free-market fundamentalism]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45437</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/23/we-cant-have-a-new-paradigm-as-long-as-people-think-the-old-one-was-free-market-fundamentalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T20:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The belief in free-market fundamentalism runs very deep. When I say that, I don’t mean that support for the concept runs deep, I mean the belief that we had been pursuing free-market policies in the years before the Trump and Biden presidency runs very deep. I was reminded of this fact in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Selfish Woes About Dark Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/my-selfish-woes-about-dark-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T19:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m not a fan of having dark mode on my site because I have a hard time choosing colors that speak to me. I like to keep things minimalistic with my colors, and for me, it’s just much easier to do with a white background. However, I know (and acknowledge) the importance of having one, and so I pushed myself to do some tinkering on the blog this morning. Besides, my eyeballs also hate me when I look at my site at night, and so I’m sure it’s the case for other people too.
I subscribe to a lot of blogs via RSS reader, but I do take the extra step to launch their site to read the post. I have a deep appreciation for those who take the time to design their site the way they want, and so I want to read their posts the way it was meant to be read. It’s kind of like: listening to an album in order because I know that the artist ordered it a specific way for people to listen to. At the same time, it’s OK if you want to shuffle the playlist if you as the consumer want to, just like it’s OK for those who read my posts to do so via an RSS feed.
Anyways, this is just a quick post to say that, if your preference is dark mode, it is now available on here. I’ll revisit my site again at night time to test out the color contrasts (since I worked on this during daytime) to see if it makes sense, or if my eyeballs are still straining to read things.
Due to this, I’ve also gone ahead and created a Changelog for my site, so I can keep track of the little (and big) changes I make on here.
Side note:
I typically do have my screens on dark mode, and so if the sites/blog I read have dark mode, I read those in dark mode. It’s a weird thing for me to want my site in a lighter background, but I do struggle with it sometimes. Thanks to those who have put up with probably burning your retinas reading my posts if you weren’t doing so in an RSS reader. I appreciate you.
🐘 Reply on Mastodon // 📧 Reply by email
Subscribe via RSS here]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TrianguloY in "Start all of your commands with a comma (2009)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769974</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769974"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T19:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Those can really be called comma_nds!
Ahem. Nice idea though, I think I'll start using it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TrianguloY</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by civilized in "I am using AI to drop hats outside my window onto New Yorkers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769123</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40769123"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T17:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not your mistake, he does his best to imply that the hats are dropping on heads.
He's got a future in marketing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>civilized</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by OkGoDoIt in "I am using AI to drop hats outside my window onto New Yorkers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40768981</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40768981"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T17:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you watch the video, it actually falls several sidewalk tiles away and he has to go pick it up. From the text of the blog, I had assumed he was using AI to actually land it directly on a person’s head, which would’ve been crazy impressive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OkGoDoIt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Anthropic's Claude Sonnet 3.5 All You Need -  Vibe check]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/sonnet-vibe-check/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intro
Source
    
I have been subbed to Claude Opus for a few months (yes, I am an earlier believer than you people). Couple of days back, I was working on a project and opened Anthropic chat. Then I realised it was showing "Sonnet 3.5 - Our most intelligent model" and it was seriously a major surprise.
I have been playing with with it for a couple of days now. Wrote some code ranging from Python, HTML, CSS, JSS to Pytorch and Jax. Made it do some editing and proof-reading. So far it's been smooth sailing. Maybe we haven't hit a wall yet (Ok I am not important enough to comment on this but you gotta remember it's my blog).
But why vibe-check, aren't benchmarks enough? Oversimplifying here but I think you cannot trust benchmarks blindly. There can be benchmark data leakage/overfitting to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/23/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273748</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/links-6-23-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T10:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A National Cartel Fixing Rental Housing Prices: The Scandal Continues to Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273739</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/evidence-continues-to-pile-up-that-a-national-cartel-has-been-fixing-dental-housing-prices-for-years.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T10:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company at the heart of the rapacious conspiracy finally makes a statement following FBI raid in Atlanta and increasingly incriminating and devastating details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British Government Invents Phantom Skripals to Refuse to Testify in the Novichok Inquiry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273763</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/british-government-invents-phantom-skripals-to-refuse-to-testify-in-the-novichok-inquiry.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T09:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new lawyer materializes in a London court to say the Skripals refuse to testify in Novichok Inquiry, but it appears as though counsel has had no contact with the Skriprals.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Narbonne Cathedral (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52793</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/23/sunday-photoblogging-narbonne-cathedral-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T06:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Long War Against the Press in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325862</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/23/israels-long-war-against-the-press-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T05:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by Mohammed Ibrahim.
Defenders of Israel as “the only democracy in the Middle East” had their hands full last month, particularly when it came to freedom of the press, a cornerstone of genuine democracies. On May 5, Al Jazeera reported that its offices in East Jerusalem — internationally recognized Palestinian territory occupied by Israel — were raided and shut down by Israeli police following the banning of the news network by the Israeli government. Al Jazeera continues to operate in the rest of the West Bank and the Gaza Strip, but is still barred from reporting or broadcasting in Israel proper. Then, on May 21, the Associated Press reported that Israeli authorities had confiscated AP’s equipment in Southern Israel, despite the news agency submitting to Israeli military censorship. AP’s equipment was eventually returned, but only after the United States’ government intervened on behalf of the US company. Across the border, in the Gaza Strip, the situation for journalists was much more dire. Among the more than 37,266 Palestinians killed in the ongoing Israeli genocide, as reported by Al Jazeera, were at least 103 journalists, according to the Committee to Protect Journalists.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Israel’s Long War Against the Press in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arvind Dilawar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feedback Dope]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326143</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/23/feedback-dope/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T05:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The monetization of the feedback model has begun to seem to me to be perhaps the single most important characteristic of the post-WWII literary and academic culture. ‘Give me a 5-star rating,’ the Zomato food delivery person tells me after thanking me for the tip; ‘I hope you’ll give me an A,’ a student tells me after only a few classes in the semester; ‘Show me some love by giving my book a good rating on Amazon and Goodreads,’ says a writer on their social media; ‘I hope the students don’t give me a poor rating for not praising their essays,’ said a colleague to me on WhatsApp; Are you the Sumana Roy who wrote “Asp72 of Pro-Peptide is an Important pH Sensor in the Zymogen…”? asks Academia.edu; a Paula from somewhere has quoted from some essay I wrote in my last life – if I want to know more, I will have to buy a subscription or pay a membership fee; I get an email from someone whose Gmail signature declares that they are the ‘second-most cited academic in India’.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Feedback Dope appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumana Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cali Alley in Berkeley, CA]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/cali-alley-in-berkeley-ca/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/cali-alley-in-berkeley-ca/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Location: 1012 Grayson St, Berkeley, CA 94710
I initially had my doubts about this place, and even opted to skip out on it the first time we encountered it on Yelp. Then during a mental health day back in May (05/02), we decided to go check it out. After all, it had a 4.7⭐ rating on Yelp, so maybe some of these people knew what they were talking about (plus LSC really wanted to try it out).
I will be the first to admit that I 1000% regret my decision to have skipped out on it the first time. I loved it, and am already wanting to go back again.
We went during a Thursday for a late-ish lunch so it was pretty quiet. It's an alley (duh), and it is street parking only within some kind of neighborhood. They also only have outdoor seating, and you order through a window at the end of the alley. They were super nice, and even handed us a dog water bowl when they saw Cocoa.

House Grilled Pork Belly Rice bowl with seaweed, pickled ginger, pickled carrots/jalapenos, gingered kale, soft boiled egg, crispy noodles, and pickled cucumbers.
I ordered the dish pictured above ($19) and it was absolutely delicious. The pork belly was tender (melt in your mouth softness), and incredibly flavorful. For the rice bowl, you also have the option to choose your protein such as tofu ($18), grilled brisket burger ($19) or bamboo grilled prawns ($21). When I go back, I may be tempted to get it again, although I probably should try out other things on the menu.

The entrance has their full menu, so you'll know what to order prior to going to the window.

actual alley, and all the way at the end to the right is where you order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Rooum - Anarchism is about individuals]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/donald-rooum-anarchism-is-about-individuals?v=1719066834"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T14:33:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Donald Rooum
Title: Anarchism is about individuals
Date: 1986
Notes: From the 1986 centenary issue of Freedom, pp. 56–57
Source: Retrieved on 2024-06-21 from https://files.libcom.org/files/freedom-centenary.pdf

 There is no such thing as human society. 
 A lot of muddled thinking rests on the error that because ‘society’ is a useful noun, it must refer to a thing. It is one of those nouns like ‘journey’ and ‘tennis’, which refers not to a thing but to a relationship between things. The statement ‘human society exists’ is simply a less cumbersome way of saying ‘human individuals relate to each other in certain complicated ways’. The question, ‘what is the purpose of human society?’ means the same as, ‘why do human individuals associate in the way they do?’. 
 Human craving for soci…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Recycling Has Become a Largely Empty Gesture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=273746</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/06/how-recycling-has-become-a-largely-empty-gesture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T14:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Corporations sold Americans on the chasing arrows — while stripping the recycling logo of its worth.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by asanwal in "After my dad died, I ran and sold his company (2018)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40759208</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40759208"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T13:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi - author here.
This is a big question tbh and the lack of a succession plan is a function of many things:
1. This was my dad's baby. He loved the engineering and the science of it and so the idea of retiring from it was difficult for him to conceive. Doing that also requires thinking about one's mortality which I also believe was difficult for him.
2. This was a small market business in a tier 2 city in India. Attracting talent that could take it over was challenging. And myself and my siblings having been born and brought up in the States and being utterly clueless about the engineering/science of the company made us a non-starter.
3. As others have pointed out, he was thinking about succession/exit because he knew it was required for the biz to live on and grow. But life unfortunately had other plans and he was taken away from us unexpectedly.
There are definitely lots of could haves, should haves, would haves, etc I've thought about afterwards, but this was clearly one of those "play the cards you're dealt" kind of situations.
Thanks for reading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asanwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The day I talked to my crush.]]></title>
        <id>https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/</id>
        <link href="https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-day-i-talked-to-my-crush/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T13:44:53.532Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It was exciting, to say the least. I had an exam that day, and people usually finish their exams and go on their way. The problem was I had never talked to my crush before, so I couldn't exactly call her up to meet me. I finished my exam really early—about an hour and a half early—so that I wouldn't miss her.
Let's cut back to the morning of that day. I had already prepared what I wanted to say to her. But since I might talk non-stop, I decided to go with a letter (yeah, I'm old school that way—don't judge me). I woke up and did my morning routine (yes, I do have a routine). Then I wrote what I wanted to say, put it in an envelope, and went to the gym because I was too excited and nervous.
Now back to the scene where I'm waiting in the corridor for her to come out of the exam hall. Man, I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lying Down With Netanyahu, Getting Up With…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326239</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/22/lying-down-with-netanyahu-getting-up-with/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T12:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who knows Benjamin Netanyahu, and Joe Biden has for nearly 50 years, could see it coming. Sooner or later he was bound to bite the hand that feeds him. Bite it hard enough to draw blood, confident that not only could he get away with it but that he’d get more food as a […]
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Lying Down With Netanyahu, Getting Up With… appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fault-isolated, zonal deployments with AWS CodeDeploy]]></title>
        <id>6bdb1a94f1d30c014904a2d39161cd2f38f4fcfb</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/fault-isolated-zonal-deployments-with-aws-codedeploy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post you’ll learn how to use a new feature in AWS CodeDeploy to deploy your application one Availability Zone (AZ) at a time to help increase the operational resilience or your services through improved fault isolation. Introducing change to a system can be a time of risk. Even the most advanced CI/CD […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Haken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five ways Amazon Q simplifies AWS CloudFormation development]]></title>
        <id>325586d795e23aaa06a2c511ac9f946c1213c70b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/five-ways-amazon-q-simplifies-aws-cloudformation-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction As a builder, AWS CloudFormation provides a reliable way for you to model, provision, and manage AWS and third-party resources by treating infrastructure as code. First-time and experienced users of CloudFormation can often encounter some challenges when it comes to development of templates and stacks. CloudFormation offers a vast library of over 1,250 resource […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Kiel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by benrutter in "Language is primarily a tool for communication rather than thought [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40756941</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40756941"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:44:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It absolutely melts my mind every time I come across the two facts that:
- People experience their thoughts very differently
- We all secretly believe that deep down, everyone experiences thought like we do.
I've never really had a strong internal monologue when thinking, so my assumption would always be that of course, thinking isn't very linguistic (even if we can use it as a tool while thinking).
It seems like there's a large number of people who experience their thought exclusively as language.
That sounds absolutely nuts to me, but I've heard people say the exact same in reverse. Even more fringe is that there's a sizable number of people who when thinking about words (i.e. remembering names) visualize their words as text. What!? I can't imagine that anymore than I can imagine how a jellyfish feels?
The University of Wisconsin did a cool study that comes with a fun quiz you can do to see just how much of a wierdo you truly are: https://uwmadison.co1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_3NMm9yyFsNio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benrutter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shape Rotation 101: An Intro to Einsum and Jax Transformers]]></title>
        <id>https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/einsum-new/</id>
        <link href="https://sankalp.bearblog.dev/einsum-new/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T04:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acknowledgements
First, I would like to acknowledge my friends and kind internet strangers who helped me with this post.
This post heavily adapts from the following -
Tested Jax Transformer code via xjdr |  Github Link
Einstein summation in pytorch
Einstein summation in numpy
Basic guide to einsum
Big thanks to _xjdr, Felix, Pushkar and Tokenbender for proof-reading.
Intro
I have been “delving” into jax and einsum notation lately in my quest to become a shape-rotator.
This post is divided into two parts. In the first part, we go through einsum notation basics. The second part is about understanding simple transformer code in jax which uses a lot of einsum.
From your end, I want some brains (no I am not a zombie, I just want your attention). I also assume knowledge of numpy basics, matrix m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost my notebook... And a fresh start.]]></title>
        <id>https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/lost-my-notebook-and-a-fresh-start/</id>
        <link href="https://zoeloukia.bearblog.dev/lost-my-notebook-and-a-fresh-start/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, new corner of the internet I've just found!
I found this place in the most fun way, I found a zine that was (I can only assume) planted in the library I work at by
veronique.ink! I thought it was the coolest thing I've ever seen, the coolest idea. Initially I didn't realize it was a website link that was written on the page, but an instagram handle, so I was struggling to find them for only a second before I found the sense to type it into google.
I recently lost my notebook, or at least can't find it in the mess of my room. Usually I write my random thoughts in there, as I figured I had become above the notes app and was looking for reasons to stay off my phone. Of course, as soon as I lose my means of documenting my ideas, all sorts of events pass me by with nowhere to write about them. I've only just finished high school, recently lost my grandmother, and all sorts of change is crashing my way, and now I need to just stew in it..? Or worse, take to my notes app??
Then lo and behold, there's the zine just sitting on the shelf. Scrolling through these websites here, I figured maybe it was a sign. Or I'm just bored and want a new hobby. Only God knows. So anyway, I'm hoping I'll still find my notebook once I get around to cleaning my room. Maybe then I can even publish those thoughts in there! For now I'll just write them straight from screen to the world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark clouds over Europe with a few sunny patches]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Dark-clouds-over-Europe-with-a-few-sunny-patches</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Dark-clouds-over-Europe-with-a-few-sunny-patches"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T03:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are publishing here a transcript of an interview with Éric Toussaint by journalist and publisher Mario Hernandez for the radio programme “Metropolis”, broadcast on June 13, 2024 on Radio del Pueblo (People's Radio), AM 830, in the city of Buenos Aires. 
English

/ 
Europe, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Mario Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by OptionOfT in "My Windows Computer Just Doesn't Feel Like Mine Anymore"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755675</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755675"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T02:24:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I can't even remove 'Recommended' from the start menu, not even on a Pro for Workstations.
Every time I search on the start menu there is a web search, impossible to turn off. How is that acceptable?
I install Edge Beta to test something, and the I uninstall it. All of the sudden my search provider in my normal Edge is reset.
And the nagging everywhere. No I don't want 'back-up' my files (OneDrive is not backup, it's sync). And I don't want to be reminded later. I don't want to be reminded ever. All this fuzzy language makes me feel like I'm dealing with a kindergarden teacher addressing his/her pupils.
It's not my computer any more.
Oh, I update a driver. And 2 days later Windows installs an older version. Since when is 6.6.1.40 better than 6.6.1.72? Why would you do that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OptionOfT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by silverquiet in "My Windows Computer Just Doesn't Feel Like Mine Anymore"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755641</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755641"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T02:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a year ago I dumped Windows from my personal PC for good. I ran a Linux desktop at work for a decade, but my Steam collection get me with at least a bit of a tether to Microsoft. But Valve finally made Linux gaming a reality. I hope more people can make the switch someday because I'm quite happy with the system (Pop!_OS is my distro of choice these days).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>silverquiet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryandrake in "Internet Archive forced to remove 500k books after publishers' court win"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755293</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40755293"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T00:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I believe in hundreds, maybe thousands of years, after humanity has finally evolved past our current monkey mentality, future historians will look back at this time period in awe: "They had the technology to make the sum of all human knowledge available to everyone... And they blew it! Further, they had the means to feed everyone, clothe everyone, house everyone, but they just walked away in the other direction, purely to maintain existing economic power structures." The future historians are going to wonder how strong our ideology was that we sacrificed all of what we could have at the altar of our scarcity-based religion.
If Star Trek Replicators were invented today, we're so stupid we'd outlaw them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryandrake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TaylorAlexander in "Internet Archive forced to remove 500k books after publishers' court win"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40754916</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40754916"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T23:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no greater folly of contemporary human society than the purposeful restriction of such vast and easily shareable repositories of knowledge. Perhaps these schemes made sense in the past but with the advent of the internet and independent groups willing to fund all hosting fees, we should move to models of publishing that do not require this restriction of information. Library genesis exists but necessarily must hide and create some friction in the discovery process. A legally unencumbered free library of all books for all people would be the greatest achievement in all of human history. We prevent this achievement due to our attachment to a specific economic system that serves as the current means of financially supporting authors. We must build alternatives to for-profit publishing, and the only resilient and widely acceptable system I can imagine is one where every community owns and controls the means of production upon which they depend for their survival. In such an economic system, the need for automation would be obvious and once implemented, all people would receive the benefits of automation. This would include such a wide allowance for leisure and free time that authors would no longer need to restrict access to their books to extract profits from their value their shared knowledge creates. All people would be free to do what they will.
It would take great effort to build such a system, but open source and digital repositories of machine designs would ensure that efforts are not duplicated. The effort would still be substantial, but what hangs in the balance is the opportunity to assure the freedom of all people and the creation of the most significant repository of knowledge humanity has ever conceived of. If we succeed it will be our greatest achievement as a species.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TaylorAlexander</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AceJohnny2 in "I kind of like rebasing"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40754234</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40754234"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T21:54:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah! My people.
I, too, much prefer a rebase-heavy workflow. It allows me to both have a dirty "internal" history and clean up for publication.
As a side-effect, it also makes me comfortable having a mostly linear-history for what I publish, as opposed to a many-branched, merge-heavy one, which I dislike, and makes history confusing.
I reject the argument that a no-rebase, merge-only history "preserves the true history of how commits were created", because I believe that is irrelevant. What is relevant is what the tree looks like once the merge (or rebase) lands.
Should a merge conflict arise, in a rebase workflow the conflict resolution is folded into the rebased commit, so it looks like it was fine all along. In a merge workflow, the fix is in the separate merge commit. In both cases you still have to handle the merge conflict. And in my opinion it is not significant for the merge conflict resolution to be separate from the original commit itself because, again: what's important is the final state of the repo.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AceJohnny2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tanvach in "Self-driving Waymos secure final clearance for expansion beyond S.F"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40752504</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40752504"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T18:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently started using Waymo more often:
- Quality of Lyft and Uber rides have gone down significantly.
- Consistently spacious, clean and quiet cars. You know what you'll get.
- AC always works and not up to the whim of the driver.
- No chatty driver to disturb our sleeping baby.
Negatives:
- Rides have usually 10% mark up over Lyft and Uber.
- Pick up and drop off tend to be a small walk from requested locations.
Forgot one more positive - you can choose a soothing music play list in the car and it automatically resumes in the next ride. Small but really nice detail when traveling with a baby.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tanvach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ecshafer in "Innovation heroes are a sign of a dysfunctional organization"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40751493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40751493"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T17:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My goto example of a dysfunctional and bureaucratic organization is an example I saw in a finance company I worked for.
I was a on team that we were doing a major project. We basically ran Kanban but had to run "sprints" so we chose 4 week sprints to get it out of the way and we put everything on the board we had to get done that month to stay on track. Our pipeline was setup in such a way that you were required to have a jira ticket to push a commit. We were really crushing our timeline, doing 2x the work we were expected, a really great team honestly. But we opened up bugs and additional features in the middle of our sprints to track our work as we did it.
What this amounted to was maybe us saying we have to do 40 tickets this month, and wed be closing like 80. Everyone should have been thrilled by this development! Well we had a sprint review where some "Senior Project Manager" That wasn't really affiliated with our project but was some manager higher up was mad that us opening up new tickets mid sprint and closing them was ruining the org level burn down charts and expected delivery. They wouldn't give up on this, and said it was our fault for not estimating better (which sure, but we were beating expectations!). So we did the reasonable thing and improved our estimates! No of course not, we doubled our number of tickets and filled in "placeholder" on half of them, and used them as needed then closed everything out at the end of the sprint, where we were congratulated by everyone for our phenomonal estimation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ecshafer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Java 8 to Java 17: A Comprehensive Guide to New Features]]></title>
        <id>https://igorstechnoclub.com/upgrading-to-java-17-a-comprehensive-guide-to-new-features/</id>
        <link href="https://igorstechnoclub.com/upgrading-to-java-17-a-comprehensive-guide-to-new-features/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Java has evolved significantly since the release of Java 8 in 2014. Java 17, released in 2021, brings a host of new features and improvements that can enhance your code's readability, maintainability, and performance. This article will guide you through the key features introduced between Java 8 and Java 17, providing examples of how to migrate your code to take advantage of these new capabilities.
Sealed Classes
Java 17 introduces sealed classes, a powerful feature that enhances Java's object-oriented programming model and works seamlessly with pattern matching in switch expressions.
New Syntax:
The sealed keyword declares a sealed class or interface, and the permits clause specifies allowed subclasses:
public sealed interface Shape permits Circle, Rectangle, Triangle { }

Su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the UEFA Euro 2024 football games are impacting local Internet traffic]]></title>
        <id>667596a1a4598c000bd70354</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-uefa-euro-2024-football-games-impact-internet-traffic"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover how UEFA Euro 2024 is shifting Internet traffic patterns during games across Europe with insights into traffic drops and cybersecurity concerns during national team games]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TehShrike in "Spending 3 months investigating a 7-year old bug and fixing it in 1 line of code"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40750399</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40750399"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I particularly liked this part:
> Knowing very little about USB audio processing, but having cut my teeth in college on 8-bit 8051 processors, I knew what kind of functions tended to be slow. I did a Ctrl+F for “%” and found a 16-bit modulo right in the audio processing code.
That feeling of saving days of work because you remember a clue from previous experience is so good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TehShrike</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exam-ining recent Internet shutdowns in Syria, Iraq, and Algeria]]></title>
        <id>66747b7aa4598c000bd70245</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/syria-iraq-algeria-exam-internet-shutdown"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Similar to actions taken over the last several years, governments in Syria, Iraq, and Algeria have again disrupted Internet connectivity nationwide in an attempt to prevent cheating on exams. We investigate how these disruptions were implemented, and their impact]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dustin Illingworth: &ldquo;Private Riddles&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/private-riddles</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/private-riddles"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yoko Tawada and Paul Celan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ilan Pappé: &ldquo;The Collapse of Zionism&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-collapse-of-zionism</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-collapse-of-zionism"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T10:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six signs of breakdown.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edwin F. Ackerman: &ldquo;Transforming Mexico&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/transforming-mexico</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/transforming-mexico"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Claudia Sheinbaum’s new regime.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Team Ignores Israel’s History of Deceit and Deception]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326077</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/biden-team-ignores-israels-history-of-deceit-and-deception/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T06:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s history over the past 76 years is replete with examples of deceit.  This was true from the start, when the Israelis denied their role in expelling hundreds of thousands of Palestinians from their homes during Israel’s War of Independence.  The Arab world refers to the expulsion as the “nakba” (the catastrophe), which is largely denied in Israel.  The Israeli legacy of denying the “nakba” is no different from those who deny the Holocaust. More
The post Biden Team Ignores Israel’s History of Deceit and Deception appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Hedge Fund Manager and Right-Wing Donor is Financing an Israeli Influence Op Masquerading as a Journalism Project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325979</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/how-a-hedge-fund-manager-and-right-wing-donor-is-financing-an-israeli-influence-op-masquerading-as-a-journalism-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T06:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Krauthammer Fellowship was launched in 2019, a year after his death, and was established to honor his dedication to  “pursuing truth through honest, rigorous argument,” in the words of the Tikvah Fund’s website, though that description bears absolutely no resemblance to its namesake’s oeuvre. An egregious hack and one-man state-controlled news outlet, Krauthammer ceaselessly churned out bilge throughout his career, with a heavy focus on “America’s special role” in the world, its superficially similar but somehow entirely distinctive  “special place” in the world, and the “special responsibility” the United States must carry on its shoulders as a result. More
The post How a Hedge Fund Manager and Right-Wing Donor is Financing an Israeli Influence Op Masquerading as a Journalism Project appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ken Silverstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roaming Charges: The Man From Quiet Room 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326025</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/roaming-charges-115/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The entire time Al-Hadi was held in Afghanistan he never saw the sun, never knew what time it was, when to say his prayers or in which direction to say them. Unlike many other CIA prisoners, who were blasted with loud music, Al-Hadi was condemned to six months of silence. From his Quiet Cell, he couldn’t hear street noises, bird songs or human voices. He was living in a void. More
The post Roaming Charges: The Man From Quiet Room 4 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firewalls of Ignorance and Disappearance:  Corporate Media in the Age of Fascist Politics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326105</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/firewalls-of-ignorance-and-disappearance-corporate-media-in-the-age-of-fascist-politics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The corporate media undermines moral witnessing by often prioritizing the discredited notion of balance over the more crucial goal of seeking truth in the service of accountability and democracy. This retreat from holding power accountable not only discredits the pursuit of truth in the service of justice and the strengthening of democracy but also tends to fall prey to the seductions of corruption, political theater and entertainment. More
The post Firewalls of Ignorance and Disappearance:  Corporate Media in the Age of Fascist Politics appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coming in From the Cold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325983</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/coming-in-from-the-cold/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Self-Exfiltration I can’t say exactly how or when I realized my cover was blown and that I had to leave the U.S. Perhaps it was when I couldn’t read past the headlines in the New York Times without feeling despair; or maybe it was the downcast glances from my wife and handler, Harriet; or else  More
The post Coming in From the Cold appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trumping the Shark on Lake Michigan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326106</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/trumping-the-shark-on-lake-michigan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In much of the public imagination, and in Trump’s own fantasies, Trump rallies are political juggernauts with armies of thousands marching relentlessly toward a Trump restoration on November 5, 2024. But even if you just stream live into one of his rallies—as I did recently in Racine, Wisconsin—you come away with the impression that he’s little more than a tired vaudeville act that is getting ready to close out of town. More
The post Trumping the Shark on Lake Michigan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Wishful Thinking’ – Does Israel Have All the Cards in Gaza?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326089</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/wishful-thinking-does-israel-have-all-the-cards-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is often criticized for failing to produce a vision for the ‘next day’, meaning the day following the end of the Gaza war. Some of these criticisms emanate from Israel’s traditional western allies, who are wary of Netanyahu’s personal and political agendas, which are fixated on delaying his corruption trials  More
The post ‘Wishful Thinking’ – Does Israel Have All the Cards in Gaza?  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At the Edge of Apocalypse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326120</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/at-the-edge-of-apocalypse/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Biblical flooding, scorching heat, collapsing grid system, animals crumbling, waters rising, crops wilting, economy on the brink, and millions displaced. Welcome to the future of climate change… Pakistan. If one could classify a global warming beta test as a success towards the ultimate goal of apocalypse, unfortunately, it has turned Pakistan into a country populated  More
The post At the Edge of Apocalypse appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beekeeper in Kathmandu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=325966</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/the-beekeeper-in-kathmandu/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Laxman Gurung picks me up in the morning and we ride from Thamel on his motorcycle toward the hills which surround the Kathmandu valley. You can barely see them through the haze. I had remembered to bring a mask to cover my mouth and nose, but forgotten sunglasses. The air pollution is not only seen,  More
The post The Beekeeper in Kathmandu appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Saul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State Repression of Social Movements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326042</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/state-repression-of-social-movements/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up in my hometown of Greensboro, North Carolina I heard all about the infamous 1979 massacre. My parents and teachers lacerated the adventurist Communist Workers Party/Workers Viewpoint Organization (CWP/WVO) for courting death through increasingly aggressive rhetoric against the Ku Klux Klan. Family friends who were there on the day emphasized the complicity of law  More
The post State Repression of Social Movements appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zara Jemuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New World, New Hope: The Struggle for a Free Western Sahara Continues]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326171</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/new-world-new-hope-the-struggle-for-a-free-western-sahara-continues/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Life under occupation is a constant struggle. This is continually expressed at the international media conference in a refugee camp in Western Sahara. The conference takes place from May 1–5 and is organized by the Sahrawi Union of Journalists and Writers (UPES). Western Sahara is occupied by Morocco, a country where King Muhammad VI has full control over Morocco’s  More
The post New World, New Hope: The Struggle for a Free Western Sahara Continues appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc B. Sanganee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When U.S. Officials Show You Who They Are, Believe Them]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326163</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/when-u-s-officials-show-you-who-they-are-believe-them/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“When someone shows you who they are,” Maya Angelou said, “believe them the first time.” That should apply to foreign-policy elites who show you who they are, time after time. Officials running the Pentagon and State Department have been in overdrive for more than 250 days in support of Israel’s ongoing slaughter of Palestinian civilians  More
The post When U.S. Officials Show You Who They Are, Believe Them appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Corporations Are Fueling Geopolitical Tensions and Global Conflicts in the 21st Century]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326152</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/how-corporations-are-fueling-geopolitical-tensions-and-global-conflicts-in-the-21st-century/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after the outbreak of the Israel-Hamas War and the beginning of the widescale destruction of Gaza in October 2023, McDonald’s executives in Chicago found themselves inadvertently entangled in the conflict. Local owners of McDonald’s restaurants are given significant autonomy over profits and operations, and franchisees had begun taking sides. Social media posts by McDonald’s  More
The post How Corporations Are Fueling Geopolitical Tensions and Global Conflicts in the 21st Century appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heat Wave Crisis: Developing Nations Bear the Brunt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326157</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/heat-wave-crisis-developing-nations-bear-the-brunt/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April 2024, extreme heat hit South and Southeast Asia, affecting nations like India, the Philippines, Bangladesh, Indonesia, Malaysia, and Myanmar. These heat waves severely impacted some of the world’s most densely populated regions, taking a heavy toll on health, the economy, and education. In May and June, tens of millions of people faced dangerous  More
The post Heat Wave Crisis: Developing Nations Bear the Brunt appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pranjal Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reality Has Changed: the Ukraine War Slams Europe Rightward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326166</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/reality-has-changed-the-ukraine-war-slams-europe-rightward/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So has fascism come back to Europe or are Europeans simply sick of the Empire’s endless wars? The smart money’s on the latter, because what mostly unites the diverse right-wingers recently elected to the European Parliament is objection to the Ukraine War. But even that unity shows many cracks, as this motley collection of rightists  More
The post Reality Has Changed: the Ukraine War Slams Europe Rightward appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Art of the Submarine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326122</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/the-art-of-the-submarine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walk through any art museum and you’re likely to see a mix of the classical and contemporary, impressionist and surrealist, refined and raw, beautiful, eerie, and provocative. Looking at art allows me at least a few moments of relief from the “that’s just the way it is” attitude of our hyper-consumerist, hyper-militarized, hyper-nihilist nation. I  More
The post The Art of the Submarine appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frida Berrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Passing of a Troublemaker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=326173</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/06/21/the-passing-of-a-troublemaker/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A unique figure within a unique generation of activists, Frank Emspak (born June 21, 1943 and died June 14, 2024) spent his final days as he always lived: offering inspiration and strategic advice to those around him. In this case, it was to his hospital caregivers who are currently grappling with a hard-pressed union struggle. He had  More
The post The Passing of a Troublemaker  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Buhle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by observer987 in "Gilead shot prevents all HIV cases in trial"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40744964</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40744964"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T00:29:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paradox of living in this day and age is witnessing astonishing advances in science, while enduring the increasing levels of anti-intellectualism that pervades society like a cancer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>observer987</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anti-Militarist Initiative, Anonymous - The left of capital is sabotaging the anarchist movement: let’s fight back!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anti-militarist-initiative-anonymous-the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-l?v=1718919809</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anti-militarist-initiative-anonymous-the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-l?v=1718919809"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anti-Militarist Initiative, Anonymous
Title: The left of capital is sabotaging the anarchist movement: let’s fight back!
Date: June 2024
Source: https://antimilitarismus.noblogs.org/post/2024/06/14/the-left-of-capital-is-sabotaging-the-anarchist-movement-lets-fight-back/

 Soon after the escalation of the war in Ukraine, two completely different tendencies began to emerge under the banner of anarchy. One tendency insists that all inter-state wars are wars of the bourgeoisie against the proletariat, and therefore our participation in them cannot benefit the interests of the exploited class. The other tendency focuses on material, ideological and propaganda work in support of Ukraine’s state war effort and it sees such an approach as a pragmatic step for future self-organization. 
 R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[reflections on the fear of failure and seeking recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-the-fear-of-failure-and-seeking-recognition/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/reflections-on-the-fear-of-failure-and-seeking-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi,
I don't know... Lately, I've been thinking a lot about my fear of failure (or maybe I've already failed?), seriously.
I'm a very hardworking person... I have courses from prestigious universities (currently over 95 courses), I know four languages and am fluent in three, and I have certifications that many people would love to have, but every day I feel like I'm failing more.
I work in the technology sector (and IT has more branches than medicine). Specifically, I specialize in databases and server infrastructure. I even have my own setup at home, including cloud, Git, blog, documentation, and various other things. Recently, I became unemployed because I lost my freelance contracts with companies, and on the same day my last contract ended, I took all my savings and paid off what I coul…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeArtifact adds support for Rust packages with Cargo]]></title>
        <id>154d6b6a2483f420a12068e91b98f67bb15db6b1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-codeartifact-adds-support-for-rust-packages-with-cargo/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CodeArtifact now supports Rust packages, enabling secure storage and management of Rust crates within your organization's private repositories, mitigating legal and security risks from external package sources while ensuring efficient collaboration across teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blogging about blogging versus adding value through your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7868</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/blogging-about-blogging-versus-adding-value-through-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Less blogging about blogging: The majority of my posts are either platform explanations/justifications or organizational posts. Stuff like, “I’m moving the Archives here” or “I’ve added a ton of Links there.” Other times it’s simple announcements about me moving my blog someplace new. So, why do I feel the need to talk about this? This […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easy OS, an experimental Linux distro, by Barry Kauler]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7866</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/easy-os-experimental-linux-distro-barry-kauler/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m in the process of migrating my OS away from Windows. I’ve been running Linux Mint, considered to be a user-friendly, Windows-like distribution of the Linux family of OS’s, on a backup device for almost two weeks now. It’s been a learning curve naturally, but so far, so good. In the meantime though, the word […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Burritos power Guzman Y Gomez to hot sharemarket debut]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7862</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/burritos-power-guzman-y-gomez-hot-sharemarket-debut/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shares in Australian founded Mexican food restaurant Guzman Y Gomez (GYG: it’s not only an initialism, it’s a ticker code) had a stellar debut on their first day of trading on the ASX, with one market pundit describing the launch as “the hottest float on the stock market in years“: Its shares opened at $30, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Peaky Blinders military unit helping to defend Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7860</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/peaky-blinders-military-unit-defend-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T19:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kathryn Diss and Mathew Marsic, writing for ABC News: For Commander Anton, it’s difficult to imagine returning to his quiet life before the war. The 33-year-old former builder is now a battle-hardened soldier who risks his life every day, just kilometres from the Russian border. He is part of an elite squad of soldiers who […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "Small claims court became Meta's customer service hotline"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40741842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40741842"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small claims court does get a company's attention. They either have to show up or lose. Not that showing up means a win.
I'm surprised that someone had trouble serving a subpoena on Facebook.
Looking up "Meta" in California Corporation Search brings up everything with "Metal" in it, which is a hassle. Their actual company name is "Meta Platforms, Incorporated". Search for "Meta Platforms" here.[1] California company registration #2711108.
Subpoenas are sent, using a process server, to their registered agent,
which is Corporation Service Company in Sacramento, a business which exists to receive subpoenas for other companies. And, conveniently, there are process serving companies with offices in the same building, and you can find them by searching for the address of CSC and "process server", then ignoring the spam results.
Most small claims court web sites explain all this.
[1] https://bizfileonline.sos.ca.gov/search/business]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the death of mgx]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/the-death-of-mgx/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/the-death-of-mgx/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:29:53.294Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bearblog.dev allows for open discussion and exchange of ideas in a low-stakes way. Putting my thoughts into writing on Bear means there are chances that some readers may open it and engage with it. At that moment, they are actively interpreting and making sense of it based on their own background. I find it liberating to release my raw text entries into the world and see what resonates or sparks new internal discussions for others. There is also a sense of relief in getting ideas that have been swirling in my mind out in the open. Once published, it feels like a task completed. While I don't necessarily stay involved in conversations about my posts, I appreciate seeing the ripple effects as others reflect on or debate the topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropic’s Claude 3.5 Sonnet model now available in Amazon Bedrock: Even more intelligence than Claude 3 Opus at one-fifth the cost]]></title>
        <id>362d245ccfb6f0d5062ec50122393c4a6f14ee2a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/anthropics-claude-3-5-sonnet-model-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock-the-most-intelligent-claude-model-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This powerful and cost-effective model outperforms on intelligence benchmarks, with remarkable capabilities in vision, writing, customer support, analytics, and coding to revolutionize your workflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danilo Poccia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[France: With the New Popular Front against the deadly fascist threat!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/France-With-the-New-Popular-Front-against-the-deadly-fascist-threat</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/France-With-the-New-Popular-Front-against-the-deadly-fascist-threat"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When, just after the announcement of the results of the European elections, French President Macron surprised everyone by deciding to dissolve the Parliament and to call general elections for June 30, it was obvious that he aspired to repeat, once again, the successful blackmail thanks to which he had won his two presidential elections: to find himself alone against Marine Le Pen and her far-right party, thus forcing left-wing voters to vote for him in the absence of a left-wing alternative (...)
English

/ 
France, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most potent drug - Nostalgia]]></title>
        <id>https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-most-potent-drug-nostalgia/</id>
        <link href="https://logeshwara.bearblog.dev/the-most-potent-drug-nostalgia/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:41:24.134Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just had a nostalgic moment in my exam hall. It was so quiet except for the sound of the ceiling fan and people's footsteps outside. I was looking at the wall clock 45 minutes into my exam (that's what I do in exam halls). This particular time, it brought back memories of my childhood (like in 5th or 6th grade) when I used to play Monopoly with my friends during power cuts.
Another memory that recently surfaced depicted my school at 3:30 PM when classes would be over, and there would be clamoring in the corridor until we went to the parking lot. This was triggered by people chatting in front of the exam halls. There is a certain comfort in these noises.
Savor these moments when they happen, but don't be jailed by them. Remember, time is a cruel mistress who will make you forget the struggles and just remember the good parts.
It's like what Andy says in The Office: "I wish there was a way to know you're in the good old days before you've actually left them."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional paper:  Fungal banking]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52776</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/06/20/occasional-paper-fungal-banking/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So in the last couple of decades we’ve discovered that many plants rely on networks of soil fungi to bring them critical trace nutrients. This is a symbiotic relationship: the fungal network can access these nutrients much better than plants can, and in return the plants provide the fungus with other stuff — particularly energy, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recap of the Data Engineering Open Forum at Netflix]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/6b4d4410b88f</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/a-recap-of-the-data-engineering-open-forum-at-netflix-6b4d4410b88f?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T15:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A summary of sessions at the first Data Engineering Open Forum at Netflix on April 18th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Finn: why I joined Cloudflare as VP Sales for the Americas]]></title>
        <id>66730ec6a4598c000bd701a7</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/patrick-finn"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T13:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick S. Finn is joining Cloudflare as Vice President of Sales in the US, Canada, and Latin America]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick S. Finn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Stream Generated Captions, powered by Workers AI]]></title>
        <id>66738564a4598c000bd701da</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/stream-automatic-captions-with-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With one click, users can now generate video captions effortlessly using Stream’s newest feature: AI-generated captions for on-demand videos and recordings of live streams]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mickie Betz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by erk__ in "Tetris Font (2020)"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40737869</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40737869"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:21:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I did kinda the opposite and instead of making a font out of tetris I made a font play Tetris.
I did it with the Harfbuzz shaper which now have experimental support for embedding WebAssembly programs to shape fonts.
Talk where I show it off: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ms1Drb9Vw9M
Source code: https://github.com/Erk-/programmable-fonts
You can also see actual uses of this WebAssembly embedding to show that is not just for fun here: https://github.com/harfbuzz/harfbuzz-wasm-examples]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>erk__</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Growing Risk of Spillovers and Spillbacks in the Bank‑NBFI Nexus]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30345</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/06/the-growing-risk-of-spillovers-and-spillbacks-in-the-bank-nbfi-nexus/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nonbank financial institutions (NBFIs) are growing, but banks support that growth via funding and liquidity insurance. The transformation of activities and risks from banks to a bank-NBFI nexus may have benefits in normal states of the world, as it may result in overall growth in (especially, credit) markets and widen access to a wide range of financial services, but the system may be disproportionately exposed to financial and economic instability when aggregate tail risk materializes. In this post, we consider the systemic implications of the observed build-up of bank-NBFI connections associated with the growth of NBFIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Viral V. Acharya, Nicola Cetorelli, and Bruce Tuckman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMT — the key insights]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45432</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/06/20/mmt-the-key-insights-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T05:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll As has become abundantly clear during the last couple of years, it is obvious that most mainstream economists seem to think that Modern Monetary Theory is something new that some wild heterodox economic cranks have come up with. That is actually very telling about the total lack of knowledge of their own […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cleandreams in "Please don't mention AI again"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40735151</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40735151"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T05:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I worked for an AI startup that got bought by a big tech company and I've seen the hype up close. In the inner tech circles it's not exactly a big lie. The tech is good enough to make incredible demos but not good enough to generalize into reliable tools. The gulf between demo and useful tool is much wider than we thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cleandreams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG Node]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/20/sig-node-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/06/20/sig-node-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of container orchestration, Kubernetes reigns
supreme, powering some of the most complex and dynamic applications across the globe. Behind the
scenes, a network of Special Interest Groups (SIGs) drives Kubernetes' innovation and stability.
Today, I have the privilege of speaking with Matthias
Bertschy, Gunju
Kim, and Sergey
Kanzhelev, members of SIG
Node, who will shed some
light on their roles, challenges, and the exciting developments within SIG Node.
Answers given collectively by all interviewees will be marked by their initials.
Introductions
Arpit: Thank you for joining us today. Could you please introduce yourselves and provide a brief
overview of your roles within SIG Node?
Matthias: My name is Matthias Bertschy, I am French and live next to Lake Geneva, near the
French…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before Sunrise turns thirty, my theory about what happens]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7854</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/before-sunrise-turns-thirty-theory-what-happens/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T21:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a favourite around here. Because don’t we love meeting someone we connect with at first sight? But Sunday 16 June 2024, marked the thirtieth anniversary (Facebook link) of the premiere of Before Sunrise, directed by Richard Linklater, and starring Julie Delpy and Ethan Hawke. Another two films followed, with about nine years separating each […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining forces with the social movement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Joining-forces-with-the-social-movement</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Joining-forces-with-the-social-movement"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T20:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 150 trade unionists, social movement activists and alternative leftists are responding to the call for a New Popular Front and calling for grassroots involvement to push back the far right and go further in the rupture and the alternative. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
France, 
Antifascism, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Front Populaire Social</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blue/Green Deployments to Amazon ECS using AWS CloudFormation and AWS CodeDeploy]]></title>
        <id>c563b7b56de1bb98ce0af62f110d3bfe4644c1d1</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/blue-green-deployments-to-amazon-ecs-using-aws-cloudformation-and-aws-codedeploy/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Many customers use Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) for running their mission critical container-based applications on AWS. These customers are looking for safe deployment of application and infrastructure changes with minimal downtime, leveraging AWS CodeDeploy and AWS CloudFormation. AWS CloudFormation natively supports performing Blue/Green deployments on ECS using a CodeDeploy Blue/Green hook, but this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajay Mehta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by insane_dreamer in "Safe Superintelligence Inc."]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40730485</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40730485"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T17:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I understand the concern that a "superintelligence" will emerge that will escape its bounds and threaten humanity. That is a risk.
My bigger, and more pressing worry, is that a "superintelligence" will emerge that does not escape its bounds, and the question will be which humans control it. Look no further than history to see what happens when humans acquire great power. The "cold war" nuclear arms race, which brought the world to the brink of (at least partial) annihilation, is a good recent example.
Quis custodiet ipsos custodes? -- That is my biggest concern.
Update: I'm not as worried about Ilya et al as commercial companies (including formerly "open" OpenAI) discovering AGI.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>insane_dreamer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the general availability of fully managed MLflow on Amazon SageMaker]]></title>
        <id>08ada00504b244657e6aef9431dc3e5146c80453</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/manage-ml-and-generative-ai-experiments-using-amazon-sagemaker-with-mlflow/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Amazon SageMaker with MLflow to track experiments, compare runs, register candidate models, and transition models from experimentation to production.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ghostlight Vintage and things]]></title>
        <id>https://jeddacp.me/ghostlight-vintage-and-things/</id>
        <link href="https://jeddacp.me/ghostlight-vintage-and-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quiet Sunday (6/16) stroll in downtown Richmond this past weekend.
I've always loved the vintage aesthetic, but have been more drawn to it recently. Been loving this little area in the MOM & POP art shop in downtown Point Richmond (CA). We've gotten a few pins and a record (or 2) here in the past.
Here are some of my favorite snapshots...





And then some more finds around the area...
In case you didn't know, I have a thing for photographing old school pay phones.


I also really happen to love typewriters.

A photo series is never complete without a quick snap of Cocoa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CloudFormation Linter (cfn-lint) v1]]></title>
        <id>b60372369f3a21376c62a03980413e24b51b8836</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/aws-cloudformation-linter-v1/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction The CloudFormation Linter, cfn-lint, is a powerful tool designed to enhance the development process of AWS CloudFormation templates. It serves as a static analysis tool that checks CloudFormation templates for potential errors and best practices, ensuring that your infrastructure as code adheres to AWS best practices and standards. With its comprehensive rule set and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin DeJong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVF: A novel metric for understanding AI systems’ vulnerability against SDCs in model parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21376</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/06/19/data-infrastructure/parameter-vulnerability-factor-pvf-ai-silent-data-corruption/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re introducing parameter vulnerability factor (PVF), a novel metric for understanding and measuring AI systems’ vulnerability against silent data corruptions (SDCs) in model parameters. PVF can be tailored to different AI models and tasks, adapted to different hardware faults, and even extended to the training phase of AI models. We’re sharing results of our own [...]
Read More...
The post PVF: A novel metric for understanding AI systems’ vulnerability against SDCs in model parameters appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video annotator: building video classifiers using vision-language models and active learning]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8ebdda0b2db4</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/video-annotator-building-video-classifiers-using-vision-language-models-and-active-learning-8ebdda0b2db4?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harness domain expertise with Video Annotator: streamline ML annotations, cut costs, and deploy faster using a human-in-the-loop system 🚀]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rsstack in "Ask HN: What happens when I click "request for quote" on your SaaS?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40729115</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40729115"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been part of the team that sets up this process at a few SaaS's, and I've done SaaS procurement for a while, so I clicked that button often (if I didn't know anyone at the company).
1. It gets added to a list of marketing website leads, which is owned by SDRs/BDRs who are there to filter and qualify leads. These are usually early-career people, with a base salary + quota for qualifying leads. The website is many times their least preferred channel of leads due to the quality, but they can't ignore it because sometimes good customers do come through there.
2. The SDR will either work over email or on a call; their goal is to identify if you're a real potential customer (vs shopping for prices, vs confused about what we sell), write up notes, and identify which customer segment you belo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rsstack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by miah_ in "Neofetch developer archives all his repositories: "Have taken up farming""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40727795</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40727795"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T12:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe they have saved enough from working in tech that they can grow vegetables for themselves in a very low scale way. Its nice to escape from the career you've had for decades. Sometimes its not even an escape from the career, but the career and the city you've lived in. Moving to the forest and growing some vegetables and raising chickens isn't that difficult. You certainly don't need "millions in equipment". Its exactly what I did.
I found it difficult to get a job in tech at the start of COVID after working in it for ~25 years. I moved to Michigan, and now live in the woods. My Cost of Living is a fraction of what it was. My mortgage is only 80% of what I was paying for rent in the SFBay area. Its peaceful and quiet here. It actually gets dark too. I no longer hear BART screeching on the rails at 2am or the constant flow of traffic. I.. do once again work in tech though at a much 'smaller' scale. My company is small and work demands don't dominate my life. I have balance.
This year I've planted ~200 onions, ~100 potatoes, ~100 garlic, ~60 strawberry. I have blueberry from a few years back starting to flourish. I have wild blackberry, and mushrooms galore. "touching grass" is a daily activity as we manage our small flock of chickens.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>miah_</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by driverdan in "Neofetch developer archives all his repositories: "Have taken up farming""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40727702</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40727702"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T12:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time this topic comes up I say the same thing. If you've never worked on a farm and have some kind of romantic idea about it then you shouldn't do this. Farming is hard work. Modern farmers have college degrees, millions in equipment, and a vast amount of knowledge and experience you do not have.
If you're thinking of doing this and do not have experience go work on a farm for a year before you buy in.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>driverdan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[India : Analysis of Budget 2024–25, Part 1: Declining Budget Outlay]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Analysis-of-Budget-2024-25</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Analysis-of-Budget-2024-25"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have shown in considerable detail in previous articles published in the Janata Weekly on the economic situation in the country in early 2024 that the Indian economy is in deep crisis. The actual growth rate of the economy is much less than is being projected by the Modi Government. [1] The people are facing a colossal unemployment, poverty and hunger crisis. [2] Within the framework of welfare capitalism, the most effective solution to this crisis is that the government should greatly (...)
English

/ 
India, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Neo-liberalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neeraj Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by anymouse123456 in "AI-powered conversion from Enzyme to React Testing Library"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40726935</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40726935"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:43:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Misleading title. Maybe try this one?
"Slack uses ASTs to convert test code from Enzyme to React with 22% success rate"
This article is a poor summary of the actual article, which is at least linked to Slack's engineering blog [0].
[0] https://slack.engineering/balancing-old-tricks-with-new-feat...
[updated]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>anymouse123456</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by johndoe0815 in "ExectOS – brand new operating system which derives from NT architecture"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40725547</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40725547"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T06:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would I trust an OS which states "Why don’t you use GCC? – Because GCC is a crap." in the project's FAQ [1]? This isn't really inspiring confidence.
Also, it's completely not obvious from your web pages which features already work in your OS. And, IMHO, Discord is definitely not "the perfect place to connect, collaborate, and contribute".
Just my 2ct...
[1] https://exectos.eu.org/faq/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>johndoe0815</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hn_throwaway_99 in "Ask HN: Why do message queue-based architectures seem less popular now?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40725060</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40725060"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T05:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I like a lot of the answers, but something else I'd add: lots of "popular" architectures from the late 00s and early 2010s have fallen by the wayside because people realized "You're not Google. Your company will never be Google."
That is, there was a big desire around that time period to "build it how the big successful companies built it." But since then, a lot of us have realized that complexity isn't necessary for 99% of companies. When you couple that with hardware and standard databases getting much better, there are just fewer and fewer companies who need all of these "scalability tricks".
My bar for "Is there a reason we can't just do this all in Postgres?" is much, much higher than it was a decade ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hn_throwaway_99</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and IMF have set their sights on East Timor, a state officially born in May 2002]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-and-IMF-have-set-their-sights-on-East-Timor-a-state-officially</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-and-IMF-have-set-their-sights-on-East-Timor-a-state-officially"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
South, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Flag - Dancing with the devil: On the politics of Green Anarchist, again!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-flag-dancing-with-the-devil-on-the-politics-of-green-anarchist-again?v=1718752635</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/black-flag-dancing-with-the-devil-on-the-politics-of-green-anarchist-again?v=1718752635"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:17:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Black Flag
Title: Dancing with the devil: On the politics of Green Anarchist, again!
Subtitle: Black Flag defends class struggle anarchism against the nihilist-terrorism of Green Anarchist
Date: 1999
Source: Black Flag #217 & LibCom. <libcom.org/article/dancing-devil-politics-green-anarchist-again>

 In issue 215 of Black Flag we ran a critique of the politics of Green Anarchist, “Irrationalism — Steve Booth Against the Machine”, which attacked propositions by Steve Booth (in Green Anarchist 51) in favour of “acts of intense violence against the system with no obvious motives, no pattern”. Booth stated that: 
 “The Oklahoma bombers had the right idea. The pity was that they did not blast any more government offices...The Tokyo sarin cult had the right idea. The pity was that in tes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Host the Whisper Model with Streaming Mode on Amazon EKS and Ray Serve]]></title>
        <id>071152e0b7b8a8532d450ad7e82d606ecbac2952</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/host-the-whisper-model-with-streaming-mode-on-amazon-eks-and-ray-serve/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Whisper is a pre-trained model for automatic speech recognition (ASR) and speech translation. It has demonstrated strong ASR performance across various languages, including the ability to transcribe speech in multiple languages and translate them into English. The Whisper model is open-sourced under the Apache 2.0 license, making it accessible for developers to build useful […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel McGowan - My Own Pearl Harbor]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-mcgowan-my-own-pearl-harbor?v=1718752020</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-mcgowan-my-own-pearl-harbor?v=1718752020"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Daniel McGowan
Title: My Own Pearl Harbor
Date: Dec 7, 2022
Source: medium.com/@danielmcgowannyc

 December 7, 2005 was my own personal Pearl Harbor: the moment that defines the ‘before’ and ‘after’. The morning started out normal enough. I had plans to stuff some holiday cards for my job and then stop off at a sporting goods store to pick up a gift for my brother-in-law. After that, I was going to babysit for my sister, which I really looked forward to. 
 After some mundane hours in the office, I looked up for a second and a few men were in the doorway of my cube. “Daniel McGowan?,” they said and before I knew it, I was standing, spun around onto the desk and being cuffed. “You’re going back to Oregon” is the phrase that sent me spinning. And like that, the past had caught up with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[friends of Daniel McGowan - Live from Little Guantanamo]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-mcgowan-live-from-little-guantanamo?v=1718751718</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/daniel-mcgowan-live-from-little-guantanamo?v=1718751718"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T23:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: friends of Daniel McGowan
Title: Live from Little Guantanamo
Subtitle: A Conversation with Daniel McGowan Inspired by the Film If a Tree Falls
Date: Fall of 2011
Source: earthfirstnews.wordpress.com

 The award-winning documentary, If A Tree Falls: A Story of the Earth Liberation Front, premiered at Sundance last spring and continues to screen in theaters across the globe. The film, which aired on PBS earlier this fall and is now available on DVD, details the events that led to the imprisonment of environmental activist Daniel McGowan and raises critical questions about ecological crisis, terrorism, and government repression of political activists. 
 Those who see If A Tree Falls are likely to be left with a number of lingering questions. How is Daniel doing now? When will he be re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freedom News - Toby Shone and the spectre of ‘anarchist terror’]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/toby-shone-and-the-spectre-of-anarchist-terror?v=1718751511</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/toby-shone-and-the-spectre-of-anarchist-terror?v=1718751511"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Freedom News
Title: Toby Shone and the spectre of ‘anarchist terror’
Date: May 9th, 2022
Source: freedomnews.org.uk

 Having failed last year to show its much heralded “anti-terror” raids against anarchists in 2020 were justified, the State last week lost a second bid to silence their main target, Toby Shone. 
 The cops’ attempt at targeted repression, using anti-mafia laws against someone unlucky enough to have had drugs in his home during the raids, is just the most recent attack against European anarchists however. It’s part of a broader pattern which has emerged as energy for the moral panic over fundamentalist Islam subsides. 
Europe-wide crackdown
 There is a strain of insurrectionary anarchism in Europe which has maintained itself for decades, and often pops up particularly …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alfredo M. Bonanno - No political position of compromise had to be accepted]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alfredo-m-bonanno-no-political-position-of-compromise-had-to-be-accepted?v=1718748994</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/alfredo-m-bonanno-no-political-position-of-compromise-had-to-be-accepted?v=1718748994"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Alfredo M. Bonanno
Title: No political position of compromise had to be accepted
Date: April 18, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=14083>. Retrieved on 09/06/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 This interview was carried out by a correspondent of Columna Negra after a gathering held in the city of Monza, Italy on the 24th-25th of November of the past year, a moment in which some discussions were carried out in respect to current repression world wide, the Mapuche situation amongst other topics. This first exchange of ideas with Alfredo Maria Bonanno turned into what you will read below. 
CN: Considering the scenarios of crisis at the global scale, characterized by the massive de-legitimization of the traditional political models, the economic and social destabilization people are n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending June 16, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240618</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240618"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Antipolitika - A CALL AGAINST ARMS]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antipolitika-a-call-against-arms?v=1718746033</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/antipolitika-a-call-against-arms?v=1718746033"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T21:27:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Antipolitika
Title: A CALL AGAINST ARMS
Subtitle: SYSTEMIC DRIVERS OF THE WAR(S) AND AN AUTONOMOUS, ANTICAPITALIST ANTI-WAR POSITION
Date: May 25th, 2024
Notes: Antipolitika: anarchist journal from the balkans
Source: https://antipolitika.noblogs.org/post/2024/05/25/a-call-against-arms/

1. PRELIMINARY NOTES
 The Houthis attacks on cargo ships, the USA/UK strikes against Yemen, the USA/EU naval fleet deployed in the Red Sea, the ISIS-K Crocus City Hall attack[1], the Iran/Israel missile attacks[2] constitute new expressions of the emerging global reality: competing groups/blocks of capitalists have chosen the route of war, in order to establish themselves in a better position within the hierarchies of a globalised economy that is in stagnation, and is also dealing with the exhausti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we have IndieWeb how are others to find it?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7848</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/now-we-have-indieweb-how-to-find/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T21:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do people who don’t know about IndieWeb, but would like to escape the web-scape funk they’re beholden to, find out about IndieWeb, asks Delyo Dobrev. This is the million dollar question. Everyone and their grandma and their dog is talking about social media’s bad influence. But do they do anything about it, or do […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ashanti Alston - Ashanti Alston on the Black Panthers and the Zapatistas | Black Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ashanti-alston-ashanti-alston-on-the-black-panthers-and-the-zapatistas-black-anarchism?v=1718742157</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ashanti-alston-ashanti-alston-on-the-black-panthers-and-the-zapatistas-black-anarchism?v=1718742157"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ashanti Alston
Title: Ashanti Alston on the Black Panthers and the Zapatistas | Black Anarchism
Date: 2006
Source: <youtube.com/watch?v=kYQ8N6sit2E>

Ashanti: First thing, first thing, first thing... Power to the people. 
Audience: silence
Ashanti: Oh! Wait a minute... First thing, first thing, first thing... Power to the people. 
Audience: Power to the people! 
Ashanti: Oh my God, I'm like, whoa... And what we usually say when someone says power to the people, the response is; all power to the people! Alright, so I give you the first one. Yeah, I mean, that's OK, 'cause I was practiced, right? 
 But all power means that all power goes to the people, right? Didn't say to the party. Didn't say to the state. It didn't say to the slick talkers. Not other ones. To the people, to the pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Danny Evans and Liz Stainforth - Learning to live]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/danny-evans-and-liz-stainforth-learning-to-live?v=1718732376</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/danny-evans-and-liz-stainforth-learning-to-live?v=1718732376"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Danny Evans and Liz Stainforth
Title: Learning to live
Subtitle: Anarcho-syndicalism and utopia in Spain, 1931–37
Date: 15 June 2023
Notes: Received: 27 September 2021; Accepted: 14 March 2022
Source: https://eprints.whiterose.ac.uk/194715/

Nos piden desde el principio un régimen perfecto, garantía de que las cosas se harán así y no de este otro modo, sin coscorrones, sin tanteos. Si hubiéramos de aprender a vivirlo, no terminaríamos nunca el aprendizaje. Ni el niño aprendería a andar, ni el chico montaría en bicicleta, ni sería posible adquirir un oficio o una especialización. Al contrario, en la vida se hacen al revés las cosas. 
 Isaac Puente, El Comunismo Libertario ([1932] 1933) 
 [We are asked from the outset to come up with a flawless system, to guarantee that things will w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>