<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-15T12:44:42.711Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-15T12:44:42.711Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anton Jäger: &ldquo;Into the Void&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/into-the-void</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/into-the-void"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T13:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reply to Richard Seymour.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276752</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T10:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tastefully presented daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Americans Love Free Speech, Survey Finds − Until They Realize Everyone Else Has It, Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276745</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/americans-love-free-speech-survey-finds-%e2%88%92-until-they-realize-everyone-else-has-it-too.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T07:49:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new American norm: "Free speech for me, but not for thee!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saving in Itself Is Merely Negative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276743</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/saving-in-itself-is-merely-negative.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T07:13:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debunking yet another appealing-sounding but elite-serving idea, here the premise that savings is always good and more is better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Defense Firms Reluctant to Cooperate with Ukraine Due to Safety, Corruption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276741</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/us-defense-firms-reluctant-to-cooperate-with-ukraine-due-to-safety-corruption.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle surprise! The grand scheme to build a weapons industry in Ukraine appears to be going pear shaped.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gavin Newsom’s War on Rooftop Solar Is a Bad Omen for the Country]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330763</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/gavin-newsoms-war-on-rooftop-solar-is-a-bad-omen-for-the-country/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large utilities make their money by repairing and expanding the energy grid. Residential solar directly threatens that revenue stream because it doesn’t rely on an ever-expanding network of power stations and transmission lines. The electricity that residential solar power produces typically remains at the community level or, better yet, in the home itself, especially if coupled with local battery storage. Not surprisingly then, by 2018, 20 transmission lines had been canceled in California, mainly because so many homes were already producing solar power on their own rooftops, saving $2.6 billion in total consumer energy costs. More
The post Gavin Newsom’s War on Rooftop Solar Is a Bad Omen for the Country appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joshua Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To Avert Wider War in the Middle East, Biden Should Resign]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330749</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/to-avert-wider-war-in-the-middle-east-biden-should-resign/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Netanyahu sows chaos in order to keep himself in power (and out of jail), Biden merely mutters diplomatic niceties, while occasionally indicating he’s oh-so upset with his longtime friend. But Biden’s words matter less than his actions, and he keeps greenlighting Netanyahu’s warring by providing him with billions in weapons. Biden does this even though a wider war will endanger thousands of US troops at bases scattered throughout the Middle East. They’re “sitting ducks for local militias,” said Erik Sperling of Just Foreign Policy. More
The post To Avert Wider War in the Middle East, Biden Should Resign appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election 2024: A Step Back From The Permanent Campaign?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330867</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/election-2024-a-step-back-from-the-permanent-campaign/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“What if our campaigns were much, much shorter?” Ben Smith asks at Semafor. “The presidential campaign is currently a two-year cycle, which begins just after the prior midterm elections. … [Kamala] Harris is accidentally demonstrating the alternative: She’s the hot new thing in August, riding on vibes and goodwill six months after the Super Tuesday  More
The post Election 2024: A Step Back From The Permanent Campaign? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[They Would Not Know Us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330750</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/they-would-not-know-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone can be a barbarian; it requires a terrible effort to remain a civilized man. ~Leornard Woolf This week marks the 75th anniversary of the signing of the Geneva Conventions, an attempt by the world’s nations to restrain and prohibit the horrors and terrors of modern warfare. The victors of World War II were the  More
The post They Would Not Know Us appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Hoh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resisting AUKUS: The Paul Keating Formula]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330865</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/resisting-aukus-the-paul-keating-formula/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From his own redoubt of critical inquiry, the former Australian Prime Minister Paul Keating has made fighting the imperialising leprosy of the AUKUS security pact between Australia, the UK and the United States a matter of solemn duty. In March 15, 2023, he excoriated a Canberra press gallery seduced and tantalised by the prospect of nuclear-powered submarines,  More
The post Resisting AUKUS: The Paul Keating Formula appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Corporate Press (Finally) Sounds the Alarm on Project 2025 But Omits Warnings for Journalism and Media]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330869</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/the-corporate-press-finally-sounds-the-alarm-on-project-2025-but-omits-warnings-for-journalism-and-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of expert legal and public policy analysis, advocacy group warnings, and independent press reporting on the Presidential Transition Project 2025 (Project 2025 for short), the corporate press is finally catching up. Capturing headlines is Project 2025’s Mandate for Leadership, a 180-day playbook for the next conservative administration. Its authors are a cadre of ultra-conservative,  More
The post The Corporate Press (Finally) Sounds the Alarm on Project 2025 But Omits Warnings for Journalism and Media  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mischa Geracoulis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance is a Classic Example of “Poornography”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330758</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/jd-vance-is-a-classic-example-of-poornography/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JD Vance has climbed to his current position as former President Donald Trump’s running mate, in part, by selling himself as a hillbilly, calling on his Appalachian background to bolster his credentials to speak for the American working class. “I grew up as a poor kid,” Vance said on Fox News in August 2024. “I  More
The post JD Vance is a Classic Example of “Poornography” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lennard J. Davis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris Picking Walz Was All About the Electoral Votes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330753</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/harris-picking-walz-was-all-about-the-electoral-votes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many commentators have said that VP Kamala Harris should have selected Josh Shapiro, Governor of Pennsylvania rather than Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz. The most repeated reason for selecting Shapiro was that he could have probably secured Pennsylvania’s 19 electoral votes. They assume that Harris cannot win the election without winning that state. Their logic is  More
The post Harris Picking Walz Was All About the Electoral Votes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cult of Military Service: Tim Walz as Soldier-Teacher]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330840</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/the-cult-of-military-service-tim-walz-as-soldier-teacher/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Soon after Vice-President Kamala Harris introduced Minnesota Governor Tim Walz as her running mate, the attacks on his military record began. Quick comparisons were drawn in the media to the “Swiftboating” of Democratic candidate John Kerry in 2004. Too be straight about it, debating the finer points of Walz’s military record misses the larger point being made  More
The post The Cult of Military Service: Tim Walz as Soldier-Teacher appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Donald Trump Undermined the Health and Safety of American Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330842</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/how-donald-trump-undermined-the-health-and-safety-of-american-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During his four years as President of the United States, Donald Trump was remarkably active and often successful in sabotaging the health and safety of the nation’s workers. Trump, as the AFL-CIO noted, targeted Medicare and Medicaid for $1 trillion in funding cuts, eroded the Affordable Care Act (thereby increasing the number of Americans lacking health  More
The post How Donald Trump Undermined the Health and Safety of American Workers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Wittner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Homophobia’s Role in Political Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330901</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/15/homophobias-role-in-political-manipulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“People have faced attacks, evictions, and been denied access to health services.” This week, I spoke with Healy Thomson about the impact of the Anti-Homosexuality Act in Uganda. The legislation, signed into law last year, permits the death penalty for certain offences related to homosexuality. “Across Africa, LGBTI persons find themselves…confronting formidable obstacles to their  More
The post Homophobia’s Role in Political Manipulation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Young men aren’t shifting right …]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52985</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/15/young-men-arent-shifting-right/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T01:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[… at least in the “Anglosphere” One of the striking features of the racist riots in Britain has been the wide spread of ages among those (nearly all men) convicted so far[1]. This is unusual, since criminal violence of all kinds is most commonly associated with young men. And it’s a counter-example to what has […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Side discussion]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52983</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/15/side-discussion/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As requested by a couple of commenters, I’ve created a separate thread to discuss the issues raised by commenter “closet conservative” in response to my post on US academia. I’ll moderate, but not participate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.31: Accelerating Cluster Performance with Consistent Reads from Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/consistent-read-from-cache-beta/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/15/consistent-read-from-cache-beta/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is renowned for its robust orchestration of containerized applications,
but as clusters grow, the demands on the control plane can become a bottleneck.
A key challenge has been ensuring strongly consistent reads from the etcd datastore,
requiring resource-intensive quorum reads.
Today, the Kubernetes community is excited to announce a major improvement:
consistent reads from cache, graduating to Beta in Kubernetes v1.31.
Why consistent reads matter
Consistent reads are essential for ensuring that Kubernetes components have an accurate view of the latest cluster state.
Guaranteeing consistent reads is crucial for maintaining the accuracy and reliability of Kubernetes operations,
enabling components to make informed decisions based on up-to-date information.
In large-scale cluster…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta animates AI-generated images at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21542</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/14/production-engineering/how-meta-animates-ai-generated-images-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:20:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched Meta AI with the goal of giving people new ways to be more productive and unlock their creativity with generative AI (GenAI). But GenAI also comes with challenges of scale. As we deploy new GenAI technologies at Meta, we also focus on delivering these services to people as quickly and efficiently as possible. [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta animates AI-generated images at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat of AI, demise of blogging, the world in February 2015]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8288</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/threat-ai-demise-blogging-world-february-2015/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since re-booting disassociated in May 2022, I’ve been slowly (incredibly slowly) restoring selected posts from the previous version of the blog that was online between 2007 and 2017. The restored posts are tagged legacy, and also include a few posts written prior to 2007, going back to 2003. On checking as I typed this, I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending August 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240814</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240814"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Karpenter 1.0]]></title>
        <id>3adac2c0ec9122f00dd8e58fe5412f2d5a1d5f9f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/announcing-karpenter-1-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T20:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction In November 2021, AWS announced the launch of v0.5 of Karpenter, “a new open source Kubernetes cluster auto scaling project.” Originally conceived as a flexible, dynamic, and high-performance alternative to the Kubernetes Cluster Autoscaler, in the nearly three years since then Karpenter has evolved substantially into a fully featured, Kubernetes native node lifecycle manager. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Kestner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving Frugal Architecture using the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>663012dc40f89e066329be90a662febacc172e3c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/achieving-frugal-architecture-using-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T19:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the re:Invent 2023 keynote, Dr. Werner Vogels introduced the Frugal Architect mindset. This mindset emphasizes the importance of continuous learning, curiosity, and regular revision of architectural choices with a focus on cost and sustainability. Cost and sustainability should be treated as critical non-functional requirements, alongside factors like security, compliance, and performance. The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley DeLoach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TrackerFF in "How I won $2,750 using JavaScript, AI, and a can of WD-40"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41249310</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41249310"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T18:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that 75% of the post was OP checking the math on whether or not he should join the contest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TrackerFF</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276716</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T18:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by subsubzero in "Texas sues GM for unlaw­ful­ly collecting and selling dri­vers' pri­vate data [pdf]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41248584</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41248584"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T17:40:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fun fact, as a owner of a GMC auto I got a innocent looking email about the discontinuation of the Onstar Smart driver service which was the service in question that violated many US laws and sent data to insurance companies without customers authorization. I hope this hits GM really hard as this type of behavior will never cease until massive amounts of money is extracted from the perpetrators(GM etc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subsubzero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by slazaro in "Show HN: If YouTube had actual channels"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247704</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247704"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T16:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'd echo the sentiment that this is amazing, and that a TV guide would be awesome.
I'd also suggest maybe adding the channel names (like the comment you posted here) to the app itself (although i think it's cool when it's unnamed and you get the old-school feeling of channels just being numbers).
Also, I'd love to have permalinks for the channels. Not for the individual videos themselves, but just a link that when sharing would bring somebody else to the same channel you're watching right now.
Another thing, although probably outside your control, is that I use a Firefox extension called "SoundFixer" that I use to force the youtube audio to mono (since a lot of channels are annoying to me using headphones, they pan the audio sources too hard left/right and it's super distracting), but it doesn't seem to work on this website, probably because of the way they're embedded. I don't know if this can be changed somehow, or have a mode to force mono audio (which would be also oldschool like old TVs with one speaker only!). It's probably too niche and hard to do though.
Also I don't seem to find any volume control except mute?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>slazaro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tantalor in "Show HN: If YouTube had actual channels"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247268</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247268"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T15:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best part of this is the channel doesn't pause when you flip away from it. It is always "running" and if you flip away you will miss it. That builds in a FOMO trade-off which causes user to automatically/subconciously decide on channel they most want to watch, because they can't watch everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tantalor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hadisafa in "Show HN: If YouTube had actual channels"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247037</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41247037"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T15:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Channel 1: Science and Technology
Channel 2: Travel and Events
Channel 3: Food
Channel 4: Architecture
Channel 5: Film and Animation
Channel 6: Documentaries
Channel 7: Comedy
Channel 8: Music
Channel 9: Autos and Vehicles
Channel 10: News and Politics
Channel 11: UFC
Channel 12: Podcasts/Interviews/Talk Shows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hadisafa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yleisradio enhances digital services with Amazon EKS and IPv6 Adoption]]></title>
        <id>94c09e9e264ea0f58ded29d7f22edf19a693faf4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/yleisradio-enhances-digital-services-with-amazon-eks-and-ipv6-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T14:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yleisradio is a Finnish broadcasting company running most of its online and mobile services – which roughly 2.1 million Finns use every day – on AWS. Like many organizations, they use IP Address Management (IPAM) systems to allocate IP addresses across their AWS environment to make sure routing works, even between AWS and their on-premises […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Asuja</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Culture Clash: What 14 Million Images Tell Us About Times A-Changin’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276701</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/culture-clash-what-14-million-images-tell-us-about-times-a-changin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An effort to track culture changes over time via diversity of coiffure and attire....but the data has some not-acknowledged biases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paris 2024 Olympics recap: Internet trends, cyber threats, and popular moments]]></title>
        <id>66bbc4064a25d6000ae1cf95</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/paris-2024-olympics-recap"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Paris 2024 Olympics ended, our analysis shows the event’s impact on the Internet in France and other countries at different moments, its effect on specific web properties, and a spike in cyber threats and emails related to Simone Biles and others]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our media, Puigdemont's Catalonia and the violent undemocratic traditions of the Spanish state!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Our-media-Puigdemont-s-Catalonia-and-the-violent-undemocratic-traditions-of-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Our-media-Puigdemont-s-Catalonia-and-the-violent-undemocratic-traditions-of-the"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T12:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's true that we couldn't expect better coverage of the new Puigdemont affair from our media. For decades now, the international media, of almost all political persuasions, has either ignored the often historic events taking place in Catalonia, or presented them in a way that would not displease Madrid's rulers, of all persuasions, including the nostalgics of Franco. 
English

/ 
Spanish State]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[­­A New Set of Indicators of Reserve Ampleness]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31294</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/a-new-set-of-indicators-of-reserve-ampleness/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve (Fed) implements monetary policy in a regime of ample reserves, where short-term interest rates are controlled mainly through the setting of administered rates, and active management of the reserve supply is not required. In yesterday’s post, we proposed a methodology to evaluate the ampleness of reserves in real time based on the slope of the reserve demand curve—the elasticity of the federal (fed) funds rate to reserve shocks. In this post, we propose a suite of complementary indicators of reserve ampleness that, jointly with our elasticity measure, can help policymakers ensure that reserves remain ample as the Fed shrinks its balance sheet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Kevin Clark, Brian Gowen, Gabriele La Spada, JC Martinez, Jason Miu, and Will Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/14/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276625</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-14-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T10:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our vivid daily links: runaway turtle, Ozempic as magic? Covid Olympics, King Coal still reigns, China's rising diplomatic power, CIA in Argentina, Iran reaffirms retaliation, Kursk incursion debate, DEF CON Bluetooth and WiFI warning, Kamala planting fake news, EU retreats on Must, Google breakup? VCs heart jerks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on the War on Work as a War on Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276687</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/reflections-on-the-war-on-work-as-a-war-on-workers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T10:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recalling what good union jobs  once meant for workers and communities and describing some damage done by the war on labor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FDA Rejects MDMA-Assisted Therapy for PTSD Treatment – A Drug Researcher Explains the Challenges Psychedelics Face]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276690</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/fda-rejects-mdma-assisted-therapy-for-ptsd-treatment-a-drug-researcher-explains-the-challenges-psychedelics-face.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T10:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FDA is wary of approving club drugs like MDMA and psychedelics for medial purposes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Border]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52981</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/14/green-border/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T10:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I spent yesterday evening watching Agnieszka Holland’s remarkable film “Green Border” which has just been released to streaming in the UK after spending about 30 seconds in cinemas. The episode that provides the film’s context is the 2021 decision of Alexander Lukashenko, dictator of Belarus and Putin’s puppet, to make use of refugees as a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America Needs Intel Economically and Politically—But Is It Too Late?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276657</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/america-needs-intel-economically-and-politically-but-is-it-too-late.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T07:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Intel's storied history and self-destruction via greed, and now US stealthy financial support with no accountability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ecuador's poisoned loans from the World Bank and the IMF]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-s-poisoned-loans-from-the-World-Bank-and-the-IMF</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Ecuador-s-poisoned-loans-from-the-World-Bank-and-the-IMF"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. (...)
English

/ 
Ecuador, 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
South, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tgsovlerkhgsel in "Disney seeks dismissal of wrongful death lawsuit citing waiver in Disney+ terms"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41243048</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41243048"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T06:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The bug in the legal system is that by filing this motion/claim, Disney can only win.
In the unlikely best case, they get the case dismissed, but even in the most likely case that the motion is denied, they win by wearing down their opponent who has much more limited resources and is personally affected by the case dragging out, i.e. more likely to accept a (lower) settlement than without this tactic. The only downside is a tiny bit of legal costs.
Courts should be able to issue sanctions/extra damages for the use of such tactics. If using such a tactic turned the claim from "you killed this person negligently" to "you killed this person negligently, then willfully tried sleazy tricks to create additional suffering for the husband", and had the potential to double the award, companies would be much less eager to play this game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tgsovlerkhgsel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Capitalism, Mass Anger and the 2024 Elections]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330695</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/capitalism-mass-anger-and-the-2024-elections/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T06:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the wake of his huge defeat on June 30, 2024, when 80 percent of voters rejected French “centrist” President Emmanuel Macron, he said he understood the French people’s anger. In the UK, Conservative loser Rishi Sunak said the same about the British people’s anger, as Labor leader Starmer now says as the anger explodes.  More
The post Capitalism, Mass Anger and the 2024 Elections appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[African Politics is Invisible to the Wider World: How Nigeria Became a ‘Soldier’s Paradise’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330770</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/african-politics-is-invisible-to-the-wider-world-how-nigeria-became-a-soldiers-paradise/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“If you want to keep militaries out of civilian politics, you have to offer people some other way,” scholar argues. British rule had profound effects on Nigeria starting in the late 1800s and largely included economic, political, social, and cultural forms of imperialism. Many of the devastating impacts are still visible in the country today and are especially  More
The post African Politics is Invisible to the Wider World: How Nigeria Became a ‘Soldier’s Paradise’ appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Vice-Presidential Pick Tim Walz Make Democrats the Education Party Again?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330800</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/can-vice-presidential-pick-tim-walz-make-democrats-the-education-party-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In choosing Minnesota Governor Tim Walz to be her running mate, Vice President and Democratic presidential candidate Kamala Harris has not only picked a progressive governor and a Midwestern populist to lead the party’s national ticket but she also may have signaled that the Democratic Party is ready to take back its reputation as the education party.  More
The post Can Vice-Presidential Pick Tim Walz Make Democrats the Education Party Again? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Bryant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Death by Incarceration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330804</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/death-by-incarceration/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Walter Bourque, Jr., has been incarcerated in New Hampshire for 68 years for the murder of a 4-year-old girl in December 1955.  Kenneth Nicely has been incarcerated in Arkansas for 65 years for killing a police officer.  And Francis “Frank” Smith served 72 years in a Connecticut facility for his part in the killing of a night watchman until 2022 when,  More
The post Death by Incarceration appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rosen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Will Coach the Coaches? Reflections on Tim Walz, the United Front and High School Football]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330802</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/who-will-coach-the-coaches-reflections-on-tim-walz-the-united-front-and-high-school-football/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent stories about Tim Walz— the governor of Minnesota, and Kamala Harris’s running mate— which have emphasized his days as a football coach, reminded me of my years as an athlete who played football and lacrosse and who also wrestled in the 158-pound weight class— all under the watchful eyes of a handful of  More
The post Who Will Coach the Coaches? Reflections on Tim Walz, the United Front and High School Football appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: The Sun Also Rises]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330657</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/letter-from-london-the-sun-also-rises/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One morning last week I headed out to the local newsagents in what had rapidly become an overexcitable land. The sun was warm on my face. There wasn’t a cloud in the sky. The local butcher shop was being gutted for refurbishment. The nearby Turkish food store was not quite open yet. The optician was  More
The post Letter from London: The Sun Also Rises appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rat Poison is Threatening Carnivores Around the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330650</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/rat-poison-is-threatening-carnivores-around-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This mountain lion, known as P-47, was found dead in Southern California on March 21, 2019, with rat poison in his system. National Park Service via AP Rats thrive around humans, for good reason: They feed off crops and garbage and readily adapt to many settings, from farms to the world’s largest cities. To control  More
The post Rat Poison is Threatening Carnivores Around the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meghan P. Keating</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mountain Bikers Push to Ride Through Wilderness]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330664</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/mountain-bikers-push-to-ride-through-wilderness/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:42:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Something will have gone out of us as a people if we ever let the remaining wilderness be destroyed…” — Wallace Stegner The goal of the Wilderness Act, now celebrating its 60th birthday, was to set aside a small proportion of public land in America from human intrusion. Some places, the founders said, deserved to be  More
The post Mountain Bikers Push to Ride Through Wilderness appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Proescholdt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Iran Strike Israel?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330649</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/will-iran-strike-israel/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iran may be about to launch a proper missile strike on Israel for the first time ever – in retaliation for the attack on Tehran last month which killed Ismail Haniyeh.  Israeli intelligence says an attack is likely to come within days. The Jerusalem Post on 11 August quoted Ahmad Bakhshayesh Ardestani, a member of  More
The post Will Iran Strike Israel? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harris and Trump Agree on a Key Point: Moths Will Not Be a 2024 Campaign Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330724</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/14/harris-and-trump-agree-on-a-key-point-moths-will-not-be-a-2024-campaign-issue/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent column, Paul Street wrote how there “are plenty of deadly sirens in contemporary American life but few are as powerful as the savagely time-staggered big money corporate crafted narrow spectrum major party big media candidate-centered ‘quadrennial [electoral] extravaganzas’—Noam Chomsky’s term—that are sold to the masses as ‘politics,’ the only politics that matters.” Street is  More
The post Harris and Trump Agree on a Key Point: Moths Will Not Be a 2024 Campaign Issue appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by torstenvl in "Disney seeks dismissal of wrongful death lawsuit citing waiver in Disney+ terms"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41242682</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41242682"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T04:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the agreement at the time is anything like the current agreement, this is a serious misrepresentation to the court.
The terms do require Disney+ users to "agree to resolve, by binding individual arbitration as provided below, all Disputes" with some IP exceptions.
But "Disputes" is a term of art that "includes any claim, dispute, action, or other controversy, whether based on past, present, or future events, whether based in contract, tort, statute, or common law, between you and Disney concerning the Disney Products or this Agreement" (emphasis added).
What are the Disney Products? They are "certain websites, software, applications, content, products, and services in any media format or channel."
I hope the lawyers get sanctioned and disbarred.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>torstenvl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by chc4 in "Google Pixel 9 Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41241219</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41241219"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have negative desire to get a phone billing itself around AI and LLM features. I turn off every AI assistant feature on my existing devices, I actively don't want a phone that ties Gemini and AI photoshop even tighter into it. If Google wanted to actually improve their phones they would add basic software functionality they're still missing instead like, say, a per-app volume mixer that half the 3rd party Android phones I've used have added but is still missing from AOSP and Pixel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>chc4</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 1.31: Moving cgroup v1 Support into Maintenance Mode]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/14/kubernetes-1-31-moving-cgroup-v1-support-maintenance-mode/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/14/kubernetes-1-31-moving-cgroup-v1-support-maintenance-mode/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Kubernetes continues to evolve and adapt to the changing landscape of
container orchestration, the community has decided to move cgroup v1 support
into maintenance mode in v1.31.
This shift aligns with the broader industry's move towards cgroup v2, offering
improved functionalities: including scalability and a more consistent interface.
Before we dive into the consequences for Kubernetes, let's take a step back to
understand what cgroups are and their significance in Linux.
Understanding cgroups
Control groups, or
cgroups, are a Linux kernel feature that allows the allocation, prioritization,
denial, and management of system resources (such as CPU, memory, disk I/O,
and network bandwidth) among processes. This functionality is crucial for
maintaining system performance and ensuring that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.31: PersistentVolume Last Phase Transition Time Moves to GA]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/14/last-phase-transition-time-ga/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/14/last-phase-transition-time-ga/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the graduation to General Availability (GA) of the PersistentVolume lastTransitionTime status
field, in Kubernetes v1.31!
The Kubernetes SIG Storage team is excited to announce that the "PersistentVolumeLastPhaseTransitionTime" feature, introduced
as an alpha in Kubernetes v1.28, has now reached GA status and is officially part of the Kubernetes v1.31 release. This enhancement
helps Kubernetes users understand when a PersistentVolume transitions between
different phases, allowing for more efficient and informed resource management.
For a v1.31 cluster, you can now assume that every PersistentVolume object has a
.status.lastTransitionTime field, that holds a timestamp of
when the volume last transitioned its phase. This change is not immediate; the new field will be populated whenever a PersistentVolume
is updated and first transitions between phases (Pending, Bound, or Released) after upgrading to Kubernetes v1.31.
What changed?
The API strategy for updating PersistentVolume objects has been modified to populate the .status.lastTransitionTime field with the
current timestamp whenever a PersistentVolume transitions phases. Users are allowed to set this field manually if needed, but it will
be overwritten when the PersistentVolume transitions phases again.
For more details, read about
Phase transition timestamp in the Kubernetes documentation.
You can also read the previous blog post announcing the feature as alpha in v1.28.
To provide feedback, join our Kubernetes Storage Special-Interest-Group (SIG)
or participate in discussions on our public Slack channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manufacturing jobs: unions made them good, not the factories]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45537</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/13/manufacturing-jobs-unions-made-them-good-not-the-factories/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T21:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The effort to bring back manufacturing jobs has been a major theme in the 2024 election. Both parties say they consider this a high priority for the next administration. However, there is a notable difference in that the Biden-Harris administration has actively supported an increase in unionization, while the Republicans have indicated, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create an AI version of yourself on Instagram to do who knows what]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8281</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/create-ai-version-yourself-instagram/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T21:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe back in 2006, I was in a discussion with then Australian web designer Jen Leheny, on the then forums of the Australian INfront, a design community we had helped establish in the late 1990’s, about WordPress. I was still using static HTML files to run disassociated, but was considering migrating to the then much […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven thousand five hundred tabs open in Firefox, a new world record?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8275</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/seven-thousand-five-hundred-tabs-firefox-new-world-record/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T20:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dedicated Firefox web browser fan had nearly seven thousand five hundred browser tabs open, all at the same time, at one point. And maybe still does. Seven thousand five hundred? I feel I’m lucky to have seventy-five tabs, no, half that number really, open, across the three browsers I run, which include Firefox. That […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by appel in "Google Pixel 9 Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237927</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237927"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T18:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm glad they finally went this route. I can't be the only one who usually wants the specs of the Pro but always opts for the smallest phone (p1, p3, p5 & now p8).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>appel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by myself248 in "Captain Disillusion debunks David Beckham beach kicks [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237660</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237660"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T17:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Captain D produces some of the most impressive technical content out there, wrapped in subtle and not-so-subtle zingers, and breathtakingly illustrated. Decomposing a frame into its brightness channel, rotating it, and collapsing the columns to make a waveform graph? Mind completely blown.
The debunk videos are his major stock in trade, but I personally love (and discovered him through) the explainers about frame rate and shutter speed, color spaces, interlacing, and other details of the video art.
And of course, his mindbogglingly detailed exploration of Flight of the Navigator -- if you've seen the film, make some time tonight and watch it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>myself248</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bloggie in "Google Pixel 9 Pro"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237483</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41237483"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T17:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Unlock Gemini Advanced for a year on us ($239 value)"
Who thinks they are booking phone sales as AI revenue to juice the numbers?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bloggie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AWS powered Prime Day 2024 for record-breaking sales]]></title>
        <id>d7b5d20444338457f621b12a46f70828e2d3fbc6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/how-aws-powered-prime-day-2024-for-record-breaking-sales/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T16:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dive into the numbers from Amazon's record-breaking Prime Day 2024, from AI chip deployment to the staggering transaction volumes across AWS services like Amazon DynamoDB, Aurora, CloudFront, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Richard Seymour: &ldquo;Dreaming of Downfall&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/dreaming-of-downfall</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/dreaming-of-downfall"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:43:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Riots in the UK.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[P-Sets in Philosophy]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52976</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/13/p-sets-in-philosophy/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, I received my contributor copy of The Art of Teaching Philosophy: Reflective Values and Concrete Practices, edited by Brynn Welch.[1] It’s an exciting book, and I’m proud to have gotten to contribute to it. My chapter on advising graduate students about teaching was coauthored with an excellent teacher (and researcher), a near-former […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gina Schouten</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing HTTP request traffic insights on Cloudflare Radar]]></title>
        <id>66b64e2b4a25d6000ae1cc8f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/http-requests-on-cloudflare-radar"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traffic graphs on Cloudflare Radar have been enhanced to include HTTP request traffic. This new metric complements the existing bytes-based “HTTP traffic” view, and the new graphs can be found on Radar’s Overview and Traffic pages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by elzbardico in "NASA investigation finds Boeing hindering Americans' return to moon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41234572</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41234572"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T11:57:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What MBAs and Financists destroyed so far:
- Western Industry.
- The blue-collar middle class
- The Middle Class
- Our health care system
- Our education
- Western Economic Leadership.
- Social Mobility
Now they are busy destroying western technology, science and innovation on their never-ending selfish wealth-extraction quest.
They convinced us that our homes are investments, so they can fleece us with their usurary schemes. So, what next? our organs?
They convinced us to exchange our pensions for the privilege of being the mark on a market where the sharks like them do whatever the fuck they want, from blatant insider trading, to pump and dump schemes, to outright fraud, having for all practical purposes bought the SEC a long time ago.
What they will kill next?
How long are we going to transfer wealth to those slimmy sweet talking ignorant greedy bean counters?
Our daily work is like being in a mad house because almost everything is subordinated to the the most sacred goal of cooking the next quarter numbers to ensure we maximize executive bonuses, and fuck the long run! crazy projects started, spin offs, merges, projects cancelled, company killing layoffs, fuck long term value generation! they want more and more, and more, and they fucking want it right now! the fucking bonus gollums.
Everything is fucked in our society but executive compensation. Xerox, HP, IBM, Boeing... How many other proud symbols of our economy and civilization are we going to let them destroy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>elzbardico</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Are Central Bank Reserves Ample?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31340</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/when-are-central-bank-reserves-ample/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Reserve (Fed) implements monetary policy in a regime of ample reserves, whereby short-term interest rates are controlled mainly through the setting of administered rates. To do so, the quantity of reserves in the banking system needs to be large enough that everyday changes in reserves do not cause large variations in the policy rate, the so-called federal funds rate. As the Fed shrinks its balance sheet following the plan laid out by the Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) in 2022, how can it assess when to stop so that the supply of reserves remains ample? In the first post of a two-part series, based on the methodology developed in our recent Staff Report, we propose to assess the ampleness of reserves in real time by estimating the slope of the reserve demand curve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Domenico Giannone, Gabriele La Spada, and John C. Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Duane Rousselle - Preface to Turkish Edition of “Post-Anarchism and Psychoanalysis”]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-preface-to-turkish-edition?v=1723543794</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/duane-rousselle-preface-to-turkish-edition?v=1723543794"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Duane Rousselle
Title: Preface to Turkish Edition of “Post-Anarchism and Psychoanalysis”
Date: 2024
Source: duanerousselle.medium.com

The following is a preliminary draft of the preface to the Turkish edition of my book Post-Anarchism and Psychoanalysis, which will be published in a few months.
 This book is the result of spoken improvisations that occurred during a strange period of wandering. I was removed from my position as Professor and Chair of Sociology at a major Russian university due in part to a renewed military conflict between Russia and Ukraine. The consequent wandering extended also to the streets of Tomsk, Sochi, Nur Sultan, Vienna, and Budapest, before arriving for a prolonged residential retreat in Cork, Ireland, under a temporary protection order from the Europe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Years After the Death of Michael Brown, the Conditions That Led to the Uprisings Remain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330628</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/ten-years-after-the-death-of-michael-brown-the-conditions-that-led-to-the-uprisings-remain/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T06:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[April 29, 1992: I am in Harlem, preparing for my AAU basketball team practice in Riverside Church’s basement. As I am warming up, my coach suggests I leave immediately. He had heard unrest was likely to erupt on 125th Street after the acquittal of the police who brutally beat Rodney King in Los Angeles (LA).  More
The post Ten Years After the Death of Michael Brown, the Conditions That Led to the Uprisings Remain appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Hyra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comfy in Camo: Getting to Know Tim Walz]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330667</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/comfy-in-camo-getting-to-know-tim/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kase Wickman at Vanity Fair calls it big dad energy. Tim Walz brings “a long military career, recognition in the Midwest, a white male presence…” And how about the image of Walz hugging a piglet at the Minnesota State Fair? And the video of Walz thinking about finding a corn dog… But Walz’s daughter, Hope, is  More
The post Comfy in Camo: Getting to Know Tim Walz appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No First Use of Nuclear Weapons: Rejecting Nuclear Annihilation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330573</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/no-first-use-of-nuclear-weapons-rejecting-nuclear-annihilation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent collapse of nuclear weapons talks between China and the United States in July 2024, followed the withdrawal by the U.S. and Russia from long-established nuclear weapons treaties, like the Anti-Ballistic Missile Treaty, (ABM) Intermediate-Range Forces Treaty (INF), and The Iran Nuclear Deal (JPCOA). Nuclear tensions have regressed to dangerous levels not seen since the Cold War. More
The post No First Use of Nuclear Weapons: Rejecting Nuclear Annihilation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Muhich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fish ‘n Chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330708</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/fish-n-chips/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The King of any Countrey is the Publique Person, or Representative of all his own subjects. And God the King of Israel was the Holy one of Israel. The Nation which is subject to one earthly Soveraign, is the Nation of the Soveraign, that is, of the Publique Person. So the Jews, who were Gods Nation, were called (Exod.  More
The post Fish ‘n Chips appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Gilk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Tale of Two Horrid Tales]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330715</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/a-tale-of-two-horrid-tales/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tale Number One On 19 July 2024, Donald Trump gave a speech to “The Believers’ Summit,” a gathering of Christian fundamentalists seeking “practical knowledge and strategies to live out their faith boldly and counteract the prevailing ‘woke’ narratives.” Among other chimeras spun that evening, Trump implied to his audience that in four years hence there would be  More
The post A Tale of Two Horrid Tales appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private Fortunes vs. Public Education]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330625</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/private-fortunes-vs-public-education/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The United States essentially invented public education. Back in the 1780s, notes the Center on Education Policy, federal legislation “granted federal lands to new states and set aside a portion of those lands to be used to fund public schools.” By the 18th century’s close, most Americans had embraced the notion of “using public funds  More
The post Private Fortunes vs. Public Education appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A False Accusation Put Me in Prison, a Safety Net Could Have Kept Me Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330719</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/a-false-accusation-put-me-in-prison-a-safety-net-could-have-kept-me-out/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I received a 60-year prison sentence for a murder I didn’t commit. After 25 years of fighting this injustice, I was exonerated. I’ve learned some hard lessons about our criminal justice system. I’ve also learned how simple safety net policies — like a modest guaranteed base income or no-strings-attached child allowance — could have kept  More
The post A False Accusation Put Me in Prison, a Safety Net Could Have Kept Me Out appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leon Benson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Putting War and Peace on the Ballot]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330709</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/putting-war-and-peace-on-the-ballot/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:51:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The corporate media report on elections — especially the biggie coming up — as though they were sporting events. If you win, hurray! You get the gold cup or whatever. The election process is a matter of shrewd strategy combined with, uh, likability. Thus, as per the New York Times: “Tim Walz is going to bring  More
The post Putting War and Peace on the Ballot appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enough With The “Stolen Valor” Whining Already]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330627</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/13/enough-with-the-stolen-valor-whining-already/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:45:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ah, the tempest teapot of vice-presidential campaigns: Republican veep nominee JD Vance, Senator from Ohio, accuses Democratic veep nominee apparent Tim Walz, governor of Minnesota, of engaging in “stolen valor garbage.” Vance’s allegations seem to involve three components: First, that Walz retired from the National Guard after 24 years in infantry and artillery jobs, instead  More
The post Enough With The “Stolen Valor” Whining Already appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by azinman2 in "Study shows that tacking the “AI” label on products may drive people away"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41232477</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41232477"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:15:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> said Dogan Gursoy, one of the study’s authors and the Taco Bell Distinguished Professor of hospitality business management at Washington State University
The irony… I cannot imagine a more hilariously negative way to reduce a title than to say someone is the Taco Bell professor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>azinman2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes v1.31: Elli]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/13/kubernetes-v1-31-release/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/13/kubernetes-v1-31-release/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editors: Matteo Bianchi, Yigit Demirbas, Abigail McCarthy, Edith Puclla, Rashan Smith
Announcing the release of Kubernetes v1.31: Elli!
Similar to previous releases, the release of Kubernetes v1.31 introduces new
stable, beta, and alpha features.
The consistent delivery of high-quality releases underscores the strength of our development cycle and the vibrant support from our community.
This release consists of 45 enhancements.
Of those enhancements, 11 have graduated to Stable, 22 are entering Beta,
and 12 have graduated to Alpha.
Release theme and logo
The Kubernetes v1.31 Release Theme is "Elli".
Kubernetes v1.31's Elli is a cute and joyful dog, with a heart of gold and a nice sailor's cap, as a playful wink to the huge and diverse family of Kubernetes contributors.
Kubernetes v1.31 mar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mananaysiempre in "NASA investigation finds Boeing hindering Americans' return to moon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41230563</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41230563"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T23:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> During a visit to Michoud in 2023, for example, inspectors discovered that welding on a component of the SLS Core Stage 3 did not meet NASA standards. Per the report, unsatisfactory welding performed on a set of fuel tanks led directly to a seven-month delay in EUS completion.
> “According to NASA officials, the welding issues arose due to Boeing’s inexperienced technicians and inadequate work order planning and supervision,” the OIG says. [...]
Welders are highly qualified and well-paid craftsmen. Wouldn’t surprise me if they’d been hit particularly hard by management that doesn’t value tenured, expensive employees.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mananaysiempre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rising together: honoring Cloudflare’s outstanding partners]]></title>
        <id>66b3ff414a25d6000ae1ca29</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/partner-award-winners-2023"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T22:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s success is fueled by exceptional partnerships. Our PowerUP program empowers these collaborations, driving innovation, profitability, and growth. We celebrate outstanding achievements with the Partner Awards. Let’s recognize the partners shaping our future]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by FickleRaptor in "Room inspections at Resorts World confuse, annoy DEF CON attendees"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41229769</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41229769"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T21:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was walking through resortsworld when a security guard started walking next to us. After about 50 feet, he demanded our ID, informed us we were on private property, and threatened to have us arrested for trespassing, all in the same sentence. The issue was that my colleague was one of the amateur radio VE for the ham radio village and happened to have his handheld with him. The guard was aggressive, entitled, and arrogant.
Yesterday, I poked another friend to see where they were at the conference. They were not at the conference. They were stuck at resorts world three hours after the conference had started. Their conference badges had been confiscated by security. The security team had tried to force them to throw them in the garbage, and for a while it appeared that security had thrown …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>FickleRaptor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The website song: everyone is free to write websites, an IndieWeb anthem]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8271</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/website-song-everyone-free-write-websites-indieweb-anthem/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody’s Free (To Write Websites), by Robb Knight, and Keenan. Spectacularly riffing off Australian filmmaker Baz Luhrmann’s 1999 video, the Sunscreen Song, this is for the graduating Indie Web class of whenever. There is an abundance of sage advice here. If I could offer you only one tip for the future, coding would be it. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Corporate jargon alternatives by Matt Watson]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8267</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/corporate-jargon-alternatives-matt-watson/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American web developer Matt Watson has re-written many latter-day, jarring, corporate-speak terms, with words and phrases from long past times. For instance, instead of “circle back”, say “bring word again”. Or, replace “open communication” with the surely eye-brow raising “regular intercourse”. In other examples, ASAP becomes “betimes”, change agent (what?) becomes “efficient cause”, while lean […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hed in "Federal appeals court finds geofence warrants “categorically” unconstitutional"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228818</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228818"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Unsurprisingly, however, the court found that in 2018, police could have relied on such a warrant in “good faith,” because geofence technology was novel, and police reached out to other agencies with more experience for guidance. This means that the evidence they obtained will not be suppressed in this case.
That the guy's case gets a right affirmed yet in his individual case it won't make a difference has to be a pretty bitter pill to swallow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by danShumway in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228545</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41228545"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T19:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another point that Patreon isn't really emphasizing here that seems relevant to any conversations about "fairness" is that Apple's fees on Patreon subscriptions in-app are now higher than Patreon's fees.
It's important to recognize any time that we're talking about the market that services charge what they can, not what is fair. The market does not have a concept of fairness, only competition. This is why there is no such thing as a benevolent monopoly that charges fair prices - because fairness does not exist in the market, only competition.
BUT... since fairness gets so often brought into conversations about Apple's fees, often with the implicit suggestion that Apple "deserves" to be compensated for all of the work they're putting into hosting and curating apps and for (in heavy quotes) "creating" a market that they supposedly also don't have duopoly control over: does anybody want to argue that Apple hosting the Patreon app on iOS provides more value to Patreon subscribers and creators than the existence of Patreon itself does?
Like, if we're going to talk about what's egregious and what's not egregious, charging higher fees per-transaction than the platforms you are hosting seems like it might be a good indicator that things have gotten out of control.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danShumway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by AlexandrB in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41227566</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41227566"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T18:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has quietly been one of the biggest culprits in the proliferation of subscription software. They still don't support upgrades/upgrade pricing. Subscriptions are also the easiest way to implement a software demo or trial in the App Store. Finally they use their control of the App Store to coerce anyone doing something different than monthly/yearly subscriptions into that model (as we see here).
It sucks big time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AlexandrB</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize your .NET application using AWS App2Container and AWS Toolkit for .NET]]></title>
        <id>320801e855cd9287d2d4d32d6e3f92c93b03b8c3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/replatform-and-refactor-your-workload-to-aws-using-aws-app2container-and-aws-toolkit-for-net-refactoring-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview As businesses increasingly embrace cloud computing, many organizations are seeking to migrate their existing .NET applications from on-premises data centers to AWS. However, the transition of these workloads can often be complex and time-consuming. To simplify this process, AWS App2Container(A2C) is a robust command-line tool that assists users in lifting and shifting their on-premises […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shubham Sharan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Getir optimized their Amazon EKS compute using Karpenter]]></title>
        <id>c830c70b5a62c96358f60beae8c9ec9b409b72ff</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-getir-optimized-their-amazon-eks-compute-using-karpenter/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Getir is the pioneer of ultrafast grocery delivery. Getir was founded in 2015 and revolutionized last-mile delivery with its grocery in-minutes delivery proposition. Today, Getir is a conglomerate incorporating nine verticals under the same brand. Challenge Getir uses Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) to host applications on AWS. One of the foremost challenges […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tunahan Yediel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Mithra, Amazon Titan Image Generator v2, AWS GenAI Lofts, and more (August 12, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>3760f7c717826e880f11a584dc886851e903659a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-mithra-amazon-titan-image-generator-v2-aws-genai-lofts-and-more-august-12-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Dr. Swami Sivasubramanian, VP of AI and Data, was an intern at Amazon in 2005, Dr. Werner Vogels, CTO of Amazon, was his first manager. Nineteen years later, the two shared a stage at the VivaTech Conference to reflect on Amazon’s history of innovation—from pioneering the pay-as-you-go model with Amazon Web Services (AWS) to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bkraz in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41226460</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41226460"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a longtime YouTube creator who uses Patreon for financial support, the news is terrible: Patreon informed me that all creators must switch to a monthly subscription schedule instead of the per-creation schedule that I and many other currently use. The whole point of per-creation is that it allows me to take time off, and only charge people when I release something, thus incentivizing me, and being fair to my supporters. I'm really annoyed by this change, and will start pushing back, but if it happens as planned, I may be forced to switch to another platform, or come up with some other solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bkraz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by whywhywhywhy in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225827</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225827"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world where Apple is just completely fine with Apple users paying $13 instead of $10 for a subscription if they do it through an app is an interesting one.
Obviously this makes a lot of money for them but when you think about it they must think very little of their customers treating them with disrespect like this. This is how 'Tim Cook's Apple' should be remembered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>whywhywhywhy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jprete in "Apple's requirements are about to hit creators and fans on Patreon"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225668</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41225668"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:38:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember reading that per-creation billing is a very important feature for Patreon creators, because it removes the moral obligation to produce content just to justify a subscription.
If Patreon really doesn't want to kill the feature itself, but is just responding to Apple's enforcement, then it seems like a really clear illustration of monopoly power - pushing unrelated markets to change their own structure and products just to fit Apple's preferred billing flow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jprete</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deirdre McCloskey’s shallow and misleading rhetoric]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45535</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/12/deirdre-mccloskeys-shallow-and-misleading-rhetoric/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll This is not new to most of you of course. You are already steeped in McCloskey’s Rhetoric. Or you ought to be. After all economists are simply telling stories about the economy. Sometimes we are taken in. Sometimes we are not. Unfortunately McCloskey herself gets a little too caught up in her […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lairv in "Go is my hammer, and everything is a nail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41224877</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41224877"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T14:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go is everything I don’t want in a language for my personal projects. It’s verbose, every simple task feels like a lot to write. It’s not expressive, what would be a one-liner in Python makes you write three for loops in Go. I constantly need to find workarounds for the lack of proper enums, lack of sum types, no null safety etc.
I’m sure these are the exact reasons why Go is good for enterprise software, but for personal projects, I get no fun out of using it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lairv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bborud in "Go is my hammer, and everything is a nail"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41224825</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41224825"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T14:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People always under-estimate the cost of properly learning a language.  At any given time I tend to have a "main go-to language".  I typically spend 2-4 years getting to the point where I can say I "know" a language.  Then I try to stick to it long enough for the investment to pay off.  Usually 8-10 years.
A surprising number of people think this is a very long time. It isn't.  This is typically the time it takes to understand enough of the language, the compiler, the runtime, the standard library, and idiomatic ways to do things.  It is the time it takes to where you can start to meaningfully contribute to evolving how the language is used and meaningfully coach architects, programmers and system designers. It is also what you need to absorb novices into the organization and train them fast.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bborud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing Threat Intelligence: JA4 fingerprints and inter-request signals]]></title>
        <id>667deb80a4598c000bd706b4</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/ja4-signals"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T13:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how Cloudflare's JA4 fingerprinting and inter-request signals provide robust and scalable insights for advanced web security and threat detection]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Bocharov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reallocating Liquidity to Resolve a Crisis]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30992</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/reallocating-liquidity-to-resolve-a-crisis/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shortly after the collapse of Silicon Valley Bank (SVB) in March 2023, a consortium of eleven large U.S. financial institutions deposited $30 billion into First Republic Bank to bolster its liquidity and assuage panic among uninsured depositors. In the end, however, First Republic Bank did not survive, raising the question of whether a reallocation of liquidity among financial institutions can ever reduce the need for central bank balance sheet expansion in the fight against bank runs. We explore this question in this post, based on a recent working paper.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kinda Hachem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Feature Gates to Client-Go: Enhancing Flexibility and Control]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/12/feature-gates-in-client-go/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/12/feature-gates-in-client-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes components use on-off switches called feature gates to manage the risk of adding a new feature.
The feature gate mechanism is what enables incremental graduation of a feature through the stages Alpha, Beta, and GA.
Kubernetes components, such as kube-controller-manager and kube-scheduler, use the client-go library to interact with the API.
The same library is used across the Kubernetes ecosystem to build controllers, tools, webhooks, and more. client-go now includes
its own feature gating mechanism, giving developers and cluster administrators more control over how they adopt client features.
To learn more about feature gates in Kubernetes, visit Feature Gates.
Motivation
In the absence of client-go feature gates, each new feature separated feature availability from enablement i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mark and Evette Moran Nib Literary Nib Award 2024 longlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8264</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/mark-evette-moran-nib-literary-nib-award-2024-longlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T21:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seventeen books have been included on the recently announced Mark and Evette Moran Nib Literary Nib Award 2024 longlist. Also known as the “Nib”, the literary award celebrates excellence in Australian literary research, and as such works of any genre, including fiction, non-fiction, and autobiography, are eligible for inclusion. A Very Secret Trade, by Cassandra […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing about Kissing by Kathryn Lomer wins 2024 Furphy literary award]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8259</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/nothing-about-kissing-kathryn-lomer-wins-2024-literary-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T20:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hobart based Australian poet, and young adult writer, Kathryn Lomer, has been named winner of the 2024 Furphy literary award for short stories, with her work Nothing about Kissing (PDF). Set in Tasmania’s Museum of Old and New Art (Mona), also in Hobart, Nothing about Kissing, is the story of an unnamed museum cleaner, who’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bangladesh : Who is Muhammad Yunus, the new prime minister ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-Who-is-Muhammad-Yunus-the-new-primer-minister</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Bangladesh-Who-is-Muhammad-Yunus-the-new-primer-minister"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T17:21:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CADTM welcomes the departure of Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina as a victory for the courageous student movement, which has been in July-August 2024 the victim of a terrible repression that left over 400 people dead. Nevertheless, given the social and economic orientation of the new Prime Minister, Muhammad Yunus, we can only fear that the neo-liberal capitalist extractivist export model will continue and that the debt system will also continue. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Bangladesh, 
Capitalism, 
South, 
Microcredit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM, Denise Comanne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by erlend_sh in "Verso – Web browser built on top of the Servo web engine"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41216030</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41216030"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T13:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In other exciting Servo-browser news, Servo and Redox OS have submitted a joint proposal to fund the porting of SpiderMonkey and WebRender to Redox: https://www.redox-os.org/news/this-month-240731/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>erlend_sh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Cranes]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52970</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/11/sunday-photoblogging-cranes/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gklitz in "Captain Disillusion debunks David Beckham beach kicks [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41214646</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41214646"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T07:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As always this is so much more than merely a video debunking. It’s a great piece of comedy, an insightful analysis of technology and even great commentary on the historical development both back when the video was made but also the now current state of the environment around social media creators. Absolutely amazing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gklitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roderick McMillan - Can Stoicism Be Reconciled With Anarchy?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/roderick-mcmillan-how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with-anarchy?v=1723312426</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/roderick-mcmillan-how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with-anarchy?v=1723312426"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T17:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Roderick McMillan
Title: Can Stoicism Be Reconciled With Anarchy?
Subtitle: A comparative examination of Anarcho-Stoicism
Date: 10th August 2024
Source: Retrieved on August 10, 2024 from https://morewretchthansage.substack.com/p/how-can-stoicism-be-reconciled-with

How can Stoicism, a philosophy that has largely come down to us from the hierarchical, centralised, statist, Roman Empire and whose most famous adherent was an absolute Monarch, be reconciled with Anarchy?
 At first consideration Anarchy and Stoicism seem unlikely bedfellows. Much of Stoicism has come down to us through the Roman' Late Stoa' of Seneca, Epictetus, and Marcus Aurelius. Seneca was a Billionaire slave-owner politician, and Marcus Aurelius was an absolute monarch… but Epictetus was a disabled enslaved person,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nicola Gai - Declaration at the trial]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nicola-gai-declaration-at-the-trial?v=1723294215</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nicola-gai-declaration-at-the-trial?v=1723294215"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T12:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nicola Gai
Title: Declaration at the trial
Date: November 11, 2013
Source: <actforfree.nostate.net/?p=15519>. Retrieved on 19/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

Declaration at the trial (October 30 2013) for the wounding of Ansaldo Nucleare managing director Roberto Adinolfi
 ‘Nobody can judge me 
 Not even you 
 The truth hurts you, I know.’ 
 C. Caselli 
 A few words to make a few simple points before the ‘truth’ is pronounced by the court; just in case it’s not clear, I am using the word ‘truth’ ironically as I don’t recognize any tribunal other than my own conscience. The only ones responsible for what happened in Genoa on May 7 2012 are Alfredo and myself. None of our friends or comrades knew what we were planning and then carried out. No matter how far you dig into our lives and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mistercow in "A wonderful coincidence or an expected connection: why π² ≈ g"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41209068</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41209068"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T12:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is interesting, but I have to quibble with this:
> If you express this value in any other units, the magic immediately disappears. So, this is no coincidence
Ordinarily, this would be extremely indicative of a coincidence. If you’re looking for a heuristic for non-coincidences, “sticks around when you change units” is the one you want. This is just an unusual case where that heuristic fails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mistercow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fascist violence and the imaginative failure of the Labour government]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52963</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/10/fascist-violence-and-the-imaginative-failure-of-the-labour-government/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T07:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often on a Friday evening, we order a curry from our local “Indian” takeaway. They deliver, but it is easier and quicker for me to walk round and collect, and, anyway, I enjoy chatting to the guy behind the counter. He’s a Man United fan, I’m Liverpool, so we have some banter with a bit […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lchengify in "Susan Wojcicki has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207918</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207918"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T07:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Was shocked to hear this news. I worked for Google years ago but I was in the NYC office, so we didn't run into the YouTube folks much.
Opinions about YouTube may be mixed here on HN, but it is objectively one of the most successful businesses in tech or media to emerge in the past 15 years. If it weren't buried inside Alphabet, Youtube would be worth on the order of $400 billion, more than Disney and Comcast combined. It's a weird mix of a huge creator monetization network, a music channel, an education platform, a forever-store of niche content, and a utility.
It's also not a business that rested on it's laurels. It's easy to forget how novel creator monetization was when YouTube adopted it. They do a lot of active work to manage their creators, and now have grown into a music and podcast platform that is challenging Apple. To top it off, YouTube TV, despite costing just as much as cable, is objectively a good product.
Few products have the brand, the reach, monetization, and the endurance that YouTube has had within Google. And I know for a fact that this is in no small part due to the way it was managed.
I've probably watched tens of thousands of hours of YouTube at this point. Some of it sublime, some of it absurd, some of it critical for my work or my degree. I couldn't imagine a world without it.
RIP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lchengify</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yyyfb in "Susan Wojcicki has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207776</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207776"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T06:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next time you're thinking "I wish I was the one who had made a billion dollars with my startup idea", remember that only health and family matter, and to have fun while you're alive. RIP.
Edit: some people misinterpreted my comment. I'm just one anonymous  voice on the Internet, but am deeply saddened by the passing of Susan Wojcicki, who meant a lot to me as one of the many people who crossed paths with her professionally. I wish her family strength in a very trying moment. She did not deserve this. I've not met another business leader demonstrate everyday kindness to the degree that she did.
Her untimely passing is also a reminder to those of us who sometimes look up to such successful businesspeople that we should all appreciate our luck to be alive and enjoy it to the fullest, as I hope that she did as well, and as I'm sure that she'd prefer we did. RIP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yyyfb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus - A Letter to the Libertarian Left]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left?v=1723265632</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/dsa-libertarian-socialist-caucus-a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left?v=1723265632"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: DSA Libertarian Socialist Caucus
Title: A Letter to the Libertarian Left
Date: 8/8/2024
Source: Retrieved on 8/8/2024 from https://dsa-lsc.org/2024/08/08/a-letter-to-the-libertarian-left/

 “The idea is like grass. It craves light, likes crowds, thrives on crossbreeding, grows better for being stepped on.” 
 - The Dispossessed, Ursula K. Le Guin 
 We in the Libertarian Socialist Caucus (LSC) of the Democratic Socialists of America (DSA) recognize that our formation has dual obligations, both to the development of the socialist movement in the United States and to the broader libertarian socialist movement that exists outside of DSA. While much of our caucus’ focus thus far has been on DSA’s internal politics, we believe in cross-pollination with the broader libertarian left via an …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gorgoiler in "Rivian reduced electrical wiring by 1.6 miles and 44 pounds"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207331"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T04:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The before/after ECU layout diagram is very instructional.
I like to imagine some kind of engineering “meet cute” whereby, one random day, the headlights engineer and the parking radar engineer happen to be working on the front of the car together.  Their eyes meet:
“hey, I’m John — I didn’t know you had an ECU here!”,
“hi, I’m Claire — wow, you have an ECU right up front too?  It’s, like, right next to mine and we never knew!”
“I know, crazy right?!  Hey this is going to sound really forward and I don’t normally do this but I’m only running at 70% compute capacity.  I don’t suppose you need any real-time budget this evening?”
“So funny you should ask, I was just about to run a whole bunch of heavy new wiring to…”
And in a story as old as time they get ECU married and raise their control loops in the same front-of-vehicle ECU together instead of living their separate, lonely, ECU-right-next-to-each-other-and-they-didn’t-know-it lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gorgoiler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by oefrha in "Building a highly-available web service without a database"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207172</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41207172"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T03:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seems weird to start with “not talking about using something like SQLite where your data is still serialized”, then end up with a home grown transaction log that requires serialization and needs to be replicated, which is how databases are replicated anyway.
If your load fits entirely on one server, then just run the database on that damn server and forget about “special architectures to reduce round-trips to your database”. If your data fits entirely in RAM, then use a ramdisk for the database if you want, and replicate it to permanent storage with standard tools. Now that’s actually simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oefrha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Clarity: Enhancing Code Understanding and Efficiency with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>f383bcb9ec048b73375bec51ac8752a5b1290f19</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/code-clarity-enhancing-code-understanding-and-efficiency-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“All code will become legacy”. This saying, widely recognized amongst software developers, highlights the reality of their day-to-day activities. While writing new code is an integral part of a developer’s role, a significant portion of their time is dedicated to refactoring and maintaining existing codebases. Developers typically encounter numerous challenges when attempting to understand and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jehu Gray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alibaba Cloud 2024 Autumn MVP Application Now Open]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d29c26909580</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/alibaba-cloud-2024-autumn-mvp-application-now-open-d29c26909580?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T09:05:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest batch of Alibaba Cloud MVP applications is now open! Apply before 10 September, 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building RAG Services on Compute Nest with Alibaba Cloud Model Studio and AnalyticDB for…]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8f26bee20273</id>
        <link href="https://alibaba-cloud.medium.com/building-rag-services-on-compute-nest-with-alibaba-cloud-model-studio-and-analyticdb-for-8f26bee20273?source=rss-8cdb52f9cdca------2"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article guides the setting up of a RAG service using Alibaba Cloud Model Studio, Compute Nest, and AnalyticDB for PostgreSQL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alibaba Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unfulfilled promises of microcredit: some new evidence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-unfulfilled-promises-of-microcredit-some-new-evidence</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-unfulfilled-promises-of-microcredit-some-new-evidence"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The student movement in Bangladesh ousted Sheikh Hasina last Monday, August 5, 2024. A new interim government has been formed to restore order, end repression, and hold a fair election to facilitate a democratic transition of power. Nobel laureate Muhammad Yunus has been sworn in as the interim government's chief adviser, and many civil society activists and student leaders who have led the rebellion are included in the advisory group. There is a widespread hope that Prof. Yunus, the (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Bangladesh, 
Third World Debt, 
Private debt, 
Microcredit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM, Stéphanie Jacquemont</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>