<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-13T06:34:41.273Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-13T06:34:41.273Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter From London: Urban Wildlife]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342801</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/13/letter-from-london-urban-wildlife/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T06:32:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the rest of the world realigns, the little reported super-fast 200mph peregrine falcon is once more king of the London skies. There is even such a thing as the London Peregrine Partnership now, a kind of City firm invested in Falco peregrinus. This has been created to protect them when breeding and nesting in  More
The post Letter From London: Urban Wildlife appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We Have a Sacred Duty – All of Us]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343144</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/13/we-have-a-sacred-duty-all-of-us/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T06:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Election Night in my small town, I sat around a folding table with four election clerks, sworn in by the election warden and doing my civic duty to count every vote. The polls had closed. Darkness pressed heavy against the windows, as it does this time of year in Northern Maine. Rain hushed down  More
The post We Have a Sacred Duty – All of Us appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rivera Sun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Call to Post-Election Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343141</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/13/a-call-to-post-election-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T06:13:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He Ran the Table Unbelievably, Donald Trump not only won the presidency – capturing the popular and electoral votes necessary to do so fair and square – but he also ran the table, meaning his party likely controls both houses of Congress and the Supreme Court. Whatever he wants to do for the next four years is going to  More
The post A Call to Post-Election Action appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bergel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “Abandon Harris” Movement Had an Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=343135</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/13/the-abandon-harris-movement-had-an-impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T06:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the Kamala Harris campaign, I had progressive friends from different organizations using clashing strategies to reach their goals. You’ve probably seen videos of Kamala “I’m speaking!” Harris shutting down my pro-Palestinian gang, which crashed her rally, demanding her administration stop backing the Israeli genocide in Palestine. Also in attendance were my militant union sisters and brothers—who have  More
The post The “Abandon Harris” Movement Had an Impact appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Weinstein</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving to Canada (not)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53395</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/13/moving-to-canada-not/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-13T05:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After Trump’s second election victory, lots of Americans are talking about emigrating, most commonly to Canada. This happens with every rightwing election win[1], but nothing ever comes of it. With the real prospect of indefinite Trumpist rule, the issues are more serious, but it seems unlikely that much will happen. But why not? It’s fairly […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Q</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian high school drama Heartbreak High returns for third series]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8817</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-high-school-drama-heartbreak-high-third-series/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T21:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third — and it seems, final — series of Heartbreak High, in the second inception of the gritty Australian high-school TV drama, is on the way. Set at the fictional Hartley High, in Sydney, Heartbreak High originally screened between 1994 and 1999. A rebooted version of the show debuted in 2022. Series one of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netflix’s Distributed Counter Abstraction]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8d0c45eb66b2</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/netflixs-distributed-counter-abstraction-8d0c45eb66b2?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T20:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By: Rajiv Shringi, Oleksii Tkachuk, Kartik Sathyanarayanan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The science of standing desks does not quite stack up]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8812</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/science-standing-desks-does-not-quite-stack-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T20:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty popular are sit/stand desks at the moment. I’ve helped a few people assemble them, when they’ve bought one for their home office. Good for your health, sit/stand desks, or so we’re told. Mainly because you’re not sitting all day while working. Some recent research however, suggests the health benefits of sit/stand desks could be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282099</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T19:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Deploy the Blame Cannons! Boeing avoids liability for Ethiopian MCAS crash in settlement, restarts production but with layoffs; Elite maleficence at ASHRAE, hospitals, and Infection Prevention and Control; More money does buy more happiness ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a Bear Blog Archive]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/bear-blog-archive/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/bear-blog-archive/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T18:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my first requests for Bear, about two years ago, was for an archive feature. There still isn't one, but I had an idea when I read today that Herman added filtering by multiple tags.
I thought it would work well to create a nice blog archive. Inspired by the cool archive that mgx has, which I don't have the skills to create, this is what I came up with.
By assigning month and year as tags for each post and then using the embedded posts feature, it's fairly easy to create an archive. The downside is that once a month, the archive page and the post template need to be updated, but I think that's okay.
A small advantage is that you can choose to exclude posts you don't want in the list, and that for one reason or another are not suitable as pages.
Happy blogging!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major polluters absent from climate summit + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/major-polluters-absent-from-climate-summit-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/major-polluters-absent-from-climate-summit-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists warn of the potential collapse of the Atlantic current; major polluters skip UN climate talks amidst climate finance discussions; ADB boosts climate finance to $7.2 billion with US and Japan support; Israel fails to meet US deadline for increased humanitarian aid to Gaza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Meta built large-scale cryptographic monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21935</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/11/12/security/how-meta-built-large-scale-cryptographic-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T17:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptographic monitoring at scale has been instrumental in helping our engineers understand how cryptography is used at Meta. Monitoring has given us a distinct advantage in our efforts to proactively detect and remove weak cryptographic algorithms and has assisted with our general change safety and reliability efforts. We’re sharing insights into our own cryptographic monitoring [...]
Read More...
The post How Meta built large-scale cryptographic monitoring appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by donatj in "The EdTech Revolution Has Failed"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42116365</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42116365"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T15:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work in EdTech, I have for a very long time now, and the problem I have seen is no one in education is willing to ACTUALLY let kids learn at their own level.
The promise of EdTech was that kids could learn where they are. A kid who's behind can actually continue to learn rather than being left behind. A kid who's ahead can be nurtured.
We had this. It worked well, in my opinion at least, and the number of complaints and straight up threats because kids would learn things "they shouldn't be" was just… insanely frustrating.
Now in order to keep schools paying for our services, every kid is banded into a range based on their grade. They are scored/graded based on their grade level rather than their growth. It's such a crying shame.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>donatj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Lost $210 to a Stripe Dispute Despite Proof]]></title>
        <id>https://zarar.dev/how-i-lost-210-to-a-stripe-dispute-despite-proof/</id>
        <link href="https://zarar.dev/how-i-lost-210-to-a-stripe-dispute-despite-proof/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I lost a Stripe dispute of USD $210 because the customer that purchased tickets from my site used an email that he claimed to his bank was not his. Stripe and the bank asked me to provide evidence that this wasn't fraudulent and I sent them:
The invoice sent to the email the customer entered
The actual tickets that were sent
Despite this evidence I lost the dispute because of the customer's "it wasn't me" defense. Here's Bank of America's response:
Compelling documents shows name is matching with customer, but email id and ip address does not match with our customer. No
proof our customer benefited from this transaction. Our customer maintains charge is unauthorized/fraud.
This is a lie because I never even sent them the IP address since that isn't shown in the evidence I submitted. Notice…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Ukraine Embrace an Era of ‘War-Wilding’?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282094</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/will-ukraine-embrace-an-era-of-war-wilding.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T14:55:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of Ukraine’s wartime environmental catastrophes, scientists say, can be turned into long-term ecological gains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[African People's Counter-COP denounces the COP system and demands climate justice for Global South be at the centre of the climate action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/African-People-s-Counter-COP-denounces-the-COP-system-and-demands-climate</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/African-People-s-Counter-COP-denounces-the-COP-system-and-demands-climate"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T13:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From October 7th to 10th, the African Climate Justice Collective (ACJC) held the first physical African People's Counter-COP (APCC) in Saly, Senegal. Over one hundred participants, from 21 countries, representing social movements, grassroots communities, women, youth, civil society organisations, academics, workers, and others, joined the event. 
English

/ 
Ecological debt, 
Africa, 
Ecology/Climate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>La Via Campesina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banking System Vulnerability: 2024 Update]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=32617</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/11/banking-system-vulnerability-2024-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a period of relative stability, a series of bank failures in 2023 renewed questions about the fragility of the banking system. As in previous years, we provide in this post an update of four analytical models aimed at capturing different aspects of the vulnerability of the U.S. banking system using data through 2024:Q2 and discuss how these measures have changed since last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matteo Crosignani, Thomas Eisenbach, and Fulvia Fringuellotti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282013</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our wacky daily links: Thailand cat uproar, dengue in US, 1.5 C sightings, China trade surplus friction, moar Germany tsuris, Qatar v. Hamas fake news, EU censorship on Russia, Germany wants more NATO, Trump appointments, R House margin challenges, Harris women push underperformed, Beatles AI, Mr. Market]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Central Bank in Europe Warns Citizens to Have Cash “Under the Mattress” Amid Rising Payments System Fragility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282017</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/another-central-bank-in-europe-just-warned-citizens-to-have-cash-under-the-mattress-amid-rising-system-fragility.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["You have to take into account that you may not be able to pay by debit card for a longer period of time," notes the Dutch National Bank. "Then you have to have cash under the mattress, or be able to pay with QR codes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saudi-Iranian Relations Warm as Middle East Braces for Trump’s Return]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282084</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/saudi-iranian-relations-warm-as-middle-east-braces-for-trumps-return.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T11:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supposedly isolated Iran continues to build bridges in its region.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Amsterdam Attacks: The Politics of Collective Violence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342909</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/the-amsterdam-attacks-the-politics-of-collective-violence/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T07:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction This article contains and curates Middle East historian Lawrence Davidson’s collection of Mouin Rabbani’s tweets on the 2024 Amsterdam football riots. Read them while they last. Rabbani, a director of the Palestine American Research Center, is a leading analyst on Palestinian politics and Middle Eastern affairs. A senior fellow at the Institute for Palestine  More
The post The Amsterdam Attacks: The Politics of Collective Violence appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Did I “Predict” That Trump, Despite His Repulsive Personality and Politics, Would Prevail?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342661</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/how-did-i-predict-that-trump-despite-his-repulsive-personality-and-politics-would-prevail/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly a month before the November 5 elections, I anticipated that Donald Trump would win and wrote about it in a couple of articles. My “prediction” created some controversy, especially since the polls showed Harris and Trump in a dead heat.  Not surprisingly, people have been asking me the last few days how I came  More
The post How Did I “Predict” That Trump, Despite His Repulsive Personality and Politics, Would Prevail? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Walden Bello</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Time To Play Just Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342658</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/no-time-to-play-just-defense/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Donald Trump about to re-enter the White House and his sidekicks about to assume control over Congress, America’s progressives are once again shifting — to playing defense. But the best defense, as one old football adage suggests, almost always turns out to be a good offense. In the coming Trump redux, can we progressives  More
The post No Time To Play Just Defense appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electing an American Fuhrer as Wall Street Cheers and Soars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342914</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/electing-an-american-fuhrer-as-wall-street-cheers-and-soars/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On September 17, 1787, the last day after the drafting of our Constitution in Philadelphia, Ben Franklin was leaving the building when a prominent resident, Elizabeth Willing Powel, asked him “Well Doctor, what have we got – a republic or a monarch?” Franklin replied, “A republic, if you can keep it.” On November 5, 2024,  More
The post Electing an American Fuhrer as Wall Street Cheers and Soars appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden’s Gaza Policy Leaves the Middle East in Flames]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342916</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/president-bidens-gaza-policy-leaves-the-middle-east-in-flames/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Joe Biden has now joined the ranks of Jimmy Carter and George W. Bush as a president whose Middle East policy crashed and burned spectacularly. Unlike Carter, who was stymied by the Iranian hostage crisis, or Bush, who faced a popular Iraqi resistance movement, Biden’s woes weren’t inflicted by an enemy. Quite the opposite,  More
The post President Biden’s Gaza Policy Leaves the Middle East in Flames appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Cole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Musings of Shigeru Ishiba: Visions of an Asian NATO]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342959</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/the-musings-of-shigeru-ishiba-visions-of-an-asian-nato/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japan’s new prime minister, Shigeru Ishiba, is stirring the pot – notably on regional security matters.  He has proposed something that has done more than raise a few eyebrows in the foreign and defence ministries of several countries.  An Asian version of NATO, he has suggested, was an idea worth considering, notably given China’s ambitions in the  More
The post The Musings of Shigeru Ishiba: Visions of an Asian NATO appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Will Trump Victory Change US-Brazil Relations?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342962</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/how-will-trump-victory-change-us-brazil-relations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:55:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout Brazilian history, the U.S. government and expanded state actors have frequently interfered to control, destabilize and overthrow Brazil’s leadership. Today, actors like Elon Musk, The New York Times, and Tucker Carlson are spreading false narratives designed to destabilize President Lula’s administration. Under Trump, these narratives could be inserted into official policy, aiming either to oust Lula or ensure  More
The post How Will Trump Victory Change US-Brazil Relations? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Mier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump and the Geopolitical Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342956</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/donald-trump-and-the-geopolitical-landscape/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“It was like a scene from the final hours of the Roman Empire: Everywhere you looked, some prominent politician was degrading himself in public.” — Hunter S. Thompson With America staring down the barrel of another reactionary Trump regime, it’s easy to discern what the domestic agenda for the Republican Party is. Which is to  More
The post Donald Trump and the Geopolitical Landscape appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Inskeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Cuba Hasn’t Adjusted to US Sanctions After Six Decades]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342919</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/why-cuba-hasnt-adjusted-to-us-sanctions-after-six-decades-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the thirty-second time in so many years, the US blockade of Cuba was globally condemned at the UN General Assembly’s annual vote in October. Only Tel Aviv joined Washington in defending the collective punishment, which is illegal under international law. For the vast majority of Cubans, who were born after the first unilateral coercive  More
The post Why Cuba Hasn’t Adjusted to US Sanctions After Six Decades appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roger Harris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Hide in the Age of Trump and Vance: An Eleven Step Program]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342953</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/how-to-hide-in-the-age-of-trump-and-vance-an-eleven-step-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hid folks in the 1960s and 1970s and learned a few things about hiding from the police. Here are some suggestions. Hiding is not a game. It’s hard work and can be exhausting. It takes practice. Don’t go into hiding unless it’s necessary for your survival. 1.   Don’t isolate yourself. Create a circle of trusted  More
The post How to Hide in the Age of Trump and Vance: An Eleven Step Program appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fault is in Ourselves:  The Arabs and Their Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342664</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/the-fault-is-in-ourselves-the-arabs-and-their-leaders/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The question often asked but rarely explored or answered is why the Arab Middle East has remained quiet and on the sidelines as their fellow Arabs in Palestine and Lebanon are being slaughtered.  Although they wield enormous economic clout that could be used to end the genocide, they have chosen instead to be butlers to  More
The post The Fault is in Ourselves:  The Arabs and Their Leaders appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Economy and the Tariffs and Tax Breaks to Launch It]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282072</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/the-new-economy-and-the-tariffs-and-tax-breaks-to-launch-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:50:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Analyses of planned Trump tariffs differ somewhat on the impact, but all find them to be negative. Will the Supremes save Trump from himself?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Military-Industrial Complex Is Fueling Climate Catastrophe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342912</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/the-military-industrial-complex-is-fueling-climate-catastrophe/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:44:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we write, New York City is an unsettling 70 degrees in November. Meanwhile, a cohort of war profiteers, their pockets lined by the very industries destroying our climate, are flying to COP, the annual U.N. climate summit hosted by a petrostate, no less. They’re gathering to “discuss climate solutions”—but one of the world’s biggest  More
The post The Military-Industrial Complex Is Fueling Climate Catastrophe appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Kirshenbaum - Melissa Garriga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NYT Version of the Big Lie: Technology Created Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342721</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/12/the-nyt-version-of-the-big-lie-technology-created-inequality/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T06:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a Big Lie pushed by centrist types that is almost as pernicious as the Big Lie that Donald Trump won the 2020 election. It is that inequality was driven by technology, an autonomous force in the world, not policy choices made by politicians. This lie permeates just about all political discussions in major  More
The post The NYT Version of the Big Lie: Technology Created Inequality appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Copilot Edits]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/11/12/introducing-copilot-edits</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/blogs/2024/11/12/introducing-copilot-edits"/>
        <updated>2024-11-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Copilot Edits allows you to get to the changes you need in your workspace, across multiple files, using a UI designed for fast iteration. You can specify a set of files to be edited, and then use natural language to simply ask Copilot what you need. You stay in the flow of your code while reviewing the suggested changes, accepting what works, and iterating with follow-up asks.
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by simonw in "How I ship projects at big tech companies"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42111534</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42111534"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T23:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is great. I particularly liked this observation:
> Shipping is a social construct within a company. Concretely, that means that a project is shipped when the important people at your company believe it is shipped.
A lot of the ideas in here resonated with me a lot. This is the kind of article I wish I'd read before I spent a few years leading an engineering team at a medium-sized tech company!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>simonw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an insurance company implements disaster recovery of 3-tier applications]]></title>
        <id>e2015f2cd424af618996edcdd7eedadc060d1a98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-an-insurance-company-implements-disaster-recovery-of-3-tier-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T22:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good strategy for resilience will include operating with high availability and planning for business continuity. It also accounts for the incidence of natural disasters, such as earthquakes or floods and technical failures, such as power failure or network connectivity. AWS recommends a multi-AZ strategy for high availability and a multi-Region strategy for disaster recovery. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Narang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veterans Day: Goya on War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282025</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/veterans-day-goya-on-war.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T22:25:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Goya paintings and etchings on war's unrefined cruelty]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peek inside your AWS CloudFormation Deployments with timeline view]]></title>
        <id>1f09d2ded522fc8dd52761fd03c0930842c9a7fe</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/peek-inside-your-aws-cloudformation-deployments-with-timeline-view/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T21:48:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS CloudFormation makes it easy to model and provision your cloud application infrastructure as code. CloudFormation templates can be written directly in JSON or YAML, or they can be generated by tools like the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK). These templates are submitted to the CloudFormation service and the resources are deployed together as stacks, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Idriss Laouali Abdou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build custom nodes workflow with ComfyUI on Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>68a0459bd6aa36b976d6b7e064fc8cb64386d591</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/how-to-build-custom-nodes-workflow-with-comfyui-on-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T21:27:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ComfyUI is an open-source node-based workflow solution for Stable Diffusion and increasingly being used by many creators. We previously published a blog and solution about how to deploy ComfyUI on AWS. Typically, ComfyUI users use various custom nodes, which extend the capabilities of ComfyUI, to build their own workflows, often using ComfyUI-Manager to conveniently install and manage their […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doomscrolling social media does not result in brain rot]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8807</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/doomscrolling-social-media-brain-rot/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T21:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So say psychologists at the Sydney based University of New South Wales (UNSW): Dr Poppy Watson, adjunct lecturer with UNSW’s School of Psychology, says while the idea warrants exploration, there is a lack of evidence showing excessive doomscrolling of social media is responsible for the mental fatigue, lack of focus, and reduced cognitive function often […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=282027</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T19:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Deploy the Blame Cannons! First head rolls at Boeing, breakup rumors; Angus Deaon on economics and economists; Sentinel intelligence ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Barker: &ldquo;Dealignment&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/dealignment</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/dealignment"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T18:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the US elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rain and Melancholy]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/rain-and-melancholy/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/rain-and-melancholy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T17:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling melancholic.
I don't know what it is. It could be the rain, or it could be because it's Monday. Either way, I'm feeling all the feels today1. I'm currently sitting in my home office, staring out of my balcony door, watching the moody skies cover my neighborhood in a shade of gray. The weather's got a mood, and it's contagious.
I love the sound of rain. I think it's soothing. It always just makes me want to get under the covers, drink a warm cup of coffee, and read (or nap) the day away2. Today, it just reminds me of how quickly the weekend slipped away. I hate that it's Monday. Weekends always feel like they end before they even properly start, and now here we are, kicking off another long work week ahead.
Maybe it's just one of those days. I've done a bit of analogue journaling already, but I still had a few more words that needed to come out.
And so, here I am, putting words together with feelings that I don't quite know what to do with just yet.
That's all.
83/100
Comments

It's snowing in Eastern Canada! 🤩❄️
-Denis
It’s a wet day here too. A sort of stead drizzle that just envelops everything in tiny teardrops. Hope you feel less melancholy tomorrow and maye, the sun will come out.
-Alexandra Wolfe
Reply by email
Then again, it's been like this more so since a week ago.↩


Today, I got the coffee covered. Blankets, reading and nap will have to wait since I have to work.↩]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Occasional Paper: Four Hidden Species of Portuguese man-o’-war]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53373</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/11/occasional-paper-four-hidden-species-of-portuguese-man-o-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T17:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a a certain amount of negativity floating around lately. So, let’s talk about a toxic, venomous freak of nature and the parasite that afflicts it. Biology warning, this gets slightly squicky. Let’s start with the toxic, venomous freak of nature:  the Portuguese man-o’-war. If you’ve spent a lot of time in warm ocean […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Doug Muir</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS BuilderCards second edition at re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>1b972c986ad234970d6a5b2bc6acce608303a33a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-buildercards-second-edition-available-at-reinvent-2024-and-online/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T17:06:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS BuilderCards 2nd Edition: Gamify AWS learning with enhanced design, new mission cards, generative AI deck, and improved game mechanics for seamless architecturing fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Barr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: 20 years of AWS News Blog, Express brokers for Amazon MSK, Windows Server 2025 images on EC2, and more (Nov 11, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>63dc088e1a235b56ccbe5088651fd4791fe06772</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-20-years-of-aws-news-blog-express-brokers-for-amazon-msk-windows-server-2025-images-on-ec2-and-more-nov-11-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T16:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy 20th Anniversary of the AWS News Blog! 🎉🥳🎊 On November 9, 2004, Jeff Barr published his first blog post. At the time, he started a personal blog site using TypePad. He wanted to speak to his readers with his personal voice, not the company or team. On April 29, 2014, we created a new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binary vector embeddings are so cool]]></title>
        <id>https://emschwartz.me/binary-vector-embeddings-are-so-cool/</id>
        <link href="https://emschwartz.me/binary-vector-embeddings-are-so-cool/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vector embeddings by themselves are pretty neat. Binary quantized vector embeddings are extra impressive. In short, they can retain 95+% retrieval accuracy with 32x compression and ~25x retrieval speedup. Let's get into how this works and why it's so crazy.
What are embeddings?
Embeddings let you turn an arbitrary piece of text into a series of numbers that manage to represent the meaning of the content. These embedding vectors can range in dimension from 512 on the shorter end all the way up to 8192 or more. Typically each of the weights in the vector is represented as a 32-bit floating point number.
LLMs use embeddings to represent input text, but embeddings can also be used on their own.
Embeddings enable you to easily search for pieces of content that have similar meanings by finding t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[to-do yerine, to-think]]></title>
        <id>https://vitriolpodcast.blog/to-do-yerine-to-think/</id>
        <link href="https://vitriolpodcast.blog/to-do-yerine-to-think/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[hareket her şeydir, nihai hedef hiçbir şeydir. — eduard bernstein
to-do listlerimin çoğu artık to-think olarak değişmiş vaziyette. serbest çağrışım tabii.
bunu bir üşengeçlik olarak göreceklerin kokusunu buradan alıyorum. bunu bir üşengeçlik, tembellik, zararlı davranış, “öyle olmaz”cılık olarak alanlar oldu, hayatımın her döneminde.
onur ile ocak’ta ikinci senesini dolduracak olan aralıksız her çarşamba oturup en az üç fikir üzerine düşünmelerimizi feyzalarak bir şeyler karalamak istedim. üzerine yoğunlaştığımız bir iş yokken de varken de disiplinli olarak her çarşamba günü, büyük olasılıkla öğlen 12:00 civarında, en az 1 saat boyunca, yoğun bir şekilde odaklanmanın ne demek olduğunu, bu odaklanma halinin işin kendisini yapmaktan ne kadar daha fayadalı olduğunu, çağdaş toplumun yapmaktan …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tonyvince7 in "Behaviors reveal sophisticated tool use and possible “pranking” among pachyderms"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42106725</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42106725"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T12:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am from south India where a lot of wild elephants roam the villages and towns. When elephants come to roam the streets most people lock themselves in their homes and alert the forest division authorities. Someone I know once rescued a baby elephant from a trap set for boars. Every year, a herd of elephants stop by his gate and leave presents - mostly bananas and coconuts. They wait for him to come out, make a friendly gesture - folding their trunks in a specific way, and leave peacefully. Our elders tell us that elephants have memory and show gratitude and they can hold a grudge so be respectful all the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tonyvince7</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281970</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T11:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 'ghostly' neutrino fog descends as Trump's election reverberates around the world, and Obama worries about his legacy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Enthusiasm for Mass Deportation, A Hard and Likely Largely Losing Way to Deal with Illegal Immigration?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281975</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/why-the-enthusiasm-for-mass-deportation-a-hard-and-likely-largely-losing-way-to-deal-with-illegal-immigration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T11:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why the idea of mass deportation is set to become the "Defund the Police" of the right: vague but appealingly absolute, and unworkable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the visit]]></title>
        <id>https://krischerukuri.bearblog.dev/the-visit/</id>
        <link href="https://krischerukuri.bearblog.dev/the-visit/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a lazy Sunday morning, September 2015, in Bangalore. The city’s atmosphere makes everyone a little sluggish. Deciding to shake off the weekend haze, I went out and found myself wandering the streets of BTM. Suddenly, a small shop caught my eye, filled to the brim with books—as if there were no bricks in the walls, only shelves and stacks of paperbacks and hardcovers. Curiosity got the better of me, and I stepped inside, calling out to see if anyone was there. An old, weathered hand raised itself from behind a towering pile, and a soft, respectful voice answered, “What do you want, sir?”
Startled, I scanned the room until I spotted an old man in the midst of this sea of books. “Hi,” I replied. “Is this a library or an old bookshop?” He chuckled and explained that it was a private libra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post’s David Ignatius Mysteriously Sees “Significant Progress” in Stabilizing Three Dangerous Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342640</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/washington-posts-david-ignatius-mysteriously-sees-significant-progress-in-stabilizing-three-dangerous-wars/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T07:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past year, the Washington Post’s senior diplomatic columnist, David Ignatius, has been loyal to the U.S. and Israeli national security teams, playing the role of stenographer in sharing and repeating their optimism about peace in the Middle East.  He has reported one hopeful scenario after another, and avoids criticizing the self-serving comments from Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and Secretary of State Antony Blinken over the past year regarding the outlook for peace.   More
The post Washington Post’s David Ignatius Mysteriously Sees “Significant Progress” in Stabilizing Three Dangerous Wars appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Removing Hydropower Dams Can Restore Ecosystems, Build Climate Resilience, and Restore Tribal Lands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342531</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/removing-hydropower-dams-can-restore-ecosystems-build-climate-resilience-and-restore-tribal-lands/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A free-flowing river supports abundant fish and wildlife, provides drinking water, and other intangible recreational benefits. But humans have sought to block rivers with dams for millennia. While dams have provided benefits like hydroelectricity and water storage, they have also been ecologically disastrous. Besides blocking fish migrations, these human-made structures can destroy seasonal pulses of  More
The post Removing Hydropower Dams Can Restore Ecosystems, Build Climate Resilience, and Restore Tribal Lands appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Katie Schmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Wave of Movements Against Trumpism is Coming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342731</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/a-new-wave-of-movements-against-trumpism-is-coming/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For many of us, the immediate aftermath of Donald Trump’s decisive electoral victory has been a time of deep despair and mourning. There has been plenty of commentary trying to make sense of Trump’s win and the factors that led to it. But no analysis changes the fact that the outcome represents a serious blow  More
The post A New Wave of Movements Against Trumpism is Coming appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Engler - Paul Engler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump: It’s the Economy, Stupid]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342812</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/trump-its-the-economy-stupid/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bill Clinton’s strategist, Jim Carville, coined the quip “It’s the economy, stupid!” to explain his successful strategy for winning the 1992 U.S. presidential election against incumbent George H. W.  Although Carville advised Vice President Kamala Harris’s presidential campaign, he apparently didn’t share that advice with Harris. In Harris’s defense, as one pundit explained, any incumbent president, and by  More
The post Trump: It’s the Economy, Stupid appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Trump Won: And Some Consequences]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342833</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/why-trump-won-and-some-consequences/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s now more than 48 hours after the election, the dust has settled, and the results are in except for a late counting in the state of Arizona–the outcome of which won’t affect the results of the election. Trump has won an undeniable victory, both in the electoral college and in the popular vote. Political  More
The post Why Trump Won: And Some Consequences appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Rasmus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[At the Neoliberal Funeral: “I’m Sorry for Your Loss”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342834</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/at-the-neoliberal-funeral-im-sorry-for-your-loss/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:55:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, yeah, I’m standing here at the funeral looking at the corpse. It’s got a liberal application of makeup covering the reality of death, but you can still see it steaming under there. It’s that hidden decay that moves forward despite the chemical concoctions. Microscopic changes until they aren’t. This is one of those funerals  More
The post At the Neoliberal Funeral: “I’m Sorry for Your Loss” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Happened, What’s Next]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342728</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/what-happened-whats-next/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Got Up, got out of bed. Why? To start the next round. Why? Because the fight is not over. Trump won a very big battle. Yes, he did. No denying it. Sickening. But it wasn’t because he is stupid. It wasn’t because he’s an idiot. Is he the luckiest human ever to walk the planet?  More
The post What Happened, What’s Next appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Albert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can Call Center Workers of the World Unite?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342742</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/can-call-center-workers-of-the-world-unite/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American politicians love to pose as defenders of factory workers threatened by globalization, corporate restructuring, and overseas outsourcing. But their campaign spiels rarely mention other jobs at risk, for the same reasons, in white-collar workplaces that now employ more workers than all domestic manufacturers of steel, autos, airplanes, and other machinery combined. Among them are the nearly  More
The post Can Call Center Workers of the World Unite? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Early</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NATO’s Imperialist March and Its Victims]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342643</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/natos-imperialist-march-and-its-victims/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the summer of 1999, just months after NATO bombed an independent country (then Yugoslavia) without the authorisation of the UN Security Council, I attended a lecture by the late Prof. Johan Galtung, the father of peace research. Known for his integrity and intellectual courage, he didn’t mince words. He said bluntly: “This world has  More
The post NATO’s Imperialist March and Its Victims appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Biljana Vankovska</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making America Great Again, 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45732</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/11/making-america-great-again-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Shimshon Bichler & Jonathan Nitzan In 2019, we published a RWER paper assessing Trump’s promise to ‘Make America Great Again’. https://bnarchives.net/id/eprint/630/ Here are updates of two key charts from this paper. The first figure depicts the relative global decline of U.S. corporations. It shows that U.S. firms currently accounts for ~1/3rd of global corporate profit, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Song of the PFC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342649</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/song-of-the-pfc/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We said it each day of our miserable lives. We said it when it rained, and when it didn’t rain, when it was hot, when it was hotter. “It don’t mean nothin,” we said. We said it because it sounded tough. We said it to keep from crying. We said it because it might be  More
The post Song of the PFC appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jack Parente</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Swedish American Marine Grunt Became a Documentary Photographer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342646</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/how-a-swedish-american-marine-grunt-became-a-documentary-photographer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was born in Sweden in 1943. My father was highly educated and very successful in his field. I, however, was pretty much the opposite. An immature loser, I failed to graduate from high school. After working in mines and doing odd jobs I was ordered to enter the Swedish Army in the fall of  More
The post How a Swedish American Marine Grunt Became a Documentary Photographer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Per-Olof Odman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Essential Question, Still Unanswered]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342734</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/an-essential-question-still-unanswered/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than one year after the brutal attack on innocent Israelis that left more than 1,200 dead and scores of injured, as well as more than 42,000 Palestinians dead and hundreds of thousands injured, an essential question remains unanswered? Why did Hamas do it? Why did they sacrifice their lives, those of their families and  More
The post An Essential Question, Still Unanswered appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar Chelala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pissoff Effect: a Glyph]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342662</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/11/the-pissoff-effect-a-glyph/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-11T06:02:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post The Pissoff Effect: a Glyph appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Sanders</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Völkermord in Gaza. Two million deaths are in the cards.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45737</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/10/volkermord-in-gaza-two-million-deaths-are-in-the-cards/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T22:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new UN report on deaths in Gaza makes for Grim Reading. According to the admirable work of UN data sleuths, details close to 10.000 of the official 40.000+ deaths have been added. These are only the direct victims; indirect victims (starvation, stress, sickness) are omitted. One of the findings is that, unlike during earlier […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FireDucks : Pandas but 100x faster]]></title>
        <id>https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/fireducks-pandas-but-100x-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://hwisnu.bearblog.dev/fireducks-pandas-but-100x-faster/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T22:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
My main background is a hedge fund professional, so I deal with finance data all the time and so far the Pandas library has been an indispensable tool in my workflow and my most used Python library.


Then came along Polars (written in Rust, btw!) which shook the ground of Python ecosystem due to its speed and efficiency, you can check some of Polars benchmark here.
I have around +/- 30 thousand lines of Pandas code, so you can understand why I've been hesitant to rewrite them to Polars, despite my enthusiasm for speed and optimization. The sheer scale of the task has led to repeated delays, as I weigh the potential benefits of a faster and more efficient library against the significant effort required to refactor my existing code.
There has always been this thought in the bac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mastazi in "IMG_0416"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42102707</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42102707"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T21:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The website http://astronaut.io/ does a similar thing but for recent videos, and not just from iPhones. From the home page:
> These videos come from YouTube. They were uploaded in the last week and have titles like DSC 1234 and IMG 4321. They have almost zero previous views. They are unnamed, unedited, and unseen (by anyone but you).
At one point you might be at a school recital in Malaysia, and the next minute you are at a birthday in Ecuador. It's amazing!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mastazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Star Bores: A Few Cope, as fourth Star Wars trilogy announced]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8801</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/star-bores-few-cope-fourth-star-wars-trilogy-announced/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T21:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years I was excited by the prospect of a Star Wars sequel trilogy. This, long before what became episodes seven through nine, were even announced. I used to burn the midnight oil reading fan-written Star Wars EU plots and stories, that were published on various Star Wars forums and wikis. But all three films, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[new zine! Monstrous Existence vol. 3]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/new-zine-monstrous-existence-vol-3/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/new-zine-monstrous-existence-vol-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Sunday:) just popping in to let you know I've added Monstrous Existence vol. 3 to the shop this morning.
It's a one-page (double-sided) zine about being saddened by the election results, needing a break, starting a new sketchbook, + a mini music list, doodles, and scattered thoughts.
This zine is a limited print of 30 copies. Each copy has red marker accents that are unique to each print.
Made with love ❤︎]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["koan" theme for bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/koan-theme-for-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/koan-theme-for-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Koan is a direct modification and subtle enhancement of Bear Blog's default theme. Feel free to use it as a starter theme and customize it further. On macOS, Koan loads Avenir Next; on all other machines, it falls back to Inter, followed by system fonts.
Preview: Visit bear.css.observer and select the Koan preset. 
https://static.mgx.me/bear/themes/koan.css.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Gruissan]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53385</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/10/sunday-photoblogging-gruissan/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T09:22:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US election 2024: inflation, immigration and identity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-2024-inflation-immigration-and-identity</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-2024-inflation-immigration-and-identity"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T07:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the FT put it: “In the end, it wasn't even close. A presidential election long forecast to dance on a knife's edge very quickly turned out to be a rout for Donald Trump.” Trump polled 73.4m votes or 50.7% of the those who voted, while Harris polled 60m or 47.7% of the vote. Third party candidates mustered just 1.6%. Trump's 4.3m lead was more than Biden had in 2020, or Hillary Clinton had over Trump in 2016. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Inflation, 
Precarity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by synapsomorphy in "Marine pilot loses command after ejecting from F-35B that kept flying"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42098722</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42098722"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T05:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The report criticizes the pilot for ejecting, but also says he did everything by the book (F35 manual), but the book was wrong. And the pilot should've figured that out? Feels like they just need someone to blame for losing the plane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>synapsomorphy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI will make you a worse person]]></title>
        <id>https://hapax.bearblog.dev/ai-will-make-you-a-worse-person/</id>
        <link href="https://hapax.bearblog.dev/ai-will-make-you-a-worse-person/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T02:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My wife and I have been watching Parks and Rec a lot lately. Every ad break it seems like one of Apple's ads for "Apple Intelligence" comes up. These ads feature someone suddenly realizing that they're unprepared: a wife realizes that she forgot her husband's birthday; a lawyer realizes that he forgot to read an important document; an actor realizes that they forgot to read a pitch for a show. The unprepared person is able to quickly "save the day" by using Apple Intelligence to generate a summary of important information, or in the wife's case, to generate an animated slideshow of sentimental photos.
These ads consistently leave me with a bad taste in my mouth.
Obviously, everyone is unprepared sometimes. Everyone occasionally forgets an important birthday, or shows up to a meeting without having prepped. That's part of being human. The myth of AI is that we can eliminate human fallibility, that we can smooth out our rough edges with enough technology. News flash: more technology won't make us more perfect. The more we expect "perfection" from others, the less grace we will have with them. The less space we leave for forgiveness and understanding.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin Carson - When You Cross Pinochet With a Cyberpunk Dystopia…]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kevin-carson-when-you-cross-pinochet-with-a-cyberpunk-dystopia?v=1731200320</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/kevin-carson-when-you-cross-pinochet-with-a-cyberpunk-dystopia?v=1731200320"/>
        <updated>2024-11-10T00:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Kevin Carson
Title: When You Cross Pinochet With a Cyberpunk Dystopia…
Date: November 9th, 2024
Source: Retrieved on November 9th, 2024 from https://c4ss.org/content/59956

 …what do you get? Answer: “Special Little Freedom Zones.” 
 That’s what Reason’s Liz Wolfe calls the Honduran “charter cities,” officially known as ZEDEs (Zones for Economic Development and Employment), which were declared illegal in September by the Honduran Supreme Court (“No More Special Little Freedom Zones,”” September 25). The ruling prohibits the creation of new ZEDEs; its effect on existing ones, like Próspera, Ciudad Morazán, and Zede Orquidea, is as yet unknown. 
 Wolfe describes such charter cities as “special economic economic zones that are still bound by criminal law but able to create their own c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Notes 030]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-030/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/week-notes-030/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T20:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🗓️ // November 2 - November 8, 2024
The days are long but the years are short
-Gretchen Rubin
I think Gretchen Rubin forgot to talk about the weeks in between. This week has been both difficult, and heartbreaking. I honestly am still not done processing everything post-election. My heart has been heavy, and I cannot shake the sadness that seems to have permanently enveloped my soul.
Let’s talk about this week anyways.
📖 We went back to Barnes and Noble last Saturday to finally pick up the most beautiful edition of my favorite book The Seven Husbands of Evelyn Hugo by Taylor Jenkins Reid. I already have the paperback version but this hardback is absolutely stunning.
📖 LC picked up a collectible edition of The Great Gatsby and Other Classic Works. This one also has a stunning white and go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by marmaduke in "OpenCoder: Open Cookbook for Top-Tier Code Large Language Models"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42096191</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42096191"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T19:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Unlike most prior efforts, we release not only model weights and inference code, but also the reproducible training data, complete data processing pipeline, rigorous experimental ablation results, and detailed training protocols for open scientific research.
Regardless of the specific performance of this model versus another model, I think it’s good to keep in mind that everyone benefits from this kind of work]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>marmaduke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The submissive university]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53375</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/09/the-submissive-university/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T16:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Together with many other academics in the Netherlands, I have been very busy in organizing a nation-wide demonstration next Thursday against the 1 billion budget cuts to higher education that our very-right-wing government has announced. (For background explanation, see this earlier post). Today, I have a long opinion piece in the daily newspaper NRC Handelsblad […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ingrid Robeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Re: Try writing posts, not comments; or, In defence of comments]]></title>
        <id>https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/re-try-writing-posts-not-comments-or-in-defence-of-comments/</id>
        <link href="https://negativeb.bearblog.dev/re-try-writing-posts-not-comments-or-in-defence-of-comments/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've added a link to Scott's post - I forgot to add it, and that was unintentional. Anyways, here it is: https://scojjac.com/posts-not-comments/
I've been noticed online, which is surprising. Scott Jack is the person in question to notice me, indeed he wrote a reply to my blogpost on what I learnt about Bearblog. He raises some good points about one specific section of the post - that being, the part where I mention that I wish there were comment sections.
Maybe I'm too used to seeing comment sections, what with me growing up in a generation that uses Instagram and TikTok like they're vitamin supplements, and comments come naturally with them. The same goes with blogs, before Bearblog almost every post I saw came with one embedded. That's not to say blogs with comment sections are better, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strangers In a Tangled Wilderness - Life Without Law]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strangers-in-a-tangled-wilderness-life-without-law?v=1731157792</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/strangers-in-a-tangled-wilderness-life-without-law?v=1731157792"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T13:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Strangers In a Tangled Wilderness
Title: Life Without Law
Subtitle: An introduction to anarchist politics
Date: Fall 2013, revised 2024
Notes: The first edition was published in 2013. This revised edition was published in 2024. Both were published by Strangers In a Tangled Wilderness. This is the 2024 revised edition.
Source: Retrieved on November 18th, 2013 from http://www.tangledwilderness.org/life-without-law/

I want freedom, the right to self-expression, everybody’s right to beautiful, radiant things.
 —Emma Goldman, 1931 
 An anarchist is someone who rejects the domination of one person or class of people over another. Anarch-ism is a very broad umbrella term for a group of political philosophies that are based on the idea that we can live as anarchists. We anarchists want a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by briandw in "It's legal for police to use deception in interrogations. Some want that to end"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42091637</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42091637"/>
        <updated>2024-11-09T00:37:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cases like Tom Perez should never happen. He was held for the murder of his father who was alive. They told him they had video of him dumping bloddy clothes and they knew where he had buried the body. They the said that they would kill his dog and even brought the dog in for him to say goodbye. Should be illegal.
https://abc11.com/post/city-fontana-reaches-900k-settlement-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>briandw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by meneton in "Mitochondria Are Alive"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42090502</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42090502"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T21:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is framed as if there is something novel and profound here, but the "aliveness" of mitochondria is simply a matter of how we choose to apply the label "life" - a human linguistic construct that exists independently of the biological phenomena. This is not a new discussion - science has been considering this question for many decades, just as it has with viruses. These all come down to arguments about semantics and don't add anything to the science.
Mitochondria are fascinating and there is still a huge amount to learn about them but they are totally dependent on the cell's machinery. Most of their genes, the code for their structure, are in the nuclear DNA. A glaring omission if you are trying to make the case that mitochondria are independently living. My heart can exist independently of me, and be transplanted into other people, but does it mean that it is alive?
The implication of the whole article is that there something we have missed. This really isn't the case. Lynn Margulis's endosymbiotic origin of mitochondria was challenged by many, and it did spark a scientific debate - that's how science works. She won the argument comprehensively decades ago and is well established science. There have been many such endosymbiotic events in the history of life - there are subfields of evolutionary biology that study these processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>meneton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon EKS now supports Amazon Application Recovery Controller]]></title>
        <id>4d144c1e62ede65b1d5a0614af432f0bb118f173</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/amazon-eks-now-supports-amazon-application-recovery-controller/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:41:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) now supports Amazon Application Recovery Controller (ARC). ARC is an AWS service that allows you to prepare for and recover from AWS Region or Availability Zone (AZ) impairments. ARC provides two sets of capabilities: Multi-AZ recovery, which includes zonal shift and zonal autoshift, and multi-Region recovery, which includes routing […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahalingam Sivaprakasam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing new APIs for Amazon Location Service Routes, Places, and Maps]]></title>
        <id>f2e28e6d6afe14773ad8b19dd716a4664f30bb45</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-new-apis-for-amazon-location-service-routes-places-and-maps/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T18:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Location unveils 17 new APIs with enhanced route optimization, toll cost calculations, GPS trace snapping, proximity search, predictive suggestions, and static/dynamic map rendering - streamlining developer experiences across a wide range of location-based applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sébastien Stormacq</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China unveils $1.4 trillion stimulus package + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-unveils-1-4-trillion-stimulus-package-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-unveils-1-4-trillion-stimulus-package-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China launches a $1.4 trillion fiscal package to support its economy; Earth is set to experience its hottest year ever, exceeding 1.5 degrees Celsius.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For-Profit Academic Publishers Love LLM Garbage]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53370</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/08/for-profit-academic-publishers-love-llm-garbage/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite metasciences lines is: “Does anyone look around and say…things are going great, I just think we need MORE PAPERS?” Obviously, we all want more scientific progress, better evidence, broader scope — but I don’t think that this is best accomplished by churning out more of these fancy peer-reviewed pdfs. Indeed, our systems […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we prevent conflicts in authoritative DNS configuration using formal verification]]></title>
        <id>5LVsblxj2Git54IRxadpyg</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/topaz-policy-engine-design"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We describe how Cloudflare uses a custom Lisp-like programming language and formal verifier (written in Racket and Rosette) to prevent logical contradictions in our authoritative DNS nameserver’s behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Larisch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read – Logic and truth in economics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45724</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/08/weekend-read-logic-and-truth-in-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T12:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll To be ‘analytical’ and ‘logical’ is something most people find recommendable. These words have a positive connotation. Scientists think more deeply than most other people because they use ‘logical’ and ‘analytical’ methods. In dictionaries, logic is often defined as “reasoning conducted or assessed according to strict principles of validity” and ‘analysis’ as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem is the nation-state]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53366</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/08/the-problem-is-the-nation-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T09:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obviously people are shocked, and particularly shocked at the rejection of normal sensible politics by the rubes who have elected an oaf, a criminal and a rapist to the White House, again. But the trouble is that this kind of thing keeps happening, or nearly happening, and not just in the United States. And it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by schoen in "FDA proposes ending use of oral phenylephrine as OTC nasal decongestant"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42084367</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42084367"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T05:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Context for readers from countries where this isn't an issue, or anyone who hasn't followed decongestant news: one of the most effective decongestants is called pseudoephedrine.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pseudoephedrine
In the past this was easily available, with the most popular brand being Sudafed. My parents always told me that one should take Sudafed when flying after having had a cold, in order to avoid severe ear pain from the pressure changes, but people would also obviously take it when not flying, just in order to reduce the discomfort of the congestion itself.
Pseudoephedrine is very effective. It is also used to synthesize the somewhat related illegal drug methamphetamine ("meth"). Historically, meth manufacturers would hire people to buy large amounts of pseudoephedrine pil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>schoen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kens in "FDA proposes ending use of oral phenylephrine as OTC nasal decongestant"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42084008</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42084008"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T03:59:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite papers is "A simple and convenient synthesis of pseudoephedrine from N-methylamphetamine" [1].
This is a satirical paper. Because pseudoephedrine (i.e. the good decongestant) is very difficult to obtain due to restrictions, but "N-methylamphetamine can be procured at almost any time on short notice", the paper describes how to synthesize pseudoephedrine from meth with a procedure that looks valid.
[1] https://improbable.com/airchives/paperair/volume19/v19i3/Pse...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kens</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering Engineers with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17258</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/empowering-engineers-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background and motivation In the fast-paced world of software development, having the right tools can make all the difference. At Slack, we’ve been working on a set of AI-powered developer tools that are saving 10,000+ hours of developer time yearly, while meeting our strictest requirements for security, data protection, and compliance. In this post, we’ll…
The post Empowering Engineers with AI appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srivani Bethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nritchie in "Ambulance hits cyclist, rushes him to hospital, then sticks him with $1,800 bill"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42082693</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42082693"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:18:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a bicyclist, I'm constantly told how dangerous bicycles are.  Usually, I get a blank look when I explain, bicycles are very safe, it is the cars that are the dangerous part of the equation.  Now I'll have to add fast billing ambulances to the list of dangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nritchie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving deployment visibility for Amazon ECS services]]></title>
        <id>e3489d87aec9d9472e0447501bc2b7e420782e8f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/improving-deployment-visibility-for-amazon-ecs-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying software, it’s critical to have visibility into all stages of the deployment process. Knowing the status of ongoing deployments, troubleshooting issues when things go wrong, and having an audit trail of past deployments are essential for ensuring a safe and reliable release process. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) now provides enhanced observability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great movie title drops are like clever cameo appearances]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8798</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/great-movie-title-drops-like-clever-cameo-appearances/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title Drops, by Germany based data visualisation designer and developer Dominikus Baur, analyses the number of times a movie’s title is mentioned during the story. It’s something that’s not always possible though. I’m looking at 2001: A Space Odyssey, as an example. Although if you can think of a way it could, somehow, happen, let […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who brought us Trump?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45721</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/07/who-brought-us-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Battle is joined … This might annoy some of you — it is my hasty first thought. The Democrats have been thoroughly defeated.  Deservedly so.  They no longer relate to, or reflect, the American working class.  Without building such a relationship they cannot regain power.  Nor should they. Yesterday, early on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "QNX is now free for anything non-commercial, plus there's an RPi image"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If only you could believe them.
QNX has been "opened" twice before. Each time, there was a rug pull, and it went closed again.
Before the first rug pull, open source groups routinely added QNX to their target list. There was a Firefox for QNX. Eclipse had QNX as a target. GCC and most of the Gnu command line tools could be built for QNX.
There was a desktop environment, Photon. I used that as a primary desktop for three years when working on a DARPA Grand Challenge vehicle.
All of that went away after the Harman acquisition of QNX in 2004.
Then, in 2007, QNX went open source. You could even look at the microkernel. It wasn't openly licensed, but you could look inside and build it.
In 2010, RIM acquired QNX, and, with no warning, closed the source. All open source development related to QNX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Express brokers for Amazon MSK to deliver high throughput and faster scaling for your Kafka clusters]]></title>
        <id>01d53755d355acb2eb3a13497efb3eb22cb032f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-express-brokers-for-amazon-msk-to-deliver-high-throughput-and-faster-scaling-for-your-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 3x throughput, 20x faster scaling, and 90% reduced recovery time, Express brokers deliver unmatched performance for Apache Kafka on AWS, streamlining operations while cutting infrastructure costs by 50%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alsetmusic in "Even Microsoft Notepad is getting AI text editing now"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42077047</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42077047"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, they went from not updating in forever, to finally updating it in some meaningful ways a couple years ago, to adding crap that no one wants pretty much right away. Too much, MS. Shoulda quit while you were ahead with tabs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alsetmusic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 3 | Strategic considerations and the political and economic situation in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third and final day of the CADTM International Council was marked by strategic discussions on the future and a presentation of the political, economic and social context in Europe. In Europe: Economic crisis and rise of the far right 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Europe, 
CI 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the latest post-quantum signature standardization candidates]]></title>
        <id>3mOPXbiTgeQHBChx4vUuMs</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/another-look-at-pq-signatures"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIST has standardized four post-quantum signature schemes so far, and they’re not done yet: there are fourteen new candidates in the running for standardization. In this blog post we take measure of them and discover why we ended up with so many PQ signatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bas Westerbaan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly 1 Year Ago vs 8 Months HRT (+ Rhinoplasty)]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Same bathroom, same mirror...same person!
Yes, my glasses are taped because I'm still recovering from rhinoplasty and need to alleviate pressure off my nose.

For those who want to know:
20 sessions of laser + 4 sessions of electrolysis. Still slightly grey on upper and lower lip and continuing laser. I started Progesterone on month five instead of month six--and I shouldn't have. I was simply hurting too much and trying to rush the process. Cyproterone as T-blocker and patches for Estrogen. I'm not giving the amounts here because that's not what's important--it's your blood level concentration for T and E that you should be looking at.
Thinking I would at least like to be one cup bigger in breast growth!
Everyone tells me to imagine where I'll be in three years time and in all honesty, I don't even know where I'll be next year. I try not to think too far ahead now and just stay in the moment. :)
Ew-phoria moment: got checked out by a group of four men in a very uncomfortable way that made me run off. No thank you.
Weird moments: suddenly being asked out in the past two weeks and having crushes admitted to me by a few friends and I had to quickly and politely--but firmly--turn them down. Sorry, I'm very much taken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build things]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently received an email from a reader of my blog asking about my process for building things.
I was wondering if you'd be willing to share your workflow for building products. At big companies, we'd usually do a lot of planning with diagrams, documentation, etc before building anything. I tend to get stuck in analysis paralysis when it comes to building a new products. Seeing how you've built some nice tools like Bear Blog, I wanted to hear from you personally.
I've built a lot of things over the past 10 years. Mostly to satisfy my own curiosity, with a few of them becoming actual products that fund the rest of my tinkering.
My approach to building products is more akin to a gardener than to a product developer. I play around with ideas, follow interesting threads, and see where the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by imgabe in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not about the data. It’s about a foreign government controlling the algorithm that decides what millions of people see, and their ability to shape public opinion through that.
Like imagine if China owned CNN and the New York Times and decided what stories they could publish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>imgabe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by not2b in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of the laser focus on TikTok as a threat, it would be better for the US and Canada to have real data protection laws that would apply equally to TikTok, Meta, Google, Apple, and X. What the EU has done is far from perfect but it bans the worst practices. The Chinese can buy all of the information they want on Americans and Canadians from ad brokers, who will happily sell them everything they need to track individuals' locations.
Perhaps the way to get anti-regulation politicians on board with this is for someone to do what was done to Robert Bork and legally disclose lots of personal info on members of Congress/Parliament, obtained from data brokers and de-anonymized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>not2b</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 3, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune into the vibe, ignore the opinion polls]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8795</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tune-into-vibe-ignore-opinion-polls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Cowen, writing at Marginal Revolution, last July: Democrats and leftists are in fact less happy as people than conservatives are, on average. Americans noticed this, if only subconsciously. Cowen made a whole heap of observations — I’ve quoted but one — about the then upcoming US Presidential election. But it’s tuning into the vibe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>e2bd0370eff5154573d87ca62621505e561215f8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of enhanced and expanded guidance for the AWS Well-Architected Framework with the following six pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability This release includes new best practices and improved prescriptive implementation guidance for the existing best practices. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps on reusable architecture patterns focused on specific business […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ComplexSystems in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failure is in this very common exchange
Average voter: I can't afford groceries at the store. Inflation sucks.
Response: Actually, here is the correct definition of "inflation." As you can see from the correct definition, inflation rates are now good! Hopefully this helps you understand why things will never get better.
What the average voter hears: I can't afford groceries. Your solution to this problem is to reframe the current situation as "good." I still can't afford groceries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ComplexSystems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: please make sure you're up on the site guidelines before commenting: https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html. That means editing out snark, swipes, and flamebait. Or you can simply follow this metarule, which is also in there: "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."
This thread could be worse (ok, it could be a lot worse) but I'm still noticing people breaking the rules. Please follow them instead—it will be a better experience for all of us, including yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America, the country I once knew]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember living in a different country as a child, hearing everyone talk about a faraway place called America.
Everyone wanted to go to America. The adults always spoke about the diversity of people there, the opportunities we could have, and the freedom we’d experience.
Even as a seven-year-old, I sensed the importance of this. Freedom mattered. At the time, we lived in a country where men and women had to walk on separate sides of the street. Women were required to cover themselves. Men and families had separate entrances and seating in restaurants. Women weren’t allowed to drive.
America was the place to be. We would get freedom there.
That was a long time ago.
Now, after living in America for over 26 years as an adult, I see less and less of what those adults once spoke about. It’s no longer the country people dream of coming to.
Today, we are a country that elects a convicted felon. A country where 71 million people chose to elect a fascist over a more than qualified woman. America is now a place where climate change, reproductive rights, and the rights of minorities are dismissed and disregarded—a country increasingly hostile toward those who are not just like them.
I am utterly and devastatingly heartbroken (and terrified).
I went to sleep knowing he would win, but I still held on to a sliver of hope. I woke up at 5 AM and saw Associated Press officially call his win.
A lot will change over these next 4 years.
Be kind to your loved ones today.
Many of us need it.
80/100
Comments and 💬 Community Echoes

No comments available but here are some 💬 Community Echoes
Re: Various election posts by reedybear
Community Commiseration by Kevin Humdrum
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the last cohort of AWS Heroes this year – November 2024]]></title>
        <id>0d594abcf3194d827b593a47f3332675a93e001a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-last-cohort-of-aws-heroes-this-year-november-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we gear up ahead of AWS re:Invent 2024, we’re thrilled to announce our final cohort of new AWS Heroes! These individuals exemplify expertise and dedication to leveraging AWS technologies and sharing knowledge. Their contributions to the AWS community are greatly appreciated, and today we’re excited to celebrate them. Ayyanar Jeyakrishnan – Bengaluru, India Machine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>