<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-07-09T06:45:55.938Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-07-09T06:45:55.938Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The EMAILS Man]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152374</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-emails-man"/>
        <updated>2025-07-09T00:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an excellent post about the latest episode of the Times collaborating with right-wing goons in a baseless smear job, Dan Froomkin details all the journalistic errors, which are worth detailing because none of them are one-offs: All of these points are good. In particular, any time a draft of an investigative piece results in […]
The post The EMAILS Man appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Lemieux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – July 8, 2025 (#582)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23553</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/08/daily-reading-list-july-8-2025-582/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T23:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at AI assisted legacy code migrations, why writing code was never the bottleneck, and why technical debt is just an excuse for lousy code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It turns out that Elon Musk’s anti-woke AI is a literal Nazi]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152367</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/it-turns-out-that-elon-musks-anti-woke-ai-is-a-literal-nazi"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T21:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well I guess not literal, since an artificial person (h/t Lance Hendricksen) can’t literally be anything, but . . . Until a few minutes ago I lived in blissful ignorance of the fact that Elon Musk’s AI company has developed a ChatGPT type generative chatbot or whatever the fuck these things are called. Well I […]
The post It turns out that Elon Musk’s anti-woke AI is a literal Nazi appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So Very Small]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152365</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/so-very-small"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T21:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My colleague at Balloon Juice, Tom Levenson, has written another book. Tom is a popular-science writer and has written a number of books on various aspects of science – climate, Newton, Einstein are a few. So Very Small is particularly relevant to our time. It traces the development of germ theory while also giving an […]
The post So Very Small appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cheryl Rofer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Admin Claims the Epstein Files Don’t Exist, Why?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDdHY6cdsb27c8_fTStBj4B</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDdHY6cdsb27c8_fTStBj4B"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T21:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How stupid do they think everyone is?
I’ll state the obvious, then make on observation.
The Obvious Epstein was an intelligence operation, probably US intelligence and Mossad working together. Every room had cameras, and everyone who partook can be blackmailed.
Observation: The great temptation with the Epstein files isn’t to release them or destroy them, the great temptation is to use them, because they represent a vast amount of power.
Anyway, British and American elites have a predilection for under-age sex and various sexual pecadillos. A taste for being spanked and buggery, in particular, are endemic in the English ruling class due to what goes on in a lot of boys boarding schools. This is so much the case that enjoying being beaten used to be called “the English vice”. We pretend it was just a Victorian thing, but it continues.
Being part of the ruling class traditionally comes with the ability to ignore conventional mores, but members of that class didn’t (and still don’t seem to) fully understand what the changes is surveillance technology mean. Every time some idiot is outed because they filmed their own sexual perversions I laugh, but, simply put, if one must be depraved, keep it in house, don’t film it, you moron, and don’t trust anyone. (This isn’t exactly advice, but a powerful person being blackmailed is even worse than a powerful person with a private vice.)
Trump’s has so far been able to push his program thru, but his approval ratings are underwater and important goals, like the end of birthright citizens immunity to revocation of citizenship are still to come. Trump needs leverage. I suspect he’s decided to use the leverage on hand.
If you’ve read this far, and you read a lot of this site’s articles, you might wish to Subscribe or donate. The site has over over 3,500 posts, and the site, and Ian, take money to run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Only the shadow docket knows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152363</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/only-the-shadow-docket-knows"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T21:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here we go again: The U.S. Supreme Court has granted another emergency stay request from the Trump-Vance administration to stay the injunction two lower courts had approved in AFGE v. Trump that halted the unlawful reorganization of the federal government. The court’s decision permits the administration to continue with plans to restructure federal agencies using Agency Reductions in […]
The post Only the shadow docket knows appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate and modernize VMware workloads with AWS Transform for VMware]]></title>
        <id>a2b03040e8215b90fc5516342a2119a68ef68490</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/migrate-and-modernize-vmware-workloads-with-aws-transform-for-vmware/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T20:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Transform for VMware is a service that tackles cloud migration challenges by significantly reducing manual effort and accelerating the migration of critical VMware workloads to AWS Cloud. In this post, we highlight its comprehensive capabilities, including streamlined discovery and assessment, intelligent network conversion, enhanced security and compliance, and orchestrated migration execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiran Reid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide to the Madness of King Donald]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152361</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/a-guide-to-the-madness-of-king-donald"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T18:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sultan of Shrill has a useful guide to Trump’s latest round of arbitrary, unilateral, ad hoc tariffs: These tariffs are really, really high One way to look at the newly announced tariffs is in the light of history. The infamous Smoot-Hawley tariff of 1930 pushed the average tariff rate to about 20 percent. So […]
The post A Guide to the Madness of King Donald appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Lemieux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mamdani Puzzle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152357</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/the-mamdani-puzzle"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T18:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I try not to pay too much attention to New York politics, but as I often fail it’s worth sharing some of the things I’m reading… Smarter members of the Establishment recognize the existential threat posed by the nascent movement. “Mamdani’s the face of a new demographic in New York,” Hank Sheinkopf, a longtime Democratic campaign […]
The post The Mamdani Puzzle appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Farley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – The Stab in the Back]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295078</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-the-stab-in-the-back.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the war in Ukraine moves toward an ugly conclusion unfavorable to the U.S., I anticipate the appearance of a common propaganda phenomenon following lost wars: the stab in the back. This is a propaganda tactic in which military defeat is attributed to domestic treachery undermining the heroic efforts of the military. The bellicose elements […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon sells cartoon balloons in town]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152358</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/elon-sells-cartoon-balloons-in-town"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T17:34:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As finally business thrives: Jeffrey Epstein did not maintain a “client list,” the Justice Department acknowledged Monday as it said no more files related to the wealthy financier’s sex trafficking investigation would be made public despite promises from Attorney General Pam Bondi that had raised the expectations of conservative influencers and conspiracy theorists. The acknowledgment that the well-connected […]
The post Elon sells cartoon balloons in town appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Russia Greatly Accelerate Its Ukraine Tempo to Facilitate Responding to Turkiye-Azerbaijan Threat to Iran?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295125</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/will-russia-greatly-accelerate-its-ukraine-tempo-to-facilitate-responding-to-turkiye-azerbaijan-threat-to-iran.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T14:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will Azerbaijan turning against Russia, perhaps supporting an attack on Iran, force Russia to move faster than it might otherwise in Ukraine?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Una buena vista de Lamine Yamal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152351</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/una-buena-vista-de-lamine-yamal"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T14:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buena Vista is small mountain town in the central Colorado Rockies, between South Park and the San Luis Valley. We spend a lot of time there in the summer, and this weekend I had the following experience. At the intersection of Main Street and the state highway that runs through the town, I saw a […]
The post Una buena vista de Lamine Yamal appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Campos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How TimescaleDB helped us scale analytics and reporting]]></title>
        <id>4YbqxvhldlPwGPRmqgrZPn</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/timescaledb-art/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare chose TimescaleDB to power its Digital Experience Monitoring and Zero Trust Analytics products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Cepa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Oracle Database@AWS for simplified Oracle Exadata migrations to the AWS Cloud]]></title>
        <id>5802f92fb52d014bfb7bef99f452440ef3780bef</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-oracle-databaseaws-for-simplified-oracle-exadata-migrations-to-the-aws-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T11:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle Database@AWS is now generally available with planned extension to 20 new Regions. This blog shows you how to get started and how to integrate with zero-ETL integrations with Amazon Redshift, Amazon S3, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, it was “Just a Mistake” . . . We thought He was Someone Else!]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178175</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/hey-it-was-just-a-mistake-we-thought-he-was-someone-else"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a recorded piece. The link is below. I think you may be able to hear Joyce Vance and Adam Klasfeld discuss the judge’s questioning the government on what they are holding Abrego Garcia’. Throw on top of that El Salvador stating they had no power to hold 200 people in prison there. Our […]
The post Hey, it was “Just a Mistake” . . . We thought He was Someone Else! appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Erik Visits an American Grave, Part 1,920]]></title>
        <id>https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/?p=152155</id>
        <link href="https://www.lawyersgunsmoneyblog.com/2025/07/erik-visits-an-american-grave-part-1921"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the grave of Eleazar Wheelock. Born in Windham, Connecticut in 1711, Wheelock grew up in what passed for the elite of the early 18th century, which wasn’t really that wealthy. But his family had a pretty big farm and he got to go to Yale, where he graduated in 1733. He was ordained […]
The post Erik Visits an American Grave, Part 1,920 appeared first on Lawyers, Guns & Money.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erik Loomis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Facts About Medicaid Coverage for People Living in Rural Areas]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178162</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/key-facts-about-medicaid-coverage-for-people-living-in-rural-areas"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some words and 4 simple, easy to understand charts on Medicaid on who uses Medicaid in rural areas and under the age of 65 years. Four minutes of read time to get the idea. If Republicans and Tr__p are going to whack rural citizens, you might as well know a little about them. Five-minute read. […]
The post Key Facts About Medicaid Coverage for People Living in Rural Areas appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 7/8/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295059</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/links-7-8-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T10:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our rollicking daily links: RFK, Jr. hearts bird flu, nuclear renaissance? BRICS underwhelms, China-India rare earths dustup, moar NATO fear-mongering, Tucker Pezeshkian interview, Netanyahu nominates Trump for Peace Prize, Russia to gear up? Trump tariff threats, AI firings, moar market worries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Reasons Why the Tony Blair Institute’s Involvement in “Gaza Riviera” Project Should Surprise No One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295061</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/no-one-should-be-surprised-by-ft-allegations-that-tony-blairs-institute-for-global-change-took-part-in-gaza-riviera-project.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T10:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The war in Gaza has "created a once-in-a-century opportunity to rebuild Gaza from first principles . . . as a secure, modern prosperous society."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI, Antitrust & Privacy: When More Competition Makes Things Worse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295114</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/ai-antitrust-privacy-when-more-competition-makes-things-worse.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T09:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increased AI competition worsens surveillance, manipulation, and disinformation—threatening privacy, autonomy, and democracy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I stopped reading the NYT]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178183</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/why-i-stopped-reading-the-nyt"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T09:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been a bit baffled recently by comments by friends expressing anxiety about NYC mayoral candidate Zohran Mamdani. Yeah, I ignore the right-wing wind machine over at Fox. But since I stopped reading the gray lady, I missed the propaganda and misdirection she’s been pumping out. “The Times has it out for Zohran Mamdani. The […]
The post Why I stopped reading the NYT appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The European Green Deal has failed]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-european-green-deal-has-failed</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/the-european-green-deal-has-failed"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T09:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The anti-democratic, technocratic, fiscally restrictive and ideologically captured nature of the European Union make it structurally unable to implement a sensible and socially just green transition]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some thoughts on “socialism,” history and the triumph of propaganda]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178136</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/some-thoughts-on-socialism-history-and-the-triumph-of-propaganda"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T09:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The words “socialism” and “Marxism” have long been synonymous with the Soviet Union and the People’s Republic of China. Oddly, because neither country was socialist or Marxist. Lenin and the Bolsheviks (bolshevik means “majoritarian,” even though it was a minority party, a triumph of propaganda) crushed Marxist/socialist worker-led organizations after the 1917 Revolution (really a […]
The post Some thoughts on “socialism,” history and the triumph of propaganda appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Centuries-Long History of Russophobia Opens the Doors to Cold War 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295034</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/centuries-long-history-of-russophobia-opens-the-doors-to-cold-war-2-0.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T05:40:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Russophobia has been long in the making and continued to color international relations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End Of Cash &amp; The Rise Of The Non-Person]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBXREMnMdQKAXRn30Ky9mT6</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBXREMnMdQKAXRn30Ky9mT6"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T04:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image by TW Collins

Back in 2017 I wrote “The End of Cash”:
Understand, however, that getting rid of cash is part of this. Understand that blockchains, “coins” do not have to ultimately be a technology of freedom, but can easily be a totalitarian technology. Understand that virtually no one in a position of power is your friend on this: They want to know, they want to control, they want to be able to decide how you spend your money and your time, and they want to have an electronic dossier on you which is complete, and which will be usable to destroy you, because no one has never done or said something which cannot be made to look not just bad, but terrible and illegal, especially if you can pick, say, ten quotes or actions out of a lifetime.

In the 80s and 90s it was possible to live th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Study could lead to LLMs that are better at complex reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/study-could-lead-llms-better-complex-reasoning-0708</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/study-could-lead-llms-better-complex-reasoning-0708"/>
        <updated>2025-07-08T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers developed a way to make large language models more adaptable to challenging tasks like strategic planning or process optimization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – July 7, 2025 (#581)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23519</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/07/daily-reading-list-july-7-2025-581/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T23:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at enterprise-ready AI, an open-to-everyone book on agentic design patterns, and why execs who used gen AI made worse predictions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Bedrock API keys, EC2 C8gn instances, Amazon Nova Canvas virtual try-on, and more (July 7, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>1932b892f90818d65b608f0012e13ae8148aa742</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-bedrock-api-keys-amazon-nova-canvas-virtual-try-on-and-more-july-7-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T21:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Monday we tell you about the best releases and blogs that caught our attention last week. This week I’m making an exception to include a release from today: Amazon Bedrock API keys. This new feature simplifies generative AI development by providing direct API authentication without needing to manually configure IAM principals and policies. Amazon […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elizabeth Fuentes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economically weighted ISM manufacturing + services indexes continue to warrant “recession watch”]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178148</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/economically-weighted-ism-manufacturing-services-indexes-continue-to-warrant-recession-watch"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T21:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat Last month the new orders components of the economically weighted ISM manufacturing and services indexes warranted the hoisting of a yellow flag “Recession Watch.”  This month that continued. To recap, because manufacturing is much less important to the economy than in the decades before the Millennium, the economically weighted average of the […]
The post Economically weighted ISM manufacturing + services indexes continue to warrant “recession watch” appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Meta’s Mark Zuckerberg Loves To Throw Good Money After Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294971</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/meta-mark-zuckerberg-ai-bidding-war.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Mark Zuckerberg is upping the ante in the AI business, triggering a bidding war for talent and he's willing to poach from competitors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Wilson Turner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quality-focused prompts for the vibe coding addict]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23531</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/07/quality-focused-prompts-for-the-vibe-coding-addict/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T16:35:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve vibe coded an app? Congrats. That’s cool. Maybe you’re completely new to programming, or…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New postdoctoral fellowship program to accelerate innovation in health care]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/new-postdoctoral-fellowship-program-accelerate-innovation-health-care-0707</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/new-postdoctoral-fellowship-program-accelerate-innovation-health-care-0707"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched with a gift from the Biswas Family Foundation, the Biswas Postdoctoral Fellowship Program will support postdocs in health and life sciences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michaela Jarvis | Office of Innovation and Strategy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring data and its influence on political behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/exploring-data-and-its-influence-political-behavior-0707</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/exploring-data-and-its-influence-political-behavior-0707"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In MIT's course 17.831 (Data and Politics), students are introduced to the power of analysis, visualization, and research-supported insight into political outcomes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Daniel | School of Humanities, Arts, and Social Sciences</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricane Helene Set Up Future Disasters, From Landslides to Flooding – Cascading Hazards Like These Are Now Upending Risk Models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295040</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/hurricane-helene-set-up-future-disasters-from-landslides-to-flooding-cascading-hazards-like-these-are-now-upending-risk-models.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T13:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascading hazards occur when one natural event alters the landscape in ways that lead to future hazards—and they are increasing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing simple and secure egress policies by hostname in Cloudflare’s SASE platform]]></title>
        <id>1NxtPefzr7flsiIe8gZ43L</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/egress-policies-by-hostname/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare's SASE platform now offers egress policies by hostname, domain, content category, and application in open beta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Aggarwal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Courts]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178122</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/the-courts-2"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Talking about courts today. If you have ever gone to a Federal Court, it is a matter of just the facts people. Don’t look for sympathy because it is not there if you get this far in the first place. You can have the best of the best in attorneys. Judges will listen and maybe […]
The post The Courts appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Assessment of the BBB and Its Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178128</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/another-assessment-of-the-bbb-and-its-impact"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard not to talk about the Republicans and Trump’s BBB. Yep, the political party is mentioned first because they are allowing this to happen. It maybe some people do not know the detail and have no idea. For the rest of us? It is like waiting for the train to hit. You see […]
The post Another Assessment of the BBB and Its Impact appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Link 7/7/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=295026</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/link-7-7-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T10:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our explosive daily links, including Texas floods, California fires, BRICS summit, police using AI to doctor evidence photos, and a defense of joy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chaos in the Caucasus: Türkiye and Azerbaijan Make Their US-Israel-Backed Move Against Russia and Iran]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294963</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/07/chaos-in-the-caucasus-turkiye-and-azerbaijan-make-their-us-israel-backed-move-against-russia-and-iran.html"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. officials say involvement of Russia and Iran in their own backyard of the South Caucasus is "unstable and undesirable."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is a deal not a deal?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178134</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/when-is-a-deal-not-a-deal"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T09:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do we say that a blackmailer is trying to reach a “deal?” Is a successful extortion a “deal?” “Harvard’s hundreds of unionized professors are pushing the university not to make any deal with President Trump in its deepening dispute with the White House, and they say they hope to flex their increasing organizing prowess to […]
The post When is a deal not a deal? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts of a boomer]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178115</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/thoughts-of-a-boomer"/>
        <updated>2025-07-07T08:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was born squarely in the middle of the “baby boom” generation. We had daily bible readings in my first grade public school class. We said the pledge of allegiance through high school in my public school system. Boomers are sometimes identified with the protests, rebelliousness and non-conformity of the ‘60s, but many or most […]
The post Thoughts of a boomer appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tax Cuts to the Rich . . . What Are They Good for?  Absolutely Nothing . . .]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178120</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/tax-cuts-to-the-rich-what-are-they-good-for-absolutely-nothing"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T21:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dipping deep here to an old tune sung by the Temptations and then Edwin Starr. Tax Breaks to the wealthy do not pay for themselves and neither do they trickle down to lower income people. The 2017 Tax Break The reality is the 2017 Tax Cuts and Jobs Act (TCJA) did not pay for itself […]
The post Tax Cuts to the Rich . . . What Are They Good for?  Absolutely Nothing . . . appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – July 06, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAVGxOUkCOO2C4eU0TgHJ5A</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAVGxOUkCOO2C4eU0TgHJ5A"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T18:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – July 06, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
Trump not violating any law
‘He who saves his Country does not violate any Law’
Trump Stuns By Saying ‘I Don’t Know’ When Asked Directly NBC’s Kristen Welker ‘Don’t You Need to Uphold the Constitution?’
Joe DePaolo, May 4th, 2025 [mediaite.com]
Welcome to the Age of Disappearance: America’s new era of secret police 
Hamilton Nolan, July 02, 2025 [How Things Work]
…an avalanche of new funding for the Department of Homeland Security, ICE, and anti-immigration measures is, in fact, coming. This is going to spill well past the bounds of what any sane person would consider to be “immigration enforcement.” It is going to create a lavishly funded, unaccountable, quasi-secret police force that will transform our nation for the worse…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promise Kept on Tipped Income?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178111</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/promise-kept-on-tipped-income"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T18:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the signing of the Budget Bill, persons working at “an occupation which customarily and regularly receive tips” can deduct up to $25,000 of tip income provided their total income does not exceed $150,000. This deduction will be phased out beginning in 2028 unless extended by Congress. Trump made three promises to reduce taxes to […]
The post Promise Kept on Tipped Income? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Terry Nilles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elon Musk and the third party opioid]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178088</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/elon-musk-and-the-third-party-opioid"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T16:11:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see where Elon has announced that he’s starting a third party. Setting aside the problem that he backed Trump in the last election and was in the tank with the Trump administration blowing up the federal government with DOGE, what are we to make of this? Ross Perot was the most successful third party […]
The post Elon Musk and the third party opioid appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 in 4 Americans Still Reject Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178105</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/1-in-4-americans-still-reject-evolution"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another well written recreation of the Scopes Trial of 1925. It has been called the Scopes Money Trial. This a bit different than the movie you may watch on the topic. As the story goes John T. Scopes was approached by the American Civil Liberties Union to teach evolution. John Thomas Scopes was a young […]
The post 1 in 4 Americans Still Reject Evolution appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medicaid Cuts and Immigrants]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178101</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/medicaid-cuts-and-immigrants"/>
        <updated>2025-07-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of Republican fables on how healthcare programs are being taken advantage of by fraudulent enrollments. They will not be happy until something serious occurs and many are afflicted. Center for Children and Families takes the lead on debunking the governments stories. “Factchecking The White House ‘Mythbuster’ on Medicaid Cuts and Immigrants,” Center For Children […]
The post Medicaid Cuts and Immigrants appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Deal democrat’s Weekly Indicators June 30 -July 4]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178096</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/new-deal-democrats-weekly-indicators-june-30-july-4"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T20:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat My Weekly Indicators post is up at Seeking Alpha. There were almost no changes to any of the high frequency indicators in any timeframe last week. Despite that, below the surface, there has been a very gradual weakening of a number of important indicators in both the monthly and weekly data.  […]
The post New Deal democrat’s Weekly Indicators June 30 -July 4 appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCYwdakx6vQ5iCbvh2Vx6BW</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCYwdakx6vQ5iCbvh2Vx6BW"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T20:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How are You Feeling About America Today?]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178029</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/how-are-you-feeling-about-america-today"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T19:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My Two Cents: If it is of any consequence, this Baby Boomer is not happy to have Trump as the President again. He was terrible the first time. And he is really working hard to be more terrible this time. The threats keep on coming. People are kidnapped after court hearings, no warrants, masked so […]
The post How are You Feeling About America Today? appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for midterms]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178086</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/just-in-time-for-midterms"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T16:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The court announced that it will hear two voting-related challenges when the court resumes in October: a reargument of a long-running dispute of Louisiana’s congressional map and a case that could erode one of the few existing limits on campaign funding. “The Louisiana case is a challenge to the state’s congressional map, which includes two […]
The post Just in time for midterms appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ideas on Immigration and Being an American in 1907]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178052</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/ideas-on-immigration-and-being-an-american-in-1907"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was out and about looking around for interesting pieces or articles which I could post at Angry Bear. I saw this article on Infidel753’s Blog. The author of this newspaper article is right or mostly right. My thoughts? One can still be in disagreement in America as long as they are not openly or […]
The post Ideas on Immigration and Being an American in 1907 appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[His rockets blow up, his cars crash]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178084</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/his-rockets-blow-up-his-cars-crash"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T14:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Autonomous driving is the core promise around which Elon Musk has built his company. Tesla has never delivered a truly self-driving vehicle, yet the richest person in the world keeps repeating the claim that his cars will soon drive entirely without human help. Is Tesla’s autopilot really as advanced as he says? “The Tesla Files […]
The post His rockets blow up, his cars crash appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your kids’ and grandkids’ tax dollars at work]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178039</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/your-kids-and-grandkids-tax-dollars-at-work"/>
        <updated>2025-07-05T13:35:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s BBB is a huge windfall for the Department of Homeland Security: “The bill gives ICE $29.8 billion to hire new staff and conduct deportations. That will lead to a hiring spurt of deportation officers; an additional $4.1 billion bump goes to Customs and Border Protection for new personnel. “For immigration detention, also overseen by […]
The post Your kids’ and grandkids’ tax dollars at work appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Budget Bill That Will Harm Social Security’s Finances]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178044</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/a-budget-bill-that-will-harm-social-securitys-finances"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T19:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just so you know: Democrats, health advocates, and even some Republicans have spoken out against the Social Security bill firmly. They are calling it a Trojan horse cutting the safety net for millions of Americans while making up for tax breaks for the wealthiest. Mostly and if living in a house with a mortgage as […]
The post A Budget Bill That Will Harm Social Security’s Finances appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alexander Zevin: &ldquo;Gilded City&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gilded-city</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/gilded-city"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T19:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zohran Mamdani’s NYC.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The American Republic, July 4, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178041</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/the-american-republic-july-4-2025"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T18:05:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat From the Declaration of Independence: When in the Course of human events, it becomes necessary for one people to dissolve the political bonds which have connected them with another, and to assume among the powers of the earth, the separate and equal station to which the Laws of Nature and […]
The post The American Republic, July 4, 2025 appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robotic probe quickly measures key properties of new materials]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/robotic-probe-quickly-measures-key-properties-new-materials-0704</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/robotic-probe-quickly-measures-key-properties-new-materials-0704"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developed to analyze new semiconductors, the system could streamline the development of more powerful solar panels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[And they vote]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178028</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/and-they-vote"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I grew up in the state that hosted the Scopes trial. 100 years later, 25% of my fellow citizens believe in creationism. “Trollinger and Trollinger note that today approximately one-quarter of all Americans are young-earth creationists and reject much of modern biology and modern geology, not to mention modern cosmology. Answers in Genesis, which is […]
The post And they vote appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Intersections&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/intersections</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/intersections"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T12:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On expressways.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brais Fernández: &ldquo;Twilight in Spain&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/twilight-in-spain</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/twilight-in-spain"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T11:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Perils of progressivism.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Second Continental Congress adopted the Declaration of Independence]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178021</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/second-continental-congress-adopted-the-declaration-of-independence"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pres. Trump revokes our independence And on July 4, 1776, the Second Continental Congress adopted the Declaration of Independence, declaring: “We hold these truths to be self-evident, that all men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable rights, that among these are Life, Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness.” […]
The post Second Continental Congress adopted the Declaration of Independence appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Haskell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I am Too Afraid to Say “No, to Trump” Category, So, Do Something to Save WI Constituents!]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178015</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/i-am-too-afraid-to-say-no-to-trump-category-so-do-something-to-save-wi-constituents"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WI Representative Derrick: And “yes” just so you know, I did vote for the bill even though I knew it might endanger Wisconsin citizens and Wisconsin rural hospitals may be forced to close. AB: Wow, what an upright guy! Republican Congressional Representative Derrick warns Democrat Governor Tony Evers he has to do something. Bur the […]
The post I am Too Afraid to Say “No, to Trump” Category, So, Do Something to Save WI Constituents! appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Republican bill will cut Medicare]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178001</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/the-republican-bill-will-cut-medicare"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T09:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, it cuts Medicaid explicitly. But it will result in cuts to Medicare as well: “But now Republicans have created another problem. They didn’t just cut Medicaid; they also have forced nearly half a trillion dollars in cuts to Medicare, the health program for the elderly. “Because of a statutory requirement to automatically impose budget […]
The post The Republican bill will cut Medicare appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Words On The &quot;Big Beautiful Bill”]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBHixa8R0IybMWhxlEUZi1M</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBHixa8R0IybMWhxlEUZi1M"/>
        <updated>2025-07-04T03:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obviously this is a pile of steaming garbage. Four trillion of tax cuts, paid for by cutting Medicaid (11.8 million people will lose health care according to the CBO) and perhaps 8 million people will lose food benefits under SNAP. Green energy subsidies are cut (no, shut up, there are tons of dirty energy subsidies) and there’s a huge budget increase for ICE (including more prison camps), America’s Gestapo.
And, of course, there’s all sorts of nasty in the details, like, for example, a ban on States regulating AI, cuts to Planned Parenthood (which does far more than abortions), and so on.
A lot of Americans are going to be hurt by this. I’d go so far as to say it might be the worst American federal budget I’ve seen in my life, though Obama and the Fed’s giveaways to the rich were worse.
Oh, and politicians like Josh Hawley who pretend to care about ordinary people? Yeah, fake. He voted for the bill.
I reiterate that things in the US are going to get worse and worse for years, with only a small chance of a reversal (based on a Mamdani style left populism). Get out if you can, take steps to prepare and protect yourself if you can’t.
If you’ve read this far, and you read a lot of my articles, you might wish to Subscribe or donate. I’ve written over 3,500 posts, and the site, and Ian, take money to run.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Does The CCP Accomplish Goals Meant To Better China’s People?]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBt5DL45_7dJoLP51T0FcGD</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBt5DL45_7dJoLP51T0FcGD"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T18:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese and American flags flying together

When I originally formulated this article it was just “Why does the CCP accomplish its goals?”
But that’s a stupid article. Certainly there are governments which fail to accomplish their goals, in countries which lacks state capacity or are in constrained positions. But for most of my life most Western governments haven’t been all that constrained, they just acted as if they were.
The truth is that Western governments have mostly accomplished their goals over the last 45 years: it’s just that their ur-goal was to make the rich richer. If that meant burning everything else down, they were OK with that. There are a number of reasons for this, but basically political elites were bought: do what the rich want and even if you lose office you’ll be ver…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s starting already]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177996</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/its-starting-already"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T18:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“LINCOLN, Neb. (KLKN) — A clinic in southwest Nebraska announced Wednesday that it is closing due to financial challenges, including anticipated Medicaid cuts. “McCook-based Community Hospital said it is shutting down its clinic in Curtis, a town of about 900 people. “The Curtis Medical Center has been in operation for more than 30 years.” But […]
The post It’s starting already appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobless claims remain neutral]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=178003</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/jobless-claims-remain-neutral"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T17:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat In addition to the jobs report, because this is Thursday we also got the latest jobless claims numbers. To wit, initial claims declined -4,000 to 233,000, and the four week moving average declined -3,750 to 241,500. With the typical one week delay, continuing claims were unchanged at 1.964 million: The more […]
The post Jobless claims remain neutral appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[June jobs report weakness: not enough for “recession watch,” but not too far away either]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177998</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/june-jobs-report-weakness-not-enough-for-recession-watch-but-not-too-far-away-either"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T17:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat ﻿﻿Even before the new Administration took office in Washington, my focus had been on whether the economy would have a “soft” or “hard” landing, i.e., recession. That has only intensified by the utter chaos of this Administration, particularly about tariffs. So my focus now is looking for “hard” vs.”soft” data indicating […]
The post June jobs report weakness: not enough for “recession watch,” but not too far away either appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel, the US and Iran: the war has only just begun]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/israel-the-us-and-iran-the-war-has</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/israel-the-us-and-iran-the-war-has"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T13:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The old neocon dream of redrawing the Middle East through a series of regime changes to the benefit of the US and Israel, shelved for over a decade, has returned to the forefront]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivermectin Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177472</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/ivermectin-usage"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remember the drug Ivermectin during the Covid epidemic? The animal-deworming medication was used so avidly as an off-label COVID treatment during the pandemic that some feed stores ended up going out of stock. To prevent stockouts one store posted this: “MUST SHOW A PIC OF YOU AND YOUR HORSE.” A sign that demanded proof from would-be […]
The post Ivermectin Usage appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book Review “Basic Economics”]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177475</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/book-review-basic-economics"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Zetland doing a review of Thomas Sowell’s book, “Basic Economics.” I had written Mr. Sowell once, maybe a decade ago. I was the recipient of his book. I was a third of the way through it when I was called away for a business trip which lasted a month. I found the book and […]
The post Book Review “Basic Economics” appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Angry Bear</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GOP: Zohran Mamdani is the second coming of Lenin]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177984</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/gop-zohran-mamdani-is-the-second-coming-of-lenin"/>
        <updated>2025-07-03T09:28:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trump GOP has its knickers in a twist over Zohran Mamdani. He’s a Muslim, he’s young, he’s a Democratic Socialist (like Bernie) and he might be the next mayor of NYC. So the GOP hate machine is on blast: “Since the MAGA hordes first learned about the existence of NYC Democratic mayoral nominee Zohran […]
The post GOP: Zohran Mamdani is the second coming of Lenin appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Eissenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – July 2, 2025 (#580)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=23468</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/07/02/daily-reading-list-july-2-2025-580/"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T23:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the landscape of IaC tools, what agentic coding recommendations you should follow, and which warning signs tell you its time to switch CI/CD platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prices of Both Housing And Rent Are Decreasing In China]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA1-1moKa7EEmNqeJq5hArn</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItA1-1moKa7EEmNqeJq5hArn"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T21:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2016, Xi said that houses were for living in, not for speculating. The Chinese government took steps to reduce prices, those steps took time to bear fruit.
 
 
Likewise, rent prices have been dropping recently:

And yes, this is a result of government policy:
While, according to the PBOC, in the pre-pandemic decade, the annual rental inflation in China exceeded 1.2%, it slowed significantly in recent years and has been in the negative in the last twelve months. In March 2025, the rent of the rental housing component of the consumer price index (CPI) showed a 0.1% year-on-year decline, trending upwards, however, from -0.4% and -0.3% annual change rates previously registered in September 2024 and December 2024, respectively.
“In recent years, rents have declined due to lower income expect…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confronting the AI/energy conundrum]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/confronting-ai-energy-conundrum-0702</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/confronting-ai-energy-conundrum-0702"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT Energy Initiative’s annual research symposium explores artificial intelligence as both a problem and a solution for the clean energy transition.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leda Zimmerman | MIT Energy Initiative</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JOLTS survey for May still consistent with “soft landing” scenario]]></title>
        <id>https://angrybearblog.com/?p=177986</id>
        <link href="https://angrybearblog.com/2025/07/jolts-survey-for-may-still-consistent-with-soft-landing-scenario"/>
        <updated>2025-07-02T18:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[– by New Deal democrat ﻿As promised, let me parse the JOLTS survey for May, which was reported yesterday.  As a quick refresher, this survey decomposes the employment market into openings, hires, quits, and layoffs. In 2024 the data were most consistent with a “soft landing,” but the actions of the new Administration, especially on trade, […]
The post JOLTS survey for May still consistent with “soft landing” scenario appeared first on Angry Bear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewDealdemocrat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>