<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-13T12:40:30.049Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-13T12:40:30.049Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Borrowing and Lending in the Eurodollar and Selected Deposit Markets?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29775</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/who-is-borrowing-and-lending-in-the-eurodollar-and-selected-deposit-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Liberty Street Economics post discussed who is borrowing and lending in the federal funds (fed funds) market. This post explores activity in two other markets for short-term bank liabilities that are often perceived as close substitutes for fed funds—the markets for Eurodollars and “selected deposits.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Gonzalo Cisternas, and Will Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/13/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271461</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-13-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T10:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elections and Devaluations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271472</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/elections-and-devaluations.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T09:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle surprise! Regimes facing elections often goose their economies, leading to currency appreciation pre-vote and devaluations afterwards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In the Race for Space Metals, Companies Hope to Cash In]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271466</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/in-the-race-for-space-metals-companies-hope-to-cash-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T09:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mining asteroids could, in theory, reduce the burden on Earth’s resources. What could go wrong?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Jeffersonian Conversation on Antisemitism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322255</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/a-jeffersonian-conversation-on-antisemitism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The elected imbeciles strolling the halls of government. The platitudes with which they perfume their genocidal hypocrisy regarding bombed children. The Congressional committees which conduct themselves as a grotesque amalgam of the Sanhedrin and the Council Of Trent. All are a direct result of a citizenry with a limitless inability to fathom. More
The post A Jeffersonian Conversation on Antisemitism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerry Long</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Modest Proposal: The UN General Assembly and Palestinian Recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322278</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/a-modest-proposal-the-un-general-assembly-and-palestinian-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite being described in some circles as such, the latest vote in the United Nations General Assembly on Palestine’s status is hardly extraordinary.  For one, it does not vest the Palestinian territories with statehood but burnishes its credentials to join the club.  It pushes those scrappy, desperate entities so despoiled and abused into deeper involvement with the  More
The post A Modest Proposal: The UN General Assembly and Palestinian Recognition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are Greek Students Waiting For?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322152</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/what-are-greek-students-waiting-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the student movement in solidarity with the Palestinians and denunciation of their genocide by Israel intensifies in the United States and now spreads across the planet, there are growing indications that it is succeeding in influencing the central balance of forces while it is being recognized as a major factor in international developments of decisive importance! Thus, Washington's "sudden" distancing of itself from the Netanyahu government, which followed (or perhaps...preceded) Hamas' acceptance of the Qatar-Egypt peace plan, is mainly attributed to the asphyxiating pressure exerted on President Biden and the world superpower establishment by the American student movement in solidarity with the Palestinian people.r More
The post What are Greek Students Waiting For? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Giorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Banning TikTok: National Security, Civil Rights & Investments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322281</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/banning-tiktok-national-security-civil-rights-investments/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last week of April, Congress passed, and President Biden signed, a law banning TikTok in the United States if its parent company, ByteDance, did not sell it to an American company within 12 months. The New York Times Senior writer David Leonhardt provides a good summary of why this bill was passed. It is a  More
The post Banning TikTok: National Security, Civil Rights & Investments appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Zoonotic Diseases: How Humans Get Sick from Nonhuman Animals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322279</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/understanding-zoonotic-diseases-how-humans-get-sick-from-nonhuman-animals/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human and animal health are closely linked, with many diseases shared between them. As our world becomes more developed and interconnected, the proximity between wild animals and humans is shrinking, increasing the risk of disease transmission. At the same time, humans are growing increasingly dependent on animals as a source of food. The emergence of  More
The post Understanding Zoonotic Diseases: How Humans Get Sick from Nonhuman Animals appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vicky Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Local Newspapers Are Lifelines for Climate-Disaster Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322298</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/local-newspapers-are-lifelines-for-climate-disaster-communities/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When wildfires began erupting in the Texas Panhandle in February, Laurie Ezzell Brown, the editor and publisher of the Canadian Record, was in Houston on a panel discussing ways in which losing local newspapers represents a danger to democracy. Running the once-a-week Record from the Panhandle town of Canadian, she certainly knew something about the rise of “news  More
The post Local Newspapers Are Lifelines for Climate-Disaster Communities appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Braxton Little</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Is Losing In Ukraine.  Blame China, Says Blinken]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322241</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/us-is-losing-in-ukraine-blame-china-says-blinken/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the close of his recent trip to China, on April 26 while still in Beijing, Sec. of State, Anthony Blinken, made an extremely bellicose statement to the press.  Blinken’s words marked a new phase in the narrative to prepare the American and European public for more conflict with China.   As Caitlin Johnstone has reminded  More
The post US Is Losing In Ukraine.  Blame China, Says Blinken appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John V. Walsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultraprocessed Deadly Corporate Food Demands Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322292</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/ultraprocessed-deadly-corporate-food-demands-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About forty-five years ago, at a social gathering, I asked an executive of a Minneapolis-based large food processing company if he fed heavily sugared cereals to his children. He smiled as he shook his head. Smart person. His and other major companies producing what is now called Ultraprocessed Foods (UPFs) had scientists and labs. They  More
The post Ultraprocessed Deadly Corporate Food Demands Action appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With a Modest Financial Transactions Tax, Jim Simons Would not Have Been Superrich]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322177</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/with-a-modest-financial-transactions-tax-jim-simons-would-not-have-been-superrich/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times reported that Jim Simons, the founder of Medallion hedge fund, died this week. As a result of his fund, according to the article, he accumulated more than $20 billion over his lifetime. Simons was a math genius who had made many important breakthroughs in various areas of math. Back in the  More
The post With a Modest Financial Transactions Tax, Jim Simons Would not Have Been Superrich appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Run a Food Pantry, But It’s Not Enough. We Need SNAP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322239</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/i-run-a-food-pantry-but-its-not-enough-we-need-snap/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T05:33:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I run a food pantry. I’m proud of the work we do. But if lawmakers passed a liveable minimum wage or invested more in programs like SNAP, people wouldn’t need to rely on pantries like mine. Pantries are a critical piece of the anti-hunger puzzle, but they’re filler pieces. Government nutrition programs — with the  More
The post I Run a Food Pantry, But It’s Not Enough. We Need SNAP appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carla Venutra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mutual Backtracking in US-China Student Exchanges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322296</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/13/mutual-backtracking-in-us-china-student-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T04:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent talks between US and Chinese leaders, they have found common ground in support for more people-to-people exchanges, particularly in education. Presidents Biden and Xi both mentioned the importance of these exchanges at their last summit meeting, and Secretary of State Antony Blinken, during his April trip to China, gave a talk to American  More
The post Mutual Backtracking in US-China Student Exchanges appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mel Gurtov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Australian study on IndieWeb, decentralised social media]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7568</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-study-indieweb-decentralised-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Pang is studying Design in Visual Communications at the University of Technology, Sydney, in Australia. As part of the degree course, she’s doing an assignment looking at IndieWeb, and decentralised social media, such as Mastodon. She’s interested in hearing the views of people on the subject, and if you’re interested in offering your thoughts, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share links on your personal website like it was a socials channel]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7564</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/share-links-personal-website-like-socials-channel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthias Ott, writing at Own Your Web: Today, social media sites have made it seductively convenient to quickly post links that will immediately be rewarded with views, likes, and reposts. As a result, many of us seem to instinctively drop most of the interesting links we find right into the timelines of the many — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/12/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271420</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-12-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T10:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Living in Netanyahu’s America” – In More Ways Than One]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271385</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/living-in-netanyahus-america-in-more-ways-than-one.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T10:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The economic components that have served as the dehumanizing foundation to Israel’s current “plausible” genocide share many similarities with poor Americans and migrant laborers who are treated as disposable in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Their First Baby Came With Medical Debt. These Illinois Parents Won’t Have Another.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271430</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/their-first-baby-came-with-medical-debt-these-illinois-parents-wont-have-another.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T08:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For millions of new parents, medical debt is now as much a hallmark of having children as long nights and dirty diapers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Originalism For Realists: Two Obvious Thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52684</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/originalism-for-realists-two-obvious-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T07:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like I haven’t posted for a couple years. Probably time to fix that! This one kicks off from a tweet I fired off, off-handedly, that led somewhere useful. “If you were wanting a paradigm case-in-point to illustrate the plausibility of legal realism, the history of legal originalism would be hard to improve on.” A […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Abandoned restaurant complex near Mèze, France]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52680</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/sunday-photoblogging-abandoned-restaurant-complex-near-meze-france/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T06:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, How Violent: Hollywood, USC, and the Sickness of Denial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322102</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/12/oh-how-violent-hollywood-usc-and-the-sickness-of-denial/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T06:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USC Pro-Palestine encampment, YouTube screengrab.
The encampments have gone. Tall metal riot fences ring USC. Underpaid security hovers nervously at metal detectors. They paw through your bag when you enter, past the receipts, gum, phone, AirPods, and the overdue library book you never even opened. They’re searching for something. A tent? A Palestinian flag? A keffiyeh? A signed declaration of your commitment against genocide? What they are searching for is unclear, and it’s apparent they themselves don’t even know. The result is not the point; the display is. Like most college campuses, USC is invested in the performative, the circus act in all its summer and acrobatics and glory, something to distract us, for the moment, from the mundanity of reality. The mundanity that college campuses are really just another business: meaningless, archaic, and invested only in its commodification and profit.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Oh, How Violent: Hollywood, USC, and the Sickness of Denial appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ruth Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Small Islands, Deadly Stakes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322142</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/12/small-islands-deadly-stakes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T05:10:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China has considerable appeal in the Pacific as it offers market and donation benefits that are unencumbered by the regulatory millstones of Western countries, which are also offering deals like Australia’s “Step Up” initiative and development aid, and the US “Pacific Partnership Strategy” on diplomatic engagement and security. These projects have bigger geopolitical agendas than aid projects and are mainly concerned with countering China and undermining Pacific Island autonomy by setting up a donor-recipient dynamic.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Small Islands, Deadly Stakes appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julie Wark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the dust bowl]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/dust-bowl/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/dust-bowl/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T22:34:34.535Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grandpa picks up my spiral notebook filled with loopy scribbles, and I don’t stop him because I know he can’t read what I write anyway. He compliments my handwriting, which makes me feel a pang of guilt. Am I being ungrateful, spoiled when I write about my experience like this?
There is not a whole lot to do here. With my uncle gone there’s no one to take us out; while healthy, my grandparents can’t walk for very long and neither can my mom. My brother and I are useless on our own. We don’t have a data plan, can’t pay for anything because we don’t have WeChat pay set up (I think you need a Chinese bank account), and can’t even download an offline map to help us get around. If we do go out on our own we’ll have to retrace our steps by memory.
The streets are covered with a yellowish dust, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Blinks, Bibi Bites, Blinken Rewrites]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321973</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/11/biden-blinks-bibi-bites-blinken-rewrites/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T12:44:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Friday, at least 110,000 Palestinians had been forced to flee Rafah, which is now under bombardment. Many of them have already been displaced two or three times. But all of them know nowhere is safe in Gaza now. There’s no refuge, no place free of bombs and tank shellings and sniper fire, no tent camp or temporary shelter with a reliable source of water or working toilets or beds or food, no mosque to pray in as death hovers all around.
here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post Biden Blinks, Bibi Bites, Blinken Rewrites appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a long uncomfortable look in the mirror]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/uncomfortable-mirror/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/uncomfortable-mirror/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T12:22:51.397Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the morning vendors sell wares out of cargo bicycles and vans along the main road. There’s lots I recognize: strawberries and radishes caked in dust, cuts of red meat strewn on the road, fish floating upside down in kiddie pools, handmade combs and trinkets hanging from metal racks. Some things make me stop and stare: dogs in rusty wire cages (not for human consumption, I hope); caterpillars, segmented bodies still wriggling, best eaten alive; moonshine in repurposed plastic oil jugs.
If I dwell too long loud honks warn me to keep moving. The market is set up dangerously close to the road; traffic and marketgoers ebb and flow like deadly tides. Mom says my uncle was hit by a car in similar circumstances, which makes me jumpy. I try to give the vehicles weaving around us a wide berth, bu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/11/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271133</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-11-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T10:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our voluminous daily links: super night lights, dementia lucidity? China-Philippines row, Sunak's lame comments, UNGA for Gaza membership, Yemen increases attacks, Kharkiv attack? Biden impeachment noise, Minn AG FOIAs DoJ over Trump cases, IRS as political enforcer, AI bosses? Exxon out of control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Unhinged’ Israeli Ambassador Literally Shreds UN Charter Ahead of Successful Vote  Urging Security Council to Reconsider Palestine Membership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271404</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/unhinged-israeli-ambassador-literally-shreds-un-charter-ahead-of-successful-vote-urging-security-council-to-reconsider-palestine-membership.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T10:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel has yet another childish temper tantrum over the prospect of not getting its way, here over  Palestine membership advancing in the UN.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Energy: The New Geopolitical Battleground]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271402</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/nuclear-energy-the-new-geopolitical-battleground.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T10:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Collective West scrambles to replace Russia as a source of nuclear fuel and services.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read – A STIGLITZ ERROR?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45361</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/11/weekend-read-a-stiglitz-error/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T04:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford You can’t fight a war without understanding your enemy.  That’s an adage as old as war itself.  Which means it’s very old. Joe Stiglitz doesn’t understand his enemy. Now, that’s an odd thing to say bout someone who’s worldview is hardly a secret.  Stiglitz has given it his best shot for decades.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrarian views]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332409/0/themoneyillusion~Contrarian-views/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332409/0/themoneyillusion~Contrarian-views/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. The FT reports that we are edging ever closer to WWIII: European intelligence agencies have warned their governments that Russia is plotting violent acts of sabotage across the continent as it commits to a course of permanent conflict with the west.&#160; Russia has already begun to more actively prepare covert bombings, arson attacks and [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332409/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-08-at-3.05.13-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6825759">Harding, You are so delusional. There is no China-Vietnam ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6825712">Trump had nearly 50,000 people at his rally in New Jersey. Some ...</a> <i>by Ricardo</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6825650">I probably agree with 95% of this interesting post.   Not sure ...</a> <i>by Solon of the East</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6825510">“How about from all occupied Ukrainian territories?”   That ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6825397">“withdraw from the post-2022 occupied territories”   LOL, ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Political and aesthetic preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332199/0/themoneyillusion~Political-and-aesthetic-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332199/0/themoneyillusion~Political-and-aesthetic-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arts are often viewed as being in some sense &#8220;liberal&#8221;. This could mean many different things. Art might make people more liberal. Liberals might be more likely to make art. Liberals might be more likely to appreciate art. I don&#8217;t know enough about music to comment, but I have noticed that liberals are more [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332199/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-25-at-6.48.54-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825760">Carthaginian, Don't make it so complicated. Liberals have ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825698">SS- as both liberals and conservatives get richer they ...</a> <i>by Carthaginian</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825620">Kaleberg , Great comment. My home state is Wisconsin, and the ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825612">The classic East Coast example is Vermont versus New Hampshire. ...</a> <i>by Kaleberg</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825610">Carthaginian, “Everyone likes paintings of mountains and ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The once and future king]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332202/0/themoneyillusion~The-once-and-future-king/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332202/0/themoneyillusion~The-once-and-future-king/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So let me get this straight. The President of the United States encouraged the Chinese to build concentration camps in Xinjiang. The Chinese built concentration camps in Xinjiang. In response, we complain about human rights violations and launch a cold war that could easily turn into a hot war. Increasingly, I feel that America is [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332202/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-04-at-3.01.13-PM-641x1024.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6825558">Harding, Trolling is no longer cool. Get a new hobby.</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824527">Nixon actually did withdraw from South Vietnam though. I expect ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824511">Sara, Let's see, would I believe someone not known to lie, or ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824262">Is this your monthly “I need to defend China post”?   It's ...</a> <i>by Sara</i></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by grafelic in "Most of Europe is glowing pink under the aurora"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40324906</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40324906"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I feel I need to report my experience from Denmark, Jutland.
It started with white broad streaks, which most of all looked like fog, but then perhaps after 10 minutes or so, we saw colors of red, purple and green begin to emerge from the these streaks. Most astoundingly it all seemed to emanate from a fluctuating point in the middle of the sky. If you looked closely at this point  you could see it fall into itself, morphing and shifting continuously.
We went around the house and we could purple streaks at the top and orange to red patches at the bottom of the sky.
Colors observed:
Whitish blue,  
Green,
Purple,  
Red,
and Orange
An absolutely a beautiful experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>grafelic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moral Imperative]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/passion-is-fickle/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/passion-is-fickle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I was 15 I wanted to be a physicist really bad. My idol was Richard Feynman. I was convinced it was my passion. My purpose. I even made a PowerPoint presentation trying to convince my mom to let me be a physicist. She was not impressed. I could only be a doctor or engineer.
Now when I think about it I like physics but I don't feel the same passion I had. I could switch fields and go into physics now. I don't want to. It took a while to realise passion is a hoax. A fickle thing you can't rely upon.
Only last month I saw a lot of posts on Twitter about AI safety. It got me convinced that no one was paying attention to it much. That I was needed to save the world. Like some superhero. It was my purpose. The feeling only lasted a day.
If I made my career choices according to passion it would be a disaster. Hoping from one passion train to the other. Going nowhere. Whatever you do you will have hard days. Tasks which you don't like. Days where it is not fun but a slog. How do you push through when the reason you started on that trajectory is something as 'fickle' as passion?
For the longest time, I had value addition as the answer. Trying to surround myself with the right people and the right environment. With a combination of pride, you get from getting good at something. You get freedom and rewards proportional to the value you give society.
And it still is true. But 'Passion' always wins on the branding. It is one word. Evokes strong emotion. It gets the lizard brain going. Only recently I found a word that can tickle my lizard brain the same way and sits well with my personal experience - 'Moral Imperative'.
Sam Altman put it wonderfully. He believes it is his 'Moral Imperative' to bring forth a techno-utopia. And all his choices come from it. It is a powerful thing to have. Your own 'Moral Imperative'. Something you feel is your moral obligation to do on this earth. It is sturdy and powerful. Something that guides the choices you make.
I am trying to define my moral imperative. I believe you should too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the homecoming pauper]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-homecoming/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-homecoming/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T22:55:44.954Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A gold Volkswagen Jetta with no seatbelts picks us up from the airport. Our driver talks to Mom in thick accent, slurring syllables together in bunches. There are many words I can’t catch, but the lilting rhythm falls comfortably on my ears.
I grip the door tightly as empty fields and abandoned skyscrapers fly by my window at 150 kilometers an hour. The gray sky is so choked with smog I can look right at the sun, and breathing in the air makes me wince.
Fourteen long years have passed since I was last here. As I take in the vast emptiness unfolding around me on the car ride, I think about just how much has changed. The decade and a half away has put an eternity of distance between me and this place Mom calls home. It feels insurmountable now.
Grandpa comes out to greet us as we lurch to a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Region Disaster Recovery with Amazon EKS and Amazon EFS for Stateful workloads]]></title>
        <id>33ff514263343545b1e1a64d247156147200d56e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/multi-region-disaster-recovery-with-amazon-eks-and-amazon-efs-for-stateful-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T19:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Amazon Elastic File System (EFS) is a managed storage service that can be used to provide shared access to data for Kubernetes Pods running across compute nodes in different Availability Zones (AZ) managed by Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). Amazon EFS supports native replication of data across AWS Regions. This feature helps in designing a multi-Region disaster […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dumlu Timuralp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting other people’s madness –On sanism and Baby Reindeer (This entry contains spoilers)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52678</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/10/exploiting-other-peoples-madness-on-sanism-and-baby-reindeer-this-entry-contains-spoilers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This text is not about Baby Reindeer, Netflix’s latest hit. It’s about one of the most perverse dimensions of sanism and anti-madness: the exploitation of madness as an edifying aesthetic resource. It is also about the obsolescence of narratives centered on the uncritical perspective of the traditional agent of the banality of evil, the mediocre […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Macarena Marey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/10/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271370</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-10-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics: (1) New  swing state polling, Hillary Clinton on the ignorance of  youth, Trump will love jail, potential nasal spray, and you'll never guess from whom. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Found the Fiction I Love]]></title>
        <id>https://sreekarscribbles.com/finally-found-the-fiction-i-love/</id>
        <link href="https://sreekarscribbles.com/finally-found-the-fiction-i-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T17:27:14.948Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always been a non-fiction fan. Learning something new, diving deep into it, discussing it, and debating it—that's how I keep the curious-me happy!
However, the curious-me also wanted to explore fiction. And I did try—not once, not twice, but multiple times. Yet, I could never enjoy reading fiction.
But but but....something happened recently! I read a couple of novels—The Sun is Also a Star by Nicola Yoon, and A Man Called Ove by Fredrik Backman—and I enjoyed them!
This got me thinking—what was different this time? Why did these novels click with me?
I pondered over these questions plus all my failed attempts at fiction and I made some interesting observations:
No slow burns for me—I need the plot to keep moving!
Characters are way more interesting to me than settings. I'd rather delve into a character's life than read a bunch of scenic descriptions.
I hate high-end vocab. Simple, easy-to-understand words—that's what I prefer.
Book length doesn't bother me, but I like my chapters short and sweet—ten pages tops.
Plus, brownie points if the story has an element of suspense.
So, these are my current reading preferences, though I'm sure they'll evolve as I read more.
For now, I'm sticking to stories that match my taste, but who knows? Maybe I'll venture out of my comfort zone soon.
Right now, I'm reading Anxious People—another amazing book by Fredrik Backman. It's packed into 74 short chapters, each only a few pages long. I've breezed through about ten chapters and I'm already in love with it! 🫶]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: April 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T17:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In April, we experienced four incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: April 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by markgall in "Jim Simons has died"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40320608</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40320608"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T16:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Will be interesting to see how this affects math research.  He has pumped unthinkable amounts of money into the field.  The only first-class flights I've taken in my life were to get to Simons-funded conferences at super fancy hotels.  (I found these conferences a bit ridiculous, but the luxury treatment did ensure that they could get together a lot of the biggest names in the field in one place.)
Besides the conferences, there is the SCGP at Stony Brook, the Simons Center in Manhattan, whatever MSRI is called now, AMS-Simons travel grants, tons of money for the arXiv, the Magma license deal... and that's just the stuff that I've benefited from personally. I know there's more, Simons Collaboration grants and probably other things I've never heard of. He was very good to us all.
We've always joked that Phds in geometry-adjacent fields have to have one of the highest average incomes of any degree, probably at least $1 million a year.  Simons making $3 billion, the rest of us making 90k apiece.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>markgall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/impact/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:54:38.224Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A running list of things that have had a big impact on me :
Hank and John Green: Nerdfighteria is my internet home.
WaitButWhy: Deep dives into topics from first principles and cool sticky figures. Became very popular. I was one of the early ones reading the blog. Back when Tim tried to do new posts every Tuesday. Good times. Learned a lot. One of my all time favourite blogs.
Brandon Sanderson: My favourite author. Amazing fictional worlds with detailed world building. His writing literally saved me in a dark period of my life.
Staring into the singularity : The link to this was suprisingly hard to find. The orignal one taken down. I read this a long time ago. When I was around 16. Has stuck with me since.
LessWrong: Great site with awesome posts. Was about rationality back in the day. Has evolved a lot over the years. Lot of gems.
Richard Feynman's Lecture On Computation: I keep coming back to this. This man is an absolute legend. Do checkout his lectures on physics as well. His books. Everything actually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Platform of ATTAC CADTM Morocco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Platform-of-ATTAC-CADTM-Morocco</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Platform-of-ATTAC-CADTM-Morocco"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preamble 
 The most significant manifestations of capitalist globalization involve banking crises, public and private debts, the consolidation of the debt system, alongside a myriad of other challenges such as economic, food, environmental, and political crises, migration, wars and terrorism. This globalization is considered as an implementation of liberal policies that aim to universalize market logic to all aspects of human activities at the expense of social gains and needs of the (...)
English

/ 
Illegitimate debt, 
Ecology/Climate, 
CADTM, 
Private debt, 
Commercial agreements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury and PNNL threat data now available for Financial sector customers to secure applications]]></title>
        <id>663cc48e20f20e000a888027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/threat-intelligence-custom-indicator-feeds-treasury-pnnl-partnerships"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare proudly partners with the U.S. Department of the Treasury and PNNL to empower financial institutions to deploy DNS filtering policies through Cloudflare’s Gateway, using threat data from these agencies to protect against malicious links and phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Moraru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by maxrobeyns in "Apple apologizes for iPad 'Crush' ad that 'missed the mark'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40318511</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40318511"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My initial reaction to the ad, upon watching it in the launch event was "huh, that's a fun reference to the Hydraulic Press Channel". The slapstick elements (trumpet noise, squishy balls) made it come across as light-hearted, rather than an ominous display of force by a large company crushing artists' tools.
This idea of 'squashing all these tools down to a thin slab of glass' made sense given their somewhat unusual focus on the thinness of the device. It was a bit of a throwback to the early 2010s smartphone innovation, where the size of the devices was the yardstick by which manufacturers would outdo each other. I would charitably interpret it as an uninspired marketing team trying to spin some version of Jobs' classic "the iPhone is simultaneously an iPod, phone and internet device" - however the party trick is old, and nobody's impressed anymore.
Perhaps the blowback is a sign of a wider weariness that people have accumulated towards big tech companies over the past few years, mixed with a nebulous malaise about 'AI' and what it means for the status quo and people's livelihoods.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>maxrobeyns</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Meaney: &ldquo;The Winning Side&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-winning-side</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-winning-side"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T12:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Điện Biên Phủ, seventy years on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flying back one hour and fourteen years]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-tokyo-to-china/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-tokyo-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T11:46:49.743Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The plane I’m taking to China is appallingly shabby, especially after Tokyo’s sleek futurism. It’s a fitting liminal space for the transition: while I’ll miss Tokyo, I’m looking forward to not being the least put-together person on the streets. Going from understanding none of what I see and hear to about half is another plus, I suppose. (Though Tokyo has a LOT more English than where I’m going.) Still, it’ll be nice to respond to questions in the same language they’re asked without too much thought.
Seeing other tourists in Tokyo made me feel a small rush of relief, kinship. I’m not the only one lost here! Except it took me seeing a few of them to realize that when they see me, they probably don’t think the same. Fashion choices and occasional blank stare aside, I look like just another J…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mindwok in "Apple apologizes for iPad 'Crush' ad that 'missed the mark'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40317673</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40317673"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T11:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not my place to tell anyone how they should feel about anything, but the number of comments here suggesting people had a strong emotional reaction to this does kinda worry me. How do those of you who feel so strongly about this ad get through daily life? If I was feeling so upset about something like this, life would be pretty bad. Genuine question.
EDIT: I appreciate the amount of good-faith discussion on this comment. To be clear, if your reaction to the ad was along the lines of ‘this is distasteful and I don’t like it’, I totally get that. I’m referring to some of the comments I saw that likened it to ‘stress inducing’ or ‘like watching someone’s arm get cut off’ which are much more emotive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mindwok</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by benrutter in "Apple apologizes for iPad 'Crush' ad that 'missed the mark'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40317194</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40317194"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T10:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I watch the trailer, it feels very cringe.
I can absolutely see what they're going for- something like "you're iPad contains the power of all these cultural tools", but visually that connection isn't there. It just looks like "Hooray! Culture has been destroyed, now there is only iPad!"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>benrutter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by brundolf in "Apple apologizes for iPad 'Crush' ad that 'missed the mark'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40316469</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40316469"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T08:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not Japanese and it was upsetting to me
Not because eg one piano got destroyed; surely that happens all the time, even on camera for eg movies and such. But there was something about watching beautiful objects be destroyed, in slow motion, gratuitously, and with an upbeat/sunny tone, that just aesthetically made me squirm in my seat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>brundolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Medicide in Gaza: the Killing of Dr. Adnan al-Bursh]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321852</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/medicide-in-gaza-the-killing-of-dr-adnan-al-bursh/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T06:01:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adnan Al-Bursh was intelligent, humane, and committed. He could speak multiple languages. He saw and could explain the ravages of the occupation and the horrors of the war. He was exactly the kind of person, like the still imprisoned Marwan Barghouti, Israel has always feared might become a leader of the Palestinian people. For that reason, he was also exactly the kind of person Israel has been targeting for elimination under the cover of its bombardment and invasion of Gaza. More
The post Medicide in Gaza: the Killing of Dr. Adnan al-Bursh appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Parallels Between Archaic Entrepots and Modern Offshore Banking Centers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321945</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/the-parallels-between-archaic-entrepots-and-modern-offshore-banking-centers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of the origins of urbanization may provide some insight into the character of modern social problems by highlighting the long historical dynamic at work. It may not be out of place here to point out that anti‑states are well known in the modern world, above all in what the U.S. Federal Reserve Board classifies as eleven offshore banking centers. Five such enclaves are in the Caribbean: Panama, the Netherlands Antilles (Curacao), Bermuda, the Bahamas, and the British West Indies (Cayman Islands). Three enclaves—Hong Kong, Macao, and Singapore—were founded to conduct the China trade. The remaining three are Liberia, Lebanon, and Bahrain at the mouth of the Persian Gulf—the island which Bronze Age Sumerians called Dilmun when they used it to trade with the Indus valley and the Iranian shore. More
The post The Parallels Between Archaic Entrepots and Modern Offshore Banking Centers appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the UAW Could Change the South]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321732</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/how-the-uaw-could-change-the-south/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UAW is on a roll. After winning stupendous contracts at the Big Three automakers this past year, the union then organized Volkswagen in Tennessee April 20. What’s eye-popping about this is that the UAW succeeded not only in the South, but also with a foreign car manufacturer – a twofer. Now as the union zooms in on a May vote by 5000 workers at Mercedes in Alabama, the larger implications of Shawn Fain’s still relatively new union presidency have become clear, namely, a change in workers’ culture in the anti-union, right-to-work South; because if the UAW racks up more wins in the region, that will alter the local political ecosystem. Politicos will find themselves in an environment that includes a growing union presence, something they have sought to extirpate for generations. More
The post How the UAW Could Change the South appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Washington Post’s David Ignatius Remains Clueless About the Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321847</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/washington-posts-david-ignatius-remains-clueless-about-the-middle-east/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s difficult to imagine an Israeli war in the Middle East that allowed any Arab country to claim victory.  The history of the Middle East over the past 75 years has been a history of war, and the Israelis have been the overwhelming victor in each and every one of them.  Israel’s War of Independence in 1948 marked an overwhelming victory for the Israelis; it created the profound antagonisms that have marked Israeli relations with the Arab states over the past 75 years.  The United States and Israel over the years have indulged in a dialogue about a “peace process,” but Arab refugees have known neither “peace” nor “process.” More
The post Washington Post’s David Ignatius Remains Clueless About the Middle East appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Palestinian Groups Create a New Palestinian Political Project?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321737</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/will-palestinian-groups-create-a-new-palestinian-political-project/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s disregard for the negotiations and the level of its violence can be measured based on two political realities. It does not take negotiations with the Palestinians seriously and it feels that it can bomb with impunity. This is so because, firstly, Israel is backed fully by the Global North states (mainly the United States and Europe) and secondly, it does not regard Palestinian political views as vital because it has succeeded in breaking the political unity amongst Palestinians and it has succeeded in politically disorienting the various factions by the arrest of their main leadership. More
The post Will Palestinian Groups Create a New Palestinian Political Project? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vijay Prashad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Surprising Rising Seas “Must Reads”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321848</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/surprising-rising-seas-must-reads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sea levels are surging along the US coastline, exceeding 30-year expectations. Scientists are confused, concerned, searching for answers. In that regard, an excellent new series by The Washington Post d/d April 29th, 2024 “Must Reads” is an eye-opening view into the impact of global warming in real time with real people and real images. For  More
The post Surprising Rising Seas “Must Reads” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Soft Anti-Semitism of Polite Expectations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321871</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/the-soft-anti-semitism-of-polite-expectations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:56:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rules for protests I’ve been struck lately, by the inertness of criticism lodged against student protesters — they might have been written by AI. They all begin with a vague expression of support for Jewish and Islamic students, proceed to condemn anti-Semitism “in all its forms”, endorse free speech, and conclude with a vow to  More
The post The Soft Anti-Semitism of Polite Expectations  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sick, Dystopian System Worth Overthrowing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321947</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/a-sick-dystopian-system-worth-overthrowing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many friends and allies, especially younger ones, have been getting The Lecture from older Democratic Party relatives or friends – the Lesser Evil Lecture. This year the lecture comes not only with the admonition to hold your nose and vote for Joe Biden to get a second term to block the fascist monster Trump but  More
The post A Sick, Dystopian System Worth Overthrowing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Street</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Road to Hell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321833</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/the-road-to-hell/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's becoming clearer every day that our governments and leaders have no intention to promote a livable world or even one with a destination of eventual equitability. No, the goal is clearly to promote the interests of the few and to use the vast swath of humanity in much the way a parasite would utilize its host. This has likely always been the case with modern governments, but even now, a few nations seem to realize that there has to be some form of quid pro quo between their leaders and the masses. Sadly, however, in the US and Great Britain in particular, there has been a callous disregard for even the most basic well-being of their populations. The question is, how did we get to such a place? More
The post The Road to Hell appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unfurling Love from the Window]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321909</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/unfurling-love-from-the-window/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 30, when Columbia University student protesters took over Hamilton Hall, they renamed it “Hind’s Hall,” dropping a large banner out the windows above the building’s entrance. This was a hall famously occupied by students in the 1968 protests against the Vietnam War and against Jim Crow racism in the United States. The students are  More
The post Unfurling Love from the Window appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s Battle Against Free Speech: The Shuttering of Al Jazeera]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321902</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/israels-battle-against-free-speech-the-shuttering-of-al-jazeera/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Politics,” as the harsh, albeit successful German Chancellor Otto von Bismarck claimed, “is the art of the possible, the attainable – the art of the next best.”  To that should be added the stark awareness of being prudent, gingerly wise, appropriately cautious.  Mind how you go in avoiding any foolishness on the way. Going after the motley  More
The post Israel’s Battle Against Free Speech: The Shuttering of Al Jazeera appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Silent Spring: Cornell’s Slope Day, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322003</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/non-silent-spring-cornells-slope-day-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cornell University in central New York State commands a spectacular position above the city of Ithaca with Lake Cayuga stretching out of sight to the north. The Cornell alma mater casts higher education in literal terms, first, “Far above Cayuga’s waters”; then, in the second stanza, “Far above …the bustling town.” With altitude comes power.  More
The post Non-Silent Spring: Cornell’s Slope Day, 2024 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Civilizational Unity, Not Clash: How Gaza Challenged Samuel Huntington’s Fantasies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321949</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/civilizational-unity-not-clash-how-gaza-challenged-samuel-huntingtons-fantasies/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity is fluid, because concepts such as culture, history and collective self-perceptions are never fixed. They are in a constant state of flux and revision. For hundreds of years, the map of the Roman Empire seemed more Mediterranean and, ultimately, Middle Eastern than European – per the geographic, or even geopolitical demarcation of today’s Europe.  More
The post Civilizational Unity, Not Clash: How Gaza Challenged Samuel Huntington’s Fantasies appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plastic Pollution is a Crime Against People and the Planet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322009</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/plastic-pollution-is-a-crime-against-people-and-the-planet/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Louisiana’s “River Parishes,” located along the Mississippi River between New Orleans and Baton Rouge, shoulder some of the worst industry impacts in the United States. As a result, this region has acquired a grim reputation as “Cancer Alley.” Stretching across 85 miles of rural land along both banks of the Mississippi River are around 200 industrial  More
The post Plastic Pollution is a Crime Against People and the Planet appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erica Cirino</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of a Wolf Torturer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321907</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/anatomy-of-a-wolf-torturer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sadism is the word that psychoanalysts use to describe the specific malformation of manhood in the recent merciless and prideful torture and killing of a gray wolf. The young female was rendered helpless by her killer when he cravenly duct-taped her mouth shut, after he’d run over her with a snowmobile. The gleeful smile on  More
The post Anatomy of a Wolf Torturer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Scalia III</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestinian Resistance: Upsetting the U.S.-Israel Apple Cart]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=321898</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/10/palestinian-resistance-upsetting-the-u-s-israel-apple-cart/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T05:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students on campuses across the United States have “upset the U.S.-Israel military apartheid applecart” — a plan long in the making whose aim has been Israeli control over all of historic Palestine.  Israel’s plan to claim every inch of it is stated unequivocally in the Likud Party Platform of 1977.  It reads, “between the Sea and the Jordan  More
The post Palestinian Resistance: Upsetting the U.S.-Israel Apple Cart appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by edkennedy in "Apple apologizes for iPad 'Crush' ad that 'missed the mark'"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40314035</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40314035"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T23:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Missing from this extremely short and underreported article is how badly this played out in Japanese market. The culture they have states that musical instruments, creative tools have some energy and imbued sense of spirit to them. So destroying these elements of culture is really really blunt and gauche to them. The majority of the push back came from Japanese people, and then artists empathizing with their sentiment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edkennedy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything good and bad, but mostly very bad, about smoking]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7558</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/everything-good-bad-mostly-very-bad-about-smoking/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T21:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Screen cap of Kurzgesagt’s Smoking is Awesome YouTube video. This month Kurzgesagt takes on smoking. If you’re a non-smoker, this may help you understand why people like to have a puff: Smoking helps you focus at work and is an excuse to take regular breaks, which is good for you mentally. It’s a tool […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[getting a good view of things]]></title>
        <id>https://aco.bearblog.dev/getting-a-good-view-of-things/</id>
        <link href="https://aco.bearblog.dev/getting-a-good-view-of-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T20:05:51.346Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[bears and cats seem to be the only animals other than humans that are able to appreciate a good view. i saw video the other day of a bear digging himself a hole and sitting in it, onlooking a lake somewhere in the banff region. the video reminds me of the times i'd go to montenegro with my family, id dig pockets into the sand to rest my knees and stomach before laying a towel down and going to sleep. similarly, i often find my cats sitting on their cat towers outlooking the view of the lake from my balcony. genuinely good living. i always get thrown back at idea of humans getting considering as the solely "intelligent" animals. most of us can't sit for a few moments and enjoy a good view, meanwhile cat and bears do it all the time. in what world does that make sense?

anyways, i've become a bit more lax with blogging and such. it's been a bit of a secondary function these past few months. i get the itch at times to do small things, like write a post, or read, or research or code something. at other times, i get even worse itchings to do more drastic things, move away, quit my job, or delete every trace of myself on the internet and live like a hermit. i get annoyed quite honestly, theres always something to do or something i would like to do, and all these options cause me to paralyze myself. i find myself walking a lot these days. spending most days out of the house, which helps. a little coffee and a walk in nature helps me soothe myself. i feel like the bear in the video. a bit of a hopelessly lost almost-22 year old bear. i think time will probably tell how this all goes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by samfriedman in "Leaked deck reveals how OpenAI is pitching publisher partnerships"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40311333</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40311333"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T18:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>Additionally, members of the program receive priority placement and “richer brand expression” in chat conversations, and their content benefits from more prominent link treatments. Finally, through PPP, OpenAI also offers licensed financial terms to publishers.
This is what a lot of people pushing for open models fear - responses of commercial models will be biased based on marketing spend.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>samfriedman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gateway API v1.1: Service mesh, GRPCRoute, and a whole lot more]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/09/gateway-api-v1-1/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/09/gateway-api-v1-1/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following the GA release of Gateway API last October, Kubernetes
SIG Network is pleased to announce the v1.1 release of
Gateway API. In this release, several features are graduating to
Standard Channel (GA), notably including support for service mesh and
GRPCRoute. We're also introducing some new experimental features, including
session persistence and client certificate verification.
What's new
Graduation to Standard
This release includes the graduation to Standard of four eagerly awaited features.
This means they are no longer experimental concepts; inclusion in the Standard
release channel denotes a high level of confidence in the API surface and
provides guarantees of backward compatibility. Of course, as with any other
Kubernetes API, Standard Channel features can continue to evolve w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Post‑Pandemic Shift in Retirement Expectations in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29447</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/the-post-pandemic-shift-in-retirement-expectations-in-the-u-s/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most striking features of the labor market recovery following the pandemic recession has been the surge in quits from 2021 to mid-2023. This surge, often referred to as the Great Resignation, or the Great Reshuffle, was uncommonly large for an economic expansion. In this post, we call attention to a related labor market change that has not been previously highlighted—a persistent change in retirement expectations, with workers reporting much lower expectations of working full-time beyond ages 62 and 67. This decline is particularly notable for female workers and lower-income workers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Felix Aidala, Gizem Kosar, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Economics — a dismal and harmful science]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45356</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/09/economics-a-dismal-and-harmful-science/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T11:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll It’s hard not to agree with DeMartino’s critique of mainstream economics — an unethical, irresponsible, and harmful kind of science where models and procedures become ends in themselves, without consideration of their lack of explanatory value as regards real-world phenomena. Many mainstream economists working in the field of economic theory think that […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Hardt <em>&amp;</em> Sandro Mezzadra: &ldquo;A Global War Regime&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-global-war-regime</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-global-war-regime"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T09:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Theorizing the new world system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by motbus3 in "The Time I Lied to the CTO and Saved the Day"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40305975</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40305975"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T07:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are a "delivery driven" person who cancels holidays to keep working, I would say to you, from own experience: stop being stupid.
I know, that, specially when you get recognised for the hard work it is hard, but you will regret every minute.
If you work for a company that counts on your holidays and vacation to sell their products, you are helping to create the problematic world with have today.
If many do that, more will need to do. If none do it, and act like it is an absurd to request it (and it is) nobody is forced to do it and the company is forced to do real estimates even if that hurts your fav CEO pocket]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>motbus3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new generative engine and three voices are now generally available on Amazon Polly]]></title>
        <id>983b96f69eee4d261c9d226a1ddd8568914827b3</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/a-new-generative-engine-and-three-voices-are-now-generally-available-on-amazon-polly/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T03:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Amazon Polly, you can select various voice options, including neural, long-form, and generative voices, which deliver ground-breaking improvements in speech quality and produce human-like, highly expressive, and emotionally adept voices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by neilv in "The Time I Lied to the CTO and Saved the Day"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40304947</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40304947"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T03:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any impressionable kids reading... this story playing out like it did is highly company-dependent, as well as luck-dependent.
In a healthy company/organization:
* That outsourcing implementation approach probably wouldn't have happened, because an experienced person could've guessed how that would turn out, before it was started (it's such a cliche).
* Earlier on, people would tell the CTO it wasn't working out, instead of lying and saying the opposite.
* Whenever they needed to do something smarter/creative to rescue the project, they could work with the CTO on that, and maybe even with the customer.
* There wouldn't be marathon whip-cracking over the holidays, especially not after the team was already burning out.
* A manager/lead would go to bat for the success of the project and the health of the team, and insist upwards that the team needed a break over the holidays, if that needed to be clarified.
On that last point, in a "half-healthy" organization, a manager might intentionally be very vague, and omit information.  That happens, and might or might not be a good idea, depending.
But the way this story is told, it sounds like the manager/lead outright lied repeatedly up the chain of command, which is generally considered very-bad, in both healthy and unhealthy companies.
I'll add that these things are vastly easier to armchair-quarterback.  Certainly we're all going to make mistakes, especially when put in difficult positions, and/or when overextended/fatigued.  But it helps to look at scenarios, to try to learn from them, and to think from a distance how they might've been handled better, so you're armed with that "experience", the next time you're tossed into a rough situation that has some similarities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>neilv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I mean when I say that machine learning in Elixir is production-ready]]></title>
        <id>https://cigrainger.com/elixirconf-eu-2024-keynote/</id>
        <link href="https://cigrainger.com/elixirconf-eu-2024-keynote/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My ElixirConf EU 2024 keynote "Ship it! A roadmap for putting Nx into production" is up on youtube. I'm hoping it will help folks gain the confidence to go out and... ship it!
I often say 'machine learning in Elixir is ready for production'. On further reflection, I realised that this statement dramatically undersells the true potential and capabilities of machine learning within the Elixir ecosystem. (I already posted these reflections on Twitter).
When I say "production-ready," it's not just about the ability to deploy machine learning models in a live environment. In the context of Elixir, being production-ready means deep integration with the weird and wonderful thing called the BEAM (Bogdan/Björn's Erlang Abstract Machine). It means seamless compatibility with OTP (Open Telecom Platfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamline production grade clusters with Amazon AFT and Terraform EKS Blueprints]]></title>
        <id>8d6c93c3f70c38054eee1a222aed4f64f3cda8e2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/streamline-production-grade-clusters-with-amazon-aft-and-terraform-eks-blueprints/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T21:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS users need to continuously enhance their infrastructure and security processes. This typically involves a two-phase approach: discovery and design, followed by implementation. In the discovery phase, an assessment of the current infrastructure is conducted, leading to the creation of architecture documents and patterns for the subsequent implementation phase. This process delves into Account Structure, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rodrigo Bersa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can blogrolls build communities online? I think so]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7549</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/can-blogrolls-build-communities-online/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T21:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A screen cap of disassociated’s links page, circa November 1999. Them were dark days… Daniel Prindii asks, could blogrolls form the basis of community building online? Well, once upon a time, when they were known as links pages, that’s exactly what they did. But with the development of AI tools, spam, and SEO-optimized articles the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an organizational multi-Region failover strategy]]></title>
        <id>38c015e2a3e74e487516a543da81131e5248b700</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/creating-an-organizational-multi-region-failover-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T18:50:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Regions provide fault isolation boundaries that prevent correlated failure and contain the impact from AWS service impairments to a single Region when they occur. You can use these fault boundaries to build multi-Region applications that consist of independent, fault-isolated replicas in each Region that limit shared fate scenarios. This allows you to build multi-Region […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Haken</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerate your Software Development Lifecycle with Amazon Q]]></title>
        <id>23c24a4aedea0c5ed6532d065b6100beefb3c7be</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/accelerate-your-software-development-lifecycle-with-amazon-q/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T18:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development teams are constantly looking for ways to accelerate their software development lifecycle (SDLC) to release quality software faster. Amazon Q, a generative AI–powered assistant, can help software development teams work more efficiently throughout the SDLC—from research to maintenance. Software development teams spend significant time on undifferentiated tasks while analyzing requirements, building, testing, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chetan Makvana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating contradictions in life]]></title>
        <id>https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/navigating-contradictions-in-life/</id>
        <link href="https://yuricunha.bearblog.dev/navigating-contradictions-in-life/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T18:37:09.439Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the jumble of thoughts and emotions that make up my existence, I find myself entangled in a web of contradictions. It's not poetic; it's real, raw, and sometimes messy. Here's the truth about living as a paradox:
I'm drawn to happiness, sure, but I can't shake off the weight of sad thoughts that often cloud my mind. It's like there's a constant tug-of-war between the two, and I'm stuck in the middle.
I'm not always my biggest fan. I see my flaws and shortcomings more clearly than anyone else. But amidst all that self-doubt, there's a begrudging respect for the person I've become, scars and all.
When I say "I don't care," it's not because I'm indifferent. Deep down, I care too much. It's just easier to put up walls than to deal with the vulnerability that comes with caring.
Attention is a tricky thing. I crave it, no doubt, but when it comes my way, I often find myself pushing it away. It's like I'm afraid of what it might reveal about me, or maybe I'm just not used to being seen.
I've been both a healer and a wounded soul in relationships. I've tried to fix others, thinking it would fix me too, only to end up with my own heart broken in the process.
Listening comes naturally to me, but sharing doesn't. I'm great at keeping other people's secrets, but when it comes to my own thoughts and feelings, I'd rather keep them locked away.
So yeah, I'm a walking contradiction. It's messy, it's confusing, but it's real. And maybe that's okay. Maybe embracing the messiness of life's contradictions is the most honest thing we can do.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Women Lead Data Engineering at Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=16601</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/how-women-lead-data-engineering-at-slack/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Data Engineering team is responsible for Slack’s data lake, analytics dashboards, and other data services. The team’s mission is to empower users to leverage data to make decisions quickly, accurately, and easily. Slack’s data lake grew in size from sub-petabyte to over 100 petabytes in recent years and it now spans millions of tables. […]
The post How Women Lead Data Engineering at Slack appeared first on Slack Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lakshmi Mohan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forrest Hylton: &ldquo;Ghosts of &#8217;68&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghosts-of-68</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/ghosts-of-68"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Campus protests in context.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dekhn in "AlphaFold 3 predicts the structure and interactions of life's molecules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40300184</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40300184"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:46:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're a scientist who works in protein folding (or one of those other areas) and strongly believe that science's goal is to produce falsifiable hypotheses, these new approaches will be extremely depressing, especially if you aren't proficient enough with ML to reproduce this work in your own hands.
If you're a scientist who accepts that probabilist models beat interpretable ones (articulated well here: https://norvig.com/chomsky.html), then you'll be quite happy because this is yet another validation of the value of statistical approaches in moving our ability to predict the universe forward.
If you're the sort of person who believes that human brains are capable of understanding the "why" of how things work in all its true detail, you'll find this an interesting challenge- can we actually interpret these models, or are human brains too feeble to understand complex systems without sophisticated models?
If you're the sort of person who likes simple models with as few parameters as possible, you're probably excited because developing more comprehensible or interpretable models that have equivalent predictive ability is a very attractive research subject.
(FWIW, I'm in the camp of "we should simultaneously seek simpler, more interpretable models, while also seeking to improve native human intelligence using computational augmentation")]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dekhn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by moconnor in "AlphaFold 3 predicts the structure and interactions of life's molecules"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40299616</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40299616"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stepping back, the high-order bit here is an ML method is beating physically-based methods for accurately predicting the world.
What happens when the best methods for computational fluid dynamics, molecular dynamics, nuclear physics are all uninterpretable ML models? Does this decouple progress from our current understanding of the scientific process - moving to better and better models of the world without human-interpretable theories and mathematical models / explanations? Is that even iteratively sustainable in the way that scientific progress has proven to be?
Interesting times ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>moconnor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Are They Now? A Checkup on Homeowners Who Experienced Foreclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29469</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/how-are-they-now-a-checkup-on-homeowners-who-experienced-foreclosure/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The end of the Great Recession marked the beginning of the longest economic expansion in U.S. history. The Great Recession, with its dramatic housing bust, led to a wave of home foreclosures as overleveraged borrowers found themselves unable to meet their payment obligations. In early 2009, the New York Fed’s Research Group launched the Consumer Credit Panel (CCP), a foundational data set of the Center for Microeconomic Data, to monitor the financial health of Americans as the economy recovered. The CCP, which is based on anonymized credit report data from Equifax, gives us an opportunity to track individuals during the period leading to the foreclosure, observe when a flag is added to their credit report and then—years later—removed. Here, we examine the longer-term impact of a foreclosure on borrowers’ credit scores and borrowing experiences: do they return to borrowing, or shy away from credit use and homeownership after their earlier bad experience?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Belicia Rodriguez, Joelle Scally, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Real-world economists take note!]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45350</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/08/real-world-economists-take-note/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:28:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Planet is headed for at least 2.5C of heating with disastrous results for humanity, poll of hundreds of scientists finds]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sumimasening my way around]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/tokyo-first-impression/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/tokyo-first-impression/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T11:27:29.465Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I thought I’d take it easy this trip to Tokyo since I didn’t plan at all. Two days in, I’ve logged 22 miles, 56,000 steps on concrete in barefoot shoes. It’s okay, though—my overworked feet will have time to recover in China. The sheer amount of walking I’ve done is testament both to how pedestrian friendly Tokyo is and to the way I still try to minmax my travels at the expense of my physical and mental health. Old habits die hard.
I wrote a while back about how one of my favorite things about traveling is getting to microdose on cluelessness. These past few days in Japan have taught me that there is such thing as too much of a good thing. The last time I was in a place where I didn’t speak the local language was seven years ago (France and Italy), and there I could at least read, if not u…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why has global biodiversity governance failed so badly?]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52672</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/08/why-has-global-biodiversity-governance-failed-so-badly/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T06:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Later this month it will be World Biodiversity Day, and we will again celebrate the remarkable contributions that biodiversity makes to the resilience and productivity of the earth’s ecosystems. But it will also be a fitting time to face the continued failure of our institutions to grasp the scale of biodiversity loss. Or, if not […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Armstrong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF: the creditors' bailiffs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-and-the-IMF-the-creditors-bailiffs</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-World-Bank-and-the-IMF-the-creditors-bailiffs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To make the longest ever baguette bakers must go the extra mile]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7532</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/make-longest-baguette-go-extra-mile/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meanwhile, back in the real world… chefs in France recently made the world’s longest ever baguette, which clocks in at a… morsel over one-hundred and forty metres in length. (My question: did they create the world’s largest oven to cook up this oversize stick of bread?) I thought a one-hundred and forty metre long baguette […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build RAG and agent-based generative AI applications with new Amazon Titan Text Premier model, available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>0a7eb872edc2fce55e074bed2c98c3983d999e68</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-rag-and-agent-based-generative-ai-applications-with-new-amazon-titan-text-premier-model-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Titan Text Premier is the latest large language model (LLM) in the Amazon Titan family of models, further increasing your model choice within Amazon Bedrock.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tylerFowler in "Can turning office towers into apartments save downtowns?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40290252</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40290252"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:14:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's kind of odd to me (as someone who used to live there at its latest boom time) that nobody talks about Kansas City when it comes to this topic.
From the ~70's until the early 2010's Kansas City's downtown was in a similar "doom loop" of crime, undevelopment, decaying historic buildings, etc... In that city 75% of the metro lives in suburbs, drives in to downtown for work and promptly leaves. Until about 2012 or so. Urban redevelopment kicked in, adding (free!) transit, boosting retail, arts district events, a new stadium, and crucially - *massive office to housing conversion projects*.
There are tons of success stories like the historic Fidelity Tower at 909 Walnut (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/909_Walnut), a huge 35-story tower that sat vacant (creepy) for the better part of a decade and is now home to 159 units. Ditto with the Power & Light Building (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kansas_City_Power_and_Light_Bu...) (36 stories) - largely vacant for the better part of 20 years and now home to nearly 300 units. I could go on, every block has similar projects of 100+ year old buildings of nontrivial sizes that are now super unique apartments. I myself lived in the 30-story Commerce Tower (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commerce_Tower) for a while and it was incredibly cheap to do so (~$1100/month for 750sqft 1 bed on the 14th floor), I had a 10 minute commute by foot to my office, it was awesome. Even the more squat, broad midsize banking buildings have had major success with residential conversions.
These kinds of conversions have been proven out when there is willpower to do so at the city level - people will move in and prices typically get competitive fast if done at scale. I've lived in SF for 4 years now and I'm convinced its a policy problem not an economic problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tylerFowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by andsoitis in "Apple introduces M4 chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40290039</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40290039"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T18:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> In case it is not abundantly clear by now: Apple's AI strategy is to put inference (and longer term even learning) on edge devices. This is completely coherent with their privacy-first strategy (which would be at odds with sending data up to the cloud for processing).
Their primary business goal is to sell hardware. Yes, they’ve diversified into services and being a shopping mall for all, but it is about selling luxury hardware.
The promise of privacy is one way in which they position themselves, but I would not bet the bank on that being true forever.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>andsoitis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rsp1984 in "Apple introduces M4 chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289185</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289185"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Together with next-generation ML accelerators in the CPU, the high-performance GPU, and higher-bandwidth unified memory, the Neural Engine makes M4 an outrageously powerful chip for AI.
In case it is not abundantly clear by now: Apple's AI strategy is to put inference (and longer term even learning) on edge devices. This is completely coherent with their privacy-first strategy (which would be at odds with sending data up to the cloud for processing).
Processing data at the edge also makes for the best possible user experience because of the complete independence of network connectivity and hence minimal latency.
If (and that's a big if) they keep their APIs open to run any kind of AI workload on their chips it's a strategy that I personally really really welcome as I don't want the AI future to be centralised in the hands of a few powerful cloud providers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rsp1984</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Kon-Peki in "Can turning office towers into apartments save downtowns?"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289064</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289064"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:47:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Conventional wisdom is that only certain office buildings can be converted to housing.
If you can buy the building cheap enough, conventional wisdom can be thrown out the window.
I once toured a building that had been converted from an old warehouse to residential.  Huge floorplate.  They had built the condo units around the edges, created a hallway, and then the inside was divided up into "storage" spaces.  Each condo owned the space directly across the hallway.  They were very large, and people had transformed them into offices, arcades, workshops, playrooms, theaters, etc.  You could do just about anything you wanted with the space, and because it wasn't "living space" you didn't have to worry so much about noise and the property taxes were lower than they otherwise would have been.
You can't sell it for a price that includes that space as "living space" either.  Which goes back to the point - if you can buy the building cheap enough, you can make anything work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kon-Peki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gwbas1c in "Book people think they know why 9-year-olds stop reading for fun"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289049</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40289049"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T17:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Take a closer look at how much homework children have, and how much assigned, mandatory reading children have.
I went to a private "college prep" high school, and the amount of assigned, mandatory reading was insane. I spent so much time reading assigned novels that I just didn't have time to read for pleasure. (And why read for pleasure if I already spent 30+ minutes reading a boring / awful novel as part of my homework?)
Once I was out of college, I rediscovered reading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gwbas1c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[155. Happy 1st Bear birthday to me]]></title>
        <id>https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/happy-1st-bear-birthday-to-me/</id>
        <link href="https://exponixio.bearblog.dev/happy-1st-bear-birthday-to-me/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:39:20.338Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks my first completed year of writing on Bear. I have started and stopped personal blogs in the past, but I decided that I wanted to stick to one and continue with it throughout. Even though I've gotten quite busy these past few months, I feel like I've stuck it out and have been updating and dropping lore left and right. I set a goal for myself and for this blog that I truly wanted to be dedicated and wanted to make sure that I kept on task and archive my life in little bits and pieces.
When I first created this blog, I challenged myself to write every day for 40 days. I'm not into religion anymore, but one of the most profound stories I heard when I was a kid was the Temptation of Christ in the desert. Honestly, if a person had a spiritual exploration in the desert for 40 days, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by comebhack in "Road resurfacing during the daytime without stopping traffic [video]"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40287570</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40287570"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:12:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is some more detail on the bridge itself in this video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8tpv6n1ykfA
The bridge is assembled over 2 nights at a motorway exit (so traffic can bypass it by driving off and immediately back on to the road). During night 1 the two end ramps are assembled and attached together to make a short bridge. During night 2 the ramps are driven apart, the central section is built to reach the full length and the entire structure is driven to the final location.
The entire length is 236 meters long providing a working length of 100 meters underneath. The assembled bridge can flex slightly at the joins between sections, and has a turning radius of 2 kilometers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>comebhack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build generative AI applications with Amazon Bedrock Studio (preview)]]></title>
        <id>b9d853eedbab2fe828eb6466784995e2bfaf55ec</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/build-generative-ai-applications-with-amazon-bedrock-studio-preview/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T16:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Bedrock Studio accelerates the development of generative AI applications by providing a rapid prototyping environment with key Amazon Bedrock features, including Knowledge Bases, Agents, and Guardrails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antje Barth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Many Places Still Have Not Recovered from the Pandemic Recession]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29454</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/many-places-still-have-not-recovered-from-the-pandemic-recession/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than four years have passed since the onset of the pandemic, which resulted in one of the sharpest and deepest economic downturns in U.S. history. While the nation as a whole has recovered the jobs that were lost during the pandemic recession, many places have not. Indeed, job shortfalls remain in more than a quarter of the country’s metro areas, including many in the New York-Northern New Jersey region. In fact, while employment is well above pre-pandemic levels in Northern New Jersey, jobs have only recently recovered in and around New York City, and most of upstate New York—like much of the Rust Belt—still has not fully recovered and has some of the largest job shortfalls in the country.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaison R. Abel, Richard Deitz, Jonathan Hastings, and Joelle Scally</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by izacus in "Apple introduces M4 chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286397</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286397"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple usually massively exaggerates their tech spec comparison - is it REALLY half the power use of all times (so we'll get double the battery life) or is it half the power use in some scenarios (so we'll get like... 15% more battery life total) ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>izacus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by EduardoBautista in "Apple introduces M4 chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286128</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286128"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 256gb and 512gb models have 8gb of ram. The 1tb and 2tb models have 16gb. Not a fan of tying ram to storage.
https://www.apple.com/ipad-pro/specs/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EduardoBautista</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by praseodym in "Apple introduces M4 chip"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286118</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286118"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["With these improvements to the CPU and GPU, M4 maintains Apple silicon’s industry-leading performance per watt. M4 can deliver the same performance as M2 using just half the power. And compared with the latest PC chip in a thin and light laptop, M4 can deliver the same performance using just a fourth of the power."
That's an incredible improvement in just a few years. I wonder how much of that is Apple engineering and how much is TSMC improving their 3nm process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>praseodym</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dahart in "Cold brew coffee in 3 minutes using acoustic cavitation"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286074</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40286074"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:40:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I discovered that many coffee shops, maybe half in my sampling of a couple dozen in different cities, are selling cold coffee (brewed hot, then refrigerated) under the name cold brew, and even the ones that actually cold-brew them seem to be under the impression that it needs to be served cold. I was laughed at in one hipster joint for asking for a steamed or warmed cold-brew, and another one initially refused my request to warm it up saying that would make the coffee extremely sour. (It didn’t) Oh, and at least one other, maybe two, said they couldn’t warm cold brew (in view of both a steamer and microwave) or would have to charge extra (while someone’s cheaper latte was being steamed).
Reading the paper, it’s not clear whether their cold brew has lower acidity (higher pH) than the same coffee hot brewed. It does say that the sonic-brew has the same pH as the normal long-steep cold brew. I’m also curious if this cavitation/sonication brewing process is basically agitating the coffee, or doing something different, and how different it is from manually agitating a cold brew compared to letting it sit still for hours.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dahart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Cloudflare for Unified Risk Posture]]></title>
        <id>66323e697c0f59000a6a9bba</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/unified-risk-posture"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare for Unified Risk Posture, a new suite of cybersecurity risk management capabilities built on our global network, can help enterprises with automated and dynamic risk posture enforcement across their expanding attack surface]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Chang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Fortran on Cloudflare Workers]]></title>
        <id>66200f7327e210000ab29b11</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/using-fortran-on-cloudflare-workers"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Work on LLVM has enabled Fortran to compile to WebAssembly. So, today, we’re writing about running Fortran code on Cloudflare Workers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Graham-Cumming</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Marco D'Eramo: &ldquo;Problem Trump&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/problem-trump</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/problem-trump"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An influencer avant la lettre.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by metadat in "Vets fret as private equity snaps up clinics, pet care companies"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40281352</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=40281352"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T01:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Private equity is akin to toxic poison for everyone who isn't one of the (very few) general partners who bask in obscene amounts of scrooge-mcduck money.  Think of making a cool $30 million+ a quarter, per partner -- thanks real estate (and apparently, emergency medical services) "investments"!  This is a direct funnel to syphon money from the workers to the ruling class.  That's even more cash than the top brass at FAAGs make.
How can this phenomenon be reigned in and sorted in the medium to long-term?
It's a loss for everyone (99.9999%) except the miniscule quantity of winners (0.0001%, yes, that's 1 in 1,000,000 - there aren't that many large-scale P/E firms).  Housing owned by P/E couldn't be more soul sucking.  Scratch that, this applies to every case I'm aware of where P/E firms own a thing.
Anecdote: Last month my dear old dog was suddenly very ill and I spent $12k on emergency surgery to save his sweet life.  No regrets, I'm grateful he was fixable.  But in the waiting room I did the conservative math for what the SAGE Emergency Veterinary Hospital in Redwood City, CA makes in a year (before the comparatively small overhead, tax-deductible expenses) and they are pulling in at least $30 million in this single location.  That's.. a lot, for many 20 total staff.  Also they charged me $500 for each follow-up visit, which is way more than my real life surgeon charged me earlier this year! (Even including insurance, he didn't charge much for the follow-ups to make sure I survived.)  Damn.
For the dog lovers out there: Doggo is alive and well, can maybe last another year or two we hope.
Btw, who owns SAGE?  NVA, a P/E firm.
https://todaysveterinarybusiness.com/sage-veterinary-centers...
https://www.crunchbase.com/organization/national-veterinary-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>metadat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>