<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-05-16T18:28:04.215Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-05-16T18:28:04.215Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271706</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T18:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, pandemics ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Stable Diffusion ComfyUI on AWS elastically and efficiently]]></title>
        <id>dcd98043e309fb462fb16c1c99293fceecad41fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/deploy-stable-diffusion-comfyui-on-aws-elastically-and-efficiently/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction ComfyUI is an open-source node-based workflow solution for Stable Diffusion. It offers the following advantages: Significant performance optimization for SDXL model inference High customizability, allowing users granular control Portable workflows that can be shared easily Developer-friendly Due to these advantages, ComfyUI is increasingly being used by artistic creators. In this post, we will introduce […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wang Rui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Palestine Protest/Free Speech Threat: House Oversight Committee Targets 20 Pro-Palestinian Organizations,  Such as Bill & Melinda Gates Foundation, Demanding Treasury Produce Suspicious Activity Reports, Including on Employeees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271697</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/new-palestine-protest-free-speech-threat-house-oversight-committee-targets-20-pro-palestinian-organizations-such-as-bill-melinda-gates-foundation-demanding-treasury-produce-suspicious-activity-r.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T15:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new salvo against designated enemies, aka Palestinian rights advocates, which fortunately is more bark than bite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[skinny dipping with the elderly]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/public-bathhouse/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/public-bathhouse/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T12:33:37.270Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grandpa’s been trying to get my brother V and I to go to the public bathhouse with him for as long as I can remember. He asked us last time we were both here back when we were both still in elementary school. He asked us every day this past week too.
Naturally, since we don’t come from a culture where public nudity is the norm, my brother and I aren’t so keen on the idea of stripping butt-naked in front of our grandpa and his octogenarian friends. Grandpa’s tried everything to change our Nos to Yeses: at first he asked us nicely, then he tried urging us and bullying us into agreeing.
I finally caved today, more to shut him up than anything. In the wake of my uncle’s death, I’m aware that this might very well be the last time I get to spend time with my grandpa, so I figured I could lock my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Recent Inflationary Spike a Global Phenomenon?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29961</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/is-the-recent-inflationary-spike-a-global-phenomenon/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the COVID-19 pandemic, inflation rose almost simultaneously in most economies around the world. After peaking in mid-2022, inflation then went into decline—a fall that was just as universal as the initial rise. In this post, we explore the interrelation of inflation dynamics across OECD countries by constructing a measure of the persistence of global inflation. We then study the extent to which the persistence of global inflation reflects broad-based swings, as opposed to idiosyncratic country-level movements. Our main finding is that the spike and subsequent moderation in global inflation in the post-pandemic period were driven by persistent movements. When we look at measures of inflation that include food and energy prices, most of the persistence appears to be broad-based, suggesting that international oil and commodity prices played an important role in global inflation dynamics. Excluding food and energy prices in the analysis still shows a broad-based persistence, although with a substantial increase in the role of country-specific factors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martín Almuzara, Babur Kocaoglu, and Argia Sbordone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/16/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271674</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-16-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:58:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our effervescent daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kentucky Retirement Systems Plaintiffs Seek Repayment from KKR Entities of Misappropriated $137 Million Plus Interest and Punitive Damages, Totaling $771 Million….Oh, and An Accounting Too]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271669</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/kentucky-retirement-systems-plaintiffs-seek-repayment-from-kkr-entities-of-misappropriated-137-million-plus-interest-and-punitive-damages-totaling-771-million-oh-and-an-accounting-too.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The  Tier 3 Plaintiffs in the long-running public pension case, Kentucky Retirement Systems,  are fast off their marks with a blockbuster filing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Casper: &ldquo;A Bronx Tale&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/a-bronx-tale"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:47:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cooperativism in New York.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[catching up]]></title>
        <id>https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/</id>
        <link href="https://woolgathering.bearblog.dev/catching-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:28:05.926Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[woah, hello bear! it sure has been a while since i've last written.
a little bit after my last post, i went on some back-to-back trips around asia. i spent a few days in seoul and about a week in bali. i did actually write about both of those trips with the intention of sharing them with all of you on here but for some reason i couldn't quite bring myself to publish it. i've never really written on any sort of platform before this, but i'm assuming that just like visual art, some writing is just meant to be kept to yourself.
with the only things i had written in that span of 4 weeks being kept private, i didn't really have much else to post;  and the longer i went without posting, the harder it was to come back. this always happens to me. i did the exact same thing with my art account on t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Most Thorough Legal Analysis’ Yet Concludes Israel Committing Genocide in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271667</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/most-thorough-legal-analysis-yet-concludes-israel-committing-genocide-in-gaza.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel genocide denialists face more of an uphill battle as an authoritative groups renders a preliminary verdicts against the apartheid state.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Awards and Accolades: Why Gaza Journalists are the Best in the World]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322717</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/beyond-awards-and-accolades-why-gaza-journalists-are-the-best-in-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By granting its 2024 World Press Freedom Prize to Palestinian journalists covering the Israeli war on Gaza, UNESCO has acknowledged a historic truth. Even if the decision to name Gaza's journalists as laureates of its prestigious award was partly motivated by the courage of these journalists, the truth is that no one in the world deserved such recognition as those covering the genocidal war in Gaza. More
The post Beyond Awards and Accolades: Why Gaza Journalists are the Best in the World appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Descends Into Barbarism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322454</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/israel-descends-into-barbarism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Reality Unless you are the victim of a moral narrow-mindedness (and there seems to be an epidemic of this defect nowadays), it should be obvious to you that Israel has descended into barbarism. Why barbarism? Because in Israel, cruel, murderous, and otherwise criminal behavior has become state policy. Let’s review the signs of this  More
The post Israel Descends Into Barbarism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lawrence Davidson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debt Relief Still Feels Out of Reach for Many Students]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322756</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/debt-relief-still-feels-out-of-reach-for-many-students/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[College is expensive — and for most Americans, higher education is still largely unaffordable. The cost of college continues to rise at rates that salaries and income aren’t keeping up with. This is especially true for low-income and working-class students who must depend on alternative ways to fund their education like grants, scholarships, and —  More
The post Debt Relief Still Feels Out of Reach for Many Students appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Candace Milner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Zionist Politics of Joe Biden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322351</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/the-zionist-politics-of-joe-biden/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I voted for Joe Biden in the last election, I had yet to discover our American president’s uniquely potent commitment to the state of Israel nor his fanatical adherence to Zionism.   I’ve seen him in a film clip smiling enthusiastically and saying. “If I were Jewish, I’d be a Zionist.” I watched a short  More
The post The Zionist Politics of Joe Biden appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Grosso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[History Repeating Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322761</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/history-repeating-itself/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That great American wit (and anti-imperialist), Mark Twain, reputedly once remarked that history does not repeat itself — but it rhymes. Be that as it may, history right now does in fact seem to be repeating itself — once again in my own lifetime – and in a terrible and appalling kind of way. This  More
The post History Repeating Itself appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dodging the Issue: The Biden Administration Report on Israel’s Use of US Weapons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322753</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/dodging-the-issue-the-biden-administration-report-on-israels-use-of-us-weapons/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:55:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It truly is pushing the envelope of lunacy to assume that this latest revelation was revelatory.  US weapons, the wonks in Washington find, are being used by the Israeli Defense Forces to kill their opponents, many of them Palestinians, and most of them civilians.  These are detailed in a report ordered by the White House pursuant to National Security Memorandum  More
The post Dodging the Issue: The Biden Administration Report on Israel’s Use of US Weapons appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Beginning of the End of Cannabis Prohibition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322754</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/the-beginning-of-the-end-of-cannabis-prohibition/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time in its history, the Justice Department is calling for a change in the federal legal status of cannabis — which is currently classified as one of America’s most dangerous drugs. The Attorney General’s office recently confirmed that it’s circulating a proposal to reclassify marijuana from Schedule I to Schedule III under the  More
The post The Beginning of the End of Cannabis Prohibition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Armentano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World Under Spiritual Construction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322777</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/a-world-under-spiritual-construction/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s something happening here . . . Consider, for instance, the recent announcement by Union Theological Seminary, which is affiliated with Columbia University, that it is divesting from “companies profiting from war in Palestine/Israel” – and, not only that, fully supports the student encampments (at Columbia and all across the country) and condemns the arrests and  More
The post A World Under Spiritual Construction appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter From London: Podcast as Lodestar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322392</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/letter-from-london-podcast-as-lodestar/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was always fascinated as a little boy by the notion of Scots culture having retained so many of its wonderful songs, stories, and poetry through its oral traditions. The spoken word effectively saved so much of its day. Talking of the spoken word, the partner of a friend of mine acknowledged recently to me  More
The post Letter From London: Podcast as Lodestar appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thirsty in Paradise: The Growing Water Crises Across the Caribbean islands]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322347</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/16/thirsty-in-paradise-the-growing-water-crises-across-the-caribbean-islands/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the popular imagination, the Caribbean is paradise, an exotic place to escape to. But behind the images of balmy beaches and lush hotel grounds lies a crisis, the likes of which its residents have never experienced. Caribbean islands are in a water crisis, and their governments have warned that water scarcity may become the  More
The post Thirsty in Paradise: The Growing Water Crises Across the Caribbean islands appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farah Nibbs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending May 12, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20240516"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The IMF’s Chronicle of a Catastrophe Foretold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271649</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/the-imfs-chronicle-of-a-catastrophe-foretold.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T04:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dour IMF forecast bodes ill for developing economies and provides more confirmation of crises in the offing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Code to Quill: Embark on a Legendary Kubernetes Quest with SIG Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/05/16/contribute-as-sig-docs-reviewer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've likely heard the adage, "Contributing isn't just about writing code",
whispered in forums or seen etched into the digital walls of open source communities.
But what depth of truth lies within this ancient wisdom, especially in the vast,
evolving world of Kubernetes?
Today, contributing to open source extends far beyond the realm of coding.
It's an inclusive journey that welcomes the diverse skills of all who wish
to be a part of it. Whether you're a seasoned developer or someone whose strengths
lie outside traditional programming, your contributions hold immense value.
Imagine yourself embarking on a journey that leverages your expertise and love
for free software to enhance your capabilities and strengthen the very foundation
of the Kubernetes ecosystem. This is a real opportunity …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) winners]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7591</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-australian-book-industry-awards-abias-winners/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Australian Book Industry Awards (ABIAs) were held last week, on Thursday 9 May. The ABIAs are considered the Australian book publishing industry’s night of nights. A book-ish version of the Oscars, if you will. Award winners include Pip Williams, with her novel The Bookbinder of Jericho, in the General Fiction Book of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - How to find Your Local Wobbly History]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-how-to-find-your-local-wobbly-history?v=1715806685"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: How to find Your Local Wobbly History
Date: 2000
Notes: Published in Anarcho-Syndicalist Review #28, Spring 2000.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.katesharpleylibrary.net

 One can find the forgotten Wobbly names and faces, strike stories, union halls and martyrs’ graves in any city where the IWW earned its legendary reputation. It is easy to find thorough information on the luminaries, such as Tresca, Flynn and Giovanitti, but what about those local organizers who invited these major figures to town, and then kept working after they were gone, pouring the wine of rebellion into workers’ hearts? It may take some time, but in all probability you’ll find syndicalist monuments and hallowed ground that you walk past every day, but never knew existed. 
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Robert P. Helms - ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/robert-p-helms-doctors-and-druggists-among-the-early-philadelphia-anarchists?v=1715805357"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:35:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Robert P. Helms
Title: ​Doctors and Druggists Among the Early Philadelphia Anarchists
Date: September 2006
Notes: An earlier, much shorter version of this article, “Anarchists in Medicine and Pharmacy: Philadelphia, 1889–1930,” appeared in Clamor Magazine #6 (Dec. 2000/Jan. 2001), and had previously been posted on both the Guinea Pig Zero and Dead Anarchists websites.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

 In the City of Philadelphia in the late 19th and early 20th centuries, there was a large group of professionals who practiced medicine or pharmacy as a livelihood, while committing great energies to the anarchist movement. Looking past the surface, we find a closely knit community of intellectuals who treated their comrades as patients, educated the publ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minutes to hours, hours to days, this is how you spend your time]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7593</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/minute-hours-hours-days-how-you-spend-your-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A breakdown of how people, Americans in this case, spend their time, by each decade of their life. Things like sleeping, eating, working, caring for others, and socialising. The crunch is definitely on in our thirties, forties, and fifties, when time for sleep and socialising, for instance, is reduced. Kurzgesagt also did a presentation a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Voltairine de Cleyre - On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/voltairine-de-cleyre-on-domesticity-jealousy-and-abortion?v=1715804763"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Voltairine de Cleyre
Title: On Domesticity, Jealousy, and Abortion
Subtitle: A Private Letter to Samuel H. Gordon
Date: 1897
Notes: Edited and introduced by Robert P. Helms.
Source: Retrieved on 15th May 2024 from www.deadanarchists.org

​Introduction
 Voltairine de Cleyre, by far Philadelphia’s brightest anarchist light, was 30 years old when, during the late summer or fall of 1897, she wrote the following letter in London. The letter was never finished, nor was it signed, dated, or mailed. Yet the letter, clearly in her handwriting and style, came to rest in a large group of her letters in the papers of Joseph J. Cohen (1878–1953), de Cleyre’s longtime associate in anarchism, which are stored in the Bund Collection, YIVO Archives, in New York City. It is one of the most compellin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Miles Franklin longlist for Australian novel writing]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7596</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/2024-miles-franklin-longlist-australian-novel-writing/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well this is exciting, the longlist for the 2024 Miles Franklin literary award for Australian novel writing, has been published. Not sure how I missed the official announcement, but I went searching for a date the longlist would be unveiled, and instead found the longlist itself: Only Sound Remains, by Hossein Asgari Wall, by Jen […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson - All Eyes on Rafah]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/geelong-anarchist-communists-tommy-lawson-all-eyes-on-rafah?v=1715802065"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T19:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Geelong Anarchist-Communists, Tommy Lawson
Title: All Eyes on Rafah
Date: May 15th, 2024
Notes: The following article is a transcript of a speech given by Geelong Anarchist Communists member Tommy Lawson at an Independent and Peaceful Australia Network (IPAN) ‘Rally for Rafah’ held on Saturday 11th of May. Its content is supported unanimously by Geelong Anarchist Communists. We have decided to publish it today, on the 76th anniversary of the Nakba (‘catastrophe’) to declare that we stand with those resisting genocide and colonisation.
Source: Retrieved on May 15th, 2024 from https://geelonganarchists.org/2024/05/15/all-eyes-on-rafah/.

During al Nakba over 750,000 Palestinian people, from a total population of 1.9 million, were made refugees beyond the borders of their homeland. 53…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 5/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271653</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/200pm-water-cooler-5-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T18:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Pandemics, Trump's trial continues, Biden and Trump to debate  (without Kennedy), raw milk enthusiasts resist H5N1 "fearmongering", North Carolina's horrid anti-masking law, and how to make sure it doesn't pass. ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The aborted experiment of the Bank of the South in Latin America and the alternative policies that could have been adopted at the continental level]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Bank-of-the-South-s-abandoned-experiment-in-Latin-America-and-the"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2007–2008, I helped to prepare the creation of the “Bank of the South” after being requested to assist in framing Ecuador's position on the issue by Argentine and Ecuadorian economists, as well as Ricardo Patiño, Minister of Economy and Finance in the administration of President Rafael Correa of Ecuador. I did so with commitment and without remuneration. In April 2007, in Quito, we drafted a proposal outlining Ecuador's position on the statutes, operating model, and objectives of the future (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Bank of the South, 
South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A World of Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/A-World-of-Inequality"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T16:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A central feature of neo-liberal capitalism, which has ruled the global economy since the 1990s, is to deepen and widen inequalities. It makes a tiny minority indecently richer while leaving the majority in the lurch. Women and minorities such as indigenous peoples, LGBTQIA+ or racialized people are badly hit by those inequalities. In a situation in which famine and extreme poverty keep increasing, the withdrawal of the State further feeds the vicious circle of poverty and inequality. (...)
English

/ 
Poverty, 
Austerity/Structural Adjustment, 
Capitalism, 
North, 
Inegalites 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.atspotify.com/?p=7083</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.atspotify.com/2024/05/fixed-power-designs-its-not-if-you-peek-its-what-you-peek-at/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T15:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TL;DR Sometimes we cannot estimate the required sample size needed to power an experiment before starting it. To alleviate this [...]
The post Fixed-Power Designs: It’s Not IF You Peek, It’s WHAT You Peek at appeared first on Spotify Engineering.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spotify Engineering</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arsenal of Genocide: The U.S. Weapons That Are Destroying Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271645</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/the-arsenal-of-genocide-the-u-s-weapons-that-are-destroying-gaza.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Naming and shaming the weapons systems and manufacturers who are profiting from the slaughter in Gaza.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/big-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:10:26.460Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the longest time, I wanted to work in big tech. I got placed in one such company from campus placements. It was mostly due to my c programming skills and research work.
I am grateful for the role. I get to work on something I like. The people I work with are smart and kind. But it is just a job. Both to me and to the people I work with. One of the major perks that the HR department keeps repeating is a great work-life balance. You get time for yourself. That is very true.
Isn't that great? You get paid well. Get enough time for a good social life and side projects. You can also fund these side projects with your salary.
Yes, but what about working in a startup? A place where a lot of super passionate people are going ham at what they do. To them, it is not a job but a mission. A sort of crazy cult. Filled with kind passionate nerds. Some place where you own part of the dream. Have equity.
It sounds nice. But such places are very rare. The startup scene in India is pretty horrible. I have heard some really bad stories. So many of the startups look cool on the outside. Have great pay even. But are horrible to work for. I have had friends experience this.
I also feel like I am not good enough for those truly cracked places yet. So I am happy where I am for now and just Skill maxxing. I want to feel like a really capable engineer. I see so many of them at my org. All are really kind and happy to guide me.
Sometimes these essays help me put my life in context and clear my thinking a lot. This was one of those.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Consent and Bot Management features for Cloudflare Zaraz]]></title>
        <id>664272e7abf9e2000aee82a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-consent-and-bot-management-features-for-cloudflare-zaraz"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zaraz Consent Management now supports Google Consent Mode v2 and is compliant with the IAB Europe Transparency and Consent Framework. Zaraz also added Bot Management support for keeping your analytics data clean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yo'av Moshe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Unexpected Inflationary Shocks Raise Workers’ Wages?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29398</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/do-unexpected-inflationary-shocks-raise-workers-wages/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The past year’s steady decline in nominal wage growth now appears in danger of stalling. Given ongoing uncertainty in Ukraine and the Middle East, this seems an opportune moment to revisit the conventional wisdom about the relationship between inflation and wages: if an unexpected increase in energy costs drives up the cost of living, will workers demand higher wages, reversing the recent moderation in wage growth? In new work with Justin Bloesch and Seung Joo Lee examining those concerns, our analysis shows that the pass-through of such inflationary shocks to wages is weak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Weber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 5/15/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271570</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/links-5-15-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:55:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our tailored daily links: Smoking backfire, more China EV consternation, Hamas attacks in north, Putin reshuffle, North Carolina v. masks, Georgia disclosure riots, Stormy Daniels threat, Steve Keen crisis warning, non-compliant royals, Wlamart layoffs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Game Finally On! Judge Denies Key Motions to Dismiss in Kentucky Retirement Systems Litigation, Subjecting KKR, Blackstone, PAAMCO, and Top Financiers Henry Kravis, George Roberts, Steve Schwarzman, and Tomlinson Hill to Discovery]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=271476</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/05/game-finally-on-judge-denies-key-motions-to-dismiss-in-kentucky-retirement-systems-litigation-subjecting-kkr-blackstone-paamco-and-top-financiers-henry-kravis-george-roberts-steve-schwarzman-a.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-delayed Kentucky Retirement System cases are finally moving forward, causing heartburn to some top names on Wall Street.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I found a paper that denies one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism, so stating the obvious turns out to be useful!]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52696</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/15/i-found-a-paper-that-denies-one-of-my-two-obvious-thoughts-about-originalism-so-stating-the-obvious-turns-out-to-be-useful/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a couple days to think on it, I think this post is right on. I just stumbled on a paper that stumbles, badly, over one of my two obvious thoughts about originalism. So let me point that out. Quick review. My first obvious thought is it’s weird, if you think about it, that one […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presidents Barber Conable and Lewis Preston (1986-1995)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Presidents-Barber-Conable-and-Lewis-Preston-1986-1995"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In July 2024, the World Bank and the IMF will be 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday until July, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these (...)
English

/ 
World Bank, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s War on Science and the Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322329</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/donald-trumps-war-on-science-and-the-environment/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve spent 40 years putting together an apparatus to protect public health and environment from a lot of different pollutants.  [Former EPA administrator Scott} Pruitt is pulling the whole apparatus down. – William Ruckelshaus, the EPA’s first administrator, regarding former president Trump’s first EPA administrator Scott Pruitt. One of President Joe Biden’s greatest accomplishments over  More
The post Donald Trump’s War on Science and the Environment appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Random Notes About the Mexican Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322337</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/random-notes-about-the-mexican-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it may appear to be desirable that former Mexico City mayor Claudia Sheinbaum win the presidential election to avoid the threat to international solidarity that a return of the right (this time under Xóchitl Gálvez, who was a member of Vicente Fox’s cabinet) forebodes, Sheinbaum offers little for women, for the left, for the  More
The post Random Notes About the Mexican Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johnny Hazard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reflections on Student Activism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322569</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/reflections-on-student-activism/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent most of my life as an advocate for a more peaceful world. In recent years, I’ve been focused on promoting diplomacy over war and exposing the role of giant weapons companies like Lockheed Martin and its allies in Congress and at the Pentagon as they push for a “military-first” foreign policy. I’ve worked at an alphabet soup of think tanks: the Council on Economic Priorities (CEP), the World Policy Institute (WPI), the New America Foundation, the Center for International Policy (CIP), and my current institutional home, the Quincy Institute for Responsible Statecraft (QI). More
The post Reflections on Student Activism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William Hartung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anything Goes: The New Normal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322385</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/anything-goes-the-new-normal/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genocidal rhetoric is one thing; genocidal rhetoric combined with the military might to carry it out is quite another. The number of such statements uttered by Israel’s political and military leaders is too numerous to list here; however, they are rivaled by those of its American collaborators who provide the arms to carry out mass murder on the industrial scale described by Kapos. More
The post Anything Goes: The New Normal appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John G. Russell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US Labor Must Weigh in on Cuba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322654</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/us-labor-must-weigh-in-on-cuba/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking note of International Workers’ Day, several Latin American news sources this year cited José Martí’s 1886 essay “A Terrible Drama;” two of them republished it, here and here. There Martí reports on events in Chicago in 1886 and the fate of the so-called Haymarket Martyrs – seven labor journalists and agitators railroaded to prison and given death sentences.  Another received a 15-year prison term. Martí, who  More
The post US Labor Must Weigh in on Cuba appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Property Tax Quake in Helena]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322659</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/property-tax-quake-in-helena/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not since the 1935 earthquake has Helena, the home of state and federal government in Montana, been shaken quite this way. Every school levy on last Tuesday’s ballot was soundly rejected by voters.  Why? Not because they don’t support education — but because our insanely high property taxes have left homeowners tapped out. Of course  More
The post Property Tax Quake in Helena appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Public Investment Can Create Jobs and Ease the Childcare Crunch]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322657</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/how-public-investment-can-create-jobs-and-ease-the-childcare-crunch/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many American families are struggling to pay for child care, with the average price for licensed providers now nearly$11,000 a year. These high prices can be a huge barrier for workers, particularly women, forcing many to cut back on hours or drop out of the workforce entirely. A new federal program aims to help break down  More
The post How Public Investment Can Create Jobs and Ease the Childcare Crunch appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lea Woods and Julie Kashen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brown in the Philippines:  UPS joins the “pivot to Asia”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322327</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/big-brown-in-the-philippines-ups-joins-the-pivot-to-asia/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in mid-March, Gina Raimondo, the U.S. Secretary of Commerce, led a trade mission to the Philippines, that included twenty-two executives from such top U.S.-based corporations as United Airlines, Alphabet’s Google, Black & Veatch, Visa, Boston Consulting Group, KKR Asia Pacific, Bechtel, FedEx, Mastercard, Microsoft, and, finally, United Parcel Service (UPS), popularly known as “Big  More
The post Big Brown in the Philippines:  UPS joins the “pivot to Asia” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Allen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why African Homophobia is Still the Real Western Import]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322332</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/why-african-homophobia-is-still-the-real-western-import/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[African political leaders and religious zealots (both Christian and Muslim) have used homophobia as a tool for political and religious power for many years. They say that same-sex relations and gay rights are imports from the west. They have used homophobia to portray themselves as nationalists and defenders of African and religious values. They have  More
The post Why African Homophobia is Still the Real Western Import appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Volman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alliance for the Wild Rockies Says “Stop the Chop” in Colville National Forest]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322628</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/15/alliance-for-the-wild-rockies-says-stop-the-chop-in-colville-national-forest/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T05:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having lost so many times in court because they keep breaking the law, the Forest Service has now turned to what are called “landscape scale treatments” where they refuse to tell the public how, when, and where they are going to clearcut and bulldoze new logging roads. These projects cover tens of thousands of acres over  More
The post Alliance for the Wild Rockies Says “Stop the Chop” in Colville National Forest appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Garrity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem with electric vehicles]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45369</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/15/the-problem-with-electric-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker For the last quarter century, those of us hoping we could slow global warming were anxious to see a quick conversion to electric vehicles (EVs). If we could get most people using electric vehicles, and have the energy coming from clean sources, we could radically reduce greenhouse gas emissions. The problem was […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrimethInc. - How To Justify Workplace Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/crimethinc-how-to-justify-workplace-theft?v=1715732383"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T00:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: CrimethInc.
Title: How To Justify Workplace Theft
Date: 14th April 2020
Source: Retrieved on 9th September 2020 from archive.org/details/workplacetheft-web

 Whether aware of it or not, your boss is stealing from you every paycheck. Employers profit off of the “excess” wealth that you, as an employee, produce. There are two ways to get paid in America: make money off the work you do, or make money off the work that other people do. Employees generate wealth, employers collect it. 
 We live in a capitalist society. We all know that. Most people are okay with it, too. After all, the competition (state communism like the USSR) doesn’t have such a good reputation. 
 But what exactly does capitalism mean? Our good friend the dictionary says capitalism is “an economic and political syste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anne Archet - Sirventès of the Beast]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anne-archet-sirventes-of-the-beast?v=1715731162"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anne Archet
Title: Sirventès of the Beast
Date: 2014/06/27
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 I am no citizen 
 I am no consumer 
 I am no tax-payer 
 I am no employee 
 I am no convict 
 I am no beneficiary 
 I am no person of color 
 I am no lesbian 
 I am no mother 
 I am no wife 
 I am no erotic writer 
 I am no poetess 
 I am no anarchist 
 I am no woman 
 I am surely no Human 
 That vile and ethereal being 
 Which has never been spotted elsewhere 
 But in universal declarations 
 I don't want to stay seated and raise my hand 
 I don't want to wait for the teacher to tell me to speak 
 I don't want to w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous, Return Fire - The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-return-fire-the-green-farce-everywhere-nowhere-else?v=1715730807"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous, Return Fire
Title: The ‘Green’ Farce Everywhere & Nowhere Else
Subtitle: towards destroying electric mobility & decarbonizing lies
Notes: Printed in Return Fire vol.6 chap.6 (spring 2024). 
 To read the articles referenced throughout this text in [square brackets], PDFs of Return Fire and related publications can be read, downloaded and printed by visiting returnfire.noblogs.org or emailing returnfire@riseup.net

 [ed. – Taken from the German-language website SwitchOff.noblogs.org, this translation continues our interventions in the new climate movements. There are two fronts on which we would like to extend the thrust of the author/s further, in terms of its response to the text reproduced above in this chapter of Return Fire, Targets That Do Not Exist Anywhere Else. Fi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil - An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/cello-latini-pfeil-bruno-latini-pfeil-an-anarchist-historical-analysis-of-body-inscriptions-in?v=1715728910"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Cello Latini Pfeil, Bruno Latini Pfeil
Title: An Anarchist Historical Analysis of Body Inscriptions in Modern Western Society
Date: 02.22.2024
Source: Original translation of “Uma análise histórica anarquista das inscrições corporais na sociedade ocidental moderna”, published in Revista História em Reflexão 18(35), 2024. Retrieved on 05/07/2024 from https://doi.org/10.30612/rehr.v18i35.16476

Abstract
 In this paper, we aim to analyze the processes of stigmatization and pathologization to which certain categories of body inscriptions have been subjected throughout the history of modern Western society. Body inscriptions are defined as any and all modifications made to the body's structure. While some inscriptions are exalted and praised, others are stigmatized and discriminated aga…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agnes Henry - Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/agnes-henry-anarchist-communism-in-its-relation-to-state-socialism?v=1715728414"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Agnes Henry
Title: Anarchist Communism in its Relation to State Socialism
Date: June 1896
Notes: Original text split between two consecutive monthly publications, with a misprint in the latter citing the first entry as having been published in July rather than June; transcribed from Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (June 1896) and Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism (July 1896) on the Internet Archive.
Source: Liberty: A Journal of Anarchist Communism

 The question of how for Anarchist Communism agrees exactly with State Socialism, and the exact line that divides them, has long seemed to me one that it would be well to enter into. And just now, in view of the approaching International Congress, seems a time particularly appropriate for this consideration. For surely…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sophie Scott-Brown - Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sophie-scott-brown-colin-ward-and-the-art-of-everyday-anarchy?v=1715727897"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T23:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Sophie Scott-Brown
Title: Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy
Date: 2022
Notes: Routledge Studies in Radical History and Politics
Source: <doi.org/10.4324/9781003100409>

Colin Ward and the Art of Everyday Anarchy is the first full account of Ward’s life and work. Drawing on unseen archival sources, as well as oral interviews, it excavates the worlds and words of his anarchist thought, illuminating his methods and charting the legacies of his enduring influence. 
 Colin Ward (1924—2010) was the most prominent British writer on anarchism in the 20th century. As a radical journalist, later author, he applied his distinctive anarchist principles to all aspects of community life including the built environment, education, and public policy. His thought was subtle, universal in a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Igor & Phil Mailer - And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-phil-mailer-and-yet-it-moves-updated-edition?v=1715726263"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:37:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Boy Igor & Phil Mailer
Title: And Yet It Moves (Updated Edition)
Subtitle: The Realization and Suppression of Science and Technology
Date: 1985
Notes: A situationist critique of science and technology published in New York in 1985. This version is a new edition that was published on the 'Endangered Phoenix' website and credited to Phil Meyler. The Endangered Phoenix website is dead now, and I can’t find the updated version on the website through the wayback machine, so there are some footnotes and chapter heading levels which are unclear to me. Plus, I think chapter 3 & 4 were merged in the updated edition, so chapter numbers went out of sync, but chapter 8 was still called chapter 8 which makes it seem like chapter 7 is missing on the libcom website. It is all very confusing, but …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnarchyNouveau - We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anarchynouveau-we-don-t-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-comm?v=1715726103"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: AnarchyNouveau
Title: We Don’t Need a “Plethora of Tactics”, We Need a Climate Strategy
Subtitle: An anarchist-communist’s response to Freedom News
Date: March 20, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 5/10/2024 from https://freedomnews.org.uk/2024/03/23/we-dont-need-a-plethora-of-tactics-we-need-a-climate-strategy-an-anarchist-communists-response-to-freedom-news/

 In Freedom Anarchist Journal’s Winter 2023-2024 issue, Matthew Azoulay submitted an article introducing readers to Murray Bookchin’s ideas of the communalist assembly[1] which disturbed and surprised me for how much it was outdated. The means it proposes to achieve an ecologically revolutionary ends are lacking, stagnant, and fall back on modes of thinking that seem directly inherited from the anti-globalization and Occupy era[2] w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - A Proposal for the Unification of China]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-a-proposal-for-the-unification-of-china?v=1715723886"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:58:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: A Proposal for the Unification of China
Date: 1927
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

The Political Capability of the Chinese People
 There are some who doubt that the Chinese people are capable of creating a truly democratic state. We emphatically disagree. The political environment in any country is created by its leaders. The perceptions and habits of the people can be changed to follow those of the leadership. Furthermore, Chinese society has been traditionally rich in self-governing organizations, which can be effectively used to reconstruct [China as] a democratic state. 
The Real Causes of the Turmoil over the Past Sixteen Years
1. The Problem of the Provisional Constitution
 [First,] no provision…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gustav Landauer - Are These the Words of a Heretic?]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gustav-landauer-are-these-the-words-of-a-heretic?v=1715722519"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gustav Landauer
Title: Are These the Words of a Heretic?
Notes: Translated from the German Daniel Wortel-London, originally entitled "Sind das Kertzergendanken?" ("Are These Heretic Thoughts?"). Originally published in Von Judentum (On Judaism) in 1911 by the Bar Kokhba League of Jewish Students.
Source: Retrieved on May 14th, 2024 from:https://x.com/dlondonwortel/status/1787470614107763006

 A characteristic of our time is that much is accomplished in spirit but little is accomplished in reality. Perhaps even the lack of actual implementation corresponds to a special activity of the mind, which constantly strives to overcome its own formations without leaving the form of fantasy and doctrine. One could imagine a human society that is structured in such a way that the ideas in it h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Like describing a photo to a friend, how to write alt-text]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7584</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/like-describing-photo-friend-write-alt-text/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T21:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web designers and bloggers have been able to use alternative text, often referred to as “alt-text”, to describe images and photos, for decades. Alt-text helps people with little or no vision comprehend a website image, so long as the description is reasonably accurate. In recent years social media has caught up, and most channels, Instagram, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A simple text editor named Tine, by Martin Dorazil]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7582</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/simple-text-editor-tine-martin-dorazil/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A text editor without the bells and whistles, called Tine. A nice name for a text editor. The main goal of this editor is to keep the focus on the text editing and not be distracted too much by buttons, tabs, menus, and animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Untitled]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322561</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/322561/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T17:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New compute-optimized (C7i-flex) Amazon EC2 Flex instances]]></title>
        <id>a2b797c1aff33d1760b7816ad576286f2d84123f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-compute-optimized-c7i-flex-amazon-ec2-flex-instances/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The vast majority of applications don’t run run the CPU flat-out at 100% utilization continuously. Take a web application, for instance. It typically fluctuates between periods of high and low demand, but hardly ever uses a server’s compute at full capacity. CPU utilization for many common workloads that customers run in the AWS Cloud today. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Many Genders Are There?]]></title>
        <id>https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/</id>
        <link href="https://that-bloke.com/how-many-genders-are-there/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:45:06.631Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's 2 genders, right? We all know that.
Of course there is. You're either a bloke, who has the dangly bits between their legs, or you're a woman without said dangly bits.
But maybe there's more. Maybe you have the dangly bits, but it doesn't feel right to call yourself a man? Maybe it's the opposite? Or something in between?
Honestly, I don't give a fuck. For all I care, you could identify as a potato and I'll still respect your wishes. But getting pissed off at me if I mis-identify you is not cool.
Look, it's a fucking minefield out there when it comes to people identifying as non-binary. We've been mincing about this planet for hundreds of thousands of years, and for most that time there's been 2 genders. Male and female.
But in the last few decades there's been a number of other genders that have sprung up. So if I think you look like a man, and I refer to you as "him" don't get up on your high horse and start screaming "YOU ASSUMED MY GENDER! NAZI!"
I assumed your gender because you look like a fucking man. If you identify as something else, that's fine. Tell me politely and I'll happily respect your wishes. Live and let live, and all that. Makes no difference to me.
Irony is, if you're not a dick about the whole thing, you're far more likely to get people on-side. You're always gonna get bigoted wankers, that's par for the course. But just because someone makes a mistake, it doesn't make them a bigot, or a transphobe, or a TERF, or a Nazi.
It just makes them human.
Peace ✌🏻
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes of Threads for web]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21199</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/05/14/web/threads-for-web-behind-the-scenes/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T16:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Threads first launched one of the top feature requests was for a web client. In this episode of the Meta Tech Podcast, Pascal Hartig (@passy) sits down with Ally C. and Kevin C., two engineers on the Threads Web Team that delivered the basic version of Threads for web in just under three months. [...]
Read More...
The post Behind the scenes of Threads for web appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sacred black and red - Bonk]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/sacred-black-and-red-bonk-university-of-california-office-of-the-president-attacked?v=1715701274"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: sacred black and red
Title: Bonk
Subtitle: University of California Office of the President Attacked
Date: May 14, 2024
Source: Retrieved on 14 May 2024 from indybay.org/newsitems/2024/05/14/18866217.php


 “The beginning of every revolution is an exit, an exit from the social order that power has enshrined in the name of law, stability, public interest, and the greater good.” 
 - Basel al-Araj 
 With the Aurora Borealis above us and the martyrs in our hearts, we attacked the UC Office of the President in solidarity with the Palestinian Resistance. Using a fire extinguisher filled with red paint we covered the facade and smashed seven windows. Then, with access to the building, we released 500 cockroaches inside and emptied a second fire exintguisher onto the interior. We finalized…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Aparna Sinha, Capital One’s Head of AI Product]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5ad22603cb4f</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/introducing-aparna-sinha-capital-ones-head-of-ai-product-5ad22603cb4f?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation with AI product leader, Aparna Sinha, about her expertise in building and enabling enterprise AI/ML capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The student movement for Palestine is now spreading everywhere, inspiring resistance to the barbarism of our times…]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-student-movement-for-Palestine-is-now-spreading-everywhere-inspiring"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the student movement in solidarity with the Palestinians and denunciation of their genocide by Israel intensifies in the United States and now spreads across the planet, there are growing indications that it is succeeding in influencing the central balance of forces while it is being recognized as a major factor in international developments of decisive importance! Thus, Washington's “sudden” distancing of itself from the Netanyahu government, which followed (or perhaps...preceded) Hamas' (...)
English

/ 
Palestine, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delinquency Is Increasingly in the Cards for Maxed‑Out Borrowers]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29844</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/delinquency-is-increasingly-in-the-cards-for-maxed-out-borrowers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning, the New York Fed’s Center for Microeconomic Data released the Quarterly Report on Household Debt and Credit for the first quarter of 2024. Household debt balances grew by $184 billion over the previous quarter, slightly less than the moderate growth seen in the fourth quarter of 2023. Housing debt balances grew by $206 billion. Auto loans saw a $9 billion increase, continuing their steady growth since the second quarter of 2020, while balances on other non-housing debts fell. Credit card balances fell by $14 billion, which is typical for the first quarter. However, an increasing number of borrowers are behind on credit card payments. In this post, we explore the relationship between credit card delinquency and changes in credit card “utilization rates.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew F. Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle Scally, Wilbert van der Klaauw, and Crystal Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IAM done right for LLM-augmented applications]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b5abbea70c45</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/iam-done-right-for-llm-augmented-applications-b5abbea70c45?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How IAM can help you to leverage the advanced capabilities of LLMs while securing sensitive data and assets.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[i can quit any time (i won't)]]></title>
        <id>https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/</id>
        <link href="https://mei.bearblog.dev/i-can-quit-any-time-i-wont/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T14:09:15.529Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm currently writing this post as a break from working on the comic I have due at the end of the month. It's an eighteen-page oneshot and my very first contribution to an anthology, which is honestly very exciting. Intimidating, too, which is why I ended up putting off most of the work until the last minute.
Working on it has, as I anticipated, brought to light a number of my artistic weaknesses: I don't like inking, I half-ass shapes I don't understand rather than look for a reference, my faces are inconsistent... the list goes on. Seeing all the ways I fall short of my expectations is what I was afraid of happening, why I put it off for so long – but I don't really have the time anymore to sit and nitpick at my work, which is kind of a blessing. Stuff is getting done!
It's frustrating t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[hard pills to swallow]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/hard-swallow/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:56:55.178Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My throat hurts a little. I don’t know if this is because of the air quality here or because I’m actually getting sick, but I’m desperately hoping it’s not the latter. I stopped taking my immunosuppressants today and started drinking lots of juices high in vitamin C, despite research proving chugging OJ a rather ineffective method for warding off illness. (Something about all the sugar in it makes it hard for your body to absorb the Vitamin C, if I remember correctly.)
Traveling and getting sick go hand in hand for me. It’s as if arriving somewhere new triggers my immune system to self-immolate. When I visited New York in 2021 I lost my voice after a few days. I spent my first week in Latin America making chicken noodle soup and nursing myself back to health. My immune system’s never been …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Owen Hatherley: &ldquo;Radio Waves&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/radio-waves"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Ernst Schoen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[English is a very religious language]]></title>
        <id>https://itapun.bearblog.dev/english-is-a-very-religious-language/</id>
        <link href="https://itapun.bearblog.dev/english-is-a-very-religious-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:18:05.300Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never really thought about it while growing up because I was raised in a religious family anyway and it's just how I was used to people talking, but at this point I've been living in Japan for several years and I often notice that very normal phrases take on a religious persona when translated to English. For example we have this word yokatta which literally translates as "it was good", but if you were to translate it normally to English as it's used than it would come out as "thank God". Or we have this other word kotoka which would be translated as "God knows" like "God only knows how bored I am" (なんて暇なことか). Also a lot of words in English are shortened versions of old phrases with religious significance like "Goodbye" coming from "God be with ye", and a lot of set phrases or common expressions in English that people use all the time come straight from the Bible like "a drop in the bucket", "go the extra mile", "by the skin of your teeth", "the root of the matter", "a labor of love", "scapegoat", "broken heart", "eye for an eye", "rise and shine", "fall by the wayside", or "a wolf in sheep's clothing"
I'm not suggesting that it's a bad thing (and I don't think it is), and Japanese has a lot of similar words or phrases which come from a religious origin too. It's just kinda weird to notice in retrospect how in English-speaking countries everything is experienced through a Judeo-Christian lens, even if you're an atheist.
Maybe that's why Western society and Japanese society are so different. Or partly why, anyway.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare’s public IPFS gateways and supporting Interplanetary Shipyard]]></title>
        <id>6642fc97abf9e2000aee82eb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflares-public-ipfs-gateways-and-supporting-interplanetary-shipyard"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare is transitioning traffic that comes to our public IPFS gateway to Interplanetary Shipyard’s IPFS gateway. The transition is expected to be complete by August 14th, 2024]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Batraski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reclaiming CPU for free with Go's Profile Guided Optimization]]></title>
        <id>663cf36120f20e000a888047</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/reclaiming-cpu-for-free-with-pgo"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang 1.20 introduced support for Profile Guided Optimization (PGO) to the go compiler. This post covers the process we created for experimenting with PGO at Cloudflare, and measuring the CPU savings]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Douch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[you want a revelation]]></title>
        <id>https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/you-want-a-revelation/</id>
        <link href="https://savetooru.bearblog.dev/you-want-a-revelation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:12:02.449Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[my supposed last term in college, i ended up failing a class and falling into academic purgatory for months. 

i try not to dredge up the past but looking back, it's not that the issue was a matter of effort. sudden losses in the family and a general fear anyone else i cared about would fall ill aggravated a condition i was largely unaware of into rearing its big, ugly head. those days i'd lived not knowing 120 bpm was my resting average. and then the waitlists. and the forced leaves. and the absurd changes to curriculum. 

hard not to fault myself for ignoring my health. i mean, i was and still am obsessed with seeming invincible. who else was supposed to notice something was wrong? but at the very least, i probably would have graduated on time had the world not been actively folding in o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Battle of UCLA: Inside the Class Struggle]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322294</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/the-battle-of-ucla-inside-the-class-struggle/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T06:01:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May Day I went to embattled UCLA to cover the ongoing student revolt there. At the barricades I met with a young woman who called herself “Mona,” the press spokesperson for UCLA’s Palestine Solidarity Encampment. Mona gave me a copy of the student occupiers’ demands. More
The post The Battle of UCLA: Inside the Class Struggle appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ed Rampell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aidan Rowe - The Politics of Voices: Notes on Gender, Race & Class]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aidan-rowe-the-politics-of-voices-notes-on-gender-race-class?v=1715666454</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/aidan-rowe-the-politics-of-voices-notes-on-gender-race-class?v=1715666454"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T06:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Aidan Rowe
Title: The Politics of Voices: Notes on Gender, Race & Class
Date: 2013-04-30
Source: <wsm.ie/c/anarchism-intersecionality-gender-race-class>

 As class-struggle anarchists dealing with the relations between gender, race and class, we must, in theory and practice, pick a path between two pitfalls. On one side is economic reductionism – the reduction of all political questions to the social relations of production – which erases the perspectives and struggles of women, queers and people of colour; submerges their voices within an overly generalised class narrative, in which the idealised Worker is implicitly white heterosexual and male; or consigns their struggles to a secondary importance compared to the “real struggle” of (economic) class against class. On the other is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weight Loss Drugs Go Hand-in-Hand With Junk Food Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322500</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/weight-loss-drugs-go-hand-in-hand-with-junk-food-industry/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As obesity rates have risen in the U.S., there is an all-too-familiar blame game that individualizes the harm being caused by a capitalist system that thrives off of addiction. Doctors warn people struggling to manage their weight that they must simply restrict their intake of calories while expending more calories through rigorous exercise. High-profile reality shows such as The Biggest Loser have cemented the narrative that obesity is the result of individuals not being able to manage their urges to eat. More
The post Weight Loss Drugs Go Hand-in-Hand With Junk Food Industry appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Could the UN Actually Lead a Charge to Tax the World’s Rich?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322247</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/could-the-un-actually-lead-a-charge-to-tax-the-worlds-rich/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What might a robust new international tax agenda include? Advocates for fair taxation began circulating late in April an “ABCs of Tax” to highlight the progressive options that ought to be sitting on the worldwide tax reform table, everything from the creation of a “global asset registry” that can bring “transparency to the assets of the superrich” to a “formulary apportionment” that makes sure corporations get taxed “where they create, not book, profits.” More
The post Could the UN Actually Lead a Charge to Tax the World’s Rich? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psychiatry is Vexxing More Americans Than Ever]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322478</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/psychiatry-is-vexxing-more-americans-than-ever/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Psychiatry is ruining more lives than ever before. The New York Times recently showcased psychiatric “prevalence inflation” – a vast increase in reported mental illness among teenagers who are encouraged to view normal feelings as grave maladies requiring intervention. Oxford University psychologist Lucy Foulkes observed that school programs are “creating this message that teenagers are  More
The post Psychiatry is Vexxing More Americans Than Ever  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Bovard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palestine Solidarity in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322376</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/palestine-solidarity-in-japan/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rebecca Maria Goldschmidt, sitting in for Eric Draitser on CounterPunch Radio, talks with Hanin Siam, a Palestinian organizer based in Tokyo, Japan. They discuss the challenges of organizing the Palestine solidarity movement in Japan, including the nuances of their communities in Tokyo and Hiroshima. From the history of Japanese support for Palestine, to BDS, to  More
The post Palestine Solidarity in Japan appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rebecca Maria Goldschmidt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve Already Got an “Antisemitism Awareness Act.” It’s Called the First Amendment.]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322477</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/weve-already-got-an-antisemitism-awareness-act-its-called-the-first-amendment/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On May 1, the US House of Representatives passed the fraudulently titled “Antisemitism Awareness Act of 2023.” It’s not yet law, pending Senate passage and a presidential signature, but the lopsided House vote (320 to 91) should worry all Americans, including the country’s 7.6 million Jews. In theory, the bill merely clarifies how the US  More
The post We’ve Already Got an “Antisemitism Awareness Act.” It’s Called the First Amendment. appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Clubbable Admission: Palestine’s Case for UN Membership]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322473</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/a-clubbable-admission-palestines-case-for-un-membership/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I find it rather difficult to make it clear to my children why we are not eligible, for from one point of view it isn’t quite clear to me.” – X, “The Jew and the Club,” The Atlantic, October 1924. It must surely make certain ethnic and religious groups reflect, notably those languishing in minority  More
The post A Clubbable Admission: Palestine’s Case for UN Membership  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power Outages Linked to Heat and Storms are Rising, and Low-Income Communities are Most at Risk, NYC Maps Show the Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322244</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/power-outages-linked-to-heat-and-storms-are-rising-and-low-income-communities-are-most-at-risk-nyc-maps-show-the-impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many Americans think of power outages as infrequent inconveniences, but that’s quickly changing. Nationwide, major power outages have increased tenfold since 1980, largely because of an aging electrical grid and damage sustained from severe storms as the planet warms. At the same time, electricity demand is rising as the population grows and an increasing number  More
The post Power Outages Linked to Heat and Storms are Rising, and Low-Income Communities are Most at Risk, NYC Maps Show the Impact appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nina Flores</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will the Return to Work Mean a Return to the Open Office?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=322250</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/05/14/will-the-return-to-work-mean-a-return-to-the-open-office/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. As employees return to the workplace post-pandemic, older debates about the purpose and design of offices are resurfacing. Can you give us a rundown of the origins of open offices? Large corporate offices emerged in the late 19th century as growing industrial businesses needed more administrative coordination. Companies wanted to have offices downtown, but  More
The post Will the Return to Work Mean a Return to the Open Office? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph L. Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fully Onchain Games]]></title>
        <id>https://nadz.xyz/fully-onchain-games/</id>
        <link href="https://nadz.xyz/fully-onchain-games/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fully onchain games are the only "web3 games" that I find interesting or worthwhile.
Like many of you, I have always been a gamer and have spent tens of thousands of hours exploring in-game worlds. These days, I'm too busy with my full-time job (helping people build interesting products using blockchains) to play much, and I tend to spend more time consuming content about games than playing them. I barely ever beat/100% a game like I used to. I still find myself driven to the aura that surrounds a game, often comprising of lore, community, roleplaying, extensive multi-party discussion and the creation of adjacent media.
I understand that this opening statement might be controversial, but I have seen enough of the behind-the-scenes of web3 gaming (or its name-of-the-month; I'm glad we dropp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[East African Internet connectivity again impacted by submarine cable cuts]]></title>
        <id>66429493abf9e2000aee82af</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/east-african-internet-connectivity-again-impacted-by-submarine-cable-cuts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Sunday, May 12, issues with the EASSy and Seacom submarine cables again disrupted connectivity to East Africa, impacting a number of countries previously affected by a set of cable cuts that occurred nearly three months earlier]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Angel Baby, a story of doomed loved, and changing Australian accents]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7572</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/angel-baby-story-doomed-loved-changing-australian-accents/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A scene from Angel Baby, a film by Michael Rymer, depicting stars Jacqueline McKenzie and John Lynch. Angel Baby, trailer, is the 1995 debut feature of Australian filmmaker Michael Rymer. You may have seen some of his other work: Battlestar Galactica, Hannibal, both TV series, and/or his 2012 feature, Face to Face, but likely you’ve […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unwanted AI-generated content has a name: slop]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7579</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/unwanted-ai-generated-content-name-slop/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T20:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seen at Simon Willison’s Weblog: Not all promotional content is spam, and not all AI-generated content is slop. But if it’s mindlessly generated and thrust upon someone who didn’t ask for it, slop is the perfect term for it. Spam and slop. Now there’s a diet guaranteed to be bad for your health and mental […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Containers on AWS Fargate: Launch time improvements]]></title>
        <id>83cc88ad2930181e507d8b8c610c04c011bc627f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/windows-containers-on-aws-fargate-launch-time-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T18:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We launched AWS Fargate support for Windows Server containers on Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) in October 2021 to remove the undifferentiated heavy lifting of managing the underlying host operating system (OS). This has enabled customers to run Windows containers without having to patch, scale, and harden the Windows OS, using the serverless, pay-as-you-go compute […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Purvi Goyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Talking to Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/talking-to-computers/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/talking-to-computers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:44:20.298Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open AI released a new update. You can now talk to your computers just like a human. Low latency. More responsive. It got me thinking about how I talk to computers.
The way I do it is more intimate. I am a low-level programmer. I write firmware code in c mostly. I think about the hardware that runs my code more than the average programmer. Yet if it was the 1980's I would be a very high-level programmer. The assembly lang bros will look at me with contempt the same way I look at the python bros. The thought alone makes me shiver.
How we talk to computers has evolved. So many great engineers built the infrastructure that I use today to turn my c code into machine code. From the libraries, the operating system, and the compiler. There is a sort of deterministic heuristic-based intelligence b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New capabilities in Amazon Bedrock, AWS Amplify Gen 2, Amazon RDS and more (May 13, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>fbfc12083190a0beba131b64489794f4257a17d2</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-capabilities-in-amazon-bedrock-aws-amplify-gen-2-amazon-rds-and-more-may-13-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Summit is in full swing around the world, with the most recent one being AWS Summit Singapore! Here is a sneak peek of the AWS staff and ASEAN community members at the Developer Lounge booth. It featured AWS Community speakers giving lightning talks on serverless, Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS), security, generative AI, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Ansible to bootstrap external container instances with Amazon ECS Anywhere]]></title>
        <id>2c010b11840f18936f90d7128e55a72e9f424e56</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/use-ansible-to-bootstrap-external-container-instances-with-amazon-ecs-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) is a fully managed container orchestration service that helps you deploy, manage, and scale containerized applications. Within Amazon ECS there is a concept known as Capacity, which is the infrastructure where your containers run. Amazon ECS provides multiple options: Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instances in the AWS Cloud, AWS […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Santosh Vallurupalli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With a modest financial transactions tax, Jim Simons would not have been superrich]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45365</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/13/with-a-modest-financial-transactions-tax-jim-simons-would-not-have-been-superrich/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Dean Baker The New York Times reported that Jim Simons, the founder of Medallion hedge fund, died this week. As a result of his fund, according to the article, he accumulated more than $20 billion over his lifetime. Simons was a math genius who had made many important breakthroughs in various areas of math. Back in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>deanbaker1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Disaster Recovery on AWS Outposts to AWS Local Zones with a GitOps approach for Amazon EKS]]></title>
        <id>1bb6bef186e39209315ed15cfd5a7524cb20d7fd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/disaster-recovery-on-aws-outposts-to-aws-local-zones-with-a-gitops-approach-for-amazon-eks/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T16:08:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users often need to host their Kubernetes workloads in specific locations, geographies, or on-premises to meet data locality or low-latency requirements. Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) has a broad range of deployments options from in the cloud to on-premises on customer-managed hardware with Amazon EKS Anywhere. To extend AWS infrastructure and APIs to users on-premises, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samir Khan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[a rant? on america's youth]]></title>
        <id>https://pj.bearblog.dev/a-rant-on-americas-youth/</id>
        <link href="https://pj.bearblog.dev/a-rant-on-americas-youth/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:53:23.747Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i know, kind of random. 

these days, kids in the region where i live get chromebooks at school. 

many of my students, including the ones who are now in middle school, are not efficient typers, and in fact many of them are slamming their pointer fingers down on keys one by one, the younger ones not even remembering where any of the letters are even after countless repetitions of the same words. 

and don't even get me started on their spelling skills. 
choice, import, and scissors, although i'll cut some of the younger ones slack on scissors. 

something else i find pretty funny is that occasionally they'll try to touch the screen on the desktop to navigate. 

and this is all coming from an area where many of the school districts are top in the nation. 

did you also know that kids nowadays are more susceptible to online scams and malware? 

and overall, kids throughout the nation are reading at a significantly lower level than they should be, even with schooling. 

that's it from me, thanks for reading my rant:)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[we don’t get to choose our memories]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/family-memories/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/family-memories/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T14:16:01.122Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we had the big family reunion I’ve been waiting for all these years. My mom’s older sister came with her husband, as did my mom’s uncle (my grandma’s little brother).
My late uncle’s wife and daughter (my cousin) kindly joined us too. I mentioned how much I wanted to see my cousin in an earlier post. When we went to my uncle’s apartment with strawberries in hand to visit her I felt bad seeing the eye bags and stress lines written all over their face. In spite of all that, they invited us in and told us their side of the story while shedding tears. The details of his precipitously declining health and death were gruesome; I had to bite my tongue to keep from crying. I can’t imagine the whirlwind of emotions the last month has been for them.
That said, I was still really glad to see my…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who Is Borrowing and Lending in the Eurodollar and Selected Deposit Markets?]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=29775</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/05/who-is-borrowing-and-lending-in-the-eurodollar-and-selected-deposit-markets/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent Liberty Street Economics post discussed who is borrowing and lending in the federal funds (fed funds) market. This post explores activity in two other markets for short-term bank liabilities that are often perceived as close substitutes for fed funds—the markets for Eurodollars and “selected deposits.”]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gara Afonso, Gonzalo Cisternas, and Will Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[crawfish update]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/crawfish-update/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/crawfish-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T10:15:41.850Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[▶︎ Listen to my voice note

Almost two weeks ago, I wrote about catching a crawfish in the pond near Jiaozi Park, not far from where I live. My wife and I weren't sure what to do - whether we should put it back or keep it. Ultimately, we decided to keep it and see how it fared.
I'm happy to report that the crawfish seems to be doing very well. We've noticed that it is molting. My wife even bought special food for it. It's no longer afraid of us, either. Before, it would stop eating if we approached it, but now it continues eating even when we're nearby. It comes quickly to the surface whenever we feed it, too.
We're trying to make the crawfish feel comfortable in its new home. So far, it seems to be adjusting well. I'll provide more updates as things progress.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Australian study on IndieWeb, decentralised social media]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7568</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-study-indieweb-decentralised-social-media/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Pang is studying Design in Visual Communications at the University of Technology, Sydney, in Australia. As part of the degree course, she’s doing an assignment looking at IndieWeb, and decentralised social media, such as Mastodon. She’s interested in hearing the views of people on the subject, and if you’re interested in offering your thoughts, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M. Gouldhawke - Intro to Anarchists & Fellow Travellers on Palestine]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/m-gouldhawke-intro-to-anarchists-fellow-travellers-on-palestine?v=1715571820</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/m-gouldhawke-intro-to-anarchists-fellow-travellers-on-palestine?v=1715571820"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: M. Gouldhawke
Title: Intro to Anarchists & Fellow Travellers on Palestine
Date: 2024
Notes: Intro to a collection of links to texts by various writers.
Source: Retrieved on May 12, 2024 from mgouldhawke.wordpress.com

 Anarchists over the course of history have never had a unified stance on Palestine and Zionism. 
 Some Jewish anarchists active in the late 1800s and early 1900s, such as Bernard Lazare and Hillel Solotaroff, drifted toward Zionism over time (as noted by Mina Grauer in an article from 1994). 
 In 1906, Jewish anarchist Emma Goldman published an pseudonymously-authored article by a fellow Jewish anarchist which criticized Zionism, as well as nationalism more generally, and claimed that "Prejudices are never overcome by one who shows himself equally narrow and bigoted.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vernon Richards - Terrorism In Palestine: “Democracy” at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/vernon-richards-terrorism-in-palestine-democracy-at-work?v=1715571806</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/vernon-richards-terrorism-in-palestine-democracy-at-work?v=1715571806"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T03:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Vernon Richards
Title: Terrorism In Palestine: “Democracy” at Work
Date: 1937
Notes: From ‘Spain and the World’, Vol. 1. No. 22., 27th October, 1937,London, UK
Source: Retrieved on April 27, 2024 from mgouldhawke.wordpress.com

 The tragic events in Palestine have provided yet another happy hunting ground for Mussolini. 
 The Press announces that Arab notabilities in Lybia have sent a message to Mussolini reaffirming their solidarity with the Arabs in Palestine. This message naturally comes as a result of Mussolini’s fine words when he called himself the “defender of Islam.” On the other hand Alfred Roke, a member of the Arab Higher Committee declared to Arthur Koestler, News Chronicle special correspondent that he was expressing the opinion of the Committee, including the Mufti, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share links on your personal website like it was a socials channel]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=7564</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/share-links-personal-website-like-socials-channel/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T21:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthias Ott, writing at Own Your Web: Today, social media sites have made it seductively convenient to quickly post links that will immediately be rewarded with views, likes, and reposts. As a result, many of us seem to instinctively drop most of the interesting links we find right into the timelines of the many — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>J</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wu Zhihui and Chen Jiongming - Wu Zhihui’s Letter and Chen Jiongming’s Reply]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wu-zhihui-and-chen-jiongming-wu-zhihui-s-letter-and-chen-jiongming-s-reply?v=1715513506</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/wu-zhihui-and-chen-jiongming-wu-zhihui-s-letter-and-chen-jiongming-s-reply?v=1715513506"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T11:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Wu Zhihui and Chen Jiongming
Title: Wu Zhihui’s Letter and Chen Jiongming’s Reply
Date: May 1924
Notes: Introduced, translated, edited and annotated by Leslie H. Chen. Original Chinese versions published in Kang Baishi (1978). Chen Jiongming zhuan (A biography of Chen Jiongming). Hong Kong: Culture Book House, pp. 120–148.
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

Wu Zhihui’s Letter
 On April 29, 1924, Wu Zhihui wrote Chen Jiongming a long letter from Shanghai, in which he argued the necessity of a Chen-Sun reconciliation to save the country from disintegration. It reveals the views held by prominent members of the Nationalist Party on national affairs, politics, and political personages in China at that crucial point in modern Chin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chen Jiongming - Foreword to Minxing bao]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-foreword-to-minxing-bao?v=1715511073</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/chen-jiongming-foreword-to-minxing-bao?v=1715511073"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T10:51:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Chen Jiongming
Title: Foreword to Minxing bao
Date: 1919
Notes: Originally published in Minxing bao, in Zhangzhou, Fujian. Edited and translated by Leslie H. Chen. Excerpted from the full, original Chinese article, as printed in Wusi shiqi qikan jieshao (1959), pp. 525–529.
Source: Published in Chen Jiongming and the Federalist Movement by Leslie H. Dingyan Chen.

 The happiness of full equality is not the kind of false hope that Heaven will automatically bless every single soul on earth. Rather, it gives the human spirit the opportunity for regeneration. If we want to realize this happiness of equality and the opportunity for spiritual regeneration, there is no need for us to do any more searching. What we need is a great awakening of every mind so that all may be free of the prev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Originalism For Realists: Two Obvious Thoughts]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52684</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/originalism-for-realists-two-obvious-thoughts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T07:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looks like I haven’t posted for a couple years. Probably time to fix that! This one kicks off from a tweet I fired off, off-handedly, that led somewhere useful. “If you were wanting a paradigm case-in-point to illustrate the plausibility of legal realism, the history of legal originalism would be hard to improve on.” A […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Holbo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Abandoned restaurant complex near Mèze, France]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52680</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/12/sunday-photoblogging-abandoned-restaurant-complex-near-meze-france/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T06:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[the dust bowl]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/dust-bowl/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/dust-bowl/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T22:34:34.535Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grandpa picks up my spiral notebook filled with loopy scribbles, and I don’t stop him because I know he can’t read what I write anyway. He compliments my handwriting, which makes me feel a pang of guilt. Am I being ungrateful, spoiled when I write about my experience like this?
There is not a whole lot to do here. With my uncle gone there’s no one to take us out; while healthy, my grandparents can’t walk for very long and neither can my mom. My brother and I are useless on our own. We don’t have a data plan, can’t pay for anything because we don’t have WeChat pay set up (I think you need a Chinese bank account), and can’t even download an offline map to help us get around. If we do go out on our own we’ll have to retrace our steps by memory.
The streets are covered with a yellowish dust, w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read – A STIGLITZ ERROR?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45361</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/05/11/weekend-read-a-stiglitz-error/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T04:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford You can’t fight a war without understanding your enemy.  That’s an adage as old as war itself.  Which means it’s very old. Joe Stiglitz doesn’t understand his enemy. Now, that’s an odd thing to say bout someone who’s worldview is hardly a secret.  Stiglitz has given it his best shot for decades.  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Colin Ward - Fringe Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/colin-ward-fringe-benefits?v=1715396756</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/colin-ward-fringe-benefits?v=1715396756"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T03:05:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Colin Ward
Title: Fringe Benefits
Date: 17 June 1988 — 3 May 1996
Notes: Colin Ward’s weekly column in the journal New Statesman and Society called Fringe Benefits. Many of the titles should be read as having the words ‘Fringe Benefits:’ before it, so ‘Fringe Benefits: Back Pages’, i.e. the fringe benefits of back pages.
Source: 1. Introduction from Anarchist Seeds Beneath the Snow. Archive.org 
 <archive.org/details/Seeds_Beneath_the_Snow_9781604866674> 
 2–141. Colin Ward’s New Statesman & Society Essays — Issues 1–125. Archive.org 
 <archive.org/details/colin-wards-new-statesman-society-essays-issues-1-25> 
 <archive.org/details/colin-wards-new-statesman-society-essays-issues-26-50> 
 <archive.org/details/colin-wards-new-statesman-society-essays-issues-51-75> 
 <archive.org/deta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contrarian views]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332409/0/themoneyillusion~Contrarian-views/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332409/0/themoneyillusion~Contrarian-views/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. The FT reports that we are edging ever closer to WWIII: European intelligence agencies have warned their governments that Russia is plotting violent acts of sabotage across the continent as it commits to a course of permanent conflict with the west.&#160; Russia has already begun to more actively prepare covert bombings, arson attacks and [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332409/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-08-at-3.05.13-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332409/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6828094">“The presidents of China and Russia, Xi Jinping and Vladimir ...</a> <i>by Solon of the East</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6827778">Clerk, Thanks for those links. I am traveling now so I don't ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6827766">Harding, The Great Recession was caused by tight money. ECB ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6827703">1. Does there have to be only one ‘real threat’? Living in ...</a> <i>by Tacticus</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comment-6827643">Scott, you're right that I should try to read affirmative cases ...</a> <i>by Clerk</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/contrarian-views/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Political and aesthetic preferences]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332199/0/themoneyillusion~Political-and-aesthetic-preferences/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332199/0/themoneyillusion~Political-and-aesthetic-preferences/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The arts are often viewed as being in some sense &#8220;liberal&#8221;. This could mean many different things. Art might make people more liberal. Liberals might be more likely to make art. Liberals might be more likely to appreciate art. I don&#8217;t know enough about music to comment, but I have noticed that liberals are more [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332199/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f04%2fScreen-Shot-2024-04-25-at-6.48.54-PM.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332199/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6827460">He calls himself a right-wing liberal, LOL.   This is what ...</a> <i>by Edward</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825790">Interestingly, golf course architecture typically works in the ...</a> <i>by Steven E. Sailer</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825760">Carthaginian, Don't make it so complicated. Liberals have ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825698">SS- as both liberals and conservatives get richer they ...</a> <i>by Carthaginian</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comment-6825620">Kaleberg , Great comment. My home state is Wisconsin, and the ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/political-and-aesthetic-preferences/#comments">Plus 5 more...</a></li></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The once and future king]]></title>
        <id>https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332202/0/themoneyillusion~The-once-and-future-king/</id>
        <link href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/896332202/0/themoneyillusion~The-once-and-future-king/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T02:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So let me get this straight. The President of the United States encouraged the Chinese to build concentration camps in Xinjiang. The Chinese built concentration camps in Xinjiang. In response, we complain about human rights violations and launch a cold war that could easily turn into a hot war. Increasingly, I feel that America is [&#8230;]<div style="clear:both;padding-top:0.2em;"><a title="Like on Facebook" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/28/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/fblike20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Pin it!" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/29/896332202/themoneyillusion,https%3a%2f%2fwww.themoneyillusion.com%2fwp-content%2fuploads%2f2024%2f05%2fScreen-Shot-2024-05-04-at-3.01.13-PM-641x1024.png"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/pinterest20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Post to X.com" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/24/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/x.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by email" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/19/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/email20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a title="Subscribe by RSS" href="https://feeds.feedblitz.com/_/20/896332202/themoneyillusion"><img height="20" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/rss20.png" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;"></a>&#160;<a rel="NOFOLLOW" title="View Comments" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comments"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/comments20.png"></a>&#160;<a title="Follow Comments via RSS" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/feed/atom/"><img height="20" style="border:0;margin:0;padding:0;" src="https://assets.feedblitz.com/i/commentsrss20.png"></a>&nbsp;
<div style="clear:left;"><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comments"><h3>Comments</h3></a><ul><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6825558">Harding, Trolling is no longer cool. Get a new hobby.</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824527">Nixon actually did withdraw from South Vietnam though. I expect ...</a> <i>by Eharding</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824511">Sara, Let's see, would I believe someone not known to lie, or ...</a> <i>by ssumner</i><li><a rel="NOFOLLOW" href="https://www.themoneyillusion.com/the-once-and-future-king/#comment-6824262">Is this your monthly “I need to defend China post”?   It's ...</a> <i>by Sara</i></ul></div>&#160;</div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Money Illusion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gabriel Kuhn - The Head of SAC: Tesla Faces a ‘Stalemate’ in Sweden as the Longest Strike in Decades Grinds On]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-kuhn-the-head-of-sac-tesla-faces-a-stalemate-in-sweden-as-the-longest-strike-in-decades?v=1715385600</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/gabriel-kuhn-the-head-of-sac-tesla-faces-a-stalemate-in-sweden-as-the-longest-strike-in-decades?v=1715385600"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Gabriel Kuhn
Title: The Head of SAC: Tesla Faces a ‘Stalemate’ in Sweden as the Longest Strike in Decades Grinds On
Date: 8.5.2024
Source: Retrieved on 11 May 2024 from https://turningpointmag.org/2024/05/08/the-head-of-sac-tesla-faces-a-stalemate-in-sweden-as-the-longest-strike-in-decades-grinds-on

 Workers at Swedish service centers and dealerships of the company Tesla, best known for its electric vehicles and its celebrity billionaire owner Elon Musk, have been on strike for over five months now. The strike, which started on October 27, 2023, is the longest one in Sweden in over eighty years. 
 The strike is led by the metal workers’ union IF Metall. IF Metall is not known to be a particularly combative union. Before the Tesla conflict, no IF Metall worker had been on strike fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Region Disaster Recovery with Amazon EKS and Amazon EFS for Stateful workloads]]></title>
        <id>33ff514263343545b1e1a64d247156147200d56e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/multi-region-disaster-recovery-with-amazon-eks-and-amazon-efs-for-stateful-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T19:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Amazon Elastic File System (EFS) is a managed storage service that can be used to provide shared access to data for Kubernetes Pods running across compute nodes in different Availability Zones (AZ) managed by Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). Amazon EFS supports native replication of data across AWS Regions. This feature helps in designing a multi-Region disaster […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dumlu Timuralp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploiting other people’s madness –On sanism and Baby Reindeer (This entry contains spoilers)]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52678</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/05/10/exploiting-other-peoples-madness-on-sanism-and-baby-reindeer-this-entry-contains-spoilers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T18:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This text is not about Baby Reindeer, Netflix’s latest hit. It’s about one of the most perverse dimensions of sanism and anti-madness: the exploitation of madness as an edifying aesthetic resource. It is also about the obsolescence of narratives centered on the uncritical perspective of the traditional agent of the banality of evil, the mediocre […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Macarena Marey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finally Found the Fiction I Love]]></title>
        <id>https://sreekarscribbles.com/finally-found-the-fiction-i-love/</id>
        <link href="https://sreekarscribbles.com/finally-found-the-fiction-i-love/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T17:27:14.948Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have always been a non-fiction fan. Learning something new, diving deep into it, discussing it, and debating it—that's how I keep the curious-me happy!
However, the curious-me also wanted to explore fiction. And I did try—not once, not twice, but multiple times. Yet, I could never enjoy reading fiction.
But but but....something happened recently! I read a couple of novels—The Sun is Also a Star by Nicola Yoon, and A Man Called Ove by Fredrik Backman—and I enjoyed them!
This got me thinking—what was different this time? Why did these novels click with me?
I pondered over these questions plus all my failed attempts at fiction and I made some interesting observations:
No slow burns for me—I need the plot to keep moving!
Characters are way more interesting to me than settings. I'd rather delve into a character's life than read a bunch of scenic descriptions.
I hate high-end vocab. Simple, easy-to-understand words—that's what I prefer.
Book length doesn't bother me, but I like my chapters short and sweet—ten pages tops.
Plus, brownie points if the story has an element of suspense.
So, these are my current reading preferences, though I'm sure they'll evolve as I read more.
For now, I'm sticking to stories that match my taste, but who knows? Maybe I'll venture out of my comfort zone soon.
Right now, I'm reading Anxious People—another amazing book by Fredrik Backman. It's packed into 74 short chapters, each only a few pages long. I've breezed through about ten chapters and I'm already in love with it! 🫶]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Availability Report: April 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T17:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In April, we experienced four incidents that resulted in degraded performance across GitHub services.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://github.blog/2024-05-10-github-availability-report-april-2024/">GitHub Availability Report: April 2024</a> appeared first on <a href="https://github.blog">The GitHub Blog</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The GitHub Blog: Engineering News and Updates</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Impact]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/impact/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/impact/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:54:38.224Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A running list of things that have had a big impact on me :
Hank and John Green: Nerdfighteria is my internet home.
WaitButWhy: Deep dives into topics from first principles and cool sticky figures. Became very popular. I was one of the early ones reading the blog. Back when Tim tried to do new posts every Tuesday. Good times. Learned a lot. One of my all time favourite blogs.
Brandon Sanderson: My favourite author. Amazing fictional worlds with detailed world building. His writing literally saved me in a dark period of my life.
Staring into the singularity : The link to this was suprisingly hard to find. The orignal one taken down. I read this a long time ago. When I was around 16. Has stuck with me since.
LessWrong: Great site with awesome posts. Was about rationality back in the day. Has evolved a lot over the years. Lot of gems.
Richard Feynman's Lecture On Computation: I keep coming back to this. This man is an absolute legend. Do checkout his lectures on physics as well. His books. Everything actually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Platform of ATTAC CADTM Morocco]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Platform-of-ATTAC-CADTM-Morocco</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Platform-of-ATTAC-CADTM-Morocco"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preamble 
 The most significant manifestations of capitalist globalization involve banking crises, public and private debts, the consolidation of the debt system, alongside a myriad of other challenges such as economic, food, environmental, and political crises, migration, wars and terrorism. This globalization is considered as an implementation of liberal policies that aim to universalize market logic to all aspects of human activities at the expense of social gains and needs of the (...)
English

/ 
Morocco, 
Illegitimate debt, 
Ecology/Climate, 
CADTM, 
Private debt, 
Commercial agreements]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treasury and PNNL threat data now available for Financial sector customers to secure applications]]></title>
        <id>663cc48e20f20e000a888027</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/threat-intelligence-custom-indicator-feeds-treasury-pnnl-partnerships"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T14:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare proudly partners with the U.S. Department of the Treasury and PNNL to empower financial institutions to deploy DNS filtering policies through Cloudflare’s Gateway, using threat data from these agencies to protect against malicious links and phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alexandra Moraru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boy Igor - And Yet It Moves]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-and-yet-it-moves?v=1715348442</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/boy-igor-and-yet-it-moves?v=1715348442"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Boy Igor
Title: And Yet It Moves
Subtitle: The Realization and Suppression of Science and Technology
Date: 1985
Notes: A situationist critique of science and technology published in New York in 1985. The scan of the original edition had pages 31 or 32 & 34 missing, so text has been added from the updated edition, but ideally the original text will be found and re-added. So, text has been added between (1) "caught up in an adversary" and "to assert itself over the cult of science", plus between (2) "the terrain of pseudo-progressiveness" and "Chapter 2: The Informed Informer". <libcom.org/article/and-yet-it-moves-boy-igor>
Source: <files.libcom.org/files/2022-10/AndYetItMoves.pdf>

Introduction: The Death of Science
 Of all the spectacles science is the least attacked. In a society …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thomas Meaney: &ldquo;The Winning Side&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-winning-side</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-winning-side"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T12:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Điện Biên Phủ, seventy years on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[flying back one hour and fourteen years]]></title>
        <id>https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-tokyo-to-china/</id>
        <link href="https://tiramisu.bearblog.dev/2024-tokyo-to-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T11:46:49.743Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The plane I’m taking to China is appallingly shabby, especially after Tokyo’s sleek futurism. It’s a fitting liminal space for the transition: while I’ll miss Tokyo, I’m looking forward to not being the least put-together person on the streets. Going from understanding none of what I see and hear to about half is another plus, I suppose. (Though Tokyo has a LOT more English than where I’m going.) Still, it’ll be nice to respond to questions in the same language they’re asked without too much thought.
Seeing other tourists in Tokyo made me feel a small rush of relief, kinship. I’m not the only one lost here! Except it took me seeing a few of them to realize that when they see me, they probably don’t think the same. Fashion choices and occasional blank stare aside, I look like just another J…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>