<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-08T06:34:23.704Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-08T06:34:23.704Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Mészáros’s Critique of the State]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342387</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/on-meszaross-critique-of-the-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late István Mészáros analyzes political theories from the ancient Greek philosophers forward in Beyond Leviathan: Critique of the State, ed. and introduction, John Bellamy Foster (Monthly Review Press, 2022), 482 pp. The author’s premise is that the state and capitalism dovetail to exploit people and Mother Nature for profit, a contradiction humanity must overcome to  More
The post On Mészáros’s Critique of the State appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Sandronsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Election Will be a Win for the Military-Industrial Complex]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342284</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/the-election-will-be-a-win-for-the-military-industrial-complex/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As I write this, the day prior to the presidential election, I already know one certain outcome. Whether Kamala Harris or Donald Trump claims victory, one winner is certain: “defense” contractors. With bipartisan backing, spending on arms will continue to grow, fueling the profitability of arms manufacturers and solidifying America’s position as the top arms  More
The post The Election Will be a Win for the Military-Industrial Complex appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Houston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Architecture of Cities: Something Beautiful, Something Captured]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342328</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/architecture-of-cities-something-beautiful-something-captured/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three or maybe five Zebra Finch question the means to fornicate backwards: Eleven black crows swayed anxiously: Costumed in magpie camouflage: The bevy of black crows royal personage awaited: Adorned in baby Chinese Panda markings; three almost large orcas oscillated with stunning propulsion: The whitened arctic icebergs stood frozen: Our eyes see through our hearts:  More
The post Architecture of Cities: Something Beautiful, Something Captured appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Schulman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering Engineers with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17258</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/empowering-engineers-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background and motivation In the fast-paced world of software development, having the right tools can make all the difference. At Slack, we’ve been working on a set of AI-powered developer tools that are saving 10,000+ hours of developer time yearly, while meeting our strictest requirements for security, data protection, and compliance. In this post, we’ll…
The post Empowering Engineers with AI appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srivani Bethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving deployment visibility for Amazon ECS services]]></title>
        <id>e3489d87aec9d9472e0447501bc2b7e420782e8f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/improving-deployment-visibility-for-amazon-ecs-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying software, it’s critical to have visibility into all stages of the deployment process. Knowing the status of ongoing deployments, troubleshooting issues when things go wrong, and having an audit trail of past deployments are essential for ensuring a safe and reliable release process. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) now provides enhanced observability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great movie title drops are like clever cameo appearances]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8798</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/great-movie-title-drops-like-clever-cameo-appearances/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title Drops, by Germany based data visualisation designer and developer Dominikus Baur, analyses the number of times a movie’s title is mentioned during the story. It’s something that’s not always possible though. I’m looking at 2001: A Space Odyssey, as an example. Although if you can think of a way it could, somehow, happen, let […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who brought us Trump?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45721</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/07/who-brought-us-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Battle is joined … This might annoy some of you — it is my hasty first thought. The Democrats have been thoroughly defeated.  Deservedly so.  They no longer relate to, or reflect, the American working class.  Without building such a relationship they cannot regain power.  Nor should they. Yesterday, early on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "QNX is now free for anything non-commercial, plus there's an RPi image"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If only you could believe them.
QNX has been "opened" twice before. Each time, there was a rug pull, and it went closed again.
Before the first rug pull, open source groups routinely added QNX to their target list. There was a Firefox for QNX. Eclipse had QNX as a target. GCC and most of the Gnu command line tools could be built for QNX.
There was a desktop environment, Photon. I used that as a primary desktop for three years when working on a DARPA Grand Challenge vehicle.
All of that went away after the Harman acquisition of QNX in 2004.
Then, in 2007, QNX went open source. You could even look at the microkernel. It wasn't openly licensed, but you could look inside and build it.
In 2010, RIM acquired QNX, and, with no warning, closed the source. All open source development related to QNX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281779</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; BIden addresses the nation; Deploy the Blame Cannons!; Ventilation in schools (in Australia and the United States); Mushroom color atlas ~!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Express brokers for Amazon MSK to deliver high throughput and faster scaling for your Kafka clusters]]></title>
        <id>01d53755d355acb2eb3a13497efb3eb22cb032f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-express-brokers-for-amazon-msk-to-deliver-high-throughput-and-faster-scaling-for-your-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 3x throughput, 20x faster scaling, and 90% reduced recovery time, Express brokers deliver unmatched performance for Apache Kafka on AWS, streamlining operations while cutting infrastructure costs by 50%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Trump Presidency Might Change the Global Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281717</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-the-trump-presidency-might-change-the-global-economy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump tariffs are coming! What does that mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 3 | Strategic considerations and the political and economic situation in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third and final day of the CADTM International Council was marked by strategic discussions on the future and a presentation of the political, economic and social context in Europe. In Europe: Economic crisis and rise of the far right 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Europe, 
CI 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the latest post-quantum signature standardization candidates]]></title>
        <id>3mOPXbiTgeQHBChx4vUuMs</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/another-look-at-pq-signatures"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIST has standardized four post-quantum signature schemes so far, and they’re not done yet: there are fourteen new candidates in the running for standardization. In this blog post we take measure of them and discover why we ended up with so many PQ signatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bas Westerbaan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281756</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our foxy daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“An Honest Discussion of Covid Vaccine Side Effects Is Overdue”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281765</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/an-honest-discussion-of-covid-vaccine-side-effects-is-overdue.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with more willingness to discuss Covid side effects, most medical professionals still seem reluctant to admit to the probably frequency]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Pet from Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281755</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-to-protect-your-pet-from-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T10:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your pet more vulnerable to climate change than you might think. Some helpful suggestions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Longer-Term Treasury Yields & Mortgage Rates Explode, Yield Curve Un-Inverts Further as Bond Market Gets Spooked]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281748</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/longer-term-treasury-yields-mortgage-rates-explode-yield-curve-un-inverts-further-as-bond-market-gets-spooked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T09:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stock jockeys love Trump and bond vigilantes do not. What do their diverging views say about the prospects for the US economy?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly 1 Year Ago vs 8 Months HRT (+ Rhinoplasty)]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Same bathroom, same mirror...same person!
Yes, my glasses are taped because I'm still recovering from rhinoplasty and need to alleviate pressure off my nose.

For those who want to know:
20 sessions of laser + 4 sessions of electrolysis. Still slightly grey on upper and lower lip and continuing laser. I started Progesterone on month five instead of month six--and I shouldn't have. I was simply hurting too much and trying to rush the process. Cyproterone as T-blocker and patches for Estrogen. I'm not giving the amounts here because that's not what's important--it's your blood level concentration for T and E that you should be looking at.
Thinking I would at least like to be one cup bigger in breast growth!
Everyone tells me to imagine where I'll be in three years time and in all honesty, I don't even know where I'll be next year. I try not to think too far ahead now and just stay in the moment. :)
Ew-phoria moment: got checked out by a group of four men in a very uncomfortable way that made me run off. No thank you.
Weird moments: suddenly being asked out in the past two weeks and having crushes admitted to me by a few friends and I had to quickly and politely--but firmly--turn them down. Sorry, I'm very much taken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden’s Tardy Apology to American Indigenous Peoples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341646</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/bidens-tardy-apology-to-american-indigenous-peoples/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T07:04:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Friday, October 25, 2024, President Joe Biden formally apologized to the indigenous peoples of North America for the abuses committed against thousands of indigenous children in so-called “residential schools,” which were intended to “kill the Indian in the child.” The apology was tardy, considering that over a period of 150 years, US-government-funded boarding schools  More
The post Biden’s Tardy Apology to American Indigenous Peoples appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alfred de Zayas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Price of Eggs: Why Harris Lost to Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342068</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/the-price-of-eggs-why-harris-lost-to-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T07:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It takes some skill to make Donald J. Trump look good.  Two Democrats have succeeded in doing so: Hillary Clinton in 2016 and Kamala Harris in 2024.  The conceit of both presidential campaigns, and the belief that attacking a staggeringly grotesque moral character for being such, was laughable. (When a Clinton mocks groping philanderers and creepy molesters, one must reach for, well, the Starr Report?)  In certain countries, abominating and execrating your political adversary for being a moral defective might work.  In the United States, such figures can draw benefit from being outside the constraints of law-abiding society.  More
The post The Price of Eggs: Why Harris Lost to Trump appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Criminalizing UNRWA: How Israel is Delegitimizing the United Nations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342098</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/criminalizing-unrwa-how-israel-is-delegitimizing-the-united-nations/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:57:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On October 28, the Israeli Knesset passed a second reading of two bills that effectively ban the United Nations agency for Palestinian Refugees (UNRWA) from carrying out “any activity” in Israel and occupied Palestine. Simply put, the decision is catastrophic, because UNRWA is the main international body responsible for the welfare of millions of Palestinians  More
The post Criminalizing UNRWA: How Israel is Delegitimizing the United Nations  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Mourn, Fight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341946</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/dont-mourn-fight/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Far be it from me to claim that the US government is a democracy.  In my understanding, capitalism prevents genuine democracy because of the influence money has in elections and elsewhere throughout the political system.  This is especially true in the current monopoly phase of capitalism we call neoliberalism.  Just ask Elon Musk, the billionaire  More
The post Don’t Mourn, Fight appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I Will Fly My Flag No Longer]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342083</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/i-will-fly-my-flag-no-longer/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My father enlisted in the Navy and served in the Naval Construction Battalion, as a Navy Seabee in the South Pacific in World War II. I enlisted in the Army, graduated from OCS, and served, though not in combat, as a tank battalion staff officer during the Viet Nam War.  Our son retired as lieutenant colonel  More
The post I Will Fly My Flag No Longer appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James C. Nelson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Reality & Limits of Utopian Thinking: Not Everything Can be “Perfect”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341980</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/the-reality-limits-of-utopian-thinking-not-everything-can-be-perfect/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:50:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the idea of liberation springs to mind, I imagine an older Aunty, having migrated to the U.S. decades ago, perched on her favorite chair in her favorite room of her spacious apartment, watching her favorite Desi soap, surrounded by her grandchildren, some of them rolling their eyes at the screen. Her hands are calloused,  More
The post The Reality & Limits of Utopian Thinking: Not Everything Can be “Perfect” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sudip Bhattacharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Speech Woman vs. Zuck the Cuck: Round II]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341671</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/free-speech-woman-vs-zuck-the-cuck-round-ii/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ding! I, “Free Speech Woman,” am entering the ring for Round II of my epic legal fight with Meta, parent company of Facebook and Instagram, owned by Meta multi-owned by Meta multi-billionaire “Boy-in-the-Bubble” CEO and avid Jiu-Jitsu Blue Belt Mark Zuckerberg. To recap: I contend that when Meta’s AI “content moderation” bots censored and deactivated my Facebook profile  More
The post Free Speech Woman vs. Zuck the Cuck: Round II appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Susan Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Baltimore PD’s Spy Plane]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341468</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/on-the-baltimore-pds-spy-plane/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2020, the Baltimore Police Department had an aerial surveillance plane that could supposedly photograph and track every person in public view. Benjamin Snyder’s Spy Plane reveals what happened with this controversial policing experiment. Drawing from incredible access and direct observations inside the for-profit tech startup that ran the program for Baltimore detectives, sociologist Benjamin H.  More
The post On the Baltimore PD’s Spy Plane appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin H. Snyder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US-Iranian Scholar Excoriates the Collective West]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342009</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/us-iranian-scholar-excoriates-the-collective-west/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With increasing frequency I hear commentators on West Asia/Middle East news sites hold the Collective West responsible for genocide – ‘the crime of crimes’. Despite being appalled at my government, I winced as a New Zealander to recently hear my country described as part of the Axis of Genocide.  In Yemen US B52 bombers are  More
The post US-Iranian Scholar Excoriates the Collective West appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Lifeless Virtual Road to Nowhere]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341960</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/07/the-lifeless-virtual-road-to-nowhere/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T06:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, anything and everything either has a price or is categorized as worthless. This grander-then-grand fake binary now pervades every nook and cranny of every ecosystem on planet earth. But who decides what does and what does not have value? Is the decider even human? Or, perhaps, a Russian “bot,” or an algorithm originating on  More
The post The Lifeless Virtual Road to Nowhere appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steve Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build things]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently received an email from a reader of my blog asking about my process for building things.
I was wondering if you'd be willing to share your workflow for building products. At big companies, we'd usually do a lot of planning with diagrams, documentation, etc before building anything. I tend to get stuck in analysis paralysis when it comes to building a new products. Seeing how you've built some nice tools like Bear Blog, I wanted to hear from you personally.
I've built a lot of things over the past 10 years. Mostly to satisfy my own curiosity, with a few of them becoming actual products that fund the rest of my tinkering.
My approach to building products is more akin to a gardener than to a product developer. I play around with ideas, follow interesting threads, and see where the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by imgabe in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not about the data. It’s about a foreign government controlling the algorithm that decides what millions of people see, and their ability to shape public opinion through that.
Like imagine if China owned CNN and the New York Times and decided what stories they could publish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>imgabe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by not2b in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of the laser focus on TikTok as a threat, it would be better for the US and Canada to have real data protection laws that would apply equally to TikTok, Meta, Google, Apple, and X. What the EU has done is far from perfect but it bans the worst practices. The Chinese can buy all of the information they want on Americans and Canadians from ad brokers, who will happily sell them everything they need to track individuals' locations.
Perhaps the way to get anti-regulation politicians on board with this is for someone to do what was done to Robert Bork and legally disclose lots of personal info on members of Congress/Parliament, obtained from data brokers and de-anonymized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>not2b</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 3, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune into the vibe, ignore the opinion polls]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8795</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tune-into-vibe-ignore-opinion-polls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Cowen, writing at Marginal Revolution, last July: Democrats and leftists are in fact less happy as people than conservatives are, on average. Americans noticed this, if only subconsciously. Cowen made a whole heap of observations — I’ve quoted but one — about the then upcoming US Presidential election. But it’s tuning into the vibe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>e2bd0370eff5154573d87ca62621505e561215f8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of enhanced and expanded guidance for the AWS Well-Architected Framework with the following six pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability This release includes new best practices and improved prescriptive implementation guidance for the existing best practices. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps on reusable architecture patterns focused on specific business […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ComplexSystems in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failure is in this very common exchange
Average voter: I can't afford groceries at the store. Inflation sucks.
Response: Actually, here is the correct definition of "inflation." As you can see from the correct definition, inflation rates are now good! Hopefully this helps you understand why things will never get better.
What the average voter hears: I can't afford groceries. Your solution to this problem is to reframe the current situation as "good." I still can't afford groceries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ComplexSystems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: please make sure you're up on the site guidelines before commenting: https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html. That means editing out snark, swipes, and flamebait. Or you can simply follow this metarule, which is also in there: "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."
This thread could be worse (ok, it could be a lot worse) but I'm still noticing people breaking the rules. Please follow them instead—it will be a better experience for all of us, including yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281725</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-5-2024-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; Election 2024 roundup; Gram Parson's birthday; Welding ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America, the country I once knew]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember living in a different country as a child, hearing everyone talk about a faraway place called America.
Everyone wanted to go to America. The adults always spoke about the diversity of people there, the opportunities we could have, and the freedom we’d experience.
Even as a seven-year-old, I sensed the importance of this. Freedom mattered. At the time, we lived in a country where men and women had to walk on separate sides of the street. Women were required to cover themselves. Men and families had separate entrances and seating in restaurants. Women weren’t allowed to drive.
America was the place to be. We would get freedom there.
That was a long time ago.
Now, after living in America for over 26 years as an adult, I see less and less of what those adults once spoke about. It’s no longer the country people dream of coming to.
Today, we are a country that elects a convicted felon. A country where 71 million people chose to elect a fascist over a more than qualified woman. America is now a place where climate change, reproductive rights, and the rights of minorities are dismissed and disregarded—a country increasingly hostile toward those who are not just like them.
I am utterly and devastatingly heartbroken (and terrified).
I went to sleep knowing he would win, but I still held on to a sliver of hope. I woke up at 5 AM and saw Associated Press officially call his win.
A lot will change over these next 4 years.
Be kind to your loved ones today.
Many of us need it.
80/100
Comments and 💬 Community Echoes

No comments available but here are some 💬 Community Echoes
Re: Various election posts by reedybear
Community Commiseration by Kevin Humdrum
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the last cohort of AWS Heroes this year – November 2024]]></title>
        <id>0d594abcf3194d827b593a47f3332675a93e001a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-last-cohort-of-aws-heroes-this-year-november-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we gear up ahead of AWS re:Invent 2024, we’re thrilled to announce our final cohort of new AWS Heroes! These individuals exemplify expertise and dedication to leveraging AWS technologies and sharing knowledge. Their contributions to the AWS community are greatly appreciated, and today we’re excited to celebrate them. Ayyanar Jeyakrishnan – Bengaluru, India Machine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065765</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065765"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This will sadly be the end of FCC/FTC and all the antitrust efforts that were graining steam over the last few years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by skeuomorphism in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065473</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065473"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About 20 million votes less than the 2020 election, with about 15 million less for the democrats, and a measely 4 million less for the republicans. Thought that was interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skeuomorphism</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump wins election, leaders respond worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/trump-wins-election-leaders-respond-worldwide</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/trump-wins-election-leaders-respond-worldwide"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump wins the presidential election, prompting reactions from world leaders; NATO expresses caution about U.S. commitments; Israel welcomes his return; China remains respectful yet concerned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by niuzeta in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42064711</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42064711"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If this is what America wants, then it is what America deserves.
Political parties and candidates may sway the public one way or another, perhaps even deceive them. But in the end, it is the populace that ultimately decides.
The first time may have been a mistake, but the second time is a definite intentional.
I'm just not sure if the world deserves this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>niuzeta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Channel deflection from voice to chat using Amazon Connect]]></title>
        <id>4a012e531c71e692e94d81451466e64f58ed7579</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/channel-deflection-from-voice-to-chat-using-amazon-connect/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Sagar Bedmutha, senior solutions architect at Tata Consultancy Services, and Rajiya Patan, AWS developer at Tata Consultancy Services Service excellence helps cultivate customer satisfaction and brand loyalty. According to Gartner, one service excellence challenge is long wait times on interactive voice response (IVR) systems. Long wait times can translate into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siva Thangavel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by drawkward in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063854</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063854"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the economy, stupid:
-Inflation is not prices; it is the rate of change in prices.  Low inflation doesn't imply low prices.
-Aggregate statistics don't necessarily explain individual outcomes.
The Dems failed on this count massively, and have, for maybe the last 40 years, which is about the amount of time it took for my state to go from national bellwether (As goes Ohio, so goes the nation) to a reliably red state.  This cost one of the most pro-union Senators (Sherrod Brown) his job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>drawkward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by laniakean in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063722</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063722"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2016 : Hilary Clinton - People felt that she was chosen because it was her turn
2020 : Kamala Harris - A candidate who never ever even did well in the primaries.
I hope DNC learn from this and let people choose a candidate next time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>laniakean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netanyahu Replaces Fired Israeli Defense Minister With ‘Another Genocidal Lunatic’]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281718</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/netanyahu-replaces-fired-israeli-defense-minister-with-another-genocidal-lunatic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T14:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel's new defense minister, Israel Katz, is even more bloody-minded than the one Netanyahu sacked.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[you ever just stare at different scripts?]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/you-ever-just-stare-at-different-scripts/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/you-ever-just-stare-at-different-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@media (prefers-color-scheme: light) {
:root {
--m-left: #e9e9eb;
}
}
@media (prefers-color-scheme: dark) {
:root {
--m-left: #26252a;
}
}
.chat-container {
max-width: var(--max-width);
}
.profile-info {
display: flex;
flex-direction: column;
align-items: center;
margin-bottom: 2rem;
}
.message-image {
max-width: 100%;
border-radius: 50%;
margin-top: 5px;
min-width: 0;
}
.logo-index {
width: 50px;
}
.message {
margin: 10px 0;
display: flex;
flex-direction: column;
}
.message-right {
align-items: flex-end;
}
.message-left {
align-items: flex-start;
}
.bubble {
max-width: 70%;
padding: 8px 16px;
border-radius: 20px;
margin: 3px 0;
font-size: 16px;
word-wrap: break-word;
}
.bubble-right {
background: #007aff;
color: white;
border-top-right-radius: 4px;
}
.bubble-left {
background: var(--m-lef…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281667</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American elects its next genocidaire-in-chief as the Vatican's anime mascot finds porn fame and snow finally returns to Mt. Fuji.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Back to the Source: A Personal Reflection on Capital, Volume 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281705</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/going-back-to-the-source-a-personal-reflection-on-capital-volume-1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T11:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KLG reflects on how Marx's Capital was an important primer for him in understanding capitalism, and why it remains a seminal guide.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059842"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone living in WI who got barraged with ads from both sides, that wasn't the messaging anyone saw AFAICT. The biggest issue on people's minds was the economy. Dem messaging on economic policy was nonexistent. Women's healthcare isn't an issue that resonates with young (read: unmarried) men. It should, but it doesn't. There could have been some "look out for your wife" messaging, but there wasn't.
There's a lot of people in the comments parroting whatever narrative they cooked up for 2016, but the reality is that both candidates' approaches were wildly different this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes On The MAGA Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-the-maga-wars/</id>
        <link href="https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-the-maga-wars/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He hath returned and vanquished all despite the threat of overwhelming lawfare. Yet now begins in earnest the fierce contest to define what exactly the Last Trump administration will stand for and what will be its legacy.
Trumpism unwittingly and through organic unrest, leveraged postmodern mimetics online crashing into meatspace to vanquish the late and ailing media fiefdoms of the post-Cold War Administrative State. His uncanny charisma became a lightening rod not just for populist dissatisfaction from the dilapidated and impoverished slums of Middle America but also from within the Imperial elite from New Technocrats like Theil and Musk. Under Trumpian mimetics a MAGA working class coalesced around him, resonating with his promises to rescue Americans from corporate liberalism - mass mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by goethes_kind in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059351</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059351"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a game theoretical perspective this is a good result. It is a clear reiteration of the message to the Democrats: you won't win by claiming to be 0.1% less bad.
The Democrats should have fielded a strong personality in their own right. This is not about left or right. It's about mobilizing people by giving them something to care about. "More of the same" and "not like that guy" isn't very enticing.
I don't think the policy positions even matter that much, if you can make a strong case and gain the confidence of the electorate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>goethes_kind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aibrahem in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059017</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059017"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who spent most of his life in a dictatorship, I don’t think you appreciate how easily a society can slide into a totalitarian state and how apathetic most of the population can become.
It’s also interesting that you served in the U.S. military and didn’t recognize how self-serving and institutionally corrupt it is. I come from a country with an oversized military relative to its government, and the parallels I can draw between its behavior and that of the U.S. Army are uncanny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aibrahem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by j-krieger in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42058779</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42058779"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T09:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop calling working people without a college education stupid and stop alienating men. "Non-educated" people work just as hard or harder than the rest of us. I've been to college and the only thing it "educated" me in is Computer Science, which I majored in. I'm not in any way better as a human being than my friends working in construction. Quite the contrary, their job is far more important to society than mine. If I stopped my niche research tomorrow, no one would really care. If handymen, farmers, or truckers stopped working, there would be riots.
Also, the DNC should really stop forcing unwanted candidates down people's throats. It doesn't work, even when you spam social platforms with your narrative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>j-krieger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chronicle of a Defeat Foretold]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341881</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/chronicle-of-a-defeat-foretold/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T09:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris proved too cowardly to even address her supporters Tuesday night, as her loss to Trump became more and more inevitable. But what could she really say? She couldn't honestly say she'd run a hard campaign that championed the poor, the downtrodden, the voiceless, or that she'd fought for peace, human dignity and to fix an unraveling climate. I'd be really interested to hear her say what she thought her campaign was all about, but even Harris probably couldn't have pinpointed the purpose or the meaning of her doomed run... More
The post Chronicle of a Defeat Foretold appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody reads your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://purpleram.xyz/nobody/</id>
        <link href="https://purpleram.xyz/nobody/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if no one reads your blog, the act of writing it is clarifying, motivating and (eventually) fun. — Seth Godin
I tell myself that I blog for my own sake.
I write to express, to put thoughts out there for my own reflection.
I publish essays because it helps me tame my thinking.
And yet, that tiny toast button somehow becomes a bigger deal than it actually is.
I’d be lying if I say I don’t check the stats.
I’m a numbers guy, drawn to tracking things: expenses, books, movies, runs, etc.
Views and upvotes...
..just another metric to follow, a survey on whether anyone's reading.
A measure of... something I'm not sure anymore.
Writing has been my outlet, a habit I’ve had an on-off relationship with over the years.
In all my reasons for writing, I mostly write for myself.
I agree with Mr. Godin -- writing is clarifying, motivating and fun, even if no one's reading.
But I'll admit, it feels good knowing someone else is out there nodding along, connecting to a piece I've shared.
Imagining that somewhere, a stranger reads my words in their own quiet corner, maybe in pajamas, maybe over coffee, and smiles, resonates, or even feels a spark of recognition.
To me, that’s inspiring.
So, even if nobody reads my blog, the act of sharing still matters.
My writing is still deeply personal, a habit of expression and reflection.
And if, by chance, someone wanders in this corner of the web, that connection, however fleeting, is simply a bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Internet traffic shifts and cyber attacks during the 2024 US election]]></title>
        <id>1YyA4YHY9p5HoeHCrgO3L5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exploring-internet-traffic-shifts-and-cyber-attacks-during-the-2024-us-election"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Election Day 2024 in the US saw a surge in cyber activity. Cloudflare blocked several DDoS attacks on political and election sites, ensuring no impact. In this post, we analyze these attacks, as well Internet traffic increases across the US and other key trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New York Times Places Israel In A “Better Strategic Position”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341525</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/the-new-york-times-places-israel-in-a-better-strategic-position/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T07:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In its description of Israel’s “strategic position,” the Times has forgotten that prior to October 7, Israel’s borders were quiet, particularly the northern border with Lebanon.  Israel had domestic concerns due to Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s efforts to weaken the Israeli Supreme Court and his formation of the most right-wing government in Israel’s history.  But Israel’s economy was strong, and its economic dealings with various Arab countries due to the Abraham Accords was offering a measure of stability to the region.  There was even discussion of an Israeli-Saudi Arabian accord that would include a U.S. defense agreement with Saudi Arabia.  More
The post  The New York Times Places Israel In A “Better Strategic Position” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Divesting–and Voting–in “The End Times”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341821</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/on-divesting-and-voting-in-the-end-times/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don’t know about you, but it seems to me like these days all the right and the left can agree on is that we’re living in The End Times. We’ve got a world of right-wing mega churches and home school militias just jonesing to belly up to the bar for another shot at transforming  More
The post On Divesting–and Voting–in “The End Times” appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Desiree Hellegers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transition, What Transition? Counting the Cost of a Greener Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341329</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/transition-what-transition-counting-the-cost-of-a-greener-tomorrow/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With another annual UN Conference of the Parties (COP) on climate change starting again next week, it is worth accessing the ongoing transition from burnt fossil fuels (coal, oil, and natural gas) to manufactured renewables (wind, sun, and storage) as global warming continues to rise beyond known comfort levels. Since last year’s COP, the number-one greenhouse gas (GHG) carbon dioxide (CO2) reached 422.0 ppm up from 418.5 ppm, while the number-two GHG methane (CH4) rose from 1915.7 to 1921.8 ppb. That’s another 50 billion tons added to an  More
The post Transition, What Transition? Counting the Cost of a Greener Tomorrow appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John K. White</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruthless Settlements: BHP, Brazil and the Samarco Fundão Dam Class Action]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341846</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/ruthless-settlements-bhp-brazil-and-the-samarco-fundao-dam-class-action/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BHP Group, as with other mining giants, has much explaining to do in the way it has approached the environment.  It has become a master of the greenwashing experiment, an adept promoter of sham environmental responsibility (take, for instance, its practice of merely selling its oil and gas business to Woodside Petroleum in 2021 rather than retiring  More
The post Ruthless Settlements: BHP, Brazil and the Samarco Fundão Dam Class Action appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s Cash Grab From Patreon Harms Journalism, Advocacy, and Art]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341818</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/apples-cash-grab-from-patreon-harms-journalism-advocacy-and-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:55:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subscriber support through Patreon is a lifeline for independent artists, researchers, advocates, and journalists. I’m among the people who rely on monthly subscriptions to produce the kind of writings that don’t get aired through mainstream media, academic gatekeepers, or well-funded nonprofits. Now comes Apple’s App Store, rolling out 30% fees for new subscriptions. This affects  More
The post Apple’s Cash Grab From Patreon Harms Journalism, Advocacy, and Art appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Hall</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overshot and Kaput: Humankind Wears Out Its Welcome]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341848</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/overshot-and-kaput-humankind-wears-out-its-welcome/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When Noam Chomsky deflected questions about 9/11 — refused to speculate like a common theorist of conspiracies — but, in short, directed us to the Truth: We have bigger fish to fry and have to get to it ASAP.  No doubt, he wouldn’t deny that there were such men in the world who would be happy  More
The post Overshot and Kaput: Humankind Wears Out Its Welcome appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Kendall Hawkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Sustainability Scam: How Self-Interest Ruins Good Ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341843</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/the-sustainability-scam-how-self-interest-ruins-good-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have laws to ensure children are born into a safe, sustainable, and unpolluted environment. These laws are also meant to empower future generations and guarantee birth equity. But far from ensuring that these rights are upheld, we disfranchise children at birth because they do not have a legal say in the actions of adults that impact  More
The post The Sustainability Scam: How Self-Interest Ruins Good Ideas appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esther Afolaranmi, Carter Dillard, Beatrix Homler, and Mwesigye Robert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter from London: The Poet, the Leader, the Bishop, and the Post-Punk Maker]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341332</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/letter-from-london-the-poet-the-leader-the-bishop-and-the-post-punk-maker/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An early love of poetry kicked in after listening to Bob Dylan and reading Wilfred Owen. But there was always the Penguin Modern Poets series in which three poets were banded together in each of its 27 books. I actually rescued a copy of Penguin Modern Poets 25 with Gavin Ewart, Zulfikar Ghose and B.  More
The post Letter from London: The Poet, the Leader, the Bishop, and the Post-Punk Maker appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Reasons to Embrace the Election Results]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341892</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/top-10-reasons-to-embrace-the-election-results/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fahrenheit 451, directed by Francois Truffault with cinematography by Nicola Roeg, 1966, screeshot 1.) Dormant sales of pussy hats will rebound. 2.) Mar-a-Lago will be underwater when Baron is appointed president-for-life. 3.) Parents won’t have to consider their children’s vaccine schedules. 4.) Liz and Dick Cheney. 5.) People will discover the joys of meat packing,  More
The post Top 10 Reasons to Embrace the Election Results appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen F. Eisenman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hurricanes and Boeing Strike Depress Job Growth, But Unemployment Remains Steady]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341462</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/06/hurricanes-and-boeing-strike-depress-job-growth-but-unemployment-remains-steady/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T06:40:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The October jobs report showed little gain in hiring, with establishments adding just 12,000 jobs. The number was depressed both by the effects of the hurricanes that hit the South last month and the loss of roughly 33,000 jobs due to the strike at Boeing. The economy has now added 15.3 million jobs since President  More
The post Hurricanes and Boeing Strike Depress Job Growth, But Unemployment Remains Steady appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Infinitium reduced fraud detection time by 95% with Amazon ECS and AWS Fargate on AWS Graviton]]></title>
        <id>2e567519a3a358bb6da330f9a89fab65c95942f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-infinitium-reduced-fraud-detection-time-by-95-with-amazon-ecs-and-aws-fargate-on-aws-graviton/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was created in collaboration with Infinitium Engineering Team. Introduction Infinitium (a Euronet Company) is a leading digital payments company in Southeast Asia, specializing in secure online payment solutions and risk management services. With a strong presence across the Asia Pacific region, Infinitium offers cutting-edge technologies such as 3D Secure (3DS) authentication, fraud detection […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Surendran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Bank and IMF: 80 Years is Enough! Abolition!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/World-Bank-and-IMF-76-Years-is-Enough-Abolition</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/World-Bank-and-IMF-76-Years-is-Enough-Abolition"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Third World Debt, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by naming_the_user in "Only 5.3% of US welders are women. After years as a professor, I became one"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42056718</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42056718"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T01:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What comes across from the article to me is the class barrier more than the gender one - basically it's a posh person finding out what the "real world" looks like.
Shop talk and banter are fairly universal. Any difference is going to be a target. Thin bloke who doesn't look strong enough? Ginger hair? Tall guy, short guy? Weird tattoo, etc. Definitely the one black guy or the one white guy is going to get shit. But is it malicious? Almost certainly not.
The other thing, which in my experience is relatively common worldwide, is that working class communities are more accepting of male-female dynamics. In academia and in highbrow society the tendency is to basically sanitise every social interaction. When you're in an environment where that isn't happening then you can't suddenly ignore it any more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>naming_the_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Modern data architectures]]></title>
        <id>b2aef35d472cc9890aa4fac148154f9dc8a8154c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-modern-data-architectures-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is the fuel for AI; modern data is even more important for generative AI and advanced data analytics, producing more accurate, relevant, and impactful results. Modern data comes in various forms: real-time, unstructured, or user-generated. Each form requires a different solution. AWS’s data journey began with Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) in 2006, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMT — debunking the deficit myth]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45718</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/05/mmt-debunking-the-deficit-myth-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We have already shown that deficit spending increases our collective savings. But what happens if Uncle Sam borrows when he runs a deficit? Is that wht eats up savings and forces interest rates higher? The answer is no. The financial crowding-out story asks us to imagine that there’s a fixed supply of savings from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The music has stopped for musicians and their support workers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8793</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/music-stopped-musicians-support-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just as it is becoming near high impossible to make a full-time living as an author, unless a writer’s work is regularly topping best-seller lists, the same increasingly goes for musicians. And their support teams. Gone are the days road crews, stage hands, recording studio workers, and the like, can make a full-time living in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[by the power of bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/by-the-power-of-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/by-the-power-of-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Bear blog appreciation post.
I discovered Bear in 2023 through a Google search for minimal blogging platforms. Today, 379 days later, Bear has integrated into my routine.
I publish frequently without any pressure on the quality of my content. I write about whatever random things come to mind.
I programmatically sync my blog posts into my server to ensure I always have an archive. But I have no plans to leave Bear - as a user and observer of Herman's product garden, I'm happy to support the platform.
I also tinker with my site around Bear without compromising the web performance. I have added routes like /pics, /status, and other handy features to mgx.me. I have removed the page hits (analytics) as well.
On rare occasions, people used to message me to say they connected with a particular post. However, I later removed contact details because now I prefer observing the community from the sidelines.
Beyond writing, I've become a daily reader of Bear blog discovery feed (Most recent > Trending). I love finding interesting blog posts, especially offbeat entries and commentaries. It's become a habit I look forward to.
After a year, Bear still feels like a great fit. Herman has created the perfect blogging experience that feels fluid with my digital habits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 20,000 displaced in Paris for Olympics + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nearly-20-000-displaced-in-paris-for-olympics-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nearly-20-000-displaced-in-paris-for-olympics-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 20,000 people displaced in Paris as Olympics approach, with eviction rates rising; US voters decide on abortion rights measures in nine states for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share Your Shit]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/share-your-shit/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/share-your-shit/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:56:06.895Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to never share how I really felt, not even with my closest friends. Blogging about it would have been completely unthinkable.
On the outside, everything looked peaceful and happy. No problems here! But deep down, I felt terrible.
When I finally realized the seriousness of it and sought help, a whole new world opened up for me. I realized that I was far from alone in feeling this way. Suddenly, it no longer felt wrong or shameful, but human and understandable.
Nowadays, I'm open about both my past and during periods when I'm feeling down. I feel like it helps me, and actually others too. It creates a comforting sense of belonging and a realization that we humans are quite similar after all.
We're only human...
It's liberating to talk or write about it, it's valuable for our fellow human beings, and we can get strengthening and motivating support. A wonderful example of this is the lovely comments I received in the guestbook and on Mastodon after yesterday's post, Daunting Doubts. Thank you everyone!
I'm not saying everything is appropriate to share. I'm also not saying that you should force yourself to be open. But sharing that human "ugly and embarrassing" stuff we try to hide, I think that's very healthy and valuable.
So next time you feel lost, share your shit!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF: Fake Good News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/IMF-Fake-Good-News</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/IMF-Fake-Good-News"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early November 2024, the IMF decided to create a 25th Executive Director position. The move had been under discussion for some fifteen years, and the seat was to be given to sub-Saharan Africa. But is this really good news for Africa? Will Africa now be entitled to greater consideration in the IMF and its decision-making bodies? 
English

/ 
Africa, 
IMF, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US election part two: Trump v Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-part-two-Trump-v-Harris</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-part-two-Trump-v-Harris"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's just one day to go before the US presidential election vote and in this second part of my posts on the US economy, I shall look at the economic policies of the two main candidates. 
 In one sense, who wins matters little to big finance and big business. Both candidates are dedicated to the capitalist system and making it work better for the owners of capital. Larry Fink of BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, said he is “tired of hearing this is the biggest election in (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Capitalism, 
Imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMA - What advice would you give someone graduating from high school?]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/advice-to-graduates/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/advice-to-graduates/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The question is from Brandon - What advice would you give someone graduating from high school?
This question is a cross between what it says and what I'd like a chance to do if I were 18 all over again. It would be cool to have nearly 60 years of accumulated knowledge crammed into an 18-year old head. Let's go.
Yep, go to college
All the people out there making noise about how college isn't for everyone and that becoming a plumber or joining the army are good solid alternatives, you know the ones I'm talking about, those people are anti-education conservatives who went to college themselves and who plan on sending their children. They are trying to cover for the inability or unwillingness to make education affordable to the masses like the social democracies in Europe do—the countries that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Tiratelli <em>&amp;</em> Ali Helwith: &ldquo;Sinking Ship&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/sinking-ship</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/sinking-ship"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T09:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The logic of the Treasury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wolf at Our Door]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341513</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/the-wolf-at-our-door-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CounterPunch went online 30 years ago, just in time for Clinton’s war on Serbia. Clinton’s war was premeditated, our transit to the World Wide Web was reluctant, at best. Alexander Cockburn’s relationship with computers was hostile. Mine was indifferent. I surfed the web, like anyone else, but had no idea how it would be useful for us. At the time, CounterPunch was a 6-page newsletter that we published fortnightly. We called it “fortnightly” because the word had a nice ring to it and no one was precisely sure how many days or even weeks a fortnight encompassed. But if we ran pieces online, who would pay to receive our newsletter? We remained stubbornly committed to print and our 5,000 or so subscribers. Where will the web be when the electromagnetic pulse wipes the slate clean? More
The post The Wolf at Our Door appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Person, One Vote, One Joke…on Democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341279</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/one-person-one-vote-one-joke-on-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Americans, we hold dear several core democratic values, none more basic than “one person, one vote.” But our contemporary economic realities have essentially obliterated this core value’s essence. “One person, one vote,” we’re relearning this year, simply cannot exist in an America where a single individual can hold 1.4 million times more wealth than  More
The post One Person, One Vote, One Joke…on Democracy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Africa’s Memorial to the ICJ: More Evidence on Israel’s Genocide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341518</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/south-africas-memorial-to-the-icj-more-evidence-on-israels-genocide/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a media statement from its Department of International Relations and Cooperation dated October 28, the South African government announced its filing of a Memorial to the ICJ pertaining to its ongoing case against Israel.  The Memorial itself runs into 750 pages, with 4000 pages of supporting exhibits and annexes.  (Its December 2023 application had run into 84 pages.)  “The problem we have is that we have too much evidence,” remarked South Africa’s representative to The Hague, Ambassador Vusimuzi Madonsela to Al Jazeera. More
The post South Africa’s Memorial to the ICJ: More Evidence on Israel’s Genocide appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Air Force Doesn’t Want Us to Notice on Election Night]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341554</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/what-the-air-force-doesnt-want-us-to-notice-on-election-night/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:56:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much significance will happen at the end of Election Day, and a countdown will begin at 11:00 p.m. PDT on November 5th. While everyone’s attention will be on who our next president will be, the U.S. The Air Force will test-launch an Intercontinental Ballistic Missile with a dummy hydrogen bomb on the tip from Vandenberg  More
The post What the Air Force Doesn’t Want Us to Notice on Election Night appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leah Yananton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Planned, Socialist Economy Works: The Economic Success of China]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341512</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/a-planned-socialist-economy-works-the-economic-success-of-china/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overnight American conservatives have gone from “socialism can’t work, communism can’t work” to “watch out–the Chinese Communist Party is taking over the world!” Yet few seem to see the unresolvable contradiction between these two views.  Over the past four decades China has risen from the third world to possessing the world’s second-largest Gross Domestic Product. How?  More
The post A Planned, Socialist Economy Works: The Economic Success of China appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Glenn Sacks</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private School Helped Make Me a Socialist]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341521</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/05/private-school-helped-make-me-a-socialist/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T06:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a famous quote, attributed to various people, that says, “If a man is not a socialist by the time he is 20, he has no heart. If he is not a conservative by the time he is 40, he has no brain.” I’m a few years shy of 40. While I’m more of champagne  More
The post Private School Helped Make Me a Socialist appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jon Hochschartner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Times publishes stinging rebuke of Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8789</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/new-york-times-publishes-stinging-rebuke-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the eve of the US Presidential election, The New York Times has published a strongly worded dis-endorsement of Republican candidate Donald Trump. It’s short, succinct, and well worth reading. Unlike counterpart publications, including The Washington Post, and Los Angeles Times, The New York Times issued an endorsement of Democrat candidate Kamala Harris, at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtrack Discoverability on Bandcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/soundtrack-discoverability-on-bandcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/soundtrack-discoverability-on-bandcamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:44:39.747Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know how, for the past however many years, Bandcamp has had a little Discovery chart at the bottom that tracks best-selling albums in various categories?
Well, now it looks a bit like this:
There's something very weird to me about hiding the discoverability of albums behind a series of links without any...you know, albums on display.
The biggest thing to me, however, is the categories chosen & what seems very noticeably omitted... Soundtracks are nowhere to be found. Game music is a huge part of Bandcamp's presence, and game soundtracks have always felt like an embarrassing little side-effect of Bandcamp's popularity. Nearly every editorial focuses on indie hits, the big hitters that've come to the platform, etc. etc... Yet somehow, Epic bought Bandcamp at one point in time before it w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On caring for my ADHD instead of fighting it]]></title>
        <id>https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/caring-for-my-adhd/</id>
        <link href="https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/caring-for-my-adhd/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of you probably know that I have ADHD. I talk about it fairly often.
I didn't get diagnosed until somewhat recently, because, as is the story for a lot of women with ADHD, my symptoms as a little girl were different than the ones that were typically recognized, AKA the ones that young boys tend to exhibit more often. I was incredibly messy: my desks, lockers, backpacks, and bedroom tended to be absolute chaos. I lost things like homework and winter gloves a lot. I was constantly spacing out and daydreaming. I was generally kind of weird and bad at conversations.
But I wasn't disruptive or hyperactive, and I got good grades despite my problems with remembering to do homework, so my symptoms weren't seen as symptoms. They were flaws. I didn't need help, I just needed to try to be bette…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Hartog Book Of The Year 2024 shortlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8782</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/harry-hartog-book-year-2024-shortlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian indie bookseller Harry Hartog has entered the literary prize fray with their inaugural Book Of The Year award. A shortlist featuring three titles, in three categories respectively, fiction, non-fiction, and children’s and young adults, was published a few days ago. No surprise to see Intermezzo by Sally Rooney nominated in fiction. Nor All I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda, Amazon Bedrock, Amazon Redshift, Amazon CloudWatch, and more (Nov 4, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>a9e737b930cb419056cfc7211b775ff3ac6718b0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-amazon-bedrock-amazon-redshift-amazon-cloudwatch-and-more-nov-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spooky season has come and gone now. While there aren’t any Halloween-themed releases, AWS has celebrated it in big style by having a plethora of exciting releases last week! I think it’s safe to say that we have truly entered the ‘pre’ re:Invent stage as more and more interesting things are being released every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by horsawlarway in "We're Leaving Kubernetes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42042999</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42042999"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personally - just let the developer own the machine they use for development.
If you really need consistency for the environment - Let them own the machine, and then give them a stable base VM image, and pay for decent virtualization tooling that they run... on their own machine.
I have seen several attempts to move dev environments to a remote host.  They invariably suck.
Yes - that means you need to pay for decent hardware for your devs, it's usually cheaper than remote resources (for a lot of reasons).
Yes - that means you need to support running your stack locally.  This is a good constraint (and a place where containers are your friend for consistency).
Yes - that means you need data generation tooling to populate a local env.  This can be automated relatively well, and it's something you need with a remote env anyways.
---
The only real downside is data control (ie - the company has less control over how a developer manages assets like source code).  I'm my experience, the vast majority of companies should worry less about this - your value as a company isn't your source code in 99.5% of cases, it's the team that executes that source code in production.
If you're in the 0.5% of other cases... you know it and you should be in an air-gapped closed room anyways (and I've worked in those too...)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>horsawlarway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dbalatero in "New York Times Tech Guild goes on strike"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42041331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42041331"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T13:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is context on the strike, how long it's been brewing, and more that I happened to read yesterday:
https://www.thenation.com/article/archive/the-new-york-times...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbalatero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vladimir Putin: godfather and federator of the international far right!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Vladimir-Putin-godfather-and-federator-of-the-international-far-right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Vladimir-Putin-godfather-and-federator-of-the-international-far-right"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T10:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The subject of this article is not Putin the warmonger, nor Putin the invader of Ukraine. The subject of this article is Putin, the anti-democrat, the reactionary and the liberticide with increasingly fascist practices. So, after presenting the first pillar of the Brown International in gestation in the person of Israeli genocidaire Bibi Netanyahu, and awaiting the third who would be a Donald Trump all haloed by a possible success in the American elections in a few days' time, here is (...)
English

/ 
Russia, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "A change of heart regarding employee metrics"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038912</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038912"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T05:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>> [Why not build programmer performance measurement tooling?] It's the job of a manager to know what their reports are up to, and whether they're doing a good job of it, and are generally effective. If they can't do that, then they themselves are ineffective, and that is the sort of thing that is the responsibility of THEIR manager, and so on up the line.
Agreed wholeheartedly, but for slightly different reasons. To wit, laziness and Goodhart's law. [0]
In the absence of infinite time, automation will excuse a lack of manager curiosity, as other competing tasks absorb the freed time.
Consequently, most managers with automated dashboards showing performance metrics won't use those dashboards... plus all the person-to-person work they were previously doing. They'll only use those dashboards.
Which then slowly but inexorably turns your employees into dashboard-optimization drones via operant conditioning.
Helping a colleague doesn't show up on the dashboards? Fuck that. Digging into what looks like a security vulnerability isn't on the sprint board? Fuck that.
Which is incredibly corrosive to quality, creative system design.
And then, because this is the work reality you've created, the creative folks you really want working there bail for greener pastures, and you're left with bottom of the barrel talent and retention problems.
[0] https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Goodhart's_law]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[remove xiaomi bloatwares using adb on linux]]></title>
        <id>https://perdana.dev/remove-xiaomi-bloatwares-using-adb-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://perdana.dev/remove-xiaomi-bloatwares-using-adb-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xiaomi offers smartphones with great hardware at affordable price but pre-installed some apps i don't need. some of them can be easily uninstalled, but some need additional effort. these are the steps to remove the craps using adb:
setup
enable usb debugging on the device:
download adb command line tool:
wget https://dl.google.com/android/repository/platform-tools-latest-linux.zip
unzip platform-tools-latest-linux.zip
cd platform-tools/

connect the device to computer via usb, a pop up should appear on the device asking to allow the computer to perform usb debugging, tap ok.
then run this command to ensure the device is online:
./adb devices

if the device is listed as offline, try unplugging, disable usb debugging on the device, reenable, and replug it.
open adb shell to control/interact …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by biotechbio in "Scientists glue two proteins together, driving cancer cells to self-destruct"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038317</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038317"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T04:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a decent amount of cynicism in the comments, which I understand. I think this is a really cool and novel study, though.
Historically, cancer was treated with therapies that are toxic to all cells, relying on the fact that cancer cells divide quickly and are unable to handle stress as well as normal cells (chemotherapy, radiation).
The last couple of decades we've seen many targeted cancer therapies. These drugs generally inhibit the activity of a specific protein that lets the cancer cells grow (e.g. EGFR inhibitors) or prevents the immune system from killing the cancer cells (e.g. PDL1 inhibitors).
This mechanism is way more interesting. The gene BCL6 is usually turned on in immune cells when they are mutating to recognize foreign invaders. This process involves lots of DNA damage and stress, but BCL6 stops the cells from dying and is therefore important for normal immune function. Unfortunately, this makes BCL6 a gene that is often co-opted in cancer cells to help them survive.
The method cleverly exploits the oncogenic function of BCL6 not by inhibiting it, but by turning it into a guide, enabling the delivery of activating machinery to the targets of BCL6 and reversing the inhibitory effects on cell death.
The whole field of targeted degraders, molecular glues, and heterobifunctional molecules is a growing area of interest in cancer research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>biotechbio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lost in my own head about making art]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/lost-in-my-own-head-about-making-art/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/lost-in-my-own-head-about-making-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[for some reason, i've fantasized for years about being the kind of artist who always travels around with their iPad Pro by their side, ready to sketch and work on a moment's notice. when i sit down and actually deconstruct this fantasy, it becomes abundantly clear that it's completely unrealistic for me, and born out of incredibly shallow desires.
there's nothing wrong with people who do that. they're not shallow. it's the digital equivalent to carrying a sketchbook with you, and it's certainly more portable and intuitive to use than other digital art mediums.
but there's this mental disconnect i keep experiencing. for a long time - even when i was well into college! - people regarded my preferred medium and my job as some kind of witchcraft. "what, so the computer does all the work for yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NaNoWriMo, NaBloPoMo, and WeblogPoMo AMA, November hots up]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8776</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/nanowrimo-nablopomo-weblogpomo-ama-november/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Novel Writing Month AKA NaNoWriMo, is on this month, for better or worse. But if you’re a writer seeking distractions from various November happenings — I’m referring more to northern hemisphere inhabitants facing the onset of winter — and don’t want to write a novel, there are other options. National Blog Posting Month AKA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vijay Prashad: &ldquo;Yellow Butterflies&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/yellow-butterflies</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/yellow-butterflies"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Garcia Márquez’s Colombia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by praptak in "Touchscreens are out, and tactile controls are back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033987</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033987"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touchscreens are anti-accessibility.
Lack of tactile feedback for the sight-impaired is the obvious part but there is another thing:
Touchscreens just stop registering your touch when you get old. The older you get the less moisture there's in your skin, which at some point makes touch screens ignore you.
https://www.gabefender.com/writing/touch-screens-dont-work-f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>praptak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Dwedit in "Touchscreens are out, and tactile controls are back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033914</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033914"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The worst of both worlds is Touch Buttons.  No screen, just a touch-sensitive surface that's divided into areas that activate upon any kind of skin contact, whether intentional or not.
I always see my dishwasher having some bizarre setting active because of accidental contact with a touch button.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwedit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[daily projects]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/daily-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/daily-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i follow an artist on Tumblr who’s been doing a daily drawing since 2008.
they’re mostly self portraits.
his work is expressive, somewhat childlike, and genuine.
sometimes he shows pictures of all his notebooks lined up neatly on a wall shelf. years of daily moments recorded with pencils and other colorful media.

linus-malmqvist
a couple of things inspire me:
along with his daily drawings that he posts, he writes a few lines about his day. they’re short snippets of thoughts or daily happenings that leave the reader wanting more.
ex:
18 September 2024 
Onsdag

The logs arrive, I can now start building my house. 

the other thing that encourages me creatively is that he’s been doing this project since 2008. that’s a long time. It astounds me that more people aren’t liking his drawings.
the number of likes on his work doesn’t seem to faze him.
he just continues drawing, sharing his work, and not making things more complicated than they need to be.
he loves to draw, so he does it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US presidential election: part one – the economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-US-presidential-election-part-one-the-economy</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-US-presidential-election-part-one-the-economy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T09:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am doing two posts before the US presidential election on Tuesday. The first is on the state of the US economy; and the second will be on the respective economic policies of the two main candidates, Democrat Kamala Harris and former Republican President Donald Trump. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Crisis, 
Capitalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Nîmes, the Maison Carrée]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53350</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/03/sunday-photoblogging-nimes-the-maison-caree/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T09:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best thing about deleting my youtube history]]></title>
        <id>https://ani.bearblog.dev/the-best-thing-about-deleting-my-youtube-history/</id>
        <link href="https://ani.bearblog.dev/the-best-thing-about-deleting-my-youtube-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've deleted my youtube watch history and paused it.


friend was a bit annoyed that he couldn't see my youtube recommendations anymore, but I take this as an absolute win.
Now all I have to waste time with is my subscription tab, which is much less frequent in content I actually want to consume.
As always on bearblog, being more mindful on what you consume is a good thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step-by-Step Guide to Show Webmention Interactions on Bear Blog]]></title>
        <id>https://yordi.me/step-by-step-guide-to-show-webmention-interactions-on-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://yordi.me/step-by-step-guide-to-show-webmention-interactions-on-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post shows how to use the Webmention.io API to display all the interactions people have had with your blog posts.
You’ll need two things to make this work:
Your website must be set up to use the Webmention.io service.
You’ll need a bit of custom JavaScript to show the interactions below each blog post.
Setting up Webmention.io itself is outside the scope of this post, as this website already provides detailed instructions.
Now, let’s move on to the custom JavaScript you’ll need.
The JavaScript Code
Below is the complete JavaScript code. I’ll explain how each part works after the code.
if (document.querySelector("body").classList.contains("post")) {
  function setContent(child) {
    switch (child["wm-property"]) {
      case "in-reply-to":
        return child.content?.text;
      cas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one year of linux: a personal retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/one-year-of-linux-a-personal-retrospective/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/one-year-of-linux-a-personal-retrospective/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T01:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it's been (almost) a year since i started using Linux as my primary OS! i just double checked, and apparently i installed Linux Mint on my laptop at the end of November, not the beginning of November. but i was in the mood to write about it now, so whatever. who cares. it's my blog!!
my laptop shipped with Windows 11, and i was getting increasingly frustrated with it. it felt sluggish and unnecessarily unresponsive, despite the fact that my laptop's specs were "Decidedly Fine". between that, and needing something in my life to obsess over and fixate on, i decided to take the leap and try out Linux.
and, well. about half a year later, i ended up killing my Windows 11 partition altogether, and running Linux Mint full time. there's been pros and cons. i'll get to that.
when people usually wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by baazaa in "Get me out of data hell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42030101</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42030101"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T23:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People always say this guy just has had bad luck with his employers but I live in Melbourne and work in data and reckon the whole industry is a scam.
Like why didn't anyone catch the issue with the logs? Because it doesn't matter, every data team is a cost-centre that unscrupulous managers use to launch their careers by saying they're big on AI. So nothing works, no-one cares it doesn't work, most the data engineers are incapable of coding fizzbuzz but it doesn't matter.
People always wonder why banks etc. use old mainframes. There's like a 0% success rate for new data projects. And that 0% includes projects which had launch parties etc. but no-one ever used the data or noticed how broken it was. I don't think a lot of orgs which use data as core-infra could modernize, the industry is just so broken at this point I don't think we can do what we did 30 years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>baazaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[´Fryslan boppe´. An in-depth inspirational analysis of work rewarded with the 2024 Riksbank prize in economic sciences.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45703</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/02/fryslan-boppe-an-in-depth-inspirational-analysis-of-work-rewarded-with-the-2024-riksbank-prize-in-economic-sciences/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T22:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction< The 2024 Sveriges Riksbank Prize for Economic Sciences has been awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson for work on the influence of institutions on long-term economic progress and growth. Much has been written about this, for instance by ´Pseudoerasmus´ here and by Radford here. In this article, an ´in-depth´ analysis of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botswana's ruling party defeated after 58 years + 4 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/botswana-s-ruling-party-defeated-after-58-years-4-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/botswana-s-ruling-party-defeated-after-58-years-4-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UN warns of an apocalyptic crisis in northern Gaza; the EU allocates €160 million to bolster Ukraine’s energy; the US and South Korea form a security framework; North Korea tests a threatening missile; Botswana's political landscape shifts after decades of BDP rule.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bear blog css playground]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/bear-blog-css-playground/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/bear-blog-css-playground/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your browser does not support the video tag.
 

bear.css.observer takes any subdomain from subdomain.bearblog.dev and splits the screen into two panels. On the left is a live preview of the blog content. On the right is an editor where you can tweak the CSS in real-time. As you type, the changes are instantly applied to the preview panel on the left.
To make things more user-friendly, I included some themes that users can select from a dropdown menu. This allows for quick testing of different looks and formatting options without writing CSS from scratch. Submit your theme here.
Once you're happy with the styling, you will have a couple options. You can click a button to save the style sheet to localStorage for future sessions. Or you can copy the CSS directly from the editor to your clipboard, making it easy to paste into your bear blog's theme customization area. You can export it as a .css file as well.
Admittedly, it's a silly project, but I thought some people might find it handy to preview styles throughout their site (including inner pages) without mucking about with Overrides.
Note: bear.css.observer is set to <meta name="robots" content="noindex">, and the Playground data is stored in your browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DeathArrow in "My Time Working at Stripe"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42024884</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42024884"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T08:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>he asked the team, “for this meeting I’d like us to try and introduce ourselves a little differently. If you’re comfortable, I’d like us to try and be 10% more vulnerable than we normally would in a work setting.” I remember feeling a mix of anxiety and excitement rise in my chest. I sat pondering what I would share. I decided to go for more than 10%. I shared about how my marriage had almost collapsed a couple years prior and a taste of how painful it was. Some of my coworkers shared deeper things I’d never heard in a work setting. It was awkward. It was beautiful.
I'd rather not have my manager forcing me to do group therapy. I owe the company some work hours and they own me money.
If I want to have personal relations with someone from my work, befriend somebody, share personal things, that is my choice. My personal life is not the company business.
Of course I wouldn't say all that to the manager, but 'I'll put him on the list of people I should be careful about, and fake some confessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DeathArrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundi - The Consequences to Rahtid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T07:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fundi
Title: The Consequences to Rahtid
Date: February 1974
Notes: Transcribed from Documents of the Caribbean Revolution (Tunapuna: New Beginning, 1974) by Matthew Quest and Ryan Cecil Jobson.*
Source: Retrieved on 2024-11-02 from medium.com/clash-voices-for-a-caribbean-federation-from-below/joseph-edwards-the-consequences-of-rahtid-february-1974-71bdbe7668e6

Joseph Edwards, a Jamaican refrigeration mechanic, spoke of radical labor politics in Rasta idioms. Let’s reason “to Rahtid!”
His selected writings have been published as Workers Self-Management in the Caribbean (2014). When we read his ideas comparatively with Trinidad’s CLR James, Guyana’s Walter Rodney, and Jamaica’s Michael Manley and Trevor Munroe we can begin to see the antagonisms or debates within the Caribbean radic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundi - Union Versus Menegement]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-union-versus-menegement?v=1730521629</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-union-versus-menegement?v=1730521629"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T04:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fundi
Title: Union Versus Menegement
Date: 1970s
Notes: Transcribed by Mutt.
Source: Retrieved on 2 November 2024 from <organisemagazine.org.uk/2024/11/01/union-versus-menegement-joseph-edwards-theory-and-analysis>

This piece, authored by Joseph Edwards—also known as Fundi or the Caribbean Situationist—offers a unique perspective within the anti-authoritarian tradition of the Caribbean left.
Assumed to be the first publication of the Trinidadian labor organizing group, The New Beginning Movement (NBM) (1971–1978), this booklet was released as Abeng Pamphlet No. 1. The NBM drew inspiration from the Black Power Revolt and the legacy of C.L.R. James, applying his concepts of workers’ autonomy and self-management to forge a Pan-Caribbean International that extended links to Canada, th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ipsum2 in "Nvidia to join Dow Jones Industrial Average, replacing Intel"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42023402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42023402"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T01:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia would've acquired the culture of Intel, so it wouldn't be the company it was today if that happened.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ipsum2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless containers at AWS re:Invent 2024]]></title>
        <id>314d84d81ceb7ad31834e8a50e051e84e05cca98</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/serverless-containers-at-aws-reinvent-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T22:24:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Invent is the premier learning conference hosted by AWS for the global cloud computing community. This year the Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) and AWS Fargate teams will share the latest trends, innovations, best practices, and tips to help you increase productivity, optimize costs, and enhance business agility. Join us in Las Vegas […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henrique Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning for Anthropic’s Claude 3 Haiku model in Amazon Bedrock is now generally available]]></title>
        <id>f4c8ebbba2f21c6bef599b672f6fee9619d9b320</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/fine-tuning-for-anthropics-claude-3-haiku-model-in-amazon-bedrock-is-now-generally-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T21:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock Anthropic's Claude 3 Haiku model's full potential with Amazon Bedrock's fine-tuning for enhanced accuracy and customization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AJR, Nobel, and prompt engineering]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45700</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/01/ajr-nobel-and-prompt-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T20:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Well done AJR.  A prize deserved.  And remarkably little grumbling.  What’s wrong with that? In other news, my wife is deep into creating an artificial intelligence application.  One of the great challenges of getting AI to be useful is something called ‘prompt engineering’.   What have these two snippets of news have […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing serverless observability with Python]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3fe6f0a5bc1d</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/enhancing-serverless-observability-with-python-3fe6f0a5bc1d?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2024-11-01T18:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Key strategies and tools to leverage Python for effective serverless observability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>