<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-06-19T02:20:20.295Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-06-19T02:20:20.295Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 18, 2025 (#571)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22976</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/18/daily-reading-list-june-18-2025-571/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-19T00:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at a new "cloud finder" API, what has a bigger impact than AI coding tools on your team, and writing docs for an AI world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Texas Is the MAGA vs RINO Frontline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294169</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-texas-is-the-maga-vs-rino-frontline.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T18:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Texas is the 3rd largest US state. It's been under GOP rule for 21 years and a civil war is brewing between MAGA and RINO factions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nat Wilson Turner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Real Reason For French Collapse At The Outset Of WWII]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAMG5h0SO4_cDgHXhozxgmi"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T17:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I doubt one in ten of you know the importance of the Battle of the Marne? Quite simple, had the French plus a smallish-medium but crucial contigent of soldiers from the UK, not halted the invading Germans at the Marne, the 20th century would have looked very different. Sure, von Moltke the Younger lost his nerve and pulled two corps from his right flank, shipped East to help fend off the Russian hordes. But, the French were glorious at the Marne and each and every one of us owe a debt a gratitude to France for the elan and courage.
As Holger Herwig writes in The Marne, 1914, “At dawn on 6 September, 980,000 French and 100,000 British soldiers with 3,000 guns assaulted the German line of 750,000 men and 3,300 guns [across a front stretching from] Verdun and Paris.” The Miracle of the Marne …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine and Iran: two fronts of a piecemeal world war]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/ukraine-and-iran-two-fronts-of-a"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T15:51:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Ukraine war and the Israel-Iran conflict are not separate crises, but interlinked fronts in a piecemeal world war — one that pits the US against a de facto alliance of of Russia, Iran and China]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US Continues To Accelerate Its Decline (+Iran)]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBReBtKyLuElNXNG0663HWa"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T14:11:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wavered between writing another Iran war update and this article, so I’ll say a few things about the Iranian war. There’s evidence that Israeli intelligence networks in Iran and elsewhere are being compromised fast. It appears that:
In simple terms:
Israel’s attack on Iran exposed a hidden network. For 25 years, India’s RAW and Israel’s Mossad have worked together using Indian tech workers across the Gulf as quiet access points into sensitive infrastructure. This network runs through millions of Indian… https://t.co/zkJRVuSoPx
— Thomas Keith (@iwasnevrhere_) June 17, 2025


 
That India, a Hindu/Brahmin supremacists state which is increasingly treating its minorities the way Israel used to treat Palestinians before it went full genocidal is allied this deeply with Israel is not a surpris…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Economic Consequences of the Second Trump Administration: A Preliminary Assessment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294212</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-economic-consequences-of-the-second-trump-administration-a-preliminary-assessment.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An overview of the economic  impact of Trump's second term flurry from some Serious Economists. They don't find much to like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Log Explorer is now GA, providing native observability and forensics]]></title>
        <id>kg7dxMzYcRnJdVFrxQmCw</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/logexplorer-ga/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are happy to announce the General Availability of Cloudflare Log Explorer, a powerful product designed to bring observability and forensics capabilities directly into your Cloudflare dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jen Sells</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/18/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294121</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-18-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T10:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our punchy daily links: dodgy drugs, wild weather, Israel takes pounding, Iran says more to come, Trump threats pause, AI cognition dangers, WaPo hacked, Senators want Palantir info, UK food costs rise, Trump's China smartphone]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ancients: What Can They Teach Us About Our World and How to Live in It?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294171</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/the-ancients-have-much-to-teach-us-about-living-in-our-modern-world-if-we-will-only-listen.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T10:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently added a new volume to my Shelf of Little Books, some of which are not so little but all of which repay re-reading that helps me understand our world a little better with each successive encounter.  The newest resident of the shelf was published earlier this year by Princeton University Press: Following Nature’s […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>KLG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rob Urie: As Goes Iran, So Goes Humanity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294196</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/rob-urie-as-goes-iran-so-goes-humanity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T10:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussing the risk of nuclear escalation in Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plans for More Intense Censorship if US Joins Israel Attack on Iran?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294189</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/plans-for-more-intense-censorship-if-us-joins-israel-attack-on-iran.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T07:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Twitter post gives a credible forecast of the intensification of censorship that is in store if the US directly attacks Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect any React application to an MCP server in three lines of code]]></title>
        <id>4gk3k2ZiTN6DZoHu3e090r</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/connect-any-react-application-to-an-mcp-server-in-three-lines-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're open-sourcing use-mcp, a React library that connects to any MCP server in just 3 lines of code, as well as our AI Playground, a complete chat interface that can connect to remote MCP servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dina Kozlov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 17, 2025 (#570)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22952</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/17/daily-reading-list-june-17-2025-570/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-18T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at the expanded family of Gemini models, why you should "trust but verify" with AI in engineering, and why developers hate their tech stack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combining technology, education, and human connection to improve online learning]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/caitlin-morris-combines-tech-education-human-connection-improve-online-learning-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/caitlin-morris-combines-tech-education-human-connection-improve-online-learning-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Caitlin Morris, a PhD student and 2024 MAD Fellow affiliated with the MIT Media Lab, designs digital learning platforms that make room for the “social magic” that influences curiosity and motivation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Denise Brehm | MIT Morningside Academy for Design</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking the bias of large language models]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/unpacking-large-language-model-bias-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/unpacking-large-language-model-bias-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a new study, researchers discover the root cause of a type of bias in LLMs, paving the way for more accurate and reliable AI systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Zewe | MIT News</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A sounding board for strengthening the student experience]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/sounding-board-for-strengthening-student-experience-0617</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/sounding-board-for-strengthening-student-experience-0617"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Composed of “computing bilinguals,” the Undergraduate Advisory Group provides vital input to help advance the mission of the MIT Schwarzman College of Computing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danna Lorch | MIT Schwarzman College of Computing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tariq Ali: &ldquo;Nuclear Options&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/nuclear-options</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/nuclear-options"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T18:45:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regime change in Tehran?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coffee Break: Armed Madhouse – Israel’s Ominous Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294045</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/coffee-break-armed-madhouse-long-term-prospects-for-israel.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T18:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fog of war is thick over the current hostilities between Israel and Iran, but the intense interest in short-term outcomes of this regional war may be obscuring the ultimate prospects for Israel as negative trends undermine its militaristic foreign policy. I will describe these trends and the likely outcome. Loss of International Support The […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haig Hovaness</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS re:Inforce roundup 2025: top announcements]]></title>
        <id>b0ad377a4e23c937899926a46ac90dab8f257761</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-reinforce-roundup-2025-top-announcements/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T17:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At AWS re:Inforce 2025 (June 16-18, Philadelphia), AWS Vice President and Chief Information Security Officer Amy Herzog delivered the keynote address, announcing new security innovations. Throughout the event, AWS announced additional security capabilities focused on simplifying security at scale and enabling organizations to build more resilient applications in the cloud. Below is a comprehensive roundup […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AWS News Blog Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon GuardDuty expands Extended Threat Detection coverage to Amazon EKS clusters]]></title>
        <id>0c90d66a232b00eab18ce300f6d25e027a484483</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-guardduty-expands-extended-threat-detection-coverage-to-amazon-eks-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T16:26:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Expanded Amazon GuardDuty Extended Threat Detection for EKS clusters uses proprietary correlation algorithms to identify sophisticated multi-stage attack sequences across Kubernetes audit logs, container runtime behaviors, and AWS API activities through a new critical severity finding type: AttackSequence:EKS/CompromisedCluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unify your security with the new AWS Security Hub for risk prioritization and response at scale (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>e19fa07e98e5b8e9021afdf4e6d3f14f45d064b0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/unify-your-security-with-the-new-aws-security-hub-for-risk-prioritization-and-response-at-scale-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:57:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Security Hub has been enhanced with new capabilities that integrate multiple AWS security services to automatically discover resources, evaluate risks, analyze attack paths, and provide AI-assisted recommendations, helping security teams prioritize critical issues and respond to threats at scale with improved visualization and remediation guidance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Backup adds new Multi-party approval for logically air-gapped vaults]]></title>
        <id>5b49911bc7d41842e56590335b8e7b3615f3ef6c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-backup-adds-new-multi-party-approval-for-logically-air-gapped-vaults/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:50:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-party approval for AWS Backup logically air-gapped vaults enables organizations to recover their backup data even when their AWS account is compromised, by creating approval teams of trusted individuals who can authorize vault sharing with a recovery account through a separate authentication path.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Veliswa Boya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AWS Shield feature discovers network security issues before they can be exploited (Preview)]]></title>
        <id>5235df10e9121e0b8997ba6595bb1f96974c7419</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/new-aws-shield-feature-discovers-network-security-issues-before-they-can-be-exploited-preview/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T15:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shield network security posture management automatically discovers and analyzes network resources across AWS accounts, prioritizes security risks based on AWS best practices, and provides actionable remediation recommendations to protect applications against threats like SQL injections and DDoS attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon CloudFront simplifies web application delivery and security with new user-friendly interface]]></title>
        <id>c26dbe5841b16834450965e43bc3fd061d2cf760</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-cloudfront-simplifies-web-application-delivery-and-security-with-new-user-friendly-interface/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:52:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Try the simplified console experience with Amazon CloudFront to accelerate and secure web applications within a few clicks by automating TLS certificate provisioning, DNS configuration, and security settings through an integrated interface with AWS WAF's enhanced Rule Packs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Certificate Manager introduces exportable public SSL/TLS certificates to use anywhere]]></title>
        <id>55aea14f37e97eabeffd376d045f1bb3711feb1b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-certificate-manager-introduces-exportable-public-ssl-tls-certificates-to-use-anywhere/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can now use AWS Certificate Manager to issue exportable public certificates for your AWS, hybrid, or multicloud workloads that require secure TLS traffic termination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Verify internal access to critical AWS resources with new IAM Access Analyzer capabilities]]></title>
        <id>2bdebfa050d44d96737015f5a4beb4aa5a038a8a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/verify-internal-access-to-critical-aws-resources-with-new-iam-access-analyzer-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T14:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new capability in IAM Access Analyzer helps security teams verify which principals within their AWS organization have access to critical resources like S3 buckets, DynamoDB tables, and RDS snapshots by using automated reasoning to evaluate multiple policies and provide findings through a unified dashboard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Micah Walter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laith Marouf on Iran’s Escalatory Path and Its Expectations of a Long War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294130</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/laith-marouf-on-irans-escalatory-path-and-its-expectations-of-a-long-war.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T13:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lebanon-based jouranlist Laith Marouf provides some granular detail on Iran's and Israel's operations and what might come next in the war]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 6/17/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294048</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/links-6-17-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T10:55:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our boisterous daily links: Ozempic babies, new Covid wave, UK geoengineering weapons freakout, Trump loses mind on Iran, Iran gets Iron Dome to self sabotage? US abandoning Ukraine, immigration flp-flop, AI pollution, sacrificing for the rich,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Peak Palantir]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=294020</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/06/palantirs-perfect-world.html"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T10:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The company that " knows everything about you" is going from strength to strength as war rises and and the so-called "liberal" West turns into a dystopian novel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eskandar Sadeghi-Boroujerdi: &ldquo;Culmination&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/culmination</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/culmination"/>
        <updated>2025-06-17T09:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel attacks Iran.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 16, 2025 (#569)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22932</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/16/daily-reading-list-june-16-2025-568/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T23:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how Netflix does a unified data architecture, the role of the "agent architect", and security strategies for prompts and agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating an academic-industry collaboration to advance vehicle technology]]></title>
        <id>https://news.mit.edu/2025/celebrating-academic-industry-collaboration-advance-vehicle-technology-0616</id>
        <link href="https://news.mit.edu/2025/celebrating-academic-industry-collaboration-advance-vehicle-technology-0616"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIT Advanced Vehicle Technology Consortium marks a decade of developing data that improve understanding of how drivers use and respond to increasingly sophisticated automotive features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mackenzie Berry | MIT AgeLab | MIT Center for Transportation and Logistics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS re:Inforce 2025, AWS WAF, AWS Control Tower, and more (June 16, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>bfdcfd4bce1293e4116e091dbb0771283c97ada6</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-reinforce-2025-aws-waf-aws-control-tower-and-more-june-16-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the start of AWS re:Inforce 2025, where security professionals are gathering for three days of technical learning sessions, workshops, and demonstrations. This security-focused conference brings together AWS security specialists who build and maintain the services that organizations rely on for their cloud security needs. AWS Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) Amy Herzog will […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Esra Kayabali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Israeli War Update]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtKUgRKU9mY9fEERM4J_G7</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItBtKUgRKU9mY9fEERM4J_G7"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T14:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take this in steps.
Air Defense Iranian air defense was not active for the first attack wave. They were online for the second one, about six hours later. It’s unclear why. I have heard two credible claims. The first is that they were hit by a cyber-attack, but came online faster than the Israelis expected.
The second is that the Iranians deliberately played rope-a-dope. The first attack was largely a matter of stand-off munitions, which the Israelis have (had) very limited supplies of. The Iranians tanked that hit, counting on the fact that most military targets were underground and hardened. Then when the second attack happened, which required close in attack, the air defenses were turned on. Because they had not been compromised in the first attack (air defense use makes air defens…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not in our name]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/not-in-our-name</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/not-in-our-name"/>
        <updated>2025-06-16T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The real threat to Europe doesn’t come from Moscow — but from Israel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 15, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAzAnFPhbO16HLDoD_XO2aE</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItAzAnFPhbO16HLDoD_XO2aE"/>
        <updated>2025-06-15T18:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Week-end Wrap – Political Economy – June 15, 2025
by Tony Wikrent
 
 
 
Trump not violating any law
‘He who saves his Country does not violate any Law’
 
Trump Stuns By Saying ‘I Don’t Know’ When Asked Directly NBC’s Kristen Welker ‘Don’t You Need to Uphold the Constitution?’
Joe DePaolo, May 4th, 2025 [mediaite.com]
 
Why is Kristi Noem’s bone-chilling pledge of a “regime change” in Calif not getting media coverage?!  Trump wants to remove Democrats from office
Dean Obeidallah, June 13, 2025
But what has been largely ignored in the reporting was the bone-chilling comment that sparked Padilla to interrupt Noem during her press conference. In prepared remarks, Noem delivered a message from Trump that the military occupation of Los Angeles and beyond will not end until both Governor Gavin Ne…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCRm0S8IqqIxR-Jwg1rdqYt</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItCRm0S8IqqIxR-Jwg1rdqYt"/>
        <updated>2025-06-14T11:24:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use to discuss topics unrelated to recent posts (no Iran/Israel.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 13, 2025 (#568)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22905</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/13/daily-reading-list-june-13-2025-568/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T23:19:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at multiple patterns to consider for an agent use case, recommendations for agentic coding, and great management tips for dealing with conflict.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel’s attack on Iran: a calculated escalation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/israels-attack-on-iran-a-calculated</id>
        <link href="https://www.thomasfazi.com/p/israels-attack-on-iran-a-calculated"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T15:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israel bombs Tehran — to start a war, and win back Western support]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Fazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran Has Been Hit Hard By Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDVJb-ddItbPmrsb1yf7rO_</id>
        <link href="https://api.follow.it/track-rss-story-click/v3/niyBMplQItDVJb-ddItbPmrsb1yf7rO_"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T12:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The senior commanders of the air and missile forces are dead, and so is the commander of the Revolutionary Guard. Multiple nuclear sites were hit, plus civilian targets.
Iran previously threatened that if Israel hit their nuclear program, they would hit Israel’s nuclear sites in retaliation.
Iran’s leadership are incompetent. That statement will enrage some readers and commenters, but they have allowed their allies to be taken out one by one, they have not yet launched significant retaliation, and their current actions, sending a hundred drones to attack Israel, are pathetic. It is no favor to them to pretend their strategy is working: it is clearly failing.
They should have had a plan for an immediate, overwhelming counter-attack. Iran’s missile force is massive and has proven able to pen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Welsh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Model Context Protocol with Amazon Q Developer for context-aware IDE workflows]]></title>
        <id>a1102756c01f6a0553e01be9d19e920bb65c0763</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/use-model-context-protocol-with-amazon-q-developer-for-context-aware-ide-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T00:07:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier today, Amazon Q Developer announced Model Context Protocol (MCP) support in their Integrated Development Environment (IDE) plugins for Visual Studio Code and JetBrains. This allows developers to connect external tools or MCP servers to Q Developer, enabling more context-aware responses and complex workflows. MCP support has already been available in Amazon Q Developer for […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ritik Khatwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare service outage June 12, 2025]]></title>
        <id>2dN6tdkhtvWTTgAgbfzaSX</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-service-outage-june-12-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Cloudflare services, including Workers KV, Access, WARP and the Cloudflare dashboard, experienced an outage for up to 2 hours and 28 minutes on June 12, 2025.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeremy Hartman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer Java Upgrades: A Deep Dive into the New Selective Transformation Feature]]></title>
        <id>c7d18058f0ff9e75b45d295501a515f7bdfa9860</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-java-upgrades-a-deep-dive-into-new-selective-transformation-feature/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T21:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of Java development, keeping applications up-to-date while minimizing risk has become increasingly challenging. Amazon Q Developer transformation capabilities now support customization of Java upgrades in Java upgrade transformation CLI (command line interface) with a new selective transformation feature. Selective transformation empowers development teams with greater control over their modernization journey. Instead […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venugopalan Vasudevan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daily Reading List – June 12, 2025 (#567)]]></title>
        <id>http://seroter.com/?p=22891</id>
        <link href="https://seroter.com/2025/06/12/daily-reading-list-june-12-2025-567/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T19:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's links look at how you can uncover "tells" for AI-generated text, how to understand cloud service accounts, and whether to use MCP or APIs for your AI agents.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Seroter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May 2025 (version 1.101)]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_101</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_101"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code May 2025 Release (1.101)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>