<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-11-08T18:33:24.868Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-11-08T18:33:24.868Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China unveils $1.4 trillion stimulus package + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-unveils-1-4-trillion-stimulus-package-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/china-unveils-1-4-trillion-stimulus-package-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T17:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China launches a $1.4 trillion fiscal package to support its economy; Earth is set to experience its hottest year ever, exceeding 1.5 degrees Celsius.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[For-Profit Academic Publishers Love LLM Garbage]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53370</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/08/for-profit-academic-publishers-love-llm-garbage/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T16:28:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite metasciences lines is: “Does anyone look around and say…things are going great, I just think we need MORE PAPERS?” Obviously, we all want more scientific progress, better evidence, broader scope — but I don’t think that this is best accomplished by churning out more of these fancy peer-reviewed pdfs. Indeed, our systems […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Munger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNC Doubles Down on Failure, Rejecting Sanders’ Calling Out Party for Abandoning Workers and Economic Justice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281848</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/dnc-doubles-down-on-failure-rejecting-sanders-calling-out-party-for-abandoning-workers-and-economic-justice.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T15:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quelle surprise! Some Democratic party leaders double down, denying Sanders was right and kicking workers and the poors is not a good strategy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we prevent conflicts in authoritative DNS configuration using formal verification]]></title>
        <id>5LVsblxj2Git54IRxadpyg</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/topaz-policy-engine-design"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We describe how Cloudflare uses a custom Lisp-like programming language and formal verifier (written in Racket and Rosette) to prevent logical contradictions in our authoritative DNS nameserver’s behavior.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Larisch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Weekend read – Logic and truth in economics]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45724</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/08/weekend-read-logic-and-truth-in-economics/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T12:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll To be ‘analytical’ and ‘logical’ is something most people find recommendable. These words have a positive connotation. Scientists think more deeply than most other people because they use ‘logical’ and ‘analytical’ methods. In dictionaries, logic is often defined as “reasoning conducted or assessed according to strict principles of validity” and ‘analysis’ as […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/8/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281830</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-8-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:58:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our fat-free daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After Weeks of Political Chaos and Uncertainty, Mexico’s Judicial Coup Fizzles to Nothing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281777</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/after-weeks-of-chaos-and-uncertainty-mexicos-judicial-coup-fizzles-to-nothing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T11:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President Claudia Sheinbaum, her governing party, Morena, and arguably Mexico as a whole just dodged a rather large bullet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Age of Presidential Unilaterism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281829</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/a-new-age-of-presidential-unilaterism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T10:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A historical look at Presidential power grabs, um, authority expansion, with an eye to what that means under Trump 2.0.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Local and Federal Institutions Are (and Aren’t) Taking Care of North Carolina’s Hurricane Helene Survivors—and What Mutual Aid Groups Are Doing to Help]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281827</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-local-and-federal-institutions-are-and-arent-taking-care-of-north-carolinas-hurricane-helene-survivors-and-what-mutual-aid-groups-are-doing-to-help.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T10:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Grassroots organizations are helping rebuild North Carolina communities after Hurricane Helene. And how about FEMA?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The problem is the nation-state]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53366</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/08/the-problem-is-the-nation-state/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T09:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Obviously people are shocked, and particularly shocked at the rejection of normal sensible politics by the rubes who have elected an oaf, a criminal and a rapist to the White House, again. But the trouble is that this kind of thing keeps happening, or nearly happening, and not just in the United States. And it […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Crack-Up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342191</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/the-crack-up/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T07:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final weeks of the campaign, Trump amplified his anti-war rhetoric. Why? According to the New York Times, internal polling showed that still undecided voters were "six times as likely as other battleground-state voters to be motivated by their views of Israel’s war in Gaza." Either the Harris campaign missed this lurking demographic or, more likely, just didn't care. Of course, Trump's still going to give Netanyahu the greenlight to burn Gaza, the West Bank and southern Lebanon to the ground and then target Iran. More
The post The Crack-Up appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Descent Into Fascism Can Be Stopped]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342148</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/americas-descent-into-fascism-can-be-stopped/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T07:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it’s clear that American society changed dramatically with Reagan’s election and the corrupt rise of the billionaire elite, we must also recognize how liberals and the Democratic Party, instead of resisting, aligned with Wall Street power brokers like Goldman Sachs. In doing so, they adopted elements of neoliberalism that crushed the working class, intensified the class and racial divide, accelerated staggering levels of inequality, and intensified the long lacy of nativism,  all of which fed into the conditions for Trump’s appeal. More
The post America’s Descent Into Fascism Can Be Stopped appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Henry Giroux</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Trump Won]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342187</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/how-trump-won/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump won the  2024 Presidential election with the politics of fear carried by entertaining media, particularly the digital media anarchy that cultivated audiences with messages that were instantaneous, personal, and visual. Recurring media messages that the economy was the deciding factor dismiss the resounding Republican fears about crime and immigration. Economy was also a main issue in the 2020 election, but according to Pew researchers, “Among Trump supporters, the economy (93%), immigration (82%) and violent crime (76%) are the leading issues.” More
The post How Trump Won appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Altheide</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Long History of Palestine – Why Palestinians are Winning the Legitimacy War]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342356</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/the-long-history-of-palestine-why-palestinians-are-winning-the-legitimacy-war/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Oddly, it was Israeli historian Benny Morris who got it right, when he offered a candid prediction of the future of his country and its war with the Palestinians. “The Palestinians look at everything from a broad, long-term perspective,” he said in an interview with the Israeli newspaper Haaretz in 2019. “They see that, at  More
The post The Long History of Palestine – Why Palestinians are Winning the Legitimacy War  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Walking Along the Border on Election Day]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342338</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/walking-along-the-border-on-election-day/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The man was sitting on a bench in front of the 20-foot rust-colored border wall near where the public buses passed. He was jotting in a small notebook in the bustling center of Nogales, Sonora. It was Tuesday, Election Day in the U.S. I approached him and told him I was a journalist and was interested in what he thought about the election in the United States, especially since the border—which I pointed to right before us—was one of the election’s biggest issues. His answer was terse: “It’s another country.” More
The post Walking Along the Border on Election Day appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Todd Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump II: a Pre-Mortem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342172</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/trump-ii-a-pre-mortem/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Without Democrats left in the Senate, House of Representatives, White House or on the Supreme Court, the Trumpublicans can now turn to the business for which they are best suited: that of devouring their own. Even before January 20, 2025—that great day when all the Jan 6 rioters will stream out of their prison cells  More
The post Trump II: a Pre-Mortem appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Stevenson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billionaires Own US Climate Policy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342164</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/billionaires-own-us-climate-policy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:57:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Billions of dollars will buy almost anything anybody wants, and on November 5th billions of dollars bought the world’s leading anti-climate-change political administration, aka: the Trump Administration, which is anti-almost-everything, except for a free reign to the almighty market. Price determines policy, and it buys political office. According to Americans for Tax Fairness, 150 billionaire  More
The post Billionaires Own US Climate Policy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Hunziker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump, His MAGA Followers and Societies Gone Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341938</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/trump-his-maga-followers-and-societies-gone-wild/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:56:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s not wait for historians to analyze the Trump era and ask; Are Trump and his MAGA followers aberrations in American history or manifestations of a significant autocratic leitmotif of American historical fascism? Individuals can have bad days and stretches of unusual, destructive behavior. But what about societies democratically choosing to be led autocratically? When  More
The post Trump, His MAGA Followers and Societies Gone Wild appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Warner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody Wants to Join BRICS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341787</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/everybody-wants-to-join-brics/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s one thing the recent BRICS summit in Kazan revealed, it’s that when you divide the world into the West and the Rest, the Rest is a lot bigger and quite alienated from the western oligarchy. Much of the Rest also wants to join BRICS. After all, it’s a good deal: A way to  More
The post Everybody Wants to Join BRICS appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eve Ottenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Antiwar Promise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342363</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/trumps-antiwar-promise/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cambridge, UK  As the voting results started coming in here from Virginia at 4 am (GMT, which is five hours later than Eastern Time in the US), I went to bed, having seen enough to know that Kamala Harris’s  crash campaign for the White House was failing. I knew what was coming.  I’d experienced it  More
The post Trump’s Antiwar Promise appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Lindorff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Age of Presidential Unilaterism?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342358</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/a-new-age-of-presidential-unilaterism/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the dust settles over election day, it’s worth reflecting that it’s not only the election results that have been at stake, but the future of the presidency and its powers. Over the course of the first quarter of this century, the American presidency has accumulated ever more power, rendering the office increasingly less constrained  More
The post A New Age of Presidential Unilaterism? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen J. Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the Matter with the U.S. of A?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342268</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/whats-the-matter-with-the-u-s-of-a/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Democrats lick their wounds after the resounding defeat of Kamala Harris, the main question remains how did this country get here? Make America Great Again captured the misogyny and racist impulse of those Americans who felt suffocated by liberal impetus for diversity–– a corporate diversity oblivious toward social justice and redistributive politics. The  More
The post What’s the Matter with the U.S. of A? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Behrooz Ghamari Tabrizi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Macbeth Had Ambition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342044</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/macbeth-had-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I will support and defend the Constitution of the United States against all enemies, foreign and domestic; that I will bear true faith and allegiance to the same; that I take this obligation freely, without any mental reservation or purpose of evasion; and that I will well and faithfully discharge the duties of the office  More
The post Macbeth Had Ambition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph Natoli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Troops in Europe: Do They Put Pyongyang at Risk?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342253</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/north-korean-troops-in-europe-do-they-put-pyongyang-at-risk/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:53:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea is sending 12,000 soldiers to Russia to help Moscow in the prolonged Russia-Ukraine war. It is one of the most unexpected developments in and around the Korean peninsula recently. It is as startling for South Korea as when it first encountered the North’s nuclear development program back in 1993. This is the first-ever  More
The post North Korean Troops in Europe: Do They Put Pyongyang at Risk? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaemin Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Victory and Elite Power Over the Democratic Party]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342262</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/trumps-victory-and-elite-power-over-the-democratic-party/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of quotes, separated by eight years, spotlight a chronic political mentality at the top of the Democratic Party: “The path to victory in a state like Michigan, Harris campaign officials are betting, is through suburban counties that are home to many college-educated and white voters,” the New York Times reported three weeks ago. “For every blue-collar  More
The post Trump’s Victory and Elite Power Over the Democratic Party appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Norman Solomon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starving a Nation: The US’s Vengeful Siege on Cuba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342251</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/starving-a-nation-the-uss-vengeful-siege-on-cuba-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:53:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over a year after the Cuban Revolution’s resounding victory, a secret memo from Deputy Assistant Secretary of State for Inter-American Affairs, Lester Mallory, dated 6 April 1960, exposes the cold calculus behind the United States’ decision to impose a trade embargo on Cuba. Mallory’s covert words reveal the brutal truth: Fidel Castro’s revolution enjoys  More
The post Starving a Nation: The US’s Vengeful Siege on Cuba appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilantha Ilangamuwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No She Couldn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342447</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/no-she-couldnt/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is hard now to think back beyond Tuesday night. But I do remember that when I heard “Yes She Can” on Monday afternoon, released that day by the ardent Democrat, will.i.am, I felt that the song was a surer sign than any poll or pundit’s prediction that Kamala Harris’s White House bid was doomed.  More
The post No She Couldn’t appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Yearsley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“America Against America”  or The Night of the Living Dead Democracy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342458</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/america-against-america-or-the-night-of-the-living-dead-democracy/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Don’t expect civilization here… This is a brutal place… It may be that the centers of government were always this way and now we’ve merely pulled off the mask, exposing the truth of the matter.” – The White Plague, by Frank Herbert, 1982) “So, at this point there is no really authentic way for us  More
The post “America Against America”  or The Night of the Living Dead Democracy appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Saul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Be Like Claud Cockburn: Tell Truths to the Masses]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342107</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/be-like-claud-cockburn-tell-truths-to-the-masses/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I never cared for the expression, “Telling Truth to Power,” but didn’t know why. Now I do. In a review of a book by Patrick Cockburn about his father Claud, the reviewer, Neal Ascherson, writes that Claud “disbelieved strongly the axiom about telling truth to power” because the “rulers of the earth” didn’t give a  More
The post Be Like Claud Cockburn: Tell Truths to the Masses appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonah Raskin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Calls to Scrap Land-Based Missiles Growing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342282</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/calls-to-scrap-land-based-missiles-growing/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pentagon is preparing to replace all of today’s 400 long-range, land-based nuclear-armed missiles with a new missile dubbed “Sentinel.” In the face of widespread expert criticism of the expensive replacement, the new intercontinental ballistic missiles (ICBMs) are being built by Northrup Grumman to replace 400 Minuteman III missiles now in underground launch silos spread  More
The post Calls to Scrap Land-Based Missiles Growing appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Race, Class, and Inequality: A New Study]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342361</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/race-class-and-inequality-a-new-study/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a recent op-ed, Lydia Polgreen said that if Kamala Harris is labeled as a DEI candidate, then J. D. Vance must be as well. She supports this with research from a Tufts University scholar who claims that elite schools, like Yale, where Mr. Vance graduated law school, give extra attention and resources to poor  More
The post Race, Class, and Inequality: A New Study appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John O'Kane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starving a Nation: The US’s Vengeful Siege on Cuba]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342050</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/starving-a-nation-the-uss-vengeful-siege-on-cuba/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just over a year after the Cuban Revolution’s resounding victory, a secret memo from Deputy Assistant Secretary of State for Inter-American Affairs, Lester Mallory, dated 6 April 1960, exposes the cold calculus behind the United States’ decision to impose a trade embargo on Cuba. Mallory’s covert words reveal the brutal truth: Fidel Castro’s revolution enjoys  More
The post Starving a Nation: The US’s Vengeful Siege on Cuba appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nilantha Ilangamuwa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Native Americans Guarded Their Societies Against Tyranny]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341734</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/how-native-americans-guarded-their-societies-against-tyranny/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:47:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the founders of the United States designed the Constitution, they were learning from history that democracy was likely to fail – to find someone who would fool the people into giving him complete power and then end the democracy. They designed checks and balances to guard against the accumulation of power they had found  More
The post How Native Americans Guarded Their Societies Against Tyranny appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen DuVal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Puerto Rico Elections Show Upswing of Popular and Independence Movements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342239</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/puerto-rico-elections-show-upswing-of-popular-and-independence-movements/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The special significance of elections taking place in Puerto Rico on November 5 was evident beforehand. A commentator detected from opinion polls that, “This election already is historic. It already marks a before and an after.” For the first time ever, a gubernatorial candidate of the Puerto Rican Independence Party (PIP) was successfully challenging the candidates of the  More
The post Puerto Rico Elections Show Upswing of Popular and Independence Movements  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>W. T. Whitney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Relief in Sight for Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342349</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/no-relief-in-sight-for-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no reason to write about the election, the future, or to bend my imagination into a receptacle able to contain and contemplate the suffering ahead.  The world has its own momentum, its own secrets and a collection of beating hearts that align in strange patterns. There are already lots of writers eager to  More
The post No Relief in Sight for Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phil Wilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Articles on Netanyahu’s Support of Hamas Before October 7 and on Israeli Women Soldiers’ Warnings of a Possible Hamas Attack Being Ignored]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342158</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/articles-on-netanyahus-support-of-hamas-before-october-7-and-on-israeli-women-soldiers-warnings-of-a-possible-hamas-attack-being-ignored/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are news stories that can be found in unexpected places that deserve much greater attention and should be frequently cited. One such article was in the New York Times on December 10, 2023 under the title ‘Buying Quiet’: Inside the Israeli Plan That Propped Up Hamas.  A second example was published by Hadassah, The  More
The post Articles on Netanyahu’s Support of Hamas Before October 7 and on Israeli Women Soldiers’ Warnings of a Possible Hamas Attack Being Ignored appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Baum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst the Darkness, a Few Bright Spots in the Fight Against Inequality]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341949</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/amidst-the-darkness-a-few-bright-spots-in-the-fight-against-inequality/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:44:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever questioned whether our country has an inequality problem, this election should provide all the evidence you need. As billionaires used their financial firepower to throw support their preferred candidates’ way, Americans who’ve been left behind took out their frustrations at the ballot box. How do we get started on this next chapter  More
The post Amidst the Darkness, a Few Bright Spots in the Fight Against Inequality appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Anderson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Fencing China Out is Washington Fencing Itself In?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=341783</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/341783/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:43:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Washington doubles down on its semiconductor embargoes, a troubling paradox emerges: in trying to stymie China’s technological advances, the United States might just be fencing itself in. Each successive restriction aims to choke off China’s progress, specifically in artificial intelligence and high-performance chips. Yet these measures risk isolating the United States from global tech  More
The post In Fencing China Out is Washington Fencing Itself In? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Imran Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Has Happened Here]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342244</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/it-has-happened-here-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a dialogue in Woody Allen’s Stardust Memories (1980) when Allen’s character, Sandy Bates, a filmmaker, begins a discussion with a group of aliens in a pastoral setting. The scene is very funny because the lines the alien speaks have to do with the quality of love, the value of Sandy’s older movies, and how Sandy  More
The post It Has Happened Here appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Howard Lisnoff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Mourn, Organize]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=342181</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/11/08/dont-mourn-organize/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T06:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A phrase attributed to labor organizer Joe Hill is fitting for this moment:  “Don’t Mourn.  Organize.”  Or in the words of writer Ed Abbey, “Sentiment without action is the ruin of the soul.” During the last Trump Administration our small, gritty organization, the Alliance for the Wild Rockies, sued the Trump Administration 18 times to  More
The post Don’t Mourn, Organize appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Garrity</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Month of Chronic Migraines]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-month-of-chronic-migraines/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/a-month-of-chronic-migraines/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T01:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have had the worst migraines the past couple of weeks (months?). As someone who suffers from chronic migraines (for the past 15+ years), I track my headaches and migraines to ensure that the latest medications I’m on are actually working.
In the past month, I’ve had 13 migraines, and a few headaches.
These migraines are absolutely debilitating. Some of them include a migraine aura1, while a few did not. During these times, if I’m lucky, all I need to do is ensure I am in a dark enough room, take my abortive migraine medication, follow my usual migraine self-care routine, and hope the pain passes quickly enough. If I’m not so lucky, then nausea also comes into the picture. I’ll spare you the details because that’s just messy.
When these attacks happen during the weekend, I’m typically jus…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empowering Engineers with AI]]></title>
        <id>https://slack.engineering/?p=17258</id>
        <link href="https://slack.engineering/empowering-engineers-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-08T00:19:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Background and motivation In the fast-paced world of software development, having the right tools can make all the difference. At Slack, we’ve been working on a set of AI-powered developer tools that are saving 10,000+ hours of developer time yearly, while meeting our strictest requirements for security, data protection, and compliance. In this post, we’ll…
The post Empowering Engineers with AI appeared first on Engineering at Slack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Srivani Bethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving deployment visibility for Amazon ECS services]]></title>
        <id>e3489d87aec9d9472e0447501bc2b7e420782e8f</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/improving-deployment-visibility-for-amazon-ecs-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T22:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying software, it’s critical to have visibility into all stages of the deployment process. Knowing the status of ongoing deployments, troubleshooting issues when things go wrong, and having an audit trail of past deployments are essential for ensuring a safe and reliable release process. Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) now provides enhanced observability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olly Pomeroy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Great movie title drops are like clever cameo appearances]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8798</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/great-movie-title-drops-like-clever-cameo-appearances/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T21:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Title Drops, by Germany based data visualisation designer and developer Dominikus Baur, analyses the number of times a movie’s title is mentioned during the story. It’s something that’s not always possible though. I’m looking at 2001: A Space Odyssey, as an example. Although if you can think of a way it could, somehow, happen, let […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who brought us Trump?]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45721</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/07/who-brought-us-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T20:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Peter Radford Battle is joined … This might annoy some of you — it is my hasty first thought. The Democrats have been thoroughly defeated.  Deservedly so.  They no longer relate to, or reflect, the American working class.  Without building such a relationship they cannot regain power.  Nor should they. Yesterday, early on the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>peterradford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Animats in "QNX is now free for anything non-commercial, plus there's an RPi image"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42079976"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If only you could believe them.
QNX has been "opened" twice before. Each time, there was a rug pull, and it went closed again.
Before the first rug pull, open source groups routinely added QNX to their target list. There was a Firefox for QNX. Eclipse had QNX as a target. GCC and most of the Gnu command line tools could be built for QNX.
There was a desktop environment, Photon. I used that as a primary desktop for three years when working on a DARPA Grand Challenge vehicle.
All of that went away after the Harman acquisition of QNX in 2004.
Then, in 2007, QNX went open source. You could even look at the microkernel. It wasn't openly licensed, but you could look inside and build it.
In 2010, RIM acquired QNX, and, with no warning, closed the source. All open source development related to QNX…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Animats</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 11/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281779</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/200pm-water-cooler-11-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, Syndemics; BIden addresses the nation; Deploy the Blame Cannons!; Ventilation in schools (in Australia and the United States); Mushroom color atlas ~!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Express brokers for Amazon MSK to deliver high throughput and faster scaling for your Kafka clusters]]></title>
        <id>01d53755d355acb2eb3a13497efb3eb22cb032f5</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-express-brokers-for-amazon-msk-to-deliver-high-throughput-and-faster-scaling-for-your-kafka-clusters/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T18:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With 3x throughput, 20x faster scaling, and 90% reduced recovery time, Express brokers deliver unmatched performance for Apache Kafka on AWS, streamlining operations while cutting infrastructure costs by 50%.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun (윤석찬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Trump Presidency Might Change the Global Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281717</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-the-trump-presidency-might-change-the-global-economy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump tariffs are coming! What does that mean?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM International Council | Day 3 | Strategic considerations and the political and economic situation in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-International-Council-Day-3-Strategic-considerations-and-the-political"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:31:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third and final day of the CADTM International Council was marked by strategic discussions on the future and a presentation of the political, economic and social context in Europe. In Europe: Economic crisis and rise of the far right 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Europe, 
CI 2024 EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM International, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the latest post-quantum signature standardization candidates]]></title>
        <id>3mOPXbiTgeQHBChx4vUuMs</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/another-look-at-pq-signatures"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIST has standardized four post-quantum signature schemes so far, and they’re not done yet: there are fourteen new candidates in the running for standardization. In this blog post we take measure of them and discover why we ended up with so many PQ signatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bas Westerbaan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 11/7/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281756</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/links-11-7-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:58:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our foxy daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“An Honest Discussion of Covid Vaccine Side Effects Is Overdue”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281765</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/an-honest-discussion-of-covid-vaccine-side-effects-is-overdue.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T11:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even with more willingness to discuss Covid side effects, most medical professionals still seem reluctant to admit to the probably frequency]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Pet from Climate Change]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=281755</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/11/how-to-protect-your-pet-from-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T10:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your pet more vulnerable to climate change than you might think. Some helpful suggestions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exactly 1 Year Ago vs 8 Months HRT (+ Rhinoplasty)]]></title>
        <id>https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/</id>
        <link href="https://ninecoffees.blog/exactly-1-year-ago-vs-8-months-hrt-rhinoplasty/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Same bathroom, same mirror...same person!
Yes, my glasses are taped because I'm still recovering from rhinoplasty and need to alleviate pressure off my nose.

For those who want to know:
20 sessions of laser + 4 sessions of electrolysis. Still slightly grey on upper and lower lip and continuing laser. I started Progesterone on month five instead of month six--and I shouldn't have. I was simply hurting too much and trying to rush the process. Cyproterone as T-blocker and patches for Estrogen. I'm not giving the amounts here because that's not what's important--it's your blood level concentration for T and E that you should be looking at.
Thinking I would at least like to be one cup bigger in breast growth!
Everyone tells me to imagine where I'll be in three years time and in all honesty, I don't even know where I'll be next year. I try not to think too far ahead now and just stay in the moment. :)
Ew-phoria moment: got checked out by a group of four men in a very uncomfortable way that made me run off. No thank you.
Weird moments: suddenly being asked out in the past two weeks and having crushes admitted to me by a few friends and I had to quickly and politely--but firmly--turn them down. Sorry, I'm very much taken.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I build things]]></title>
        <id>https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/</id>
        <link href="https://herman.bearblog.dev/how-i-build-things/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently received an email from a reader of my blog asking about my process for building things.
I was wondering if you'd be willing to share your workflow for building products. At big companies, we'd usually do a lot of planning with diagrams, documentation, etc before building anything. I tend to get stuck in analysis paralysis when it comes to building a new products. Seeing how you've built some nice tools like Bear Blog, I wanted to hear from you personally.
I've built a lot of things over the past 10 years. Mostly to satisfy my own curiosity, with a few of them becoming actual products that fund the rest of my tinkering.
My approach to building products is more akin to a gardener than to a product developer. I play around with ideas, follow interesting threads, and see where the p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by imgabe in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071557"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not about the data. It’s about a foreign government controlling the algorithm that decides what millions of people see, and their ability to shape public opinion through that.
Like imagine if China owned CNN and the New York Times and decided what stories they could publish.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>imgabe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by not2b in "Trudeau government bans TikTok from operating in Canada"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42071538"/>
        <updated>2024-11-07T00:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of the laser focus on TikTok as a threat, it would be better for the US and Canada to have real data protection laws that would apply equally to TikTok, Meta, Google, Apple, and X. What the EU has done is far from perfect but it bans the worst practices. The Chinese can buy all of the information they want on Americans and Canadians from ad brokers, who will happily sell them everything they need to track individuals' locations.
Perhaps the way to get anti-regulation politicians on board with this is for someone to do what was done to Robert Bork and legally disclose lots of personal info on members of Congress/Parliament, obtained from data brokers and de-anonymized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>not2b</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending November 3, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2024/20241106"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune into the vibe, ignore the opinion polls]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8795</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/tune-into-vibe-ignore-opinion-polls/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T21:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tyler Cowen, writing at Marginal Revolution, last July: Democrats and leftists are in fact less happy as people than conservatives are, on average. Americans noticed this, if only subconsciously. Cowen made a whole heap of observations — I’ve quoted but one — about the then upcoming US Presidential election. But it’s tuning into the vibe […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing updates to the AWS Well-Architected Framework guidance]]></title>
        <id>e2bd0370eff5154573d87ca62621505e561215f8</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/announcing-updates-to-the-aws-well-architected-framework-guidance-3/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the availability of enhanced and expanded guidance for the AWS Well-Architected Framework with the following six pillars: Operational Excellence, Security, Reliability, Performance Efficiency, Cost Optimization, and Sustainability This release includes new best practices and improved prescriptive implementation guidance for the existing best practices. This includes enhanced recommendations and steps on reusable architecture patterns focused on specific business […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Haleh Najafzadeh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ComplexSystems in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067493"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The failure is in this very common exchange
Average voter: I can't afford groceries at the store. Inflation sucks.
Response: Actually, here is the correct definition of "inflation." As you can see from the correct definition, inflation rates are now good! Hopefully this helps you understand why things will never get better.
What the average voter hears: I can't afford groceries. Your solution to this problem is to reframe the current situation as "good." I still can't afford groceries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ComplexSystems</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42067489"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T19:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: please make sure you're up on the site guidelines before commenting: https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html. That means editing out snark, swipes, and flamebait. Or you can simply follow this metarule, which is also in there: "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."
This thread could be worse (ok, it could be a lot worse) but I'm still noticing people breaking the rules. Please follow them instead—it will be a better experience for all of us, including yourself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America, the country I once knew]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/america-the-country-i-once-knew/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I remember living in a different country as a child, hearing everyone talk about a faraway place called America.
Everyone wanted to go to America. The adults always spoke about the diversity of people there, the opportunities we could have, and the freedom we’d experience.
Even as a seven-year-old, I sensed the importance of this. Freedom mattered. At the time, we lived in a country where men and women had to walk on separate sides of the street. Women were required to cover themselves. Men and families had separate entrances and seating in restaurants. Women weren’t allowed to drive.
America was the place to be. We would get freedom there.
That was a long time ago.
Now, after living in America for over 26 years as an adult, I see less and less of what those adults once spoke about. It’s no longer the country people dream of coming to.
Today, we are a country that elects a convicted felon. A country where 71 million people chose to elect a fascist over a more than qualified woman. America is now a place where climate change, reproductive rights, and the rights of minorities are dismissed and disregarded—a country increasingly hostile toward those who are not just like them.
I am utterly and devastatingly heartbroken (and terrified).
I went to sleep knowing he would win, but I still held on to a sliver of hope. I woke up at 5 AM and saw Associated Press officially call his win.
A lot will change over these next 4 years.
Be kind to your loved ones today.
Many of us need it.
80/100
Comments and 💬 Community Echoes

No comments available but here are some 💬 Community Echoes
Re: Various election posts by reedybear
Community Commiseration by Kevin Humdrum
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the last cohort of AWS Heroes this year – November 2024]]></title>
        <id>0d594abcf3194d827b593a47f3332675a93e001a</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-the-last-cohort-of-aws-heroes-this-year-november-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T18:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we gear up ahead of AWS re:Invent 2024, we’re thrilled to announce our final cohort of new AWS Heroes! These individuals exemplify expertise and dedication to leveraging AWS technologies and sharing knowledge. Their contributions to the AWS community are greatly appreciated, and today we’re excited to celebrate them. Ayyanar Jeyakrishnan – Bengaluru, India Machine […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Taylor Jacobsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by paxys in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065765</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065765"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This will sadly be the end of FCC/FTC and all the antitrust efforts that were graining steam over the last few years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>paxys</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by skeuomorphism in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065473</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42065473"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About 20 million votes less than the 2020 election, with about 15 million less for the democrats, and a measely 4 million less for the republicans. Thought that was interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>skeuomorphism</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump wins election, leaders respond worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/trump-wins-election-leaders-respond-worldwide</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/trump-wins-election-leaders-respond-worldwide"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trump wins the presidential election, prompting reactions from world leaders; NATO expresses caution about U.S. commitments; Israel welcomes his return; China remains respectful yet concerned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by niuzeta in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42064711</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42064711"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T16:27:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[flagged]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>niuzeta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Channel deflection from voice to chat using Amazon Connect]]></title>
        <id>4a012e531c71e692e94d81451466e64f58ed7579</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/channel-deflection-from-voice-to-chat-using-amazon-connect/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:39:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was co-written with Sagar Bedmutha, senior solutions architect at Tata Consultancy Services, and Rajiya Patan, AWS developer at Tata Consultancy Services Service excellence helps cultivate customer satisfaction and brand loyalty. According to Gartner, one service excellence challenge is long wait times on interactive voice response (IVR) systems. Long wait times can translate into […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siva Thangavel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by drawkward in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063854</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063854"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's the economy, stupid:
-Inflation is not prices; it is the rate of change in prices.  Low inflation doesn't imply low prices.
-Aggregate statistics don't necessarily explain individual outcomes.
The Dems failed on this count massively, and have, for maybe the last 40 years, which is about the amount of time it took for my state to go from national bellwether (As goes Ohio, so goes the nation) to a reliably red state.  This cost one of the most pro-union Senators (Sherrod Brown) his job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>drawkward</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by laniakean in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063722</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42063722"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T15:24:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2016 : Hilary Clinton - People felt that she was chosen because it was her turn
2020 : Kamala Harris - A candidate who never ever even did well in the primaries.
I hope DNC learn from this and let people choose a candidate next time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>laniakean</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ryukoposting in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059842</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059842"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone living in WI who got barraged with ads from both sides, that wasn't the messaging anyone saw AFAICT. The biggest issue on people's minds was the economy. Dem messaging on economic policy was nonexistent. Women's healthcare isn't an issue that resonates with young (read: unmarried) men. It should, but it doesn't. There could have been some "look out for your wife" messaging, but there wasn't.
There's a lot of people in the comments parroting whatever narrative they cooked up for 2016, but the reality is that both candidates' approaches were wildly different this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ryukoposting</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes On The MAGA Wars]]></title>
        <id>https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-the-maga-wars/</id>
        <link href="https://theiqrafiles.com/notes-on-the-maga-wars/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[He hath returned and vanquished all despite the threat of overwhelming lawfare. Yet now begins in earnest the fierce contest to define what exactly the Last Trump administration will stand for and what will be its legacy.
Trumpism unwittingly and through organic unrest, leveraged postmodern mimetics online crashing into meatspace to vanquish the late and ailing media fiefdoms of the post-Cold War Administrative State. His uncanny charisma became a lightening rod not just for populist dissatisfaction from the dilapidated and impoverished slums of Middle America but also from within the Imperial elite from New Technocrats like Theil and Musk. Under Trumpian mimetics a MAGA working class coalesced around him, resonating with his promises to rescue Americans from corporate liberalism - mass mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by goethes_kind in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059351</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059351"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From a game theoretical perspective this is a good result. It is a clear reiteration of the message to the Democrats: you won't win by claiming to be 0.1% less bad.
The Democrats should have fielded a strong personality in their own right. This is not about left or right. It's about mobilizing people by giving them something to care about. "More of the same" and "not like that guy" isn't very enticing.
I don't think the policy positions even matter that much, if you can make a strong case and gain the confidence of the electorate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>goethes_kind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aibrahem in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059017</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42059017"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T10:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who spent most of his life in a dictatorship, I don’t think you appreciate how easily a society can slide into a totalitarian state and how apathetic most of the population can become.
It’s also interesting that you served in the U.S. military and didn’t recognize how self-serving and institutionally corrupt it is. I come from a country with an oversized military relative to its government, and the parallels I can draw between its behavior and that of the U.S. Army are uncanny.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aibrahem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by j-krieger in "Trump wins presidency for second time"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42058779</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42058779"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T09:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop calling working people without a college education stupid and stop alienating men. "Non-educated" people work just as hard or harder than the rest of us. I've been to college and the only thing it "educated" me in is Computer Science, which I majored in. I'm not in any way better as a human being than my friends working in construction. Quite the contrary, their job is far more important to society than mine. If I stopped my niche research tomorrow, no one would really care. If handymen, farmers, or truckers stopped working, there would be riots.
Also, the DNC should really stop forcing unwanted candidates down people's throats. It doesn't work, even when you spam social platforms with your narrative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>j-krieger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody reads your blog]]></title>
        <id>https://purpleram.xyz/nobody/</id>
        <link href="https://purpleram.xyz/nobody/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T08:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if no one reads your blog, the act of writing it is clarifying, motivating and (eventually) fun. — Seth Godin
I tell myself that I blog for my own sake.
I write to express, to put thoughts out there for my own reflection.
I publish essays because it helps me tame my thinking.
And yet, that tiny toast button somehow becomes a bigger deal than it actually is.
I’d be lying if I say I don’t check the stats.
I’m a numbers guy, drawn to tracking things: expenses, books, movies, runs, etc.
Views and upvotes...
..just another metric to follow, a survey on whether anyone's reading.
A measure of... something I'm not sure anymore.
Writing has been my outlet, a habit I’ve had an on-off relationship with over the years.
In all my reasons for writing, I mostly write for myself.
I agree with Mr. Godin -- writing is clarifying, motivating and fun, even if no one's reading.
But I'll admit, it feels good knowing someone else is out there nodding along, connecting to a piece I've shared.
Imagining that somewhere, a stranger reads my words in their own quiet corner, maybe in pajamas, maybe over coffee, and smiles, resonates, or even feels a spark of recognition.
To me, that’s inspiring.
So, even if nobody reads my blog, the act of sharing still matters.
My writing is still deeply personal, a habit of expression and reflection.
And if, by chance, someone wanders in this corner of the web, that connection, however fleeting, is simply a bonus.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Internet traffic shifts and cyber attacks during the 2024 US election]]></title>
        <id>1YyA4YHY9p5HoeHCrgO3L5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exploring-internet-traffic-shifts-and-cyber-attacks-during-the-2024-us-election"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Election Day 2024 in the US saw a surge in cyber activity. Cloudflare blocked several DDoS attacks on political and election sites, ensuring no impact. In this post, we analyze these attacks, as well Internet traffic increases across the US and other key trends.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>João Tomé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Infinitium reduced fraud detection time by 95% with Amazon ECS and AWS Fargate on AWS Graviton]]></title>
        <id>2e567519a3a358bb6da330f9a89fab65c95942f7</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/containers/how-infinitium-reduced-fraud-detection-time-by-95-with-amazon-ecs-and-aws-fargate-on-aws-graviton/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post was created in collaboration with Infinitium Engineering Team. Introduction Infinitium (a Euronet Company) is a leading digital payments company in Southeast Asia, specializing in secure online payment solutions and risk management services. With a strong presence across the Asia Pacific region, Infinitium offers cutting-edge technologies such as 3D Secure (3DS) authentication, fraud detection […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Surendran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[World Bank and IMF: 80 Years is Enough! Abolition!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/World-Bank-and-IMF-76-Years-is-Enough-Abolition</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/World-Bank-and-IMF-76-Years-is-Enough-Abolition"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The World Bank and the IMF are 80 years old. 80 years of financial neo-colonialism and the imposition of austerity policies in the name of debt repayment. 80 years is enough! The Bretton Woods institutions must be abolished and replaced by democratic institutions serving an ecological, feminist and anti-racist bifurcation. To mark these 80 years, we are republishing a series of articles every Wednesday, looking in detail at the history and damage caused by these two institutions. 
English

/ 
IMF, 
World Bank, 
Third World Debt, 
Finance against people, 
80 ans BM FMI EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by naming_the_user in "Only 5.3% of US welders are women. After years as a professor, I became one"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42056718</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42056718"/>
        <updated>2024-11-06T01:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What comes across from the article to me is the class barrier more than the gender one - basically it's a posh person finding out what the "real world" looks like.
Shop talk and banter are fairly universal. Any difference is going to be a target. Thin bloke who doesn't look strong enough? Ginger hair? Tall guy, short guy? Weird tattoo, etc. Definitely the one black guy or the one white guy is going to get shit. But is it malicious? Almost certainly not.
The other thing, which in my experience is relatively common worldwide, is that working class communities are more accepting of male-female dynamics. In academia and in highbrow society the tendency is to basically sanitise every social interaction. When you're in an environment where that isn't happening then you can't suddenly ignore it any more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>naming_the_user</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Architect! Modern data architectures]]></title>
        <id>b2aef35d472cc9890aa4fac148154f9dc8a8154c</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/lets-architect-modern-data-architectures-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T22:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is the fuel for AI; modern data is even more important for generative AI and advanced data analytics, producing more accurate, relevant, and impactful results. Modern data comes in various forms: real-time, unstructured, or user-generated. Each form requires a different solution. AWS’s data journey began with Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) in 2006, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Mezzalira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MMT — debunking the deficit myth]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45718</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/05/mmt-debunking-the-deficit-myth-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Lars Syll We have already shown that deficit spending increases our collective savings. But what happens if Uncle Sam borrows when he runs a deficit? Is that wht eats up savings and forces interest rates higher? The answer is no. The financial crowding-out story asks us to imagine that there’s a fixed supply of savings from […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lars Syll</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The music has stopped for musicians and their support workers]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8793</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/music-stopped-musicians-support-workers/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T21:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just as it is becoming near high impossible to make a full-time living as an author, unless a writer’s work is regularly topping best-seller lists, the same increasingly goes for musicians. And their support teams. Gone are the days road crews, stage hands, recording studio workers, and the like, can make a full-time living in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[by the power of bear blog]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/by-the-power-of-bear-blog/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/by-the-power-of-bear-blog/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T17:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another Bear blog appreciation post.
I discovered Bear in 2023 through a Google search for minimal blogging platforms. Today, 379 days later, Bear has integrated into my routine.
I publish frequently without any pressure on the quality of my content. I write about whatever random things come to mind.
I programmatically sync my blog posts into my server to ensure I always have an archive. But I have no plans to leave Bear - as a user and observer of Herman's product garden, I'm happy to support the platform.
I also tinker with my site around Bear without compromising the web performance. I have added routes like /pics, /status, and other handy features to mgx.me. I have removed the page hits (analytics) as well.
On rare occasions, people used to message me to say they connected with a particular post. However, I later removed contact details because now I prefer observing the community from the sidelines.
Beyond writing, I've become a daily reader of Bear blog discovery feed (Most recent > Trending). I love finding interesting blog posts, especially offbeat entries and commentaries. It's become a habit I look forward to.
After a year, Bear still feels like a great fit. Herman has created the perfect blogging experience that feels fluid with my digital habits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 20,000 displaced in Paris for Olympics + 1 more story]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nearly-20-000-displaced-in-paris-for-olympics-1-more-story</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/nearly-20-000-displaced-in-paris-for-olympics-1-more-story"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 20,000 people displaced in Paris as Olympics approach, with eviction rates rising; US voters decide on abortion rights measures in nine states for the 2024 elections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Share Your Shit]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/share-your-shit/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/share-your-shit/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T16:56:06.895Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I used to never share how I really felt, not even with my closest friends. Blogging about it would have been completely unthinkable.
On the outside, everything looked peaceful and happy. No problems here! But deep down, I felt terrible.
When I finally realized the seriousness of it and sought help, a whole new world opened up for me. I realized that I was far from alone in feeling this way. Suddenly, it no longer felt wrong or shameful, but human and understandable.
Nowadays, I'm open about both my past and during periods when I'm feeling down. I feel like it helps me, and actually others too. It creates a comforting sense of belonging and a realization that we humans are quite similar after all.
We're only human...
It's liberating to talk or write about it, it's valuable for our fellow human beings, and we can get strengthening and motivating support. A wonderful example of this is the lovely comments I received in the guestbook and on Mastodon after yesterday's post, Daunting Doubts. Thank you everyone!
I'm not saying everything is appropriate to share. I'm also not saying that you should force yourself to be open. But sharing that human "ugly and embarrassing" stuff we try to hide, I think that's very healthy and valuable.
So next time you feel lost, share your shit!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IMF: Fake Good News]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/IMF-Fake-Good-News</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/IMF-Fake-Good-News"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:14:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In early November 2024, the IMF decided to create a 25th Executive Director position. The move had been under discussion for some fifteen years, and the seat was to be given to sub-Saharan Africa. But is this really good news for Africa? Will Africa now be entitled to greater consideration in the IMF and its decision-making bodies? 
English

/ 
Africa, 
IMF, 
Finance against people]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[why i'm not on social media anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://aroma.bearblog.dev/why-im-not-on-social-media-anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://aroma.bearblog.dev/why-im-not-on-social-media-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Few days ago, I sat together with guys and girls around my age for a lunch. A girl passed her phone to each of us so we all can follow each other's social media account. Every time this kind of event happens, I have to tell people I don't own one or I used to. Some people get curious. Some people just don't care. In this case, it was the latter. Ultimately, I always end up wondering if I may have sabotaged potential friendships because I don't own one. However, I have had enough relapse to know that I actually don't care anymore.
How it all began wasn't because I understood the negative effects of social media since day one. It was actually because one day, I doom scrolled so hard, my eyes got hella dry and my head got so dizzy and stressed, I impulsively deactivated my account. Oh, and I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[US election part two: Trump v Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-part-two-Trump-v-Harris</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/US-election-part-two-Trump-v-Harris"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T14:06:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's just one day to go before the US presidential election vote and in this second part of my posts on the US economy, I shall look at the economic policies of the two main candidates. 
 In one sense, who wins matters little to big finance and big business. Both candidates are dedicated to the capitalist system and making it work better for the owners of capital. Larry Fink of BlackRock, the world's largest asset manager, said he is “tired of hearing this is the biggest election in (...)
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Capitalism, 
Imperialism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMA - What advice would you give someone graduating from high school?]]></title>
        <id>https://louplummer.lol/advice-to-graduates/</id>
        <link href="https://louplummer.lol/advice-to-graduates/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The question is from Brandon - What advice would you give someone graduating from high school?
This question is a cross between what it says and what I'd like a chance to do if I were 18 all over again. It would be cool to have nearly 60 years of accumulated knowledge crammed into an 18-year old head. Let's go.
Yep, go to college
All the people out there making noise about how college isn't for everyone and that becoming a plumber or joining the army are good solid alternatives, you know the ones I'm talking about, those people are anti-education conservatives who went to college themselves and who plan on sending their children. They are trying to cover for the inability or unwillingness to make education affordable to the masses like the social democracies in Europe do—the countries that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Tiratelli <em>&amp;</em> Ali Helwith: &ldquo;Sinking Ship&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/sinking-ship</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/sinking-ship"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T09:28:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The logic of the Treasury.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New York Times publishes stinging rebuke of Donald Trump]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8789</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/new-york-times-publishes-stinging-rebuke-donald-trump/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-05T00:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the eve of the US Presidential election, The New York Times has published a strongly worded dis-endorsement of Republican candidate Donald Trump. It’s short, succinct, and well worth reading. Unlike counterpart publications, including The Washington Post, and Los Angeles Times, The New York Times issued an endorsement of Democrat candidate Kamala Harris, at the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soundtrack Discoverability on Bandcamp]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.radicaldream.land/soundtrack-discoverability-on-bandcamp/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.radicaldream.land/soundtrack-discoverability-on-bandcamp/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:44:39.747Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know how, for the past however many years, Bandcamp has had a little Discovery chart at the bottom that tracks best-selling albums in various categories?
Well, now it looks a bit like this:
There's something very weird to me about hiding the discoverability of albums behind a series of links without any...you know, albums on display.
The biggest thing to me, however, is the categories chosen & what seems very noticeably omitted... Soundtracks are nowhere to be found. Game music is a huge part of Bandcamp's presence, and game soundtracks have always felt like an embarrassing little side-effect of Bandcamp's popularity. Nearly every editorial focuses on indie hits, the big hitters that've come to the platform, etc. etc... Yet somehow, Epic bought Bandcamp at one point in time before it w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On caring for my ADHD instead of fighting it]]></title>
        <id>https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/caring-for-my-adhd/</id>
        <link href="https://magmacranes.bearblog.dev/caring-for-my-adhd/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of you probably know that I have ADHD. I talk about it fairly often.
I didn't get diagnosed until somewhat recently, because, as is the story for a lot of women with ADHD, my symptoms as a little girl were different than the ones that were typically recognized, AKA the ones that young boys tend to exhibit more often. I was incredibly messy: my desks, lockers, backpacks, and bedroom tended to be absolute chaos. I lost things like homework and winter gloves a lot. I was constantly spacing out and daydreaming. I was generally kind of weird and bad at conversations.
But I wasn't disruptive or hyperactive, and I got good grades despite my problems with remembering to do homework, so my symptoms weren't seen as symptoms. They were flaws. I didn't need help, I just needed to try to be bette…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harry Hartog Book Of The Year 2024 shortlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8782</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/harry-hartog-book-year-2024-shortlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T21:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Australian indie bookseller Harry Hartog has entered the literary prize fray with their inaugural Book Of The Year award. A shortlist featuring three titles, in three categories respectively, fiction, non-fiction, and children’s and young adults, was published a few days ago. No surprise to see Intermezzo by Sally Rooney nominated in fiction. Nor All I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda, Amazon Bedrock, Amazon Redshift, Amazon CloudWatch, and more (Nov 4, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>a9e737b930cb419056cfc7211b775ff3ac6718b0</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-aws-lambda-amazon-bedrock-amazon-redshift-amazon-cloudwatch-and-more-nov-4-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T17:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spooky season has come and gone now. While there aren’t any Halloween-themed releases, AWS has celebrated it in big style by having a plethora of exciting releases last week! I think it’s safe to say that we have truly entered the ‘pre’ re:Invent stage as more and more interesting things are being released every […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by horsawlarway in "We're Leaving Kubernetes"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42042999</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42042999"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T16:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Personally - just let the developer own the machine they use for development.
If you really need consistency for the environment - Let them own the machine, and then give them a stable base VM image, and pay for decent virtualization tooling that they run... on their own machine.
I have seen several attempts to move dev environments to a remote host.  They invariably suck.
Yes - that means you need to pay for decent hardware for your devs, it's usually cheaper than remote resources (for a lot of reasons).
Yes - that means you need to support running your stack locally.  This is a good constraint (and a place where containers are your friend for consistency).
Yes - that means you need data generation tooling to populate a local env.  This can be automated relatively well, and it's something you need with a remote env anyways.
---
The only real downside is data control (ie - the company has less control over how a developer manages assets like source code).  I'm my experience, the vast majority of companies should worry less about this - your value as a company isn't your source code in 99.5% of cases, it's the team that executes that source code in production.
If you're in the 0.5% of other cases... you know it and you should be in an air-gapped closed room anyways (and I've worked in those too...)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>horsawlarway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dbalatero in "New York Times Tech Guild goes on strike"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42041331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42041331"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T13:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is context on the strike, how long it's been brewing, and more that I happened to read yesterday:
https://www.thenation.com/article/archive/the-new-york-times...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dbalatero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vladimir Putin: godfather and federator of the international far right!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Vladimir-Putin-godfather-and-federator-of-the-international-far-right</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Vladimir-Putin-godfather-and-federator-of-the-international-far-right"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T10:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The subject of this article is not Putin the warmonger, nor Putin the invader of Ukraine. The subject of this article is Putin, the anti-democrat, the reactionary and the liberticide with increasingly fascist practices. So, after presenting the first pillar of the Brown International in gestation in the person of Israeli genocidaire Bibi Netanyahu, and awaiting the third who would be a Donald Trump all haloed by a possible success in the American elections in a few days' time, here is (...)
English

/ 
Russia, 
Antifascism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yorgos Mitralias</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by ethbr1 in "A change of heart regarding employee metrics"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038912</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038912"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T05:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>> [Why not build programmer performance measurement tooling?] It's the job of a manager to know what their reports are up to, and whether they're doing a good job of it, and are generally effective. If they can't do that, then they themselves are ineffective, and that is the sort of thing that is the responsibility of THEIR manager, and so on up the line.
Agreed wholeheartedly, but for slightly different reasons. To wit, laziness and Goodhart's law. [0]
In the absence of infinite time, automation will excuse a lack of manager curiosity, as other competing tasks absorb the freed time.
Consequently, most managers with automated dashboards showing performance metrics won't use those dashboards... plus all the person-to-person work they were previously doing. They'll only use those dashboards.
Which then slowly but inexorably turns your employees into dashboard-optimization drones via operant conditioning.
Helping a colleague doesn't show up on the dashboards? Fuck that. Digging into what looks like a security vulnerability isn't on the sprint board? Fuck that.
Which is incredibly corrosive to quality, creative system design.
And then, because this is the work reality you've created, the creative folks you really want working there bail for greener pastures, and you're left with bottom of the barrel talent and retention problems.
[0] https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Goodhart's_law]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ethbr1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[remove xiaomi bloatwares using adb on linux]]></title>
        <id>https://perdana.dev/remove-xiaomi-bloatwares-using-adb-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://perdana.dev/remove-xiaomi-bloatwares-using-adb-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[xiaomi offers smartphones with great hardware at affordable price but pre-installed some apps i don't need. some of them can be easily uninstalled, but some need additional effort. these are the steps to remove the craps using adb:
setup
enable usb debugging on the device:
download adb command line tool:
wget https://dl.google.com/android/repository/platform-tools-latest-linux.zip
unzip platform-tools-latest-linux.zip
cd platform-tools/

connect the device to computer via usb, a pop up should appear on the device asking to allow the computer to perform usb debugging, tap ok.
then run this command to ensure the device is online:
./adb devices

if the device is listed as offline, try unplugging, disable usb debugging on the device, reenable, and replug it.
open adb shell to control/interact …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by biotechbio in "Scientists glue two proteins together, driving cancer cells to self-destruct"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038317</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42038317"/>
        <updated>2024-11-04T04:01:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a decent amount of cynicism in the comments, which I understand. I think this is a really cool and novel study, though.
Historically, cancer was treated with therapies that are toxic to all cells, relying on the fact that cancer cells divide quickly and are unable to handle stress as well as normal cells (chemotherapy, radiation).
The last couple of decades we've seen many targeted cancer therapies. These drugs generally inhibit the activity of a specific protein that lets the cancer cells grow (e.g. EGFR inhibitors) or prevents the immune system from killing the cancer cells (e.g. PDL1 inhibitors).
This mechanism is way more interesting. The gene BCL6 is usually turned on in immune cells when they are mutating to recognize foreign invaders. This process involves lots of DNA damage and stress, but BCL6 stops the cells from dying and is therefore important for normal immune function. Unfortunately, this makes BCL6 a gene that is often co-opted in cancer cells to help them survive.
The method cleverly exploits the oncogenic function of BCL6 not by inhibiting it, but by turning it into a guide, enabling the delivery of activating machinery to the targets of BCL6 and reversing the inhibitory effects on cell death.
The whole field of targeted degraders, molecular glues, and heterobifunctional molecules is a growing area of interest in cancer research.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>biotechbio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[lost in my own head about making art]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/lost-in-my-own-head-about-making-art/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/lost-in-my-own-head-about-making-art/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[for some reason, i've fantasized for years about being the kind of artist who always travels around with their iPad Pro by their side, ready to sketch and work on a moment's notice. when i sit down and actually deconstruct this fantasy, it becomes abundantly clear that it's completely unrealistic for me, and born out of incredibly shallow desires.
there's nothing wrong with people who do that. they're not shallow. it's the digital equivalent to carrying a sketchbook with you, and it's certainly more portable and intuitive to use than other digital art mediums.
but there's this mental disconnect i keep experiencing. for a long time - even when i was well into college! - people regarded my preferred medium and my job as some kind of witchcraft. "what, so the computer does all the work for yo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NaNoWriMo, NaBloPoMo, and WeblogPoMo AMA, November hots up]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8776</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/nanowrimo-nablopomo-weblogpomo-ama-november/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T21:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[National Novel Writing Month AKA NaNoWriMo, is on this month, for better or worse. But if you’re a writer seeking distractions from various November happenings — I’m referring more to northern hemisphere inhabitants facing the onset of winter — and don’t want to write a novel, there are other options. National Blog Posting Month AKA […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vijay Prashad: &ldquo;Yellow Butterflies&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/yellow-butterflies</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/yellow-butterflies"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Garcia Márquez’s Colombia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by praptak in "Touchscreens are out, and tactile controls are back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033987</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033987"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Touchscreens are anti-accessibility.
Lack of tactile feedback for the sight-impaired is the obvious part but there is another thing:
Touchscreens just stop registering your touch when you get old. The older you get the less moisture there's in your skin, which at some point makes touch screens ignore you.
https://www.gabefender.com/writing/touch-screens-dont-work-f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>praptak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Dwedit in "Touchscreens are out, and tactile controls are back"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033914</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42033914"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The worst of both worlds is Touch Buttons.  No screen, just a touch-sensitive surface that's divided into areas that activate upon any kind of skin contact, whether intentional or not.
I always see my dishwasher having some bizarre setting active because of accidental contact with a touch button.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dwedit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[daily projects]]></title>
        <id>https://veronique.ink/daily-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://veronique.ink/daily-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[i follow an artist on Tumblr who’s been doing a daily drawing since 2008.
they’re mostly self portraits.
his work is expressive, somewhat childlike, and genuine.
sometimes he shows pictures of all his notebooks lined up neatly on a wall shelf. years of daily moments recorded with pencils and other colorful media.

linus-malmqvist
a couple of things inspire me:
along with his daily drawings that he posts, he writes a few lines about his day. they’re short snippets of thoughts or daily happenings that leave the reader wanting more.
ex:
18 September 2024 
Onsdag

The logs arrive, I can now start building my house. 

the other thing that encourages me creatively is that he’s been doing this project since 2008. that’s a long time. It astounds me that more people aren’t liking his drawings.
the number of likes on his work doesn’t seem to faze him.
he just continues drawing, sharing his work, and not making things more complicated than they need to be.
he loves to draw, so he does it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The US presidential election: part one – the economy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-US-presidential-election-part-one-the-economy</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-US-presidential-election-part-one-the-economy"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T09:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am doing two posts before the US presidential election on Tuesday. The first is on the state of the US economy; and the second will be on the respective economic policies of the two main candidates, Democrat Kamala Harris and former Republican President Donald Trump. 
English

/ 
United States of America (USA), 
Crisis, 
Capitalism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Roberts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Nîmes, the Maison Carrée]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=53350</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/11/03/sunday-photoblogging-nimes-the-maison-caree/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T09:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The best thing about deleting my youtube history]]></title>
        <id>https://ani.bearblog.dev/the-best-thing-about-deleting-my-youtube-history/</id>
        <link href="https://ani.bearblog.dev/the-best-thing-about-deleting-my-youtube-history/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've deleted my youtube watch history and paused it.


friend was a bit annoyed that he couldn't see my youtube recommendations anymore, but I take this as an absolute win.
Now all I have to waste time with is my subscription tab, which is much less frequent in content I actually want to consume.
As always on bearblog, being more mindful on what you consume is a good thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[one year of linux: a personal retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.platinumtulip.net/one-year-of-linux-a-personal-retrospective/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.platinumtulip.net/one-year-of-linux-a-personal-retrospective/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-03T01:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[it's been (almost) a year since i started using Linux as my primary OS! i just double checked, and apparently i installed Linux Mint on my laptop at the end of November, not the beginning of November. but i was in the mood to write about it now, so whatever. who cares. it's my blog!!
my laptop shipped with Windows 11, and i was getting increasingly frustrated with it. it felt sluggish and unnecessarily unresponsive, despite the fact that my laptop's specs were "Decidedly Fine". between that, and needing something in my life to obsess over and fixate on, i decided to take the leap and try out Linux.
and, well. about half a year later, i ended up killing my Windows 11 partition altogether, and running Linux Mint full time. there's been pros and cons. i'll get to that.
when people usually wri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by baazaa in "Get me out of data hell"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42030101</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42030101"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T23:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People always say this guy just has had bad luck with his employers but I live in Melbourne and work in data and reckon the whole industry is a scam.
Like why didn't anyone catch the issue with the logs? Because it doesn't matter, every data team is a cost-centre that unscrupulous managers use to launch their careers by saying they're big on AI. So nothing works, no-one cares it doesn't work, most the data engineers are incapable of coding fizzbuzz but it doesn't matter.
People always wonder why banks etc. use old mainframes. There's like a 0% success rate for new data projects. And that 0% includes projects which had launch parties etc. but no-one ever used the data or noticed how broken it was. I don't think a lot of orgs which use data as core-infra could modernize, the industry is just so broken at this point I don't think we can do what we did 30 years ago.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>baazaa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[´Fryslan boppe´. An in-depth inspirational analysis of work rewarded with the 2024 Riksbank prize in economic sciences.]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45703</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/11/02/fryslan-boppe-an-in-depth-inspirational-analysis-of-work-rewarded-with-the-2024-riksbank-prize-in-economic-sciences/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T22:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction< The 2024 Sveriges Riksbank Prize for Economic Sciences has been awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James Robinson for work on the influence of institutions on long-term economic progress and growth. Much has been written about this, for instance by ´Pseudoerasmus´ here and by Radford here. In this article, an ´in-depth´ analysis of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>merijntknibbe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Botswana's ruling party defeated after 58 years + 4 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/botswana-s-ruling-party-defeated-after-58-years-4-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/botswana-s-ruling-party-defeated-after-58-years-4-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The UN warns of an apocalyptic crisis in northern Gaza; the EU allocates €160 million to bolster Ukraine’s energy; the US and South Korea form a security framework; North Korea tests a threatening missile; Botswana's political landscape shifts after decades of BDP rule.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[bear blog css playground]]></title>
        <id>https://mgx.me/bear-blog-css-playground/</id>
        <link href="https://mgx.me/bear-blog-css-playground/"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your browser does not support the video tag.
 

bear.css.observer takes any subdomain from subdomain.bearblog.dev and splits the screen into two panels. On the left is a live preview of the blog content. On the right is an editor where you can tweak the CSS in real-time. As you type, the changes are instantly applied to the preview panel on the left.
To make things more user-friendly, I included some themes that users can select from a dropdown menu. This allows for quick testing of different looks and formatting options without writing CSS from scratch. Submit your theme here.
Once you're happy with the styling, you will have a couple options. You can click a button to save the style sheet to localStorage for future sessions. Or you can copy the CSS directly from the editor to your clipboard, making it easy to paste into your bear blog's theme customization area. You can export it as a .css file as well.
Admittedly, it's a silly project, but I thought some people might find it handy to preview styles throughout their site (including inner pages) without mucking about with Overrides.
Note: bear.css.observer is set to <meta name="robots" content="noindex">, and the Playground data is stored in your browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by DeathArrow in "My Time Working at Stripe"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42024884</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42024884"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T08:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[>he asked the team, “for this meeting I’d like us to try and introduce ourselves a little differently. If you’re comfortable, I’d like us to try and be 10% more vulnerable than we normally would in a work setting.” I remember feeling a mix of anxiety and excitement rise in my chest. I sat pondering what I would share. I decided to go for more than 10%. I shared about how my marriage had almost collapsed a couple years prior and a taste of how painful it was. Some of my coworkers shared deeper things I’d never heard in a work setting. It was awkward. It was beautiful.
I'd rather not have my manager forcing me to do group therapy. I owe the company some work hours and they own me money.
If I want to have personal relations with someone from my work, befriend somebody, share personal things, that is my choice. My personal life is not the company business.
Of course I wouldn't say all that to the manager, but 'I'll put him on the list of people I should be careful about, and fake some confessions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>DeathArrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fundi - The Consequences to Rahtid]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/fundi-the-consequences-to-rahtid?v=1730531805"/>
        <updated>2024-11-02T07:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Fundi
Title: The Consequences to Rahtid
Date: February 1974
Notes: Transcribed from Documents of the Caribbean Revolution (Tunapuna: New Beginning, 1974) by Matthew Quest and Ryan Cecil Jobson.*
Source: Retrieved on 2024-11-02 from medium.com/clash-voices-for-a-caribbean-federation-from-below/joseph-edwards-the-consequences-of-rahtid-february-1974-71bdbe7668e6

Joseph Edwards, a Jamaican refrigeration mechanic, spoke of radical labor politics in Rasta idioms. Let’s reason “to Rahtid!”
His selected writings have been published as Workers Self-Management in the Caribbean (2014). When we read his ideas comparatively with Trinidad’s CLR James, Guyana’s Walter Rodney, and Jamaica’s Michael Manley and Trevor Munroe we can begin to see the antagonisms or debates within the Caribbean radic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>