<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2025-01-14T12:48:01.976Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2025-01-14T12:48:01.976Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/14/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285440</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-14-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T11:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even in Switzerland’s Direct Democracy, There Is Little Room for Public Choice on Digital Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285421</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/even-in-switzerland-there-is-no-public-choice-on-digital-identity.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T11:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two-thirds of Swiss voters rejected the government's proposed e-ID system in 2021, a slightly revamped "Digital Passport Act (E-ID Act)" is back on the political agenda]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is Capitalism Falling Out of Favor? We Analyzed 400,000 News Stories to Find Out]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285475</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/is-capitalism-falling-out-of-favor-we-analyzed-400000-news-stories-to-find-out.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T10:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the fundamental flaws in a study meant to assess the popularity, or lack thereof, of capitalism in the US.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trouble at the tip of the Belt and Road: South Africa's largest industrial mega-project meets eco-social resistance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Trouble-at-the-tip-of-the-Belt-and-Road-South-Africa-s-largest-industrial-mega</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Trouble-at-the-tip-of-the-Belt-and-Road-South-Africa-s-largest-industrial-mega"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T10:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's Belt and Road Initiative has many components, but in Africa, one stands out for its oft-promised mix of industrial development (since 2017) and an ambitious solar energy source (since 2022), together termed the Musina-Makhado Special Economic Zone (MMSEZ). The site is a nature reserve located at the far northern end of South Africa, on the Zimbabwe border (Map 1). An enormous controversy has arisen, over whether those two positive aspects of the MMSEZ – solar energy and industrial (...)
English

/ 
China, 
Southern Africa, 
Corporate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To achieve an ecological bifurcation we have to give up on false solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/To-achieve-an-ecological-bifurcation-we-have-to-give-up-on-false-solutions</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/To-achieve-an-ecological-bifurcation-we-have-to-give-up-on-false-solutions"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T09:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The capitalist system and its institutions have fully integrated climate change into their mental software and suggest false solutions that do not address the issues raised in Part 1 of this series, To successfully achieve the Great Bifurcation we must recognize ecological debt. In this part we shall review some of these false solutions that were highlighted at the COP 28 and 29 climate conferences. ESG bonds: a symbol of the World Bank's illusions 
English

/ 
International Institutions, 
Ecological debt, 
Ecology/Climate, 
EN Dette écologique et climatique : Qui est responsable ?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Toussaint, Maxime Perriot</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[America’s Infrastructure Crisis: Covid’s Role in a Ticking Time Bomb]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285472</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/americas-infrastructure-crisis-covids-role-in-a-ticking-time-bomb.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T08:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How falling levels of infrastructure maintenance are somewhat, perhaps significantly, due to Covid deaths and disability.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dangers of Biden’s Legacy and Trump’s Inheritance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350032</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/the-dangers-of-bidens-legacy-and-trumps-inheritance/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T07:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A key measure of any U.S. president’s success is the ability or good fortune to leave his successor with a better international situation than the one he inherited.  Donald Trump inherited a relatively stable situation from Barack Obama, but his chaotic and unstable leadership did no favors for Joe Biden.  Trump now inherits a broad pattern of disorder in Europe, the Middle East, and the Indo-Pacific, and has named a national security team that seems destined to make all of these issues worse. More
The post The Dangers of Biden’s Legacy and Trump’s Inheritance appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Empathy Inequality Index]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350005</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/the-empathy-inequality-index/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is something of a loose, informal social contract inherent to a successful human society, and that is the condition of reciprocal empathy. When one experiences misfortune, others in a healthy society care and assist, despite there being no contractual obligation. Others care when catastrophe falls upon their neighbors. It's basic empathy, not a complicated interaction. Yet we have been immersed in a society that simply wants us to feel empathy in one direction, and that is towards those who have ample resources and power but, for whatever reason, have hit a bump in their golden paved road. The empathy our power structures want us to feel is not the kind that extends downward; the narrative is that we should only feel a concern for the already powerful when they face misfortune. More
The post The Empathy Inequality Index appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathleen Wallace</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Thoughts on Curbing the Worst Excesses of U.S. Militarism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350133</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/ten-thoughts-on-curbing-the-worst-excesses-of-u-s-militarism/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As President-elect Donald Trump prepares to take America back (again!) to greatness, there’s been much talk of Elon Musk’s new DOGE, or Department of Government Efficiency, and whether it will dare tackle Pentagon spending in useful ways. Could it curb rampant fraud, waste, and abuse within military contracting? Will the Pentagon finally pass a financial audit after seven consecutive failed attempts? Might  More
The post Ten Thoughts on Curbing the Worst Excesses of U.S. Militarism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>William J. Astore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Debt and Border Abolition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350169</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/climate-debt-and-border-abolition/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is an excerpt from Environmentalism from Below. The assertion of a right to move is a central element of movements for environmentalism from below. Indeed, border abolition and the defense of refugees and migrants must be regarded as a key element of the climate justice movement. This means, first and foremost, challenging the  More
The post Climate Debt and Border Abolition appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashley Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Martin Luther King’s Prophetic Warning, Denouncing the Merchants of Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350236</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/dr-martin-luther-kings-prophetic-warning-denouncing-the-merchants-of-death-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past three years, a collective of volunteer researchers, lawyers, and commentators created The Merchants of Death War Crimes Tribunal, dedicated to holding accountable four weapon manufacturing corporations based in the U.S. Their tribunal amassed copious evidence to prove that Boeing, Lockheed Martin, RTX (formerly Raytheon) and General Atomics (a company which manufactures weaponized drones) are  More
The post Dr. Martin Luther King’s Prophetic Warning, Denouncing the Merchants of Death  appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detained Without Charge: Eleven Yemenis Leave Guantánamo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350234</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/detained-without-charge-eleven-yemenis-leave-guantanamo/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 6, the Pentagon announced that it had “resettled” 11 Yemeni men to Oman after detaining them over two decades without charge at the US naval facility of Guantánamo Bay.  Notice of this repatriation was given back on September 15, 2023 to Congress by Secretary of Defense Austin.  Their removal from a facility made notorious in the aftermath  More
The post Detained Without Charge: Eleven Yemenis Leave Guantánamo appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Mass Deportation Harms All Working People]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350049</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/how-mass-deportation-harms-all-working-people/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:55:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump vowed to begin deporting undocumented migrants “on day one” of his administration, and day one is rapidly approaching. If Trump’s working-class voters believed that deporting 13.3 million people will somehow improve their economic lives, many will soon learn that mass deportation harms all working people, not only migrants, and will help exacerbate a  More
The post How Mass Deportation Harms All Working People appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Of the Plutocrats, By the Plutocrats, For the Plutocrats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349994</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/of-the-plutocrats-by-the-plutocrats-for-the-plutocrats/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Every morning,” the billionaire Marc Andreessen smiled a few weeks after Donald Trump’s re-election this past November, “I wake up happier than the day before.” The stoked Andreessen, with Trump’s re-entry into the White House only days away, must by now be sitting in seventh heaven. He no doubt has plenty of deep-pocket company. We’ve  More
The post Of the Plutocrats, By the Plutocrats, For the Plutocrats appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Your Home and Yard Safe for Hummingbirds]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350238</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/how-to-make-your-home-and-yard-safe-for-hummingbirds/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many species of birds face a deadly threat: window collisions. They cannot distinguish a clear pane of glass from the open sky, and hummingbirds, among the smallest birds, are particularly at risk. The good news is that we now understand this danger and can protect these tiny birds. We can easily create safe environments that  More
The post How to Make Your Home and Yard Safe for Hummingbirds appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James M. Cubie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Countering Japan’s Defiance of International Whaling Conventions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350028</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/countering-japans-defiance-of-international-whaling-conventions/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many members of the international community consider whale-hunting a barbaric practice that should have been banned decades ago.  But some countries have long viewed it as a vital commercial enterprise and in some cases, an emblem of their national culture.  These contrasting viewpoints figured prominently in the promulgation of the International Convention on the Regulation  More
The post Countering Japan’s Defiance of International Whaling Conventions appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Drought That Felled Assad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350015</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/the-drought-that-felled-assad/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The meteorological drought that swept through the Fertile Crescent (stretching from the Tigris and Euphrates to the Nile Valley) in the 2000s finally ended up undoing the Assad regime in Syria and forcing Bashar al-Assad to flee to Moscow under the cover of night last month. At first glance, drought or its driver in climate  More
The post The Drought That Felled Assad appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarique Niazi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian Neutrality Is Still the Key to Peace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350139</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/ukrainian-neutrality-is-still-the-key-to-peace/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:45:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[President-elect Trump said on January 9th that he is planning a meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin about the war in Ukraine. He said “Putin wants to meet,” because “we have to get that war over with.” So what are the chances that a new administration in Washington can break the deadlock and finally bring peace to  More
The post Ukrainian Neutrality Is Still the Key to Peace appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Medea Benjamin - Nicolas J. S. Davies</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump 2.0: The Next Narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350043</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/trump-2-0-the-next-narrative/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans have long been subjected to a political and corporate sleight-of-hand, the creation of a narrative that says it is doing one thing while behind the scenes doing another. America’s corporate tyrants work with our elected officials to claim they are keeping us safe and secure in our continental cocoon of North America as they  More
The post Trump 2.0: The Next Narrative appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brad Wolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from the LA Wildfires]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350126</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/lessons-from-the-la-wildfires/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wind-blown embers leap ahead of the fire front to start new “spot” fires. Under these conditions, it is impossible to stop or control a blaze. Photo George Wuerthner The fires in Los Angeles are still burning as I write this. The loss of property, the disruption and loss of lives, and the trauma these fires  More
The post Lessons from the LA Wildfires appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Wuerthner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Queen of Angels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350131</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/14/the-queen-of-angels/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T05:20:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The late great Kei Utsume Who lived there all his life Except when he was forced Off locked in Manzanar Got on stage at Al’s Bar And declaimed: It isn’t the City of Angels It’s the city of La Reina De Los Angeles The Queen of Angels Mary, man You could call it Maryland The  More
The post The Queen of Angels appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elliot Sperber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sixo in "GitHub Git Operations Are Down"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42691458</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42691458"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T00:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[people could not be more clear that their preference is for reliable and easy-to-use centralized services maintained by professionals, and not decentralized systems that require a great deal of user expertise]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sixo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jedberg in "Sonos CEO steps down after app update debacle"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42690249</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42690249"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T22:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't think having a sales person in charge was the problem.
The problem is the fundamental disconnect between what's good for users and what's good for the company.  The company wants you to have to pay them money every month and control how you interact with the product, so that they can be a services company with recurring revenue.
The consumer wants a device that they buy once and it just works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jedberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dguido in "Sonos CEO steps down after app update debacle"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42690034</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42690034"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T22:02:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Please stop putting salespeople in charge of highly technical product companies like Sonos. I'm so glad that Tom Conrad is an engineer by training. I hope he can turn this mess around.
The key technical change that broke Sonos was abandoning their reliable UPnP (Universal Plug and Play) system for device discovery in favor of mDNS, while also shifting from direct device communication to a cloud-based API approach. This new architecture made all network traffic encrypted and routed through Sonos cloud servers (even for local operations), adding significant overhead and latency, especially for older Sonos devices with limited processing power. They also switched from native platform-specific UX frameworks to a JavaScript-based interface while moving music service interactions through their cloud instead of direct SMAPI calls, resulting in slower performance and reduced functionality.
For a more extended discussion, see this excellent LinkedIn post from Andy Pennell, a principal engineer at Microsoft with a deep technical understanding of Sonos systems. He created one of the most successful third-party Sonos apps for Windows Phone and worked directly with Sonos on their official Windows Phone 8 app.
https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/what-happened-sonos-app-techn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dguido</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TVS Supply Chain Solutions built a file transfer platform using AWS Transfer Family for AS2 for B2B collaboration]]></title>
        <id>fd3cb31ad717b211b9d8b69c5026317bbc10338b</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/tvs-supply-chain-solutions-built-a-file-transfer-platform-using-aws-transfer-family-for-as2-for-b2b-collaboration/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T21:52:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post shows how cloud-based services can transform traditional B2B communication processes, offering supply chain companies a path to improved efficiency, compliance, and customer satisfaction. For supply chain providers facing similar challenges, this solution offers a blueprint for modernizing file transfer systems while maintaining compliance with industry standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suresh Kanniappan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cmdli in "The Origins of Wokeness"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42687513</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42687513"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T19:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Woke”, for the most part, is a boogeyman that the conservative right uses as a summary label for various political movements on the left. Basically nobody on the left talks about “woke” except for perhaps a period of six months back in 2017.
Many political groups do this: they identify some aspect of the opposition, preferably one that is easy to ridicule, and then repeat those accusations ad-nauseum. The complaints about, say, LatinX have far surpassed the number of actual proponents of it, which were a small number of people of the left. However, it still brought up again and again because it forms a useful image of what people are fighting against.
The trouble with this is that a groups idea of the “enemy” typically outlasts and often surpasses the actual enemy that idea is based off of. People on the right will write endless articles and videos about wokeness not because there actually exists a problem with wokeness but to try to gain political and social status with their political group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cmdli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 1/13/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285423</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/200pm-water-cooler-1-13-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T19:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; Trump transition: Gabbard, Hegseth; "That's quite an act. What do you call it?" LA fires; Tintin now in the public domain ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by yapyap in "The Origins of Wokeness"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42686978</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42686978"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T18:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think the word “woke” means very different things to some people.
As an example I think people from the American political left to somewhere(?) in the middle see it as what it has been introduced as, that being looking past the status quo and instead looking at your own values, i.e. the morality of homelessness and not having a disdain for them but empathy for them instead.
and then on the other side it feels like the people on the American political right see it as what this website describes it as “ A self-righteously moralistic person who behaves as if superior to others.”
I think the divide has originated from taking unlikeable behaviour and labeling that as ‘woke’ (in bad faith of course) and some people have just bonded to that definition so much that they see it as that.
At least that’s what I’ve noticed online over the past few (bonkers) years]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>yapyap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: New Asia Pacific Region, DynamoDB updates, Amazon Q developer, and more (January 13, 2025)]]></title>
        <id>1acc45900a7fda30d9bf8fb9760ddc9d5552bb16</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-new-asia-pacific-region-dynamodb-updates-amazon-q-developer-and-more-january-13-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T17:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we move into the second week of 2025, China is celebrating Laba Festival (腊八节), a traditional holiday, which marks the beginning of Chinese New Year preparations. On this day, Chinese people prepare Laba congee, a special porridge combining various grains, dried fruits, and nuts. This nutritious mixture symbolizes harmony, prosperity, and good fortune — […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Betty Zheng (郑予彬)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers engineer bacteria that break down microplastics + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/researchers-engineer-bacteria-that-break-down-microplastics-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/researchers-engineer-bacteria-that-break-down-microplastics-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T17:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qatar presents final ceasefire draft to Israel and Hamas; University of Waterloo engineers bacteria to decompose microplastics; UK government announces significant AI investment initiative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Ukv in "The Origins of Wokeness"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42684750</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42684750"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T15:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Imagine having to explain to a well-meaning visitor from another planet why using the phrase "people of color" is considered particularly enlightened, but saying "colored people" gets you fired. [...] There are no underlying principles.
To understand much of our language, Gnorts would have to already be aware that our words and symbols gain meaning from how they're used, and you couldn't, for instance, determine that a swastika is offensive (in the west) by its shape alone.
In this case, the term "colored people" gained racist connotations from its history of being used for discrimination and segregation - and avoiding it for that reason is the primary principle at play. There's also the secondary/less universal principle of preferring "person-first language".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ukv</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jsheard in "Luck Be a Landlord Might Be Banned from Google Play"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42683648</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42683648"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LBAL and Balatro being banned or 18+ age-gated for having gambling "vibes" despite not actually simulating gambling, while the stores are full of gacha games which are designed to bleed players dry through real-money gambling mechanics is a ridiculous state of affairs. The latter makes Google and Apple insane amounts of money though so of course they're not going to do anything about them unless their hand is forced.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jsheard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 1/13/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285407</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/links-1-13-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T11:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our kingly daily links.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia’s Difficult Ukraine End Game Choices and the Issue of “Imposing Terms”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285350</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/russias-difficult-ukraine-end-game-choices-and-the-issue-of-imposing-terms.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T11:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Russia's seeming high class problem of being able to secure a military victory in Ukraine really is a problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Musk, Meloni, and the AfD: Trump’s Plan for Reorganizing EU Vassals Comes into Focus]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285386</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/musk-meloni-and-the-afd-trumps-plan-for-reorganizing-eu-vassals-comes-into-focus.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T11:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meloni offers vassalage to the US under faux nationalist packaging. Musk’s support of the Alternative for Germany shows it might be prepared to do the same.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Conor Gallagher</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-Inauguration Perceptions on Eve of Trump 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349927</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/pre-inauguration-perceptions-on-eve-of-trump-2-0/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T07:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s possible with Trump 2.0? As pie in the sky as it might seem or appear (and chances that admittedly approach zero), the incoming Trump 2.0 Administration does have a golden opportunity to reform the federal government, the administrative state, the ‘deep state’ and truly re-make democracy in America for, of and by the People — without dismantling or demolishing it in the process. More
The post Pre-Inauguration Perceptions on Eve of Trump 2.0 appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Drake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebuilding Rate for Santa Cruz Mountains Lightning Complex Fire Bodes Ill for Los Angeles Reconstruction, Even Before Getting to Insolvency of California State FAIR Plan Wildfire Insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285399</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/rebuilding-rate-for-santa-cruz-mountains-lightning-complex-fire-bodes-ill-for-los-angeles-reconstruction-even-before-getting-to-insolvency-of-california-state-fair-plan-wildfire-insurance.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pace of rebuilding after the Santa Cruz Mountains wildfire in 2000 bodes ill for the likely speed of Los Angeles reconstruction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Coming Fires]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350002</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/the-coming-fires/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LA completely embodies the concept of the endless American suburb, where people have historically gone to buy their little patch of paradise, or their big patch of paradise, depending on how wealthy they may be.  But now paradise has burned, again.  And whether you're one of the estimated 70,000 people in Los Angeles County living on the streets (some of whom may be staying warm in the winter with propane heaters in their tents), or a movie star in a mansion with a nice, safe, fireplace, we're all equal under the Santa Anna winds, just as prone to the errant cigarette butt as everyone else, just as strong as the weakest link in the chain. More
The post The Coming Fires appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Rovics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fires in Gaza are the Fires in LA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350045</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/the-fires-in-gaza-are-the-fires-in-la/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier on Wednesday, January 8th, I saw a prominent Zionist commentator and Twitter/X User post, “Has Greta Thunberg taken her keffiyeh off to address the fires in LA yet or are there too many Jews living here for her to be concerned?” The weird implications about a mythical antisemitic malice that climate activist Greta Thunberg has to supposedly fuel her anti-genocide and ecocide beliefs aside, the post is equally embarrassing in its lack of understanding about the exacerbators of Los Angeles’ most destructive fires in the metropolitan area’s history. Sadly, the disconnect that this post showcases is representative of many people and institutions, not only in explicitly pro-Israel spaces but also in the environmental movement. The US military is the #1 institutional polluter in the world. Cities across the country have been sacrificed by the local and federal prioritization of militarism and policing. Our endless wars have pushed forward the climate crisis, and now its catastrophic results are once again terrifyingly visible inside the belly of the beast. More
The post The Fires in Gaza are the Fires in LA appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Kirshenbaum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Santa Ana Winds and the New Normal]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349911</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/santa-ana-winds-the-new-normal/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:56:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are plenty of people lining up to lay blame for the thousands of buildings destroyed during the recent firestorms, fueled by Santa Ana winds. The incoming president blames the governor who is supposedly more interested in saving Sacramento river smelt than anything else, resulting—so it is claimed—in water shortages in Southern California. Wait, what?  More
The post Santa Ana Winds and the New Normal appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edgar Kaskla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Newsom’s Atomic Folly: Now By Fire, Next by Quake, Then by Apocalyptic Radiation?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350023</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/newsoms-atomic-folly-now-by-fire-next-by-quake-then-by-apocalyptic-radiation/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Los Angeles is now being destroyed by fire. Next will be the “Big One” earthquake everyone knows is coming. And then—unless we take immediate action—Diablo Canyon’s radioactive cloud will make this region a radioactive dead zone. My family is now besieged by four fires raging less than four miles away.  We don’t know how long our  More
The post Newsom’s Atomic Folly: Now By Fire, Next by Quake, Then by Apocalyptic Radiation?   appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harvey Wasserman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are the Republicans Now the Working-Class Party?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350065</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/are-the-republicans-now-the-working-class-party/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conservatives claim that Donald Trump’s electoral victories show that his Republican Party, not the Democrats, now represents the working class. Sen. Josh Hawley tweeted on election night 2020, “We are a working-class party now. That’s the future.”  Although unions only represent 10% of the working-class labor force, since 1980, Democrats have not dipped below 51%. However, as  More
The post Are the Republicans Now the Working-Class Party? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Licata</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Bombs, America Yawns and Gatekeepers Con]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350069</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/israel-bombs-america-yawns-and-gatekeepers-con/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As gatekeepers of the corporate information bazaar, you have served Israel well.  Echoing the propaganda of Tel Aviv and Washington has become mainstream fare, with omission at the heart of the campaign.   Thomas Jefferson, America’s third president, judiciously wrote in 1789: “Whenever the people are well informed, they may be trusted with their own government.”  Unfortunately, today’s media mind  More
The post Israel Bombs, America Yawns and Gatekeepers Con appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M. Reza Behnam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Targeting Climate Change Protests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350067</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/targeting-climate-change-protests/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change, like any crisis afflicting earth and humanity, is bound to bring out the best and the worst of a species that soils its nest, salts the earth, and poisons its nourishing rivers.  For those benefiting from plunder and bounty, change is a hard thing to accept.  Kleptocrats and the extractive industries, renters of land, and  More
The post Targeting Climate Change Protests appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware ‘Unleashing Freedom’ to Plunder and Pollute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350071</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/beware-unleashing-freedom-to-plunder-and-pollute/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:54:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In his recent inaugural speech, Montana Gov. Greg Gianforte spoke about how we have what the rest of the nation wants, saying: “The American dream lives in Montana and it’s here where we are proving what is possible when the government gets out of the way and empowers the people.” If anything, his words reflect  More
The post Beware ‘Unleashing Freedom’ to Plunder and Pollute appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israel Destroyed Gaza ‘for Generations to Come’ and the World Stayed Silent]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350029</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/israel-destroyed-gaza-for-generations-to-come-and-the-world-stayed-silent/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first official reference to Gaza becoming increasingly uninhabitable was made by the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) in 2012, when the population of the Gaza Strip was estimated at 1.8 million inhabitants. The intention of the report, “The Gaza Strip: The Economic Situation and the Prospects for Development,” was not merely  More
The post Israel Destroyed Gaza ‘for Generations to Come’ and the World Stayed Silent appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smokey Bear is Partially Right]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349941</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/smokey-bear-is-partially-right/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smokey Bear tells us “only you can prevent wildfires.” That has been Smokey’s simple message since 1944, but nevertheless he has been long associated with the policy of immediately suppressing all wildfires. This policy was called the 10 AM policy, and it meant that all wildfires should be suppressed by 10 AM of the morning  More
The post Smokey Bear is Partially Right appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sarah Hyden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Martin Luther King’s Prophetic Warning, Denouncing the Merchants of Death]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350036</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/dr-martin-luther-kings-prophetic-warning-denouncing-the-merchants-of-death/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past three years, a collective of volunteer researchers, lawyers, and commentators created The Merchants of Death War Crimes Tribunal, dedicated to holding accountable four weapon manufacturing corporations based in the U.S. Their tribunal amassed copious evidence to prove that Boeing, Lockheed Martin, RTX (formerly Raytheon), and General Atomics (a company which manufactures weaponized  More
The post Dr. Martin Luther King’s Prophetic Warning, Denouncing the Merchants of Death appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kathy Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Unfairness and Inadequacy of Social Security Cost of Living Adjustment Increases]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349947</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/the-unfairness-and-inadequacy-of-social-security-cost-of-living-adjustment-increases/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reductions in the purchasing power of one’s income occur when cost-of-living increases just keep up with the rate of inflation and are simultaneously accompanied by greater imposed costs. This has happened to Social Security recipients who are on Medicare. The 2025 Social Security Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) of 2.5% is being undermined by the  More
The post The Unfairness and Inadequacy of Social Security Cost of Living Adjustment Increases appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Baum</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Tariffs Mean Taxes at Temu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=350001</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/13/trumps-tariffs-mean-taxes-at-temu/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T06:25:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Donald Trump seems confused about how tariffs work, but that doesn’t mean the rest of us need to be also. It actually is fairly simple, let’s take the case where we are shopping at Temu. Temu advertises this neat icemaker for $52.62. Trump says he wants to place a 100 percent tariff on the goods  More
The post Trump’s Tariffs Mean Taxes at Temu appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lapcat in "Right to root access"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42679402</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42679402"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T02:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a ton of products on the market that are vastly more dangerous than computers: guns, cars, motorcycles, bicycles, chainsaws, table saws, cigarettes, alcohol, junk food. Yes, consumers do sometimes harm themselves by using these products. That's the price of freedom. I think it's bizarre that we treat computers as the most dangerous products in the world that for some reason demand paternalism, when none of these other products are locked down by the vendor.
The reason that computers are locked down by the vendors is not that computers are somehow more dangerous than other things we buy. The reason is simply that it's technically possible to lock down computers, and vendors have found that it's massively, MASSIVELY profitable to do so. It's all about protecting their profits, not protecting us. We know that the crApp Store is full of scams that steal literally millions of dollars from consumers, and we know that the computer vendors violate our privacy by phoning home with "analytics" covering everything we do on the devices. This is not intended for our benefit but rather for theirs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lapcat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by coldtea in "It's time to abandon the cargo cult metaphor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42678769</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42678769"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T00:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nah, we better abandon this kind of retroactive policing of language instead from people with nothing better to do.
Nobody who uses the term "cargo cult" in a technical settings does it out of spite or even refers to specific nations or peoples. Just refers to the core takeaway of a practice which might as we be all lore.
Care about politics and colonialism and injustice and what have you? There are 1000000 causes you could devote your time and make an active  difference to people actually suffering this very moment, rather than language policing tech terms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>coldtea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by nindalf in "I deleted my social media accounts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42678031</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42678031"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T23:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This advice to quit social media is always a hit on HN. When I was 10 years younger I read the same thing on HN, was thoroughly convinced and quit social media. I even followed the advice of trying to stay in touch by email. Sure.
Turns out that a lot of people I knew posted huge life updates that I completely missed out on. I asked them why they didn’t tell me and they were confused. They said the posted it on social media. I can’t speak for everyone, but I know a lack of social media meant that I have lost touch with old acquaintances completely. I have a few close friends and that’s it.
Maybe that’s an ok tradeoff to make, but it’s worth knowing that before getting into it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nindalf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by imgabe in "It's time to abandon the cargo cult metaphor"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42677699</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42677699"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T22:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nope, we’re not doing this in 2025. Cargo cult succinctly expresses an important concept. We’re not catering to imaginary offenses somebody hallucinates on behalf of some supposedly marginalized people anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>imgabe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Department of Governmental Efficiency (DOGE) Lacks Legal Structure and Promised Transparency]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=285368</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2025/01/the-department-of-governmental-efficiency-doge-lacks-legal-structure-promised-transparency.html"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T21:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DOGE depends on Elon Musk's charismatic authority. That's a bad thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prolonged use of social media may make you short tempered]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9077</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/prolonged-social-media-short-tempered/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Research from Massachusetts General Hospital, I believe, in the United States, possibly underscores what many of us already suspect: that prolonged use of social media may not be the best: This kind of study cannot prove that your hours of doomscrolling is directly making you Tik’d off, but in light of known associations of irritability […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The one-hundred best book covers of 2024 by PRINT]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9080</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/one-hundred-best-book-covers-2024/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T19:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PRINT’s annual list of the best book covers of 2024, features double the number of entries as 2023, one-hundred, up from fifty. Either a record number of books were published in 2024, or cover design has become so good more books needed to be included. Among inclusions is a cover for Intermezzo, Sally Rooney’s latest […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Uses and Misuses of Ideology in Analyzing the Syrian Overthrow]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=349724</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2025/01/12/the-uses-and-misuses-of-ideology-in-analyzing-the-syrian-overthrow/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-12T06:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People in Global South countries have agency. They can and do understand the realities of their material conditions. Apparently it is necessary to write the preceding two sentences.
You, dear reader, may be wondering why I have written such obvious statements. Don’t people everywhere possess agency, the ability to understand and act upon the political, cultural and social conditions of their community, nation and country? Yes of course they do. So why write the obvious? Because it appears that there are those, sadly partisans of the Left, that don’t believe the peoples of the Global South have agency.
To read this article, log in here or subscribe here.
If you are logged in but can't read CP+ articles, check the status of your access here
In order to read CP+ articles, your web browser must be set to accept cookies.		    

		 More
The post The Uses and Misuses of Ideology in Analyzing the Syrian Overthrow appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Dolack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rmccue in "Matt Mullenweg deactivates WordPress accounts of contributors planning a fork"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42669910</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42669910"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T23:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t unexpected; I’ve been deactivated on Slack since very early in this dispute, and later banned from the issue tracker as well. I’ve been contributing for 20 years to the project, am a committer, and built several large parts of WordPress including the REST API.
Matt is banning anyone who speaks out at all, even when they agree with points he’s made. A large group of contributors felt they had to make an anonymous statement from fear of the same retribution I suffered: https://www.therepository.email/core-contributors-voice-conc...
(I am a less active direct contributor these days, so I’m still able to contribute even while blocked - but many people’s livelihoods depend on it, as sponsored contributors.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rmccue</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Centigonal in "The Tsunami of Burnout Few See"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42668429</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42668429"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T19:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> The trick is to not care enough about your job to get hurt but not care so little that you could short-term be hurt.
It really depends on your personal psychology. After I burnt out in a demanding role that I adopted as a big part of my identity, I joined a new company vowing to not take work as seriously (I remember telling myself, "if excess effort isn't rewarded, the optimal strategy is to maximize compensation, minimize necessary effort, and eliminate excess effort").
After a few months of recovery and ruminating on why I still felt so bad (plus therapy), I learned a few things about myself:
1. I feel like garbage when I'm half-assing something at work or not giving my all -- especially when the people around me are putting in the work.
2. When I am giving my all and I feel like I'm …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Centigonal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global temperatures surpassed 1.5C + 2 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/global-temperatures-surpassed-1-5c-2-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/global-temperatures-surpassed-1-5c-2-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2025-01-11T16:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global temperatures surpassed 1.5C this year; the World Economic Forum forecasts 170 million new jobs by 2030; Russia halts gas supplies to Europe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "Meta's memo to employees rolling back DEI programs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42660571</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42660571"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T21:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes. What too few people realized was that the rollout of DEI was driven by what was trending at the time, designed to win political points with the groups that were politically ascendant. These programs were never a victory for the principles or the people, they were marketing.
So it should come as no shock whatsoever that now that another political group is politically ascendant the marketing that is valuable has changed, so there go the marketing programs that were designed for the old power structure.
Change that occurs through fear of your power can only last as long as your power. Lasting change is only possible by actually changing hearts and minds. Progressives have forgotten in the last 10-15 years that the progress which we've won took generations not because our predecessors were weak and slow but because it inherently takes generations to effect lasting change. It's a slow, painful process, and if you think you accomplished it in a decade you're almost certainly wrong.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by antics in "Meta's memo to employees rolling back DEI programs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42660165</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42660165"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T21:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am Wasq'u (a tribe in the PNW), I am connected to my tribe, and I am one of a handful of remaining speakers of the language. I am really tired of being caught in the maw of people fighting about my identity, what I am owed, and to some extent what place my identity has in society.
To the pro-DEI crowd: I have some hard truths for you. Actual change requires commitment and focus over an extremely long period of time. That means you have to choose probably 1 cause among the many worthy causes, and then invest in it instead of the others. You can't do everything. The problems that afflict my community are running water, drug addiction, lack of educational resources, and secular trends have have made our traditional industries obsolete. I am not saying that land acknowledgements and sports t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>antics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by firefoxd in "Meta's memo to employees rolling back DEI programs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42658998</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42658998"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T19:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote about my experience working as a software developer and being black in the industry and I was lucky to have it published on BBC [1].
What immediately followed, every large company reached out to have me work as a consultant for their diversity program. I found it fascinating that they had a team of DEI experts in place already. Like what makes one an expert?
In addition to my job, I spent nights developing programs trying to help these companies. Some folks right here on HN shared their successful experiences and I presented it to several companies. I was met with resistance every step of the way.
Over the course of a year and hundreds of candidates I presented, I've managed to place just one developer in a company.
However, most these companies were happy to change their social media profile to a solid black image or black lives matters. They sent memos, they organized lunches, even sold merch and donated. But hiring, that was too much to ask. A lot of graduates told me they never even got to do a technical interview.
Those DEI programs like to produce a show. Something visible that gives the impression that important work is being done. Like Microsoft reading who owned the land where the campus was built [2] in the beginning of every program. It eerily reminds me of "the loyalty oath crusade" in Catch-22.
[1]: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=23669188
[2]: https://youtu.be/87JXB0t6de4?si=wtnQtBOE-fs4V7gR]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>firefoxd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Martin Barnay: &ldquo;The Franc Zone&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-franc-zone</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/the-franc-zone"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T17:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twilight of Françafrique?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by JohnMakin in "Meta's memo to employees rolling back DEI programs"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42658015</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42658015"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T17:57:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a PoC, and stuff like this reads extremely bizarre to me. On the one hand, you're acknowledging rolling back DEI initiatives in part because of the "political landscape," and that you were already committed to diversity on your teams. That's all well and good, but then, why the initiative in the first place? It seems to me you're doing at least 1 thing here, and acknowledging that such DEI program was performative in the first place. This kind of announcement seems extremely self defeating and unlikely to please anyone and piss off just about anyone that cares about this in any way shape or form, on either side.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JohnMakin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ILA Evo: Meta’s journey to reimagine fiber optic in-line amplifier sites]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=22128</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2025/01/10/production-engineering/ila-evo-in-line-amplifier-sites-meta/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T17:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s rapidly evolving landscape of use cases that demand highly performant and efficient network infrastructure is placing new emphasis on how in-line amplifiers (ILAs) are designed and deployed. Meta’s ILA Evo effort seeks to reimagine how an ILA site could be deployed to improve speed and cost while making a step function improvement in power [...]
Read More...
The post ILA Evo: Meta’s journey to reimagine fiber optic in-line amplifier sites appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Workaccount2 in "I've acquired a new superpower"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42656869</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42656869"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T16:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At a local bar they had a game machine, and if you got a high score on any of the games, your tab for the evening was free.
One of the games was a "spot the differences" between two pictures with an ever decreasing timer for each round. Using this trick I was able to easily surpass the high score, and garner a crowd watching me perform this mind numbing feat.
Probably my peak fame right there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Workaccount2</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking AWS Console: Diagnosing Errors with Amazon Q Developer]]></title>
        <id>1e9253b5106cc05b2207ede3364004b821c94b8d</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/unlocking-aws-console-diagnosing-errors-with-amazon-q-developer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T13:58:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction Developers, IT Operators, and in some cases, Site Reliability Engineers (SREs) are responsible for deploying and operating infrastructure and applications, as well as responding to and resolving incidents effectively and in a timely manner. Effective incident management requires quick diagnosis, root cause analysis, and implementation of corrective actions. Diagnosing the root cause can be […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Frattallone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maria Palacios Cruz: &ldquo;Artist as Filmmaker&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/artist-as-filmmaker</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/artist-as-filmmaker"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T11:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malcolm Le Grice (1940-2024).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Urgent Need to Better Measure Household Debt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/The-Urgent-Need-to-Better-Measure-Household-Debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/The-Urgent-Need-to-Better-Measure-Household-Debt"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T10:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sébastien Michiels, Arnaud Natal, Isabelle Guérin and Timothée Narring have authored a paper on household debt in the North and Global South, which CADTM is pleased to publish. The paper looks at the measurement of household debt, the use of credit cards, and the gendered and racial dimensions of debt. It also proposes a reading in terms of social classes.
 Sushovan Dhar and Vicki Briault Manus have translated the paper. (...)
English

/ 
Private debt, 
South, 
Finance against people, 
North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnaud Natal, Isabelle Guérin, Sébastien Michiels, Timothée Narring</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CADTM and the experience of the Greek Truth Committee on Public Debt]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-and-the-experience-of-the-Greek-Truth-Committee-on-Public-Debt</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/CADTM-and-the-experience-of-the-Greek-Truth-Committee-on-Public-Debt"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T19:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2025 marks the 10th anniversary of the capitulation of a government that had promised to put an end to the ordeal of the Greek people by obtaining, among other things, the cancellation of most of the Greek debt. Throughout the year, the CADTM will be publishing analyses and documents to help us understand what happened. In this spirit, we are publishing a new extract from Christoph Sorg's doctoral thesis. This extract covers the CADTM's action in Greece from 2010 onwards. This includes the (...)
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Greece, 
CADTM, 
Sorg EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christoph Sorg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing database time-to-live (TTL) for data management]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/3f1d83cd0e8b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/capital-one-tech/introducing-database-time-to-live-ttl-for-data-management-3f1d83cd0e8b?source=rss----3db3a67cb648---4"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T18:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maximizing data management efficiency through TTL implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Capital One Tech</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scientists extract 1.2 million-year-old ice core from Antarctica + 3 more stories]]></title>
        <id>https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-extract-1-2-million-year-old-ice-core-from-antarctica-3-more-stories</id>
        <link href="https://newsletter.newsminimalist.com/p/scientists-extract-1-2-million-year-old-ice-core-from-antarctica-3-more-stories"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T17:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Webb Telescope finds 44 stars in the Dragon Arc galaxy; Greenland's importance escalates due to climate change; scientists drill 1.2 million-year-old ice core; Trump considers national economic emergency for tariffs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>News Minimalist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luke Roberts: &ldquo;Broken Voices&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/broken-voices</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/broken-voices"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T13:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Anna Gréki.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week Ending January 5, 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://lwkd.info/2025/20250109</id>
        <link href="https://lwkd.info/2025/20250109"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T06:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developer News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Last Week in Kubernetes Development</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tokinonagare in "I had to take down my course-swapping site or be expelled"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42640931</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42640931"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T02:22:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Upvoting too.
> Unless, that is, I agree to work on a comparable solution for the university focused on solving the underlying problem I was building HuskySwap for. They would presumably own the IP and were clear that I wouldn’t be compensated. But it was implied that they would then remove the hold, allowing me to graduate.
Wow. Literally blackmailing a student to do illegal work (at least would be categorized like that in my country). A student that already paid money for class and potentially a degree the univ is trying to block, mind blowing. OP, 1000% lawyer up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tokinonagare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by eykanal in "I had to take down my course-swapping site or be expelled"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42640222</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42640222"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T00:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just piling on here because upvotes are not visible. The one thing you can guarantee is that your good faith is not reciprocated by the university. Get a lawyer.
To make it easier: it sounds like you're still registered. University of Washington offers Student Legal Services ( https://depts.washington.edu/slsuw/ ). Set up a referral with one of them and talk to them. Even if they're employees of the university and don't want to work with you to sue the university itself they may be able to give you good advice about how to proceed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eykanal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by GrantMoyer in "I had to take down my course-swapping site or be expelled"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639886</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639886"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T23:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> I am not planning to get a lawyer involved as I have faith that UW leadership will make it right in the end.
All evidence so far indicates they will not make it right, but instead they may make it even worse. Your faith is wildly misplaced. Seriously, talk to a lawyer.
Keep in mind, just because you seek advice from a lawyer doesn't mean you need to take legal action against the school. Talking to a lawyer is not an escalation; the school doesn't even need to know you consulted one. A lawyer will advise whether you should take legal action and any more amicable alternatives available before they do anything on your behalf.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>GrantMoyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by didgeoridoo in "Salesforce will hire no more software engineers in 2025, says Marc Benioff"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639834</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639834"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T23:42:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was at Salesforce for 4 years, and during those years the company made a massive deal about:
2020: the first AI craze, introducing “Einstein” as their name for their analytics platform, and officially changing the corporate vision to being the “No. 1 AI CRM company”.
2021: Now it’s all about “Customer 360”, i.e. account-based marketing, i.e. what basically everyone else does without such a memeable name. You wouldn’t believe the number of slide decks I had to sit through with all our little product logos orbiting this stock art character straight out of Women Laughing While Eating Salad.
2022: Never mind, now we’re betting the company on a real-time unified database called Genie, which was neither real-time nor unified (and eventually not called Genie either). Got sued for that one.
2024: AGENTS. AGENTS EVERYWHERE. WE ARE AN AGENT COMPANY NOW.
So, let’s see how this holds up in the face of the next hot thing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>didgeoridoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by bb611 in "Salesforce will hire no more software engineers in 2025, says Marc Benioff"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639791</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639791"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T23:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Current SFDC software engineer - this is just cover for a widespread engineering hiring freeze since the layoffs in January 2023. There's a ton of pressure to control costs after the near shareholder revolt that caused the layoffs.
The public nature of the announcement is certainly marketing for our AI offerings as well, but at this point I think most engineers are just worried there will be additional layoffs, in the event management cannibalizes product for short term stock gains again.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bb611</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by NBJack in "I had to take down my course-swapping site or be expelled"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639347</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639347"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T22:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to consult with a lawyer. This is starting to sound like extortion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NBJack</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jdkaim in "I had to take down my course-swapping site or be expelled"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639331</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42639331"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T22:46:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Update: I immediately took down my class project site after receiving yesterday’s ultimatum. I still don’t think the simple demo site violated the letter or spirit of the registration rules, but I took it down because I always want to operate in good faith.
They followed up today to thank me for doing it, but also indicated that they were putting a hold on my account anyway. As a result, I am not going to be able to register for my final quarter and have been de facto expelled at the end of this quarter.
Unless, that is, I agree to work on a comparable solution for the university focused on solving the underlying problem I was building HuskySwap for. They would presumably own the IP and were clear that I wouldn’t be compensated. But it was implied that they would then remove the hold, allowing me to graduate.
I really love UW and have had a wonderful time here. But this is so demoralizing.
Update #2:
I appreciate you guys for all of your advice.
This platform was never intended to be monetized, and I am not planning to get a lawyer involved as I have faith that UW leadership will make it right in the end.
I'm not planning to pursue this project at this point. If they came up to me at first with the offer to work with them it might be different, but the way they handled it makes me just want to walk away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jdkaim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML: a programming language, not mere markup]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9067</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/html-programming-language-not-markup/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T20:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Carmody, writing for Wired: Because HTML looks easy and lacks features like formal conditional logic and Turing-completeness, it’s often dismissed as not a programming language. “That’s not real code; it’s just markup” is a common refrain. Now, I’m no stranger to the austere beauty of the command line, from automating scripts to training machine-learning […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta announces major changes to content moderation polices]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=9064</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/meta-major-changes-content-moderation/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T19:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justine Calma, writing for The Verge: Meta is essentially shifting responsibility to users to weed out lies on Facebook, Instagram, Threads, and WhatsApp, raising fears that it’ll be easier to spread misleading information about climate change, clean energy, public health risks, and communities often targeted with violence. The policy revision seemed surprising initially, but less […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source all the way down: Upgrading our developer documentation]]></title>
        <id>6HAo0CAvmODAhYHnIF5Hbr</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/open-source-all-the-way-down-upgrading-our-developer-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Cloudflare, we treat developer content like an open source product. This collaborative approach enables global contributions to enhance quality and relevance for a wide range of users. This year,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kim Jeske</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jgrahamc in "Cracking a 512-bit DKIM key for less than $8 in the cloud"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42633965</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=42633965"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T13:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Me writing over 14 years ago: https://blog.jgc.org/2010/06/facebooks-dkim-rsa-key-should-b... This was doable 14 years ago for 512-bit keys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jgrahamc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Democracy and Debt: Has the Link been Broken?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Democracy-and-Debt-Has-the-Link</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Democracy-and-Debt-Has-the-Link"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The year 2025 is considered by Christians to be a jubilee year under the banner of debt cancellation. To mark the occasion, the CADTM is republishing a series of articles on debt cancellation, the struggles for debt cancellation and the role of debt in political, social and geostrategic conflicts throughout history. 
English

/ 
Alternatives, 
Debt in History, 
Finance against people, 
Histoire Jubi EN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hudson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the new AWS Asia Pacific (Thailand) Region]]></title>
        <id>3acab191e810ab04e856c629a911bcd01c319944</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/announcing-the-new-aws-asia-pacific-thailand-region/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T02:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS launches Asia Pacific (Thailand) Region with 3 Availability Zones, accelerating cloud adoption. Strategically located to meet data residency needs, it drives innovation across industries. Early AWS adopters in Thailand share transformative success stories. Get started now!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donnie Prakoso</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>