<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2024-08-07T06:32:32.698Z</id>
    <title>pchaganti | cleo</title>
    <updated>2024-08-07T06:32:32.699Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Biden Believes He Doesn’t Have to Talk to Putin]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330018</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/330018/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T06:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The conventional wisdom is that Russia doesn’t need any security guarantees, but there will be no movement toward resolving the conflict as long as the Kremlin has no idea of Western plans for tactical and strategic deployments on its sensitive western border over the next five to ten years.  Putin, indeed no Russian leader, can willingly accept a permanently expanding role for the United States and the European NATO countries on a border that has witnessed costly invasions from Sweden, France, and Germany over the past three centuries.  What would be the U.S. reaction to Russian military alliances with Canada and Mexico…or Cuba? More
The post Biden Believes He Doesn’t Have to Talk to Putin appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melvin Goodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trans People are a Menace to God-Fearing Toilets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329992</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/trans-people-are-a-menace-to-god-fearing-toilets/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T06:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As with any narrative of ‘political correctness gone mad’, this specific example provides us with a surreal and topsy-turvy inversion.  It relocates a marginalized group – in this case trans people – in a position of great power and influence, and thereby helps disguise the vulnerability of the group and the social oppression and discrimination it is subject to.   In the US, for instance, trans women are more than four times more likely to be murdered than cisgender women.  Black trans women are seven times more likely to be murdered than the average member of the general population. More
The post Trans People are a Menace to God-Fearing Toilets appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony McKenna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Jobs?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330202</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/black-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“I love my black job,” tweeted Simone Biles, an American and Olympics star who is arguably the greatest gymnast in history. The context of her pointed comment on social media is a response to what former U.S. President Trump said about black employment and immigrants. “Coming from the border are millions and millions of people who  More
The post Black Jobs? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Seth Sandronsky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Letter From London: The MUP Show]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329994</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/letter-from-london-the-mup-show/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:52:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking further afield than this depressed and depressing land right now, I have two German friends who live in Austria. Regularly, the three of us get together over a long video call. We call it the MUP Show after the first letter of each of our first names. On the occasion when my friends are  More
The post Letter From London: The MUP Show appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Peter Bach</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Coming Tax-the-Rich Rumble in Rio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329995</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/the-coming-tax-the-rich-rumble-in-rio/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the richest among us, life on Earth can sometimes get rather boring. But worry not for our world’s deepest pockets. At least five firms worldwide, notes the swanky lifestyle Robb Report, are now racing “to deliver passengers to the stars on giant balloons attached to pressurized luxury capsules.” Sometime next year, those passengers will  More
The post The Coming Tax-the-Rich Rumble in Rio appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sam Pizzigati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuclear Resisters in German Prisons]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330183</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/nuclear-resisters-in-german-prisons/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of front-line nuclear weapon abolitionists are incarcerated in a German prison camp this week, while hundreds of activists and reporters like me just write about the anniversaries of the atomic fire-bombings of Hiroshima and Nagasaki by the United States government. Susan Crane of Redwood City, Calif., and Susan van der Hidjen of Amsterdam,  More
The post Nuclear Resisters in German Prisons appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Laforge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neoliberal Bureaucracy: Making the Left Look Bad]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330215</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/neoliberal-bureaucracy-making-the-left-look-bad/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[No one prints the syllabus for a college class anymore. They’re multi-page tomes, too long to print, and they’re usually posted online. A modern syllabus is essentially a legal document, full of policies about grading, learning outcomes, attendance, classroom conduct, artificial intelligence, academic honesty, learning accommodations, and various services offered by the school. If you’re  More
The post Neoliberal Bureaucracy: Making the Left Look Bad appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Groves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Jesus and Free Buffalo]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=328336</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/fake-jesus-and-free-buffalo/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despair and desperation. A history denied and misrepresented. A colonial legacy that still stains the lives and landscape. These describe the setting of Conor Kerr’s new novel Prairie Edge. Set in the Edmonton, Alberta area of Canada, its two primary protagonists are indigenous Metís young people angry and frustrated with a world that gives them  More
The post Fake Jesus and Free Buffalo appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ron Jacobs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sound Grammar: The Best Jazz Records of the Year So Far]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329997</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/sound-grammar-the-best-jazz-records-of-the-year-so-far/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was invited by Tom Hull to participate in the Francis Davis Jazz Critics mid-year poll for 2024. Here are my favorite recordings for the year to date, both new releases and reissues/archival albums. You can see the poll results here. New Releases 1. Vijay Iyer, Linda May Han Oh, Tyshawn Sorey: Compassion (ECM) 2. Julian  More
The post Sound Grammar: The Best Jazz Records of the Year So Far appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey St. Clair</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bragging on My Sister, and Her New Newspaper Gig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329980</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/bragging-on-my-sister-and-her-new-newspaper-gig/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between the two of us, my sister Becca Tucker and I have won dozens of journalism awards. (No, I haven’t won any.) Now, in addition to being a reporter, Bec has been promoted to deputy publisher of Straus News, making her the fourth generation of our family to help steer the company, which publishes 14  More
The post Bragging on My Sister, and Her New Newspaper Gig appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pete Tucker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Wrong and Right with Project 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276293</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/whats-wrong-and-right-with-project-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T05:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Project 2025 dog's breakfast of proposals bears watching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Midsummer Night’s Dream]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330186</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/07/a-midsummer-nights-dream/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T04:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 2, 2024, Donald Trump reneged on his commitment to participate in the presidential debate scheduled for September 10 on ABC News. He presented a counterproposal to face off Vice President Kamala Harris (whose name he mispronounces as KaMAla Harris, among other nicknames) on Fox News six days earlier than agreed on, in Pennsylvania.  More
The post A Midsummer Night’s Dream appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Frank</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spotlight on SIG API Machinery]]></title>
        <id>https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/07/sig-api-machinery-spotlight-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://kubernetes.io/blog/2024/08/07/sig-api-machinery-spotlight-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently talked with Federico Bongiovanni (Google) and David
Eads (Red Hat), Chairs of SIG API Machinery, to know a bit more about
this Kubernetes Special Interest Group.
Introductions
Frederico (FSM): Hello, and thank your for your time. To start with, could you tell us about
yourselves and how you got involved in Kubernetes?
David: I started working on
OpenShift (the Red Hat
distribution of Kubernetes) in the fall of 2014 and got involved pretty quickly in API Machinery. My
first PRs were fixing kube-apiserver error messages and from there I branched out to kubectl
(kubeconfigs are my fault!), auth (RBAC and *Review APIs are ports
from OpenShift), apps (workqueues and sharedinformers for example). Don’t tell the others,
but API Machinery is still my favorite :)
Federico: I was not as …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kubernetes Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Actually listening to 10cc.]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52956</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/06/52956/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you know my age my musical tastes as a teenager are very easy to guess. Obviously Dylan, Mitchell, the Kinks and the Beatles – equally obviously not the Stones or the Who. Richard Thompson, Sandy Denny, Fairport, Steeleye Span, Roy Harper, The Watersons, Carthy, etc, etc and more than any of them, Kevin Coyne. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Who needs LinkedIn when you can network at music festivals?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8159</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/who-needs-linkedin-network-music-festivals/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T21:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking tips for music festivals, by Harry Carr: Don’t make the mistake that most people make and switch off as soon as you reach Paddington. Maximise your train journey by reaching out to your extended network, to see if they are going to Glastonbury Music Festival. If there’s a speaker or business guru you admire […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dense Discovery notches three hundred editions, opens reader community]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8193</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/dense-discovery-three-hundred-editions-reader-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T20:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Melbourne based Australian designer and publisher Kai Brach’s weekly publication, Dense Discovery (DD), is one of the few newsletters I subscribe to. If you have an interest in, well, everything, then DD is for you. First published in September 2018, the three-hundredth edition was posted yesterday. And to mark this most impressive of milestones, Brach […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Image Generator v2 is now available in Amazon Bedrock]]></title>
        <id>2d71dc91ba8d25a9634204389216e742e9917a1e</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-titan-image-generator-v2-is-now-available-in-amazon-bedrock/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T19:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Titan Image Generator v2 provides unprecedented creative capabilities: image conditioning, color control, background removal, and subject preservation via fine-tuning for brand consistency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Channy Yun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Tectosage in "The real "Wolf of Wall Street" sales script"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41174084</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41174084"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T19:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This pitch worked much better in the 80s and 90s when
A) most investors had a broker not just for advice, but because there was no easy way to trade individually or get live stock quotes until the internet was widespread and matured
B) telephone sales in general were more common then and less likely to be a scam (Stratton Oakmont and other boiler rooms played a large role in shifting public opinion on this)
C) The most desirable prospects (High Net Worth Individuals) were accustomed to dealing with legitimate brokers over the phone and being solicited by brokers from other legitimate firms in such a way
D) The markets were raging in such a way that everyone had FOMO and was dying to hear of a hot new tip
Almost nobody legitimate in the financial advising world acquires customers via cold call pitching anymore. Cold calling is still part of the toolkit for other sales niches (eg, tech sales) but it's a tough road with a low success rate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tectosage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hintymad in "Twitter kills its San Francisco headquarters, will relocate to South Bay"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41174067</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41174067"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a famous paper about the location of company headquarters: they get as close as possible to the residence of company CEOs. If we don't consider the CEO's influence, I'm actually curious if the location of company headquarters has to do with the average age of the employees in the Bay Area. As the employees start to have families, they most likely move to the south bay for better or for worse, and I have a hard time imagine that they'd enjoy commuting via BART or Caltrain for more than an hour every day. And this is probably just me or my circles, a city's hustle and bustle becomes a distraction or at least increasing irrelevant as I age. I increasingly enjoy ample parking space, tranquil suburbs, being able to step out and start jogging in woods or huge parks, and certainly not having to deal with the craziness on SF streets. If more people are like me who prefers living outside of the city proper, then I'd imagine a company will have access to more talent by moving its headquarters to the south of SF.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hintymad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by janalsncm in "Twitter kills its San Francisco headquarters, will relocate to South Bay"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173796</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173796"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:36:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Had a recruiter call with Twitter a few months ago. Mandatory in office 5 days per week. Among other things, an hour commute both ways to work was not acceptable.
Maybe they will have better luck in Santa Clara.
I don’t buy any of the flamebait reasons for leaving SF. Reason 1 is money and reason 2 is talent pool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>janalsncm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vngzs in "Show HN: 1-FPS encrypted screen sharing for introverts"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173644</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173644"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good job releasing your project! It's a cool idea and surprisingly minimalist. That said, I've found a number of cryptographic flaws in the application source. This should not be used in instances where the encryption is mission-critical.
1) You generate a random key [0] and then feed it into PBKDF2 [1] to generate a 32-byte AES-GCM key. If you can generate 32 random bytes instead of 10 reduced-ASCII characters and a key stretch, just do that. PBKDF2 is for turning a password into a key, and it's far from the recommended algorithm nowadays; prefer scrypt if you need to do this sort of thing.
2) AES-GCM with random 12-byte nonces. Never use random IVs with GCM; this breaks the authentication [2] [3]. Given the pitfalls of AES-GCM with respect to random nonces, you might prefer switching to XSalsa20+Poly1305. The advantage of XSalsa is it has an extended nonce length, so you can use random nonces without fear.
3) Random key derivation with a restricted character set can make brute force attacks easier. You should have a 256-bit random key, and if you want that key to be within a certain character set, then encode the byte output from the CSPRNG using that character set.
4) 1fps achieves symmetric key distribution via a URL with a fragment identifier ("#") which IIRC is not sent to the server. Therefore it assumes you have a secure key distribution channel - the link contains the key, so it's important that only the intended recipient can view the part after the "#". If the server is truly malicious, it can deploy client-side Javascript to send the fragment to the server, allowing the server to access the key (and thus cleartext communication).
[0]: https://github.com/1fpsvideo/1fps/blob/main/1fps.go#L99
[1]: https://github.com/1fpsvideo/1fps/blob/main/1fps.go#L287
[2]: https://eprint.iacr.org/2016/475.pdf
[3]: https://soatok.blog/2020/05/13/why-aes-gcm-sucks/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vngzs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276295</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Politics, syndemics; best Olympic story; Walz is Kamala's VP choice; Climate tipping points unpredictable; Andy Warhol's lost Amiga Art ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dang in "Twitter kills its San Francisco headquarters, will relocate to South Bay"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173303</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41173303"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T17:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All: can you please not post low-quality angry/snarky junk comments to HN threads? They're tedious and have nasty effects.
I realize this story is a cluster of divisive topics but that's why HN's guidelines say "Comments should get more thoughtful and substantive, not less, as a topic gets more divisive."
If you wouldn't mind reviewing https://news.ycombinator.com/newsguidelines.html and taking the intended spirit of the site to heart, we'd be grateful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes things are just hard.]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/sometimes-things-are-just-hard/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/sometimes-things-are-just-hard/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T15:19:18.940Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lately, I’ve been feeling upset and frustrated about some of the things happening in my life. I’m screaming into the unknown because I’m not really sure what else to do. The right words have been hard to come by, probably because I’m not really sure what I’m legally allowed to say, and not say. I know I’m not the only one.
Talking to people in the same space as me is a challenge in itself. There is a very small circle of people that I trust, but those numbers are dwindling down even more. There are a few that I’d love to open up to, but with the environment we’re in, I’m really not too sure who to trust. With everything that’s happening, I’m not sure whether or not to be grateful about where and how I currently stand.
I have this nagging feeling that the worst is yet to come for me. I don’t know if this is just me overthinking or irrationally being a pessimist. All I know is that my mental health keeps going downhill, even when I think I’m nearing the bottom. My physical health isn’t doing any better. The more stressed I am, the worst my immune system gets.
Every day, I’m faced with another challenge, another thing actively blocking that light at the end of the tunnel. I’m trying to convince myself that I just need to persevere through this and everything will be OK, but at the same time, I think it may be time to try to actively dig my way out of it.
I just need to figure out how.
6/31 - Blaugust
Reply by email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mortgage Lock‑In Spurs Recent HELOC Demand]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=31202</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/mortgage-lock-in-spurs-recent-heloc-demand/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mortgage balances, the largest component of U.S. household debt, grew by only $77 billion (0.6 percent) in the second quarter of 2024, according to the latest Quarterly Report on Household Debt and Credit from the New York Fed’s Center for Microeconomic Data. This modest increase reflects a substantial slowdown in mortgage origination; only $374 billion was originated during the second quarter, compared to an average of about $1 trillion per quarter between 2021 and 2022. Meanwhile, after nearly thirteen years of decline, balances on home equity lines of credit (HELOC) have begun to rebound, gaining 20 percent since bottoming out at the end of 2021. In this post, we consider the factors behind this upswing, finding that HELOCs have likely become an attractive alternative to cash-out refinancings amid higher interest rates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Haughwout, Donghoon Lee, Daniel Mangrum, Joelle W. Scally, and Wilbert van der Klaauw</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“How Does OpenAI Survive?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276288</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/how-does-openai-survive.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ed Zitron explains in gory detail why OpenAI looks like the mother of all bezzles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The backbone behind Cloudflare’s Connectivity Cloud]]></title>
        <id>66b1ed934a25d6000ae1c93f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/backbone2024"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read through the latest milestones and expansions of Cloudflare's global backbone and how it supports our Connectivity Cloud and our services]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shozo Moritz Takaya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by TheAdamist in "Twitter kills its San Francisco headquarters, will relocate to South Bay"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41169901</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41169901"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T11:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thats generally the point with sudden disruptive moves - high attrition. Reduce the headcount without having to be in the news for layoffs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>TheAdamist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[choosing yourself in every moment helps develop your sense of Self]]></title>
        <id>https://froggy.bearblog.dev/choosing-yourself/</id>
        <link href="https://froggy.bearblog.dev/choosing-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(note: choosing yourself == choosing to be yourself)
I was having a phone call with my best friend last night. I know he's going through a really tough time and has been for a while. I felt anxious and stressed about whether or not I could be a good friend / what he needed. I knew that things between us are great and will be, and all I needed to do was be there to listen and support him.
So why would I be stressed? Zooming out a bit, I've always been shy, never really let anyone into my thoughts and feelings, and frequently deny any help offered to me. It's always been hard for me to get close to even my best friends. I really abused the shit out of "I'm fine", and "I don't need your help". Despite that, it felt like it really degenerated during lockdowns, to the point where I've had troub…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/6/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276206</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-6-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T10:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our frabjous daily links: beluga rescue, Ozempic backfire. Covid wins, US v. China self-driving cars, Sudan starvation, Bangladesh coup, UK violence, Gaza tinderbox, Ukraine F-16s, Dems econ worries, huge Google anti-trust loss, Kansas police newspaper arrest,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Is the Milei Government Doing With Argentina’s Gold?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276219</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/what-is-javier-milei-doing-with-argentinas-gold.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T10:45:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Argentina's cash-strapped central bank has around two million troy ounces of gold in its vaults, valued at around $4.5 billion. Or at least it did.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Corbishley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Climate Change and Hard Labor: The Rising Toll on Outdoor Workers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276275</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/climate-change-and-hard-labor-the-rising-toll-on-outdoor-workers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T10:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governments and employers are slow to adapt to the risk to workers of higher outdoor temperatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Despite the Recession-Emergency-Rate-Cut Buffoonery, the Services Sector Expands Strongly on Growth in New Orders & Employment. Inflation Pressures Still On]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276280</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/despite-the-recession-emergency-rate-cut-buffoonery-the-services-sector-expands-strongly-on-growth-in-new-orders-employment-inflation-pressures-still-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T10:15:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Services are two-thirds of the economy; as long as they’re firm, the economy will plug along just fine, even as manufacturing stalled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yves Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ussama Makdisi: &ldquo;Overwriting Palestine&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/overwriting-palestine</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/overwriting-palestine"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T08:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The complicity of the academy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Undemocratic Reality of Capitalism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329984</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/the-undemocratic-reality-of-capitalism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T06:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans of capitalism like to say it is democratic or that it supports democracy. Some have stretched language so far as to literally equate capitalism with democracy, using the terms interchangeably. No matter how many times that is repeated, it is simply not true and never was. Indeed, it is much more accurate to say that capitalism and democracy are opposites. To see why, you have only to look at capitalism as a production system where employees enter into a relationship with employers, where a few people are the boss, and most people simply work doing what they are told to do. That relationship is not democratic; it is autocratic. More
The post The Undemocratic Reality of Capitalism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard D. Wolff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can the Left Support Resistance in Venezuela Without Promoting US Hegemony?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329989</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/can-the-left-support-resistance-in-venezuela-without-promoting-us-hegemony/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Distance and lack of information allows orientalists to misrepresent the people and contexts of the Global South. In doing so it denies their full humanity. Given that it is generally done as a way of engaging in the politics of the Global North -- broadly understood to include the identity-work of individuals and groups as well -- it is a form of imperialism. It essentially uses the Global South as a resource base for consumption in the Global North.  More
The post Can the Left Support Resistance in Venezuela Without Promoting US Hegemony? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Falcone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rape & Genocide: the Israeli War Machine We Support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330121</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/rape-genocide-the-israeli-war-machine-we-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The headline above is outrageous and incendiary – it is also unquestionably true. We have a duty to bear witness to what the Palestinians must endure. The great Israeli journalist Gideon Levy wrote powerfully a couple of days ago about the rape culture that is part of the Israeli war machine.  Riots occurred at the  More
The post Rape & Genocide: the Israeli War Machine We Support appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eugene Doyle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role of Ancient DNA in Modern Traits]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330122</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/the-role-of-ancient-dna-in-modern-traits/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ancient human retrovirus DNA could be one of the markers of susceptibility to mental illness—specifically schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, and major depressive disorder, a new study suggests. An international team of researchers examined 732 post-mortem brain samples and identified variations in DNA associated with different psychiatric conditions, which they cross-referenced with data from large genetic studies.  More
The post The Role of Ancient DNA in Modern Traits appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marjorie Hecht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Learned Helplessness” and the 2024 Election]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330095</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/learned-helplessness-and-the-2024-election/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine my surprise when, nearly eight months ago, commenting on the state of the country as it approached the 2024 presidential election, New York Times columnist Michelle Goldberg noted that “Biden has set himself the task of trying to jolt the country out of its learned helplessness in the face of Trump’s exhausting provocations.” Unbeknownst to most Americans, that  More
The post “Learned Helplessness” and the 2024 Election appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karen J. Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bombs Bursting in Air]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330101</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/bombs-bursting-in-air/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Responding to the announcer’s familiar, “ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls, please rise for our national anthem,” I stood at a recent baseball game, but Francis Scott Key’s lyrics transported me from the cheerful families around me to distant families, similarly innocent and civilian, besieged in Ukraine and Gaza. Two centuries have passed since Key  More
The post Bombs Bursting in Air appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Vandenbroucke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing the Light of Secular Humanism]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330097</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/seeing-the-light-of-secular-humanism/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The invention of the telescope was more important than that of the steam engine, the transistor, the internet, or artificial intelligence. The telescope changed humankind’s understanding of the world. The Greek philosopher, Aristarchus, conceived of a heliocentric solar system in which the planets revolved around the sun. Christian revelation preached an opposing view, that the  More
The post Seeing the Light of Secular Humanism appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Topper</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret to Tax-Dodging in America: Be Rich]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329940</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/the-secret-to-tax-dodging-in-america-be-rich/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By all appearances, Donald Trump has cut a sweet deal with a dozen or two of America’s richest billionaires: Finance his campaign and he’ll keep their federal taxes super low — or even lower them — once he’s sitting back in the White House. How much do billionaires like this deal? This much: In April,  More
The post The Secret to Tax-Dodging in America: Be Rich appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Lord</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bad Was the July Jobs Report?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329978</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/how-bad-was-the-july-jobs-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After arguing for over a year that it was time for the Fed to start lowering rates to avoid an economic slowdown, I feel a need to give a bit of pushback against all the folks who are now rushing to agree with me. To be clear, I absolutely think the Fed should lower rates,  More
The post How Bad Was the July Jobs Report? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dean Baker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project 2025 and Some Poison Gas for the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330099</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/project-2025-and-some-poison-gas-for-the-future/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T05:22:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The right-wing Republicans . . . the Christian nationalists . . . have hoisted their flag: Project 2025, a.k.a., Project Hell on Earth, and it’s coming to a future near you. Or so they believe (and hope). But the Democrats are on our side! They won’t let it happen, right? While the deep right puts forth  More
The post Project 2025 and Some Poison Gas for the Future appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Koehler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by alvah in "Google loses antitrust suit over search deals on phones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41167740</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41167740"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T04:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["They simply have a better product"
I disagree. 100% they had a better product, but they have absolutely mangled it over the last few updates. Honestly, if I wanted the opinion of randomnumbers45123 on Reddit, I'd just search Reddit.
Google achieved dominance ~25 years ago by being better than the alternatives, and the other search engines pretty much withered away rapidly. They (Google) are in a very precarious position right now. They will certainly not disappear overnight, but if / when the public becomes aware of something better, the implosion could be spectacular.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>alvah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shaky Sheehy Calls for Dubious Reinforcements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329986</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/06/shaky-sheehy-calls-for-dubious-reinforcements/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T04:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It appears Tim Sheehy, hand-picked by Republican Party honchos to challenge Jon Tester for one of Montana’s Senate seats, must be feeling a little shaky about the race. Despite tons of out-of-state money flowing into his campaign Sheehy apparently thinks the increasingly befuddled Donald Trump will come to his rescue in Bozeman next week. What’s  More
The post Shaky Sheehy Calls for Dubious Reinforcements appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>George Ochenski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by epolanski in "Launch HN: Airhart Aeronautics (YC S22) – A modern personal airplane"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41166423</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41166423"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T23:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's insane the length we go as humans (in the US at least) to not invest in the easiest, most cost-effective and environmentally friendly mode of transportation: trains.
Hyperloops, wider and wider highways, now personal airplanes.
Anything but goddamn trains.
It's mental to me.
Wish the best to the startup, after all they are filling a void someone else would, but still, not happy with the direction transport is going, which seems backwards sometimes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>epolanski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Investigation of a Cross-regional Network Performance Issue]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/422d6218fdf1</id>
        <link href="https://netflixtechblog.com/investigation-of-a-cross-regional-network-performance-issue-422d6218fdf1?source=rss----2615bd06b42e---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T22:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hechao Li, Roger Cruz]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Netflix Technology Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stone Yard Devotional by Charlotte Wood included on Booker Prize longlist]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8154</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/stone-yard-devotional-charlotte-wood-booker-prize-longlist/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T21:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sydney based Australian author Charlotte Wood has been included on the 2024 longlist for the Booker Prize, with her latest novel, Stone Yard Devotional. It is the first time a work by an Australian writer has featured on the Booker longlist since 2016. I’m reading Stone Yard Devotional right now, and loving it. Some reviewers […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hudson on Super Imperialism 2]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45515</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/05/hudson-on-super-imperialism-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T20:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[from Asad Zaman and WEA Pedagogy Blog This is the second post in a sequence explaining post WW2 USA strategies for global dominance. For the previous post, see: Hudson on Super Imperialism 1 U.S. Financial Strategies for Global Dominance  Introduction: Michael Hudson, in his podcast and writings, provides a profound critique of the U.S.’s economic and financial […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asad Zaman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[disassociated turns twenty-one again, sort of]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8185</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/disassociated-turns-twenty-one-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T20:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is — again: sort of — /timeline page content, which seems to be a bit popular on InterWebs and IndieWeb at the moment. Today — or rather last Sunday 4 August 2024 — does not really mark the twenty-first birthday of disassociated. That would’ve been back in 2018, given the first non-blog inception of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insects: Apocalypse Soon?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276235</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/insects-apocalypse-soon.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T19:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world-wide decline of insect populations, strengths and weaknesses of the studies, causes and effects]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by sethkim in "Launch HN: Airhart Aeronautics (YC S22) – A modern personal airplane"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164783</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164783"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T19:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instrument-rated pilot (and engineer) here.
First - congrats on the launch! I think you're working on an interesting set of components that will prove useful to GA aircraft technology. Bringing fly-by-wire, and lowering the cost of maintenance/manufacturing are both great efforts.
That being said, my personal view is that stick-and-rudder control is one of the less critical components to improving GA safety. Everything else - flight planning, comms, automation, navigation, weather, inspections, procedures, regs, and most importantly - working in the federal airspace system - are the "hard" parts of flying and where problems tend to occur. It's common belief that single-pilot IFR is the most challenging type of flying, because of how much you have to do all at once.
It may sound snobby - but I'm not super excited about the idea of lowering the barrier to entry for GA on a foundational skill basis. Like the light-sport rating, it encourages more people to be in the (already congested) airspace system who haven't really gained all the other skills necessary or experience to be there.
To be clear - I think improving technology and lowering costs = good. Lowering early-skill requirements for pilots and pushing more people without all the other skills into federal airspace = very bad. In general, I'd frame this effort more as an effort to raise the bar for system technology, not lower the bar to become a pilot in the first place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sethkim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by cletus in "Google loses antitrust suit over search deals on phones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164566</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164566"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T19:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I expect this to be bad for everyone except Google if the ruling holds. Why? Mozilla and Apple will lose significant revenue from having Google as the default search engine and Google will no longer have to pay those billions. What's more, no one else can pay to be the default either (eg the short-lived Mozilla Bing deal).
So what's going to happen? Most users will probably still use Google, nobody is getting paid and Google is saving a bundle.
I get the thinking that you have to prevent lock-in (eg Ticketmaster and venues) but Google didn't buy its way into dominance annd maintain their dominance through exclusivity deals. They simply have a better product and I don't expect anyone to match them anytime soon (cue the DDG "I switched from Google to DDG 78 years ago" crowd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>cletus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hugh_kagi in "Google loses antitrust suit over search deals on phones"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164462</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41164462"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T19:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We face a number of challenges simply letting our paying customers change their search engine:
1. On iOS the list of allowed search engines is simply baked into OS, we have a fiddly extension that hooks outbound calls to /search and redirects them but I wish we didn't need to.
2. On Chrome, we use an extension to change the default search engine and enable search auto-complete etc, but Google has a policy that such an extension can do one thing and one thing only, and recently removed our extension on account of that [1]. We rebuilt it to meet their needs but had a lot of back-and-forth because we included 'search by image' on a context menu item and the first reviewer felt that was a bridge too far. You'll note that Chrome provides such a context menu item for Google Image search out of the box.
3. On Chrome for Linux, the default search engine API is not available, so Linux users have to configure it manually through a series of silly steps [2]. This is at least in keeping with most Linux experiences.
There are other issues, but I say all this to highlight how surprisingly difficult it is to change this setting in a practical, consumer friendly way. It is most certainly this difficult by design, that's a lot of revenue to protect.
1: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41028924
2: https://github.com/kagisearch/chrome_extension_basic?tab=rea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hugh_kagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2:00PM Water Cooler 8/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276239</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/200pm-water-cooler-8-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T18:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[~ Today's Water Cooler: Open Thread ~]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q Business, AWS CloudFormation, Amazon WorkSpaces update, and more (Aug 5, 2024)]]></title>
        <id>02edb4f291249e0bfbd2cfefedc5df1d39555858</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/aws-weekly-roundup-amazon-q-business-aws-cloudformation-amazon-workspaces-update-and-more-aug-5-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T17:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is reaching its peak for some of us around the globe, and many are heading out to their favorite holiday destinations to enjoy some time off. I just came back from holidays myself and I couldn’t help thinking about the key role that artificial intelligence (AI) plays in our modern world to help us […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matheus Guimaraes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the IndieWeb even?]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/what-is-the-indieweb-even/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/what-is-the-indieweb-even/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T16:56:14.324Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've been into running a blog or personal site very long, it's safe to say you've heard the terms "IndieWeb" or "small web" thrown around. I've only been into this stuff for a few months at this point but my understanding of what that actually means has already matured and evolved a lot.
Really, any personal website you use (instead of corporate social media) for your online presence is part of the IndieWeb. It's like independent music. You're writing, recording and distributing all on your own rather than finding a manager, record label, big name recording studio and getting wrapped up in contracts.
It's pretty punk, actually. Running your own corner of the internet is like recording an album in your bedroom and then selling it at the shows you independently worked with bars and venu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Video Games I've Owned and Played]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/video-games-ive-owned-and-played/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/video-games-ive-owned-and-played/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T16:08:19.634Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Inspired by Lou and Kerri's post about video games, I thought I'd talk a little bit about my seemingly random history of video games I've owned and played in the past.
Disclaimer: I don’t really play a lot of video games, back then and now. There were a few over the years that I enjoyed playing occasionally, but I never really got too obsessed over any of them.
Some of the ones I remember playing on the PC:
Oregon Trail: Probably one of the first PC games I ever played.
Math Blasters: My parents believed that if I were to play “video games,” I might as well learn at the same time. I surprisingly enjoyed this, despite my aversion to math.
Mavis Beacon Teaches Typing: I don’t think this is considered a video game, but this was the story of my childhood. A little bit of fun, with a mixture of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RoCE networks for distributed AI training at scale]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21522</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/05/data-center-engineering/roce-network-distributed-ai-training-at-scale/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T16:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI networks play an important role in interconnecting tens of thousands of GPUs together, forming the foundational infrastructure for training, enabling large models with hundreds of billions of parameters such as LLAMA 3.1 405B. This week at ACM SIGCOMM 2024 in Sydney, Australia, we are sharing details on the network we have built at Meta [...]
Read More...
The post RoCE networks for distributed AI training at scale appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DCPerf: An open source benchmark suite for hyperscale compute applications]]></title>
        <id>https://engineering.fb.com/?p=21502</id>
        <link href="https://engineering.fb.com/2024/08/05/data-center-engineering/dcperf-open-source-benchmark-suite-for-hyperscale-compute-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T15:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are open-sourcing DCPerf, a collection of benchmarks that represents the diverse categories of workloads that run in data center cloud deployments. We hope that DCperf can be used more broadly by academia, the hardware industry, and internet companies to design and evaluate future products. DCPerf is available now on GitHub. Hyperscale and cloud datacenter [...]
Read More...
The post DCPerf: An open source benchmark suite for hyperscale compute applications appeared first on Engineering at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Engineering at Meta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C. L. James - Anarchy]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/c-l-james-anarchy?v=1722868773</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/c-l-james-anarchy?v=1722868773"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: C. L. James
Title: Anarchy
Subtitle: A Tract for the Times
Date: 1886
Source: Retrieved on 2nd August 2024 from archive.org

 I claim credit for no originality on account of the pages which follow, except such as may be implied in putting together the discoveries of my predecessors so that they may support and illustrate each other better than this has been done previously. 
 Anarchy, from the Greek a or an (not) and arche (the first, the chief) or archon (a magistrate) means that state of society in which there is no government. It is, therefore, very improperly applied to that state in which there are two, or more, governments contending for the supremacy. What Anarchists desire, is the permanent abolition of all government. It is contended, and is doubtless true, that this would…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Brother Thinks My Blog is Broken (He Might Be Right)]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/brother-blog-broken/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/brother-blog-broken/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Long after I'd finished creating the theme for this blog, I still thought the design was spot on (and still do). It's the ideal theme in my opinion.
Recently, I asked my brother for his thoughts. He replied: "It looks like the site is broken. There are no images or anything. It's so incredibly boring!"
I'd never seen it that way, but I understand his point... haha. It's true what they say, beauty is in the eye of the beholder. When it comes to the look of this blog, I think more people agree with him than me.
Anyway, that, combined with Lou's post Website Fiddling, has inspired me to start working on a new design. It's always exciting and inspiring to try something different.
I plan to use Bear's official theme as a starting point and customize it here and there. I'm also considering some larger changes as separate 'add-ons'.
If I finish it, anyone is welcome to use it. I'm not a professional designer (and have a full-time job), so Bear with me — it might take a while...or never get finished.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C. L. James - Origin of Anarchism]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/c-l-james-origin-of-anarchism?v=1722867578</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/c-l-james-origin-of-anarchism?v=1722867578"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: C. L. James
Title: Origin of Anarchism
Date: 1902
Source: Retrieved on 3rd August 2024 from archive.org

 Anarchism, it can hardly be necessary to say, is not a conspiracy for the assassination of kings and such-like. It is not an armed movement of the proletariat or of a part of them. It is not a secret organization. Notions of its nature such as people of information have abandoned to journalists, journalists to politicians, and politicians to Mr. Roosevelt, require no further refutation. Anarchism, whatever it may give rise to, can be described as a theory only. The thesis of Anarchism is that men govern men by deceiving them — a view never very unfamiliar to statesmen like Machiavelli, but which evidently assumes a somewhat novel complexion when preached to the people who are g…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial Workers of the World - Constitution of the Industrial Workers of the World]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/constitution-of-the-industrial-workers-of-the-world?v=1722863698</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/constitution-of-the-industrial-workers-of-the-world?v=1722863698"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T13:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Industrial Workers of the World
Title: Constitution of the Industrial Workers of the World
Date: January 1, 2022
Source: https://www.iww.org/constitution/

Preamble
 The working class and the employing class have nothing in common. 
 There can be no peace so long as hunger and want are found among millions of the working people and the few, who make up the employing class, have all the good things of life. 
 Between these two classes a struggle must go on until the workers of the world organise as a class, take possession of the means of production, abolish the wage system, and live in harmony with the earth. 
 We find that the centering of the management of industries into fewer and fewer hands makes the trade unions unable to cope with the evergrowing power of the employing class…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The DeFi Intermediation Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/?p=30916</id>
        <link href="https://libertystreeteconomics.newyorkfed.org/2024/08/the-defi-intermediation-chain/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Finance, or DeFi, is a rapidly growing ecosystem of financial applications built on blockchain technology, primarily on the Ethereum network. These applications aim to recreate traditional financial instruments and services, such as lending, borrowing, trading, and insurance. The DeFi intermediation chain connects a series of intermediaries who find arbitrage opportunities, aggregate transactions into blocks, validate these blocks, and ultimately append them to the blockchain. In this post, we summarize results from our staff report describing how arbitrage opportunities arise in the Ethereum blockchain, and how the need to keep these arbitrage opportunities private gives rise to the intermediation chain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo D. Azar, Adrian G. Casillas, and Maryam Farboodi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Links 8/5/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/?p=276211</id>
        <link href="https://www.nakedcapitalism.com/2024/08/links-8-5-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T10:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Our astronomical daily links]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lambert Strether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Students in Bangladesh Are Challenging a Repressive System]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Students-in-Bangladesh-Are-Challenging-a-Repressive-System</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Students-in-Bangladesh-Are-Challenging-a-Repressive-System"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T07:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repression of student protests in Bangladesh has killed almost 200 people. The protests began over the allocation of government jobs but developed into a wider challenge to a ruling party that's out of touch and increasingly authoritarian. 
English

/ 
Social movements, 
Bangladesh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sushovan Dhar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When ‘Prophets’ Become Memes: Rise and Fall of Benjamin Netanyahu]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329876</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/when-prophets-become-memes-rise-and-fall-of-benjamin-netanyahu/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T06:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Great orators in history would not have been recognized as such if their words carried no value. Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is neither a great orator, nor did his speech before a joint Congressional session on July 24 have actual worth. It was an expression of his desperation, if not defeat, on all fronts.
This is not new. For years, Netanyahu has served the role of a social media meme. During his United Nations General Assembly speech in September 2012, the Israeli leader displayed a bomb diagram to fan the flames for another Middle East war. More
The post When ‘Prophets’ Become Memes: Rise and Fall of Benjamin Netanyahu appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramzy Baroud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former IDF Sniper Says Dehumanization of Palestinians and a Rhetoric of Hate is Driving Israel’s Forever War in Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329931</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/former-idf-sniper-says-dehumanization-of-palestinians-and-a-rhetoric-of-hate-is-driving-israels-forever-war-in-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T06:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IDF soldiers continue to slaughter Palestinians with an apparent absence of remorse or empathy. That, says Nadav Weiman, is driven in large part by the rhetoric constantly fed to them, and in particular, the use of the term ‘Amalek’. It refers to an Old Testament commandment to wipe out all Amalekians for attacking Jews as they left Egypt, and not to spare their children or livestock while destroying everything they owned. More
The post Former IDF Sniper Says Dehumanization of Palestinians and a Rhetoric of Hate is Driving Israel’s Forever War in Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Linda Pentz Gunter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Election Theater in Venezuela: a Tale From Election Day in Caracas]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330014</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/election-theater-in-venezuela-a-tale-from-election-day-in-caracas/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I covered Venezuela’s 3-week presidential campaign season, the elections, and their fallout for TeleSur English, the multilateral public TV news network funded by the governments of Bolivia, Cuba, Nicaragua, and Venezuela. I am an experienced analyst on Brazilian politics, but I do not claim to be a specialist on Venezuela. The following is not analysis  More
The post Election Theater in Venezuela: a Tale From Election Day in Caracas appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Mier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli Soldiers Will Soon Find Ways to Tell Their Media About the Terror Inside Gaza]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=329999</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/israeli-soldiers-will-soon-find-ways-to-tell-their-media-about-the-terror-inside-gaza/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Israeli soldiers, like soldiers in other countries, bask in the self-serving effusive praise showered upon them by politicians, but privately they know BS when they hear it. Right from the start on October 7th, the soldiers knew that the sudden collapse of Netanyahu’s state-of-the-art multi-tiered border defense system left the door open for the Hamas  More
The post Israeli Soldiers Will Soon Find Ways to Tell Their Media About the Terror Inside Gaza appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Nader</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kamala Harris: Papier-mâché Coronation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330017</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/kamala-harris-papier-mache-coronation/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How aristocratic it all sounds, if only in a playground, papier-mâché sense.  The language of the estates, the “crowning,” the “coronation,” words repurposed for republican politics, is much in evidence with Kamala Harris, who is all but guaranteed formal nomination at the Democratic Party Convention as US presidential candidate.  She has now secured the necessary votes from Democratic delegates,  More
The post Kamala Harris: Papier-mâché Coronation appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Binoy Kampmark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Imperial Presidency: From Gitmo to Trump v. US and Back Again]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330024</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/the-imperial-presidency-from-gitmo-to-trump-v-us-and-back-again/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 31, retired brigadier general Susan K. Escallier signed a pretrial agreement under which Walid Muhammad Salih Mubarak bin Attash, and Mustafa Ahmed Adam al-Hawsawi would have pleaded guilty to various roles in the terror attacks of 9/11 in return for sentences of life imprisonment rather than the death penalty. On August 1, bending  More
The post The Imperial Presidency: From Gitmo to Trump v. US and Back Again appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Knapp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does Arming Israel Cost?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330023</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/what-does-arming-israel-cost/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:55:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What will it take to end Israel’s genocide in Gaza? That’s the question confounding people of conscience all over the world since last October. After Israeli citizens, tax-paying residents of the United States have the most leverage over the perpetrators of genocide given that the U.S. is Israel’s biggest weapons supplier. What if our taxes were  More
The post What Does Arming Israel Cost? appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonali Kolhatkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trump’s Battle for US Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://www.counterpunch.org/?p=330020</id>
        <link href="https://www.counterpunch.org/2024/08/05/trumps-battle-for-us-sports/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T05:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following conservative outrage over the 2024 Summer Olympics opening ceremony and, in particular, the depiction of a scene resembling that in Last Supper, former U.S. President Donald Trump labeled the spectacle a disgrace. The comments marked the most recent effort by the 2024 Republican presidential nominee to merge politics with sports and echoed other right-wing figures across Europe as  More
The post Trump’s Battle for US Sports appeared first on CounterPunch.org.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John P. Ruehl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by jseliger in "Starting Hospice"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41158171</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41158171"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T04:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hacker News, thank you for all the links and all the great reading. Now I have to say goodbye.
I’m with my wife Bess (https://bessstillman.substack.com/) and my brother Sam, and crying, but it is okay. At the end of Lord of the Rings Gandalf says to the hobbits, "Go in peace! I will not say: do not weep; for not all tears are an evil.” And that is how I feel now. Ending prematurely hurts, but all things must end, and my time to end is upon me.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jseliger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by aetherspawn in "How I Program in 2024"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157813</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157813"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T03:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you have no tests your problems go away because you don’t see any test failures.
Never have I tested anything and NOT found a bug, and most things I tested I thought were already OK to ship.
Thus, when you delete your tests, the only person you are fooling is probably yourself :(
From reading your page I get the impression you are more burnt out from variation/configuration management which is completely relatable… I am too. This is a hard problem. But user volume is required to make $$. If the problem was easy then the market would be saturated with one size fits all solutions for everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aetherspawn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gentle in "Airlines are running out of 4-digit flight numbers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157691</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157691"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T02:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I love that so many people here think they can think about the problem for 10 seconds and come up with a solution that hasn't already been considered a thousand times and discarded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gentle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by zeagle in "Airlines are running out of 4-digit flight numbers"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157666</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41157666"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T02:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clearly the successor solution is to use eight groups of four hexadecimal digits each, separated by colons. Then each individual seat and peanut could be addressed to it's final destination.
More seriously the solution suggested of giving the 3 companies other unused prefixes like D* U* and A* to use with their codeshares and non rev flights to start seems the easiest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>zeagle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Echoes, a new novel by Evie Wyld, author of The Bass Rock]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8150</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/the-echoes-a-new-novel-by-evie-wyld-author-of-the-bass-rock/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T21:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[London based Anglo-Australian author Evie Wyld’s 2021 novel, The Bass Rock, which won the Stellar Prize literary award in the same year, was a riveting read. Her new book, The Echoes, looks like it will follow suit, given it incorporates elements of The Bass Rock, including settings across several locations and time, and a dollop […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the Australian winter 2024 colder than normal?]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8146</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/australian-winter-2024-colder-normal/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T20:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It depends how you define normal. Winter this year, or certainly in July, and absolutely since the recent Sudden Stratospheric Warming event, has felt distinctly chillier. But the bad news is, no this winter, when compared to the long term average, isn’t all that much cooler than “normal”. Despite the relatively cool conditions, most capitals […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by mbreese in "WhenFS: Calendar Is Now a File System"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41155382</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41155382"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T18:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Why Did You Do This?
> I used this project as an opportunity to learn about Rust and FUSE file systems. I also think it's hilarious.
> Visitors interested in the code should note that this is 
 an irredeemably messy codebase—it's full of hacks, unidiomatic code, and wildly poor design decisions.
> However, visitors should also 
note that that's okay. The 
best way to learn something 
new is to try it out for 
yourself—and creating a mess 
is a vital part of that 
process.
I absolutely love this sentiment. Why do this? Because it’s fun. And messy. And sometimes, that’s okay. Not everything needs to be a product… sometimes it’s enough to do something because you can… or want to… or because $RANDOM reason. I’m very grateful to the author and whoever decided to submit it today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>mbreese</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Plan to Not Have a Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-plan-to-not-have-a-plan/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/the-plan-to-not-have-a-plan/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T15:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my first Blaugust post, I insinuated that I had a plan on how I’m going to tackle this month’s blogging challenge.
I'll make a plan (of some sort) of how I'm going to tackle this at some point.
The truth is, my plan going into this is to not have a plan.
I joined the IndieWeb blogging community at the very tail end of March. In April, I joined a daily photo challenge hosted by Micro.blog. It was my very first challenge and had no idea what to expect. I enjoyed posting a photo a day alongside a community based on a specific prompt. I felt that sort of camraderie feeling amongst a blogging community I haven’t felt in a very long time.
That one was easy. I didn’t stress out about it because photos tend to come easier to me than words. I had a collection of photos I could dig into to meet t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So good, they can't ignore you]]></title>
        <id>https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/</id>
        <link href="https://kartikay.bearblog.dev/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I came across this concept reading a book with the same name as the title of this post. The author makes the argument that we have been led astray by the passion hypothesis. Passion is fickle and hard to define in some cases. What we really want is freedom and autonomy in the work we do. A sense of ownership and a feeling of contribution.
But there is no free lunch. You want rainbows and unicorns at work but what do you bring in exchange? You bring a skillset. Something you are so godamn good in that they can't help but hire you. Can't help but give you freedom, autonomy, and ownership. The ability to set your own hours and work on the things you like.
This is even more relevant when you are building a product. The typical indie hacking advice is to iterate fast and throw a bunch of things at the wall. See what sticks. Probably good advice to make some money but always felt like a pussy move to me. What you make is determined by the whims and fancies of the initial audience.
What happened to being that intense 'Steve Job' type of founder? YOU believe in the product with such fervor that DAMN the market. They will buy it and they will like it. You have a vision. And the habits of the people and the market will change to serve it.
It goes beyond just being so good that you cannot be ignored. No. This is a different level. You don't just move through the world, the world moves to accommodate your passing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[endings and beginnings]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/endings-and-beginnings/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/endings-and-beginnings/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T08:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The summer term is over! I'm back in my hometown, bothering my dogs and following my grandmother around the house like a little kid. I was hoping to get 100s all around this term, but I messed up one arts assignment, so I'm afraid I'll have to settle for almost there. I'll need all the tiny boosts I can get from electives if I want to graduate on time and with honors in two years. Agh.
School aside, there's nothing much to write about today. The sky's been cloudy but bright the whole day, like the sun is playing hide-and-seek with the intention of being found. I ate banana bread and another unidentified sweet bread someone brought back from a trip. The banana bread was okay, but the other one (milk? Butter? Just normal sugary bread?) was really good. Thank God for bread.
I'm starting and abandoning so many new posts. I couldn't settle on any of them, so I decided to do this one instead. Hope you had some good bread in your life today!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday photoblogging: Dean Lane]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52950</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/04/sunday-photoblogging-dean-lane/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T06:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visit the post for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Bertram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by lolinder in "The introverts are winning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151359</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151359"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T05:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> Everyone knew there were introverts and extroverts, homebodies and socialites, but it had never really mattered. The two groups complemented each other and managed to peacefully cohabit.
What a very extroverted perspective. "Everything was fine when the world was structured around an extroverted lifestyle. Then the pandemic hit and everything was miserable for a bit, but what's even worse is that those darn introverts aren't happy resuming their natural place in society!"
The pandemic gave us a taste of what life could be like if the world were structured around our preferred way of existing instead of yours. It turns out we liked it, and now that we've had that taste we're not comfortable resuming the old status quo where we just tag along for the ride in an extroverted world.
It boggles my mind that someone can write an article like this and not realize that what they're saying is they wish a group of people would go back to being an underclass.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>lolinder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by interroboink in "The introverts are winning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151285</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151285"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T05:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Must it be a war? Must there be a winner?
I think it's good that the status quo got mixed up a bit. The introverts don't have to defend themselves or feel like outsiders quite so much.
This article aligns stay-at-home-ness with "fear," "a fettered life," "hardly worth living" and says "retreating ... is an ultimately selfish choice." I believe that's a bit of a poor take. Plenty of people live rich, productive, fulfilling and engaged lives that don't especially involve a lot of interactions with other people.
This author is clearly someone whose habits were impinged by the changes brought on by the pandemic ("... naturally outgoing people – this writer included – have found it that bit harder to get their friends out of the house."), but is that the end of the world?
It almost feels like the author is eager to get back to what they are comfortable with, at the expense of (by their numbers) 1/3 of other people's lifestyles. It's almost like they are the ones afraid of this change — like they are the selfish ones.
But I don't really go for the whole us-vs-them approach at all. It has been a great (if forced) learning experience. Some people got to discover happiness they didn't know before. Other people felt the loss of something they took for granted. Perhaps we should share these lessons with each other and bring some balance and increased awareness, rather than pointing fingers and taking sides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>interroboink</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be embarrassed]]></title>
        <id>https://grubz.blog/dont-be-embarrassed/</id>
        <link href="https://grubz.blog/dont-be-embarrassed/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T04:49:24.178Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hate that lol you're nervous about something and someone tells you aw don't be nervous!
Or you're stressing over something and they scream at you to CALM THE FUCK DOWN!!
Oh okay! I didn't think about it that way! I'm so silly 🤪
For real though, one of the things about getting older is caring less about what people think. I used to think my dad looked so lame wearing 10 year old, $7 jeans from Walmart, generic black tennis shoes and a plain solid color tee shirt all the time like he's some kinda Seinfeld character. Meanwhile I was straightening my blonde emo-ver hair, wearing skin tight skinny jeans with a pink studded belt from Spencer's and walking around in loud, multicolor, just... massive tongued skating shoes.
These days, half the time I'm at work anyway so I'm wearing a long-sleev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by tptacek in "How I Use "AI""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151098</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41151098"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T04:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a running theme in here of programming problems LLMs solve where it's actually not that important that the LLM is perfectly correct. I've been using GPT4 for the past couple months to comprehend Linux kernel code; it's spooky good at it.
I'm a C programmer, so I can with some effort gradually work my way through random Linux kernel things. But what I can do now instead is take a random function, ask GPT4 what it does and what subsystem it belongs to, and then ask GPT4 to write me a dummy C program that exercises that subsystem (I've taken to asking it to rewrite kernel code in Python, just because it's more concise and easy to read).
I don't worry at all about GPT4 hallucinating stuff (I'm sure it's doing that all the time!), because I'm just using its output as Cliff's Notes for the actual kernel code; GPT4 isn't the "source of truth" in this situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tptacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ethics and Education: Touchy Subject]]></title>
        <id>https://crookedtimber.org/?p=52947</id>
        <link href="https://crookedtimber.org/2024/08/03/ethics-and-education-touchy-subject/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T20:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I think I’ve mentioned before that the Center of which I am director produces a podcast called Ethics and Education which is about… ethics and education. Just to be clear: the producer/director/voice artist/supremo is Carrie Welsh, and my involvement is mainly as a sounding board about topics and how to approach them, and doing whatever […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by gumby in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41148714</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41148714"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T19:38:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Astonishingly, It took a long time for revision control to become widespread.
Around 1991 when Cygnus had 6-7 employees and was based in the apartment complex where I lived, none of the GNU codebase was hosted in any sort of revision control.  Everything was FTPed around as obscurely named tarballs.  We had gathered something like 27 different forks of gdb floating around the net, for example.  This was back when forking was generally considered a tragedy, something I managed to change five or six years later).
Rich Pixley came and said “all of our code should be in revision control, and I want to use this newfangled thing called CVS.”  Michael was OK with it but John and I were steadfastly opposed.  We agreed to an experiment, grudgingly, subject to a whole whiteboard of absurd conditions (“must be transparently integrated into emacs so we don’t have to know it’s there).
Pixley agreed to all of that and then ignored all of it completely.  It was immediately such a win that everybody adopted it without complaint, including us two obstreperous a-holes.
A few years later a preventable crisis was how revision control first became client-server.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>gumby</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by apwell23 in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41148226</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41148226"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T18:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> and it still passed all the tests
All his sins can be forgiven because he made it so easy to refactor by writing comprehensive tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>apwell23</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Community]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/importance-community/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/importance-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T17:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I realized that the past three days share something important and beautiful: community.
Today, the pride parade took place here in Stockholm. I met up with my mom, sister, her husband, and their kids, who had come to the city for the occasion. It was wonderful sharing the event with them.
Yesterday, I decided to return to Mastodon. I missed the community and created a new account (birming@social.lol). Thank you all for the warm welcome. You're amazing!
The day before yesterday, I decided to continue this blog. Since then, I've received wonderful feedback from you readers. It's made me happy, grateful, and motivated. Thank you all!
Three days, three different experiences, but one common thread: community. It's easy to overlook this invaluable aspect of life. However, when it's absent, we truly understand its significance.
So, dear friends, thank you for being part of my life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by fouronnes3 in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147832</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147832"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T17:15:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is amazing. I can so well imagine a bright young hire joining that team, helpfully offering to "setup this thing called git" only to be laughed out of the meeting by all the "senior" staff.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>fouronnes3</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by hleszek in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147787</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147787"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T17:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I started at my first company, they had a very complex VB application running on dozens of customers around the country, each having some particular needs of course.
There was a LOT of global variables (seemingly random 4 uppercase letters) controlling everything.
At some point, the application had some bugs which were not appearing when the application was run in debug mode in Visual Studio. The solution was obvious: installing Visual Studio for each customer on site and teaching the users to run the app in debug mode from Visual Studio. I don't know how they convinced the users to do this and how they managed with the license but it was done.
What happened next was even worse.
There was no version control of course, the code being available on a shared disk on the local network of the company with the code copied over in multiple folders each having its own version, with no particular logic to it either, V1, V2, V2.3, V2a, V2_customer_name, V2_customer_name_fix, ...
After that, when there was a problem for a customer, the programmer went there to debug and modified the code on site. If the bug/problem was impacting other customers, we had to dispatch some guys for each customer to go copy/edit the code for all of them. But if the problem was minor, it was just modified there, and probably saved on the shared folder in some new folder.
What happened next was to be expected: there was no consensus on what was the final version, each customer having slightly different versions, with some still having bugs fixed years before for others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hleszek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by dmd in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147297</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147297"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T15:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Probably some of the worst code I ever worked on was a 12k+ line single file Perl script for dealing with Human Genome Project data, at Bristol-Myers Squibb, in the late 1990s.
The primary author of it didn't know about arrays. I'm not sure if he didn't know about them being something that had already been invented, or whether he just didn't know Perl supported them, but either way, he reimplemented them himself on top of scalars (strings), using $foo and $foo_offsets. For example, $foo might be "romemcintoshgranny smithdelicious" and $foo_offsets = "000004012024", where he assumes the offsets are 3 digits each. And then he loops through slices (how does he know about slices, but not arrays?) of $foo_offsets to get the locations for $foo.
By the time I was done refactoring that 12k+ was down to about 200 ... and it still passed all the tests and ran analyses identically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>dmd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by josephcsible in "Clang vs. Clang"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147014</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41147014"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T15:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[> compiler writers refuse to take responsibility for the bugs they introduced, even though the compiled code worked fine before the "optimizations". The excuse for not taking responsibility is that there are "language standards" saying that these bugs should be blamed on millions of programmers writing code that bumps into "undefined behavior"
But that's not an excuse for having a bug; it's the exact evidence that it's not a bug at all. Calling the compiler buggy for not doing what you want when you commit Undefined Behavior is like calling dd buggy for destroying your data when you call it with the wrong arguments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>josephcsible</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by Nexialist in ""We ran out of columns""]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41146789</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41146789"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T14:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My worst codebase story:
In my first real job, I worked for a company that maintained a large legacy product programmed in a combination of COBOL and Java.
In order to work on the Java side of the product, you checked out individual files from source control to work on, which 'locked' the files and prevented other developers from checking out the same files. This functionality was not part of our actual source control system, but was instead accomplished with a series of csh shell scripts you could run after ssh'ing into our development server.
Each of our customers had a 'master' jar file that represented the actual final compiled product (a jar file is really a zip file archive, which bundles together the resulting compiled java class files).
Once you had finished implementing your code changes, you ran another set of scripts which found the master jar file for each customer, unzips it, copies the compiled files from your local machine into it, and zips it back up again. Finally the source control lock is released.
This means, effectively, that the codebase was never compiled as a whole at any point in the process, instead, we just manually patched the jar file over time with individually compiled class files.
Over the years, small errors in the process allowed a huge amount of inconsistencies to creep into the codebase. Race conditions would allow two developers to lock the same file at once, or a developer would change a class that was a dependency of some other code that somebody else was changing. Sometimes code changes would make it into some of the customer jar files, but not others. Nobody knew why.
It took a small team two years to migrate the entire codebase to git with proper CI, and a huge chunk of that time was reproducing a version of the codebase that actually compiled properly as a whole. After the project was finished, I resigned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nexialist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[things i'm grateful for]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/things-im-grateful-for/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/things-im-grateful-for/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seeing as how I don't practice gratitude nearly as much as I want to, I thought that I'd keep today's post short and list a bunch of things that I am grateful for in no particular order.
The chilly morning winter air
Being able to admire beautiful sunrise and sunsets
The colourful sound of bird calls
The feeling of serenity when I have a glass of tea in the early hours of the morning
The peace I feel whenever I sit down to write a post
Moments spent with loved ones
Sleeping in on the weekends
Tasty food
You, for reading this post!
I would love to hear what your "little things" are! Leave a message in my guest book or shoot me a message on the Blaugust discord.
3/31]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[becoming valentine]]></title>
        <id>https://valentine.bearblog.dev/becoming-valentine/</id>
        <link href="https://valentine.bearblog.dev/becoming-valentine/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm Valentine. As you've probably already guessed, that is not my real name. I like my (semi-)anonymity. I may be spilling my guts on here, but I'd like to do it under the cover of a good old pseudonym.
Like a lot of people, I've been using different names online for years. Obviously not to commit crimes, but to make it less likely I become a victim of one. Also, I just like it. Names fascinate me: they make up such a big part of our first impressions. I've tried feminine names and not-so-feminine ones. I've never tried a really masculine name, though—I've always loved being a woman, online and offline, even if it comes with many inconveniences of varying sizes.
I took Valentine from the Måneskin song of the same name. But if that's too somber for you, there's also the Laufey song, which i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by rahimnathwani in "The Marshmallow Test does not reliably predict adult functioning"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140863</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140863"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T17:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The findings of the original study were called into question by a larger 2018 study[0]. The original study had 90 students. Some folks did a study with 900 people. They found the same correlation that the original study did. But when they controlled for household income, they found most of the correlation disappeared.
The obvious conclusion is that household income is a predictor of both:
- inability to delay gratification, and
- higher academic achievement
This makes sense when you consider that someone growing up in a poor household may have both:
- less reliable/continuous/predictable access to material things, meaning they would rationally seize immediate opportunities rather than taking the risk of a larger future opportunity, and
- less academic support
Now, this new study (OP) goes even further, finding that the correlation itself is weak.
[0] Watts, T. W., Duncan, G. J., & Quan, H. (2018). Revisiting the Marshmallow Test: A Conceptual Replication Investigating Links Between Early Delay of Gratification and Later Outcomes. Psychological Science, 29(7), 1159-1177. https://doi.org/10.1177/0956797618761661]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rahimnathwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by vishnugupta in "The upstream cause of the youth mental health crisis is the loss of community"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140280</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140280"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One big change I've noticed between growing up in a small town and now where I'm in my mid 40s in a big metro city in India is increased "transactional" nature of interactions of my daily life.
Back then we had a deeper ties with all those who served us by which I mean vegetable vendor, carpenter, doctor, knife sharpener, cloth shop, grocer, baker and so on. Whenever we interacted with them it would be a small chit-chat, exchange small updates (how's your son doing, is he married yet?) and then finally do the actual purchase.
It was to an extent that the carpenter would come by and just hand over a big dining table just because he thought our house deserved/needed it. He wouldn't ask for immediate payment either and also in instalments. Some other times he would come by and borrow some money.
All of that is now gone. Every single interaction I have now with vendors is 100% transactional. I don't even know their names nor they mine.
It means that I'm now connected only with my immediate family, that's it. It also means that the generation now growing up know only transactional way of interaction with non family/friends. I guess these things eventually add up to the loss of community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>vishnugupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by kelseyfrog in "The upstream cause of the youth mental health crisis is the loss of community"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140196</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41140196"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, yes, we've doubled down on mediating social interactions through economic relationships. Most of the interactions adults have in their lives are with or in the framing of economic relations. Homes, are being invaded with tablets and mobile devices which bring along with them framing interactions as economic relations through ad and consumer frames. Workplaces are inherently settings of economic relations, and third places outside of the consumer setting are becoming extinct because they are non-monetizable.
This last category, non-consumer third places are formerly the domain of kid-friendly community-building activities. When we talk about creating more of these and the response is, "they aren't economically viable," it's exactly the kind of economic calculus framing that I'm talking about.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kelseyfrog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New comment by weberer in "The upstream cause of the youth mental health crisis is the loss of community"]]></title>
        <id>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41139925</id>
        <link href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=41139925"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T15:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've noticed an uptick recently of large brands to start referring to themselves as "The [Brand] Community". The author pointed out Youtube here (who in an Orwellian manner calls their ToS "community guidelines") but I've also seen it with many other multi-million dollar companies such as Reddit, Twitter, etc. 
Young people today are reaching out for real support structures, but only receiving manipulation from corporations that want them to watch ads, while occasionally arguing with pseudo-anonymous internet strangers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>weberer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I'm JC... Probably?]]></title>
        <id>https://notes.jeddacp.com/im-jc-probably/</id>
        <link href="https://notes.jeddacp.com/im-jc-probably/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T15:10:10.164Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was supposed to do an Intro Post yesterday, but I’ve never been good at it so I delayed it until I could figure out what to say. Here we are a day later, and I still don’t quite have the words for it. I always fall back to a post I’ve written of not wanting to talk about myself as an explanation. Either way, I’ve come to realize that I never did do a proper introduction on this blog, outside of my About me page. In my defense, I think what I have written on there is enough to kind of get a gist for who I am.
But since I’m writing a post anyways, I figured I’d say something else that doesn’t completely repeat everything written on there.
Online, I typically go by JC(Probably), but most people in real life call me Jedda. You can tell a lot about how people know me, and from what moment in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[on social media addiction]]></title>
        <id>https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/on-social-media-addiction/</id>
        <link href="https://vixiss.bearblog.dev/on-social-media-addiction/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being in my early 20s, there should be no surprise that I have grown up with and have extensively used social media platforms to socialise, communicate, and share ideas with other people. It is no secret that these platforms can and have caused harm to their user's mental health (me included!), but even knowing this I've sat on my hands for years before actually taking action to remedy this situation.
However, as a lot of you know, it's not easy to just drop social media cold turkey. In my opinion, I think there are a few main reasons why this is the case, and I will attempt to argue against each one in this post.
1. Social media is addictive
Multi-million dollar companies spend huge amounts of capital and time to create algorithms where their sole purpose is to make you spend more time on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Omar Radi free !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Omar-Radi-free</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Omar-Radi-free"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T08:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Press release. 
Press releases

/ 
Social movements, 
Morocco]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ATTAC/CADTM Morocco</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nsámbu Za Suékama - Deixis and the Queer/Trans Struggle]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nsambu-za-suekama-deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminis?v=1722571298</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/nsambu-za-suekama-deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminis?v=1722571298"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T04:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Nsámbu Za Suékama
Title: Deixis and the Queer/Trans Struggle
Subtitle: A Missive from a Dialectical Transfeminist
Date: May 13, 2024
Notes: Author’s note: a straight-through read would make 200+ minutes. Please take your time with such a hefty work. Breaks are encouraged. If you are Black, trans/queer, and operating in good faith, feel free to highlight passages you would like to learn more about. Medium allows authors to interact with their readers. I might be able to provide clarification if I have spoons.
Source: <medium.com/@riptide.1997/deixis-and-the-queer-trans-struggle-a-missive-from-a-dialectical-transfeminist-4dae1e366f07>

“Deah’s plenty cunjuh in dis neighbuhhood. Deah wuz a man and his wife libed yuh. Duh man couldn git wuk an he went away. Attuh he lef, duh wife wuz t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Imprisoned Anarchists - Concerning the anti-judicial position]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/some-imprisoned-anarchists-concerning-the-anti-judicial-position?v=1722570985</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/some-imprisoned-anarchists-concerning-the-anti-judicial-position?v=1722570985"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:56:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Some Imprisoned Anarchists
Title: Concerning the anti-judicial position
Date: October 28, 2014
Source: Greece – Dialogue between Kontra newspaper and imprisoned anarchist comrades concerning the stance of the comrades in the terror-trials. <web.archive.org/web/20160409234906/http://actforfree.nostate.net/?p=18034>. Retrieved on 19/07/2024 from lib.anarhija.net.

 BELOW ARE THE TRANSLATIONS OF A SERIES OF TEXTS THAT WERE WRITTEN BY ANARCHIST COMRADES AFTER THE CRITICISM OF LEFTIST NEWSPAPER “KONTRA” ABOUT THE ANTI-JUDICIAL POSITION THAT SOME OF THEM HOLD TOWARDS THE TERROR COURT IN KORIDALLOS PRISON 
 On 28/7/14, the report of “KONTRA” newspaper (which also goes online through www.eksegersi.gr) on the ongoing terror-trial of the Pefki case (which involves imprisoned anarchist comrad…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julian Langer - Enough! Dance!]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/julian-langer-enough-dance?v=1722568619</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/julian-langer-enough-dance?v=1722568619"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Julian Langer
Title: Enough! Dance!
Date: 18/7/24
Source: https://ecorevoltblog.wordpress.com/2024/07/18/enough-dance/

1
 The ghost of Turgenev crying 
 “Enough!” 
 Is in my ears 
 My activities are glorious 
 While several seasons 
 Fighting disease 
 Living closely with personal existential uncertainty 
 My body is marked 
 There is a thin line 
 Across my left eyelid 
 A scar from where it was removed 
 I am tired of this 
 There is a book 
 Being written 
 The first section poems like this 
 I wonder if it’s my last 
 I don’t know 
2
 All things are possible 
 So say Shestov and Fondane 
 Yes, all things are possible 
 Including the impossibility 
 Of my writing another book after this 
 Yes, all things are possible 
 What is most possible though 
 For all life 
 It seems is i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ignatius - Fist Full of Concrete]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-fist-full-of-concrete-some-thoughts-towards-insurrection?v=1722568569</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ignatius-fist-full-of-concrete-some-thoughts-towards-insurrection?v=1722568569"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:16:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ignatius
Title: Fist Full of Concrete
Subtitle: Some Thoughts Towards Insurrection
Date: 2023
Notes: Published by Long Leaf Distro 2023 
 Longleaf_distro@protonmail.com 
 Reproduce to your heart’s content.
Source: Retrieved on 4 July 2023 from ia800301.us.archive.org/4/items/zines-anarchism/Fist_Full_of_Concrete-screen.pdf

It Doesn’t Have to Be This Way, You Know
 There is a beauty that creeps in under the plastic blinds, covering the window, in the form of sunlight. A beauty that seems an attempt by the world outside to draw some contrast to the words I write here, and that you will read later on. That for all the expression of pain, and dissatisfaction, and desire for more, there is still beauty to be found here, bouncing around the walls of this mold infested apartment. 
 This …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Ridin’ Dirty: A Basic Reference for Freight Hopping]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping?v=1722567881</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping?v=1722567881"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T03:04:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Ridin’ Dirty: A Basic Reference for Freight Hopping
Date: 07/20/2024
Source: https://warzonedistro.noblogs.org/post/2024/07/20/ridin-dirty-a-basic-reference-for-freight-hopping/

A Few Words From the Distro
 Riding freight is a core skill for anti-work, anti-school, individualist anarchists, lifestylists, nomads, oogles, crust punk dirty kids, and travelers. 
 Hate your job? Quit and go train hopping! 
 Sick of school? Drop out and go train hopping! 
 Feeling suicidal with no fun and excitement in your life? 
 Try something new, open a new chapter and go train hopping! 
 But train hopping is very dangerous! You SERIOUSLY could die. 
 But you could also die in a car wreck on the way to work, or die from getting shot to death by a mass shooter. 
 At the end of the da…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delfina Vannuci & Richard Singer - Come Hell or High Water]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/delfina-vannuci-richard-singer-come-hell-or-high-water?v=1722566512</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/delfina-vannuci-richard-singer-come-hell-or-high-water?v=1722566512"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T02:41:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Delfina Vannuci & Richard Singer
Title: Come Hell or High Water
Subtitle: A Handbook on Collective Process Gone Awry
Date: 2010
Notes: Originally published by AK Press. ISBN-13: 9781849350181,
Source: AK Press

PREFACE
 Welcome to the collective book on collective process! Over the course of the twenty or so years that AK Press has been publishing and distributing anarchist and radical literature, we've gotten a lot of requests for good, short overviews of topics that are of interest to the folks in our communities: anarchism, worker's rights, solidarity economics, and countless other things. We do our best to seek out books to publish or distribute that meet our readers’ needs, but it can take a while to find exactly the right author or book. One of the most common requests we get…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ichikawa Hakugen - The Problem Of Buddhist Socialism in Japan]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-the-problem-of-buddhist-socialism-in-japan?v=1722564274</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/ichikawa-hakugen-the-problem-of-buddhist-socialism-in-japan?v=1722564274"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T02:04:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Ichikawa Hakugen
Title: The Problem Of Buddhist Socialism in Japan
Date: 1970
Source: Retrieved on 7/31/24 from https://noselvesnomasters.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/ichikawa-hakugens.pdf

(1)
 The formation of Buddhist socialism in Japan made a belated start and its influence was little compared with that of Christian socialism in Europe, or even with the revolutionary movement (1851-1864) which occurred in the period of “idle peace” started by Hong Xiuquan (洪秀全) in China. The reason for the belated start seems to be indirectly concerned with national isolationism and the slow development of capitalism in Japan. The Communist Manifesto was published 20 years before the Meiji Restoration and the first volume of Das Kapital was issued a year before the Meiji Restoration. Directly…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anonymous - Hamas, anarchists in the West and Palestine solidarity]]></title>
        <id>https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-author-from-stoking-the-embers-collective-hamas-anarchists-in-the-west-and-palestine?v=1722563828</id>
        <link href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/anonymous-author-from-stoking-the-embers-collective-hamas-anarchists-in-the-west-and-palestine?v=1722563828"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Author: Anonymous
Title: Hamas, anarchists in the West and Palestine solidarity
Subtitle: An analysis
Date: July 15th 2024
Notes: Anonymous author from Stoking the Embers Collective
Source: Retrieved on August 1, 2024 from https://libcom.org/article/hamas-anarchists-west-and-palestine-solidarity-analysis

 In the West, it is practically impossible to speak publicly about Hamas in any way that isn't an outright and total condemnation. Behind such remarkable limitation of the spectrum of public debate lies the idea that Hamas represents an "evil" so deep that it lacks any complexity. In parliaments, universities and newspapers, Hamas is never discussed, simply because -- it is assumed -- there is nothing to discuss. The idea that Hamas is simply a "terrorist" group that wants nothing but dea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Anarchist Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon Q Developer just reached a $260 million dollar milestone]]></title>
        <id>f5ea5adef0b32f32d4d01cabbf34df85e6d89efd</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/devops/amazon-q-developer-just-reached-a-260-million-dollar-milestone/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T23:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To help them be more productive, developers all over the world are turning to generative AI-powered assistants like Amazon Q Developer, the most capable assistant for accelerating software development. While Amazon Q Developer is great at providing code suggestions, writing new code is one of many things developers have to do on a day-to-day basis. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aytul Arisoy Cholkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Māori Data Lens for the Well-Architected Framework]]></title>
        <id>cdca0a814b524dedcad257755ec5f53c08efc5b4</id>
        <link href="https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/architecture/introducing-the-maori-data-lens-for-the-well-architected-framework/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Aotearoa New Zealand, we have been listening and learning to better understand Māori aspirations when using cloud technology. We have been learning from Māori customers, partners, and advisors who have helped us on this journey. A common theme was how to safeguard Māori data in a digital world. Together with a group of Māori […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Craig Hind</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Praiseworthy by Alexis Wright wins 2024 Miles Franklin Literary Award]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8133</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/praiseworthy-alexis-wright-wins-2024-miles-franklin-literary-award/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T21:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As called/guessed by yours truly, Praiseworthy, the 2023 novel by Waanyi/Gulf of Carpentaria based Australian author Alexis Wright, has won the 2024 Miles Franklin Literary Award. Praiseworthy has cleaned up on the awards circuit since publication, also winning the other major Australian literary award, the Stellar Prize. Wright also won the Miles Franklin in 2007, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[your social media feed doesn't operate in a vacuum]]></title>
        <id>https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/your-social-media-feed-doesnt-operate-in-a-vacuum/</id>
        <link href="https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/your-social-media-feed-doesnt-operate-in-a-vacuum/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T20:59:49.947Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[a social media channel is one thing, but it has multiple sub-things inside
look at youtube
there's the side where someone is always selling something
there's the side where a grandma is sharing her recipe
there's the side where someone just posted a video compilation of their dead love one
there's the side where someone is laughing with their friends
earlier this year, i was complaining that my feed was full of people selling me something
but your social media feed doesn't operate in a vacuum. it shows you more of what you look for
i wanted to sell something, so i was looking for people to teach me to sell something, so i was only being recommended videos of people teaching me to sell something
i don't like that side of the internet
so i left it
you can leave the side you're on and join another
or leave altogether]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[new issue of RWER]]></title>
        <id>http://rwer.wordpress.com/?p=45508</id>
        <link href="https://rwer.wordpress.com/2024/08/01/new-issue-of-rwer-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:32:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[real-world economics review Please click here to support this journal and the WEA Issue no. 108July 2024 download whole issue The creationist foundations of Herman Daly’s steady state economyJohn Gowdy and Lisi Krall2 Data: a critical perspectiveCarlos Guerrero de Lizardi16 Enlightenment Epistemology and the Climate CrisisAsad Zaman29 Fabulous MacroeconomicsGerald Holtham33 A Tour of the Jevons […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Editor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code July 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_92</id>
        <link href="https://code.visualstudio.com/updates/v1_92"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code July 2024 Release (1.92)
Read the full article]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Visual Studio Code - Code Editing. Redefined.</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A recent spate of Internet disruptions]]></title>
        <id>66ab8bd24a25d6000ae1c5d6</id>
        <link href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-recent-spate-of-internet-disruptions-july-2024"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Radar is constantly monitoring the Internet for widespread disruptions. Here we examine several recent  noteworthy disruptions detected in the first month of Q3, including traffic anomalies observed in Bangladesh, Syria, Pakistan, and Venezuela]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Belson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Naomi Hossain: &ldquo;Bloody July&rdquo;]]></title>
        <id>https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bloody-july</id>
        <link href="https://newleftreview.org/sidecar/posts/bloody-july"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unrest in Bangladesh.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>New Left Review Sidecar recent posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why write?]]></title>
        <id>https://tanmay.bearblog.dev/why/</id>
        <link href="https://tanmay.bearblog.dev/why/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why write?
I have a ritual. Every time I set out to do something new, be it a new habit, a new course, or a new adventure in life, I ask myself, why? This exercise in setting a purpose is essential because it stays as a reminder of your initial vision about what you set out to do. So, as I launch this blog, I want to openly share the purpose and vision behind it.
This isn't just another hobby project for me. Ever since I was 13, I have wanted to write. To share my ideas with friends, aka people, across the world. There was even a time when I wanted to try to write a self help book, to understand the world and life in general, more effectively. I have always been enamoured by great ideas. For it is these great ideas, passed down from generation to generation, which have survived the test of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The blog that refuses to die]]></title>
        <id>https://birming.com/blog-refuses-die/</id>
        <link href="https://birming.com/blog-refuses-die/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T06:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday, I wrote that I had decided to end this blog. When I woke up this morning, I immediately realized that it was the wrong decision.
Crazy? Maybe.
But that’s how it sometimes is. You can’t always reason your way to the right decision. At least, I can’t. I’d been pondering this for weeks...
It was only when the idea became a reality that I realized it was a bad one. I wish I could avoid taking these detours in my decision-making process, but I’ve come to realize that will probably never happen.
And when you think about it, that “detour” is actually a shortcut to the right decision. Weeks of theoretical pondering didn’t help at all, while taking concrete action gave me an answer in a few hours.
Detours can be shortcuts, at least sometimes and for me. Sorry for the confusion — and welcome to my world. I hope you have the patience to stick around...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on 4, 5 and 6 October 2024 for our next Autumn Meetings!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cadtm.org/Join-us-on-4-5-and-6-October-2024-for-our-next-Autumn-Meetings</id>
        <link href="https://www.cadtm.org/Join-us-on-4-5-and-6-October-2024-for-our-next-Autumn-Meetings"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Autumn Meetings of CADTM Europe will occur on October 4, 5 and 6 October 2024. As of 2023, the venue will be the Simenon Youth Hostelin Liège, Belgium. 
English]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CADTM</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moderate drinking is not beneficial, in fact is it harmful]]></title>
        <id>https://disassociated.com/?p=8131</id>
        <link href="https://disassociated.com/moderate-drinking-not-beneficial-in-fact-harmful/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T21:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Michael Le Page, writing for New Scientist: Drinking even small amounts of alcohol reduces your life expectancy, rigorous studies show. Only those with serious flaws suggest that moderate drinking is beneficial. That’s the conclusion of a review of 107 studies looking at how drinking alcohol affects people’s risk of dying from any cause at a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>disassociated.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[how do people find things they like]]></title>
        <id>https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/how-do-people-find-things-they-like/</id>
        <link href="https://anonlinediary.bearblog.dev/how-do-people-find-things-they-like/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[one of my favorite things about people is their hobbies
i absolutely love watching people do the things they love doing, again and again
people who've turned a passion into mastery, who don't tire - they just show up over and over because of the love they have for their craft
it blows my mind
so i started to wonder: how do people find things they truly like?
i've been sitting with this question for a while now. i don't know if i've ever liked something well enough to stick to it long-term
my memory fails me (yes, i have shit memory at the ripe young age of my early 20's), but from what i can remember from my childhood, i loved reading, skating and writing
i remember reading Diary of a Wimpy Kid and Dork Diaries. my older sister and i created something that was an amalgamation of the two. i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bear Blog Trending Posts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>